Chapter 1187: Fang Yuan's Cultivation Opportunity

Immortal killer move — Days Pass Like Years!

Countless Gu worms flew in the sky, expending green grape immortal essence as a grand light filled the entire sovereign immortal aperture.

Splash splash splash.

The tributary of the River of Time in the sovereign immortal aperture showed its true form, it could be seen with the naked eye.

Under the power of days pass like years, this tributary of the River of Time shrank, the river surface became thinner.

"Huff—!"

Letting out a breath, Fang Yuan finally relaxed.

"I succeeded, the immortal aperture's rate of time has greatly slowed down. The interval between my calamities and tribulations have lengthened drastically." After confirming that the killer move succeeded, Fang Yuan retracted all of his concentration.

Right now, he was inside his cloud city in Lang Ya blessed land.

After annexing Han Dong blessed land, Fang Yuan immediately returned.

Tai Qiu was too dangerous, while Fang Yuan's Dark Limit had a time-limited effect, heaven's will was plotting to kill Fang Yuan at all times.

Now that his immortal aperture time was slowed down, the following calamities and tribulations were far away.

Fang Yuan felt relaxed all of a sudden, his pressure diminished.

He had undergone careful consideration before making this decision. Since he changed his cultivation method, he did not need to undergo tribulations so frequently. Annexing blessed lands could allow him to skip calamities and tribulations, this effect had nothing to do with the rate of time in his own blessed land.

The most important thing now were blessed lands.

Where could he find more blessed lands?

Fang Yuan first thought of Hu Immortal blessed land and Star Form blessed land in Central Continent.

But soon, he disregarded this unrealistic idea.

It was impossible!

Central Continent was a dangerous territory, the ten ancient sects along with Heavenly Court, which had deeper foundation than Longevity Heaven, would want nothing more than to kill Fang Yuan.

Like how Ying Wu Xie and the rest fled from Central Continent, for Fang Yuan, it was also a death zone.

Some time ago, Star Form blessed land faced its calamities and tribulations, the land spirit wrote to Fang Yuan, sobbing while asking for help, Fang Yuan ignored it, only sending some mortal Gu and immortal essence to the land spirit, asking it to save itself.

Star Form blessed land was in such straits, the exposed Hu Immortal blessed land was even more out of the question.

Fang Yuan thought of Luo Po Valley.

Or more accurately, the location that Luo Po Valley was previously at.

There was an intense battle at Luo Po Valley, with Feng Jiu Ge leading the Central Continent Gu Immortals to fight against Shadow Sect's Northern Plains branch with Qin Bai Sheng as the leader, they went through an intense battle, with victory going to the Central Continent Gu Immortals in the end.

At Luo Po Valley's original location, there were many Gu Immortals' blessed lands.

"These blessed lands are in Northern Plains, can I go over and take them?"

This was an alluring idea, but Fang Yuan hesitated for a while, and soon after, he gave up on this option as well.

Because this choice carried great risks.

Even though this battle was hidden and the Gu Immortals of Northern Plains did not know about it, Central Continent's ten great ancient sects and Heavenly Court knew about it, as well as Shadow Sect themselves.

After Gu Immortals die, blessed lands or grotto-heavens would be formed outside.

These blessed lands or grotto-heavens contain the resources accumulated by the Gu Immortals over their lifetimes, no matter how affluent a force was, they would try all ways to reclaim these resources.

"Since Central Continent could send people to Northern Plains for investigation of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's collapse, then they can naturally send others to reclaim those blessed lands."

"And Shadow Sect too, would want to take these blessed lands back."

"I did not go there earlier, there is no way I am going there now."

Fang Yuan's decision was very wise.

Because right now, the person secretly helping Central Continent to reclaim these immortal apertures was the rank eight Gu Immortal Prince Feng Xian!

If Fang Yuan was blindly hopeful and went there on his own, Prince Feng Xian would probably laugh even in his sleep, seeing how Fang Yuan went to him on his own without any effort exerted.

Fang Yuan thought of Eastern Sea next.

Eastern Sea's turbulent flow sea area, at its center, there were islands in bubbles.

One of the islands contained the secluded domain of heaven and earth, City Well, and inside City Well, there were lots of Gu Immortals' blessed lands.

These Gu Immortals were all slammed to death by Fang Yuan using the effect of City Well to amplify giant hand's power. He even went inside these blessed lands at the moment they were placed down, and went inside to scavenge for resources.

The most alluring one was Ding Qi blessed land.

Ding Qi was a blood path rank seven Gu Immortal, he self-detonated before dying, not leaving any resources, Immortal Gu, or soul for Fang Yuan, but his immortal aperture remained.

Even though Fang Yuan could annex his immortal aperture, he did not do so on the spot.

Firstly, Ding Qi blessed land's land spirit had a difficult requirement for ownership, it needed Fang Yuan to complete the blood path Immortal Gu recipe of 'Blood Revenge'. If Fang Yuan still had the light of wisdom, he could rapidly complete this. But now, wisdom Gu could not be used, and blood revenge Immortal Gu was less than ten percent complete, if Fang Yuan wanted to complete this Immortal Gu recipe, even with his blood path grandmaster attainment level, he would need to spend a lot of time and effort on it, the cost was not worth the gain.

And secondly, Fang Yuan's previous cultivation method placed emphasis on potential. He went through tribulations one by one, if he annexed Ding Qi blessed land, it would go against his plan.

But now was different.

Firstly, Fang Yuan did not achieve his goal in this Eastern Sea trip, even though he weakened Ying Wu Xie and gang, he did not kill them once and for all. Fang Yuan had a deep understanding of Ying Wu Xie, their development speed surpassed his, the next time they met, he would be on the defensive.

There was also the variant human alliance, Hei Fan grotto-heaven's contest, joining Chu Sect, and the Crazed Demon Agreement that was coming soon, his status was getting more complex. Fang Yuan felt trapped inside a vortex, in lots of situations, he could not do what he wanted, the alliance agreements were restricting his freedom.

Times were different now, as the situation continued to change, Fang Yuan realized he too needed to change.

His cultivation experiences in the five hundred years of his previous life gave him keen instinct towards how he should continue his future developments, as well as impending threats.

He had a strong feeling that if he did not make a change, the future was going to be very bleak!

Realizing the sovereign immortal aperture's special trait in annexing blessed lands was just such an opportunity.

"I am a blood path grandmaster, annexing a rank seven blessed land is not a problem in terms of attainment level. But a smaller immortal aperture cannot devour a bigger one, what does the bigger here mean?"

If it referred to cultivation level, Fang Yuan's rank six immortal aperture could not annex the rank seven Ding Qi blessed land.

But if it referred to the immortal aperture's foundation, then the sovereign immortal aperture could definitely devour the rank seven Ding Qi blessed land easily!

Fang Yuan needed an answer to this question.

It was not hard to get, he just needed to try.

"But other than that, there is another problem, the land spirit's acknowledgment."

"The acknowledgement of Ding Qi land spirit is quite difficult to get, I can't satisfy it currently. But if I attempt to use force, the land spirit would be destroyed, and the blessed land would be destroyed as well, creating the winds of assimilation."

"When these winds of assimilation blow in City Well, will it implicate the other immortal apertures? Will it destroy City Well directly?"

Fang Yuan had thought about this problem back in Eastern Sea.

Thus, he did not forcefully attempt to get those blessed lands.

To destroy the land spirit while keeping the blessed land intact, it would need to absorb a fragment of the immemorial nine heavens.

But only grotto-heavens could absorb fragments of the immemorial nine heavens.

Like Hei Fan grotto-heaven, even though Fang Yuan destroyed the heavenly spirit, it still existed. It was because this grotto-heaven world had absorbed a fragment of the immemorial nine heavens.

But that was not the case for land spirits.

And the turbulent flow sea area was far away in Eastern Sea, taking a journey there and back would use a lot of Fang Yuan's time. Heaven's will might even be plotting to prevent Fang Yuan from obtaining City Well.

Fang Yuan thought about it carefully, he found another problem limiting his annexing of immortal apertures.

It was attainment level.

Fang Yuan was not Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, the latter had high attainment levels in every path, he could easily absorb blessed lands into the sovereign immortal aperture.

But Fang Yuan could not.

"Or rather, Shadow Sect refined sovereign immortal fetus Gu in order to devour immortal apertures?"

Fang Yuan realized that if he did not take sovereign immortal fetus Gu, and allowed Spectral Soul to revive.

Then his development would be at an incredibly shocking speed!

He had the most bloodthirsty nature among the venerables, he had many killer moves, after killing Gu Immortals, he could either take their main path's dao marks and give up on the immortal aperture to raise his dao mark foundation, or annex the immortal aperture and skip calamities and tribulations, resetting the counting of his impending tribulation.

The two methods could be used in conjunction in the most efficient way.

"No wonder Spectral Soul managed to succeed in my previous life!"

"No wonder heaven's will tried all means possible to send me to the past and stop him."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan's gaze subconsciously moved towards the south.

Towards the direction of Southern Border.

Fang Yuan knew that the giant dream realm was there, a trace of Spectral Soul's remnant soul was there, it was the target that Ying Wu Xie and the rest were desperately trying to save.

"Attainment level... dream realm... Southern Border!" Fang Yuan's body shook, he suddenly thought of something.

The thoughts in his mind became extremely clear at this moment.

"The cultivation opportunity I need is in Southern Border. It is there..."

Snowy Mountain, first peak.

The refinement path Gu formation was still activated.

Lady Wan Shou was energetic, appearing in front of Ma Hong Yun again.

Ma Hong Yun saw her and his hair stood on end, he screamed: "You are here to shock me again, you want to shock me again!"

"Good that you know." Lady Wan Shou smiled, pushing the lightning ball in her hand towards him.

"Ahhhh!" Ma Hong Yun was twitching from the pain, his eyes rolled back but he did not foam saliva from his mouth.

At the same time, his voice was very clear, if one listened closely, it was rhythmic.

All in all, he lasted for a while before fainting.

"His cultivation level rose again? Also, he lasted thirty percent longer this time against the lightning refinement." Lady Wan Shou frowned as she observed.

From the eyes, nose, and ears, blood was flowing out.

This was the backlash of Gu refinement.

But Lady Wan Shou had experienced it many times, she was used to this backlash. Her healing process was also very rapid and efficient.

"It is a bit troublesome. The more times Ma Hong Yun undergoes lightning refinement, the stronger his resistance, and the more likely this crucial step is to fail. What should I do? Change the refinement method? No! If I change the method now, I will need to change the entire Immortal Gu recipe. Half of the materials we found earlier would be unusable. Snowy Mountain cannot bear such a cost anymore."

Lady Wan Shou sighed to herself, feeling extremely worried.

Chapter 1188: Crazed Demon Agreement

Some days later.

Northern Plains, Crazed Demon Cave.

"Liu Guan Yi, we have been waiting for you!" Not Immortal came to the first layer, welcoming Fang Yuan and Chu Du.

The three conversed as they got deeper into the cave.

Fang Yuan discovered that the route this time was slightly different from the previous time he came here.

"Are the demonic sounds recently very frequent?" Fang Yuan asked.

"They are getting more frequent now. Thus, our travel route also has to be modified. Once the demonic sounds start, dao marks will go into chaos. Not only will the desolate beasts go crazy, the terrain will also change." Not Immortal explained.

A moment later, they saw Pang Shan.

Pang Shan woke up from his slumber, his eyes opened slightly: "You are here again, Brother Chu."

He seemed to have a good relationship with Chu Du.

Next, he looked at Fang Yuan: "Brother Liu, I know about your capabilities, let's talk in depth after the Crazed Demon Agreement."

Fang Yuan asked: "How will we establish the Crazed Demon Agreement?"

"We will need to go down to the third last layer, I can't move easily, I will not go with you." Pang Shan said vaguely, his explanation was as good as nothing.

"Follow me." Not Immortal continued to lead the way.

The three immortals continued to go down, the deeper they went, the more turns they had to make, sometimes, the straight distance seemed to be short, but they had to make a long detour.

"Believe me, detours are much faster than walking straight in this place." Not Immortal smiled.

Chu Du nodded, pointing out to Fang Yuan: "When we get there, don't be too surprised."

Fang Yuan felt some curiosity and anticipation.

A while later, through a cavern entrance, Fang Yuan officially stepped into the third last layer of Crazed Demon Cave.

His vision was covered by bright glorious lights.

All sorts of colors were emanated from the rocks, soil, and grass in this place.

Fang Yuan sucked in a deep breath: "This, these are all lights of dao marks! Only quasi-rank nine immortal materials can radiate such lights. The dao marks here are so dense that every piece of soil and rock is a quasi-rank nine immortal material?!"

Not Immortal laughed: "Brother Liu makes sense, but these immortal materials have chaotic dao marks, they cannot be used."

Chu Du saw Fang Yuan's shock and smiled: "Back then, when I first came here, I suffered the same shock."

Not Immortal ended his laughter: "The dao marks here are extremely dense, it is not as simple as just emitting the lights of dao marks! There is almost a state of a battlefield killer move in here, moving here is extremely difficult, Brother Liu, why don't you try?"

Fang Yuan quickly shook his head: "Not Immortal, since you say this, I will believe you. No need to try."

Not Immortal looked at Chu Du, smiling: "Brother Liu is smarter than a certain person. Back then, he refused to believe it, he wanted to charge in, I could not change his mind and in the end, he suffered a lot."

Chu Du rubbed his nose, admitting to Fang Yuan: "Not Immortal is talking about me, I spent three years to recover from that injury. Don't look down at the dao marks here. This place is extremely dangerous, each step you take is precarious! I'll teach you a secret, try to get close to the dao marks of your own path, that can make your traveling easier, and face the least obstruction."

Not Immortal nodded: "That is true, I am a rule path Gu Immortal, I have to try walking on places with more rule path dao marks."

"And I cultivate strength path, I need to get close to the strength path dao marks, thus, in the following journey, we cannot help you, you have to walk on your own, Brother Liu." Chu Du said with concern.

Fang Yuan nodded.

Not Immortal stepped forward first: "I will go first, Brother Liu, watch carefully."

Fang Yuan concentrated as he looked.

Not Immortal's every step was very vigilant, the first ten steps were very easy, he could move calmly, but after ten steps, it became difficult. After twenty steps, his movements were stiff, it was like a formless force was weighing on him. After thirty steps, Not Immortal was perspiring profusely, at the forty-second step, he stopped for the first time, breathing roughly as he turned to ask Fang Yuan: "Brother Liu, did you manage to watch that?"

Chu Du laughed: "Not Immortal! Stop acting, you are clearly unable to continue, you still tried to ask Brother Liu a question to conceal the fact that you stopped."

Not Immortal was exposed, he was embarrassed and snapped: "Oh Chu Du, I want to see how many steps you can take? Can you go as far as me!"

Chu Du snorted: "Would I be afraid of you, watch closely!"

Before he finished his words, he took large steps forward on the dao marks in the area.

Initially, his speed was faster than Not Immortal, he moved like a dragon or tiger, Not Immortal's expression was dark.

But soon, Chu Du took a wrong step and the light of dao marks below him burst out, Chu Du grunted, his body shook as he spat out a mouthful of blood on the spot.

He was heavily injured, his momentum was lost but he did not stop, Chu Du endured his injuries as he continued to walk step by step, as slow as a snail.

Eventually, he took thirty-eight and thirty-nine steps, by the fortieth step, he could no longer continue.

His final burst of strength was used up.

He stopped.

"I could not compare to you after all." Chu Du wiped the blood from his mouth, sighing.

Not Immortal was very shocked, he stared at Chu Du with wide eyes: "Domination Immortal, you actually improved so much since last time! I am ashamed, I have stayed in Crazed Demon Cave for so long, I have walked along this place hundreds of times more than you, I have such a huge advantage but I only managed to take forty-two steps."

Chu Du laughed: "Alright, don't flatter me. I know you did not use your full strength, you are trying to salvage my face?"

Not Immortal did not deny it, he chuckled: "Even so, your improvement is beyond my imagination. You are truly a genius at strength path cultivation, Domination Immortal... indeed, as the saying goes, titles are never wrong."

Chu Du laughed heartily, waving his hand: "Alright, let's stop the flattery, next, we will see Brother Liu's performance."

The two immortals turned around and watched Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan nodded: "Don't laugh at me when I embarrass myself."

"Brother Liu, relax, this is your first time here, you should focus on the feeling of walking here, don't be obsessed over the number of steps." Not Immortal said.

Chu Du laughed instead: "Haha, don't worry brother Liu, I will remember your pathetic state later. I walked twenty-two steps when I first came here, if you cannot beat me, I will laugh at you forever. Haha!"

Fang Yuan laughed too, it was a harmonious scene.

But in truth, he understood internally: "These two are purposely probing me."

"Even though Chu Du recommended me, they are not confident in my ability to explore this place, thus they created this situation."

"They are working together, purposely asking me to walk alone, they want to probe my foundation."

"If I perform too poorly, and am of no help to them, they might not even set the Crazed Demon Agreement with me!"

Involving Limitless Demon Venerable and the secret of eternal life, Fang Yuan made up his mind to put up a good show, to display his strength for Not Immortal and Chu Du.

Fang Yuan's eyes shined with a mysterious light, he breathed in deeply and firmly stood on the ground as he took a step forward.

He chose the route with the most transformation path dao marks.

But at the next moment, Fang Yuan's expression changed.

"Haha." Chu Du observed his expression and laughed at the same time as Fang Yuan's changing expression: "Brother Liu, watching alone is useless, can you feel the pressure already?"

Fang Yuan felt extremely mystified on the inside, but he showed no flaws on his expression.

He did not answer Chu Du, he kept quiet and continued walking forward.

One step, two steps, three steps... like this, Fang Yuan took more than ten steps forward.

Fang Yuan's weird feeling intensified: "What is going on? Why do I feel no obstruction? I have already taken more than ten steps, it feels like I am walking on normal ground."

This was not normal.

Fang Yuan soon guessed that the situation was caused by his sovereign immortal body.

"Chu Du and Not Immortal face pressure because of the conflicting dao marks. There are a lot of dao marks here, while the Gu Immortals also have a lot of dao marks in their bodies."

"So even though they took one step at a time, walking on paths with rule path or strength path dao marks, the surrounding dao marks are nearby and will still pressure and reject them."

"But I am different, the dao marks here are not immortal killer moves, they have no offensive power, they cannot influence me!"

"Of course, this is just my guess, the truth might not be like this."

Fang Yuan thought as he continued walking, taking a few more steps ahead.

Not Immortal and Chu Du's expressions changed mildly.

"This Liu Guan Yi is so strong!" Not Immortal was extremely shocked.

"He is almost at the twentieth step, he can still move so calmly, the first time I came, every step was difficult, I had to exert all my effort, it was a pathetic sight!" Chu Du recalled his own experience, compared to the situation in front of him, his pride and self confidence was taking a huge beating.

A thought appeared in his mind uncontrollably: "Don't tell me, this Liu Guan Yi is an even greater genius in cultivating transformation path compared to me and strength path? He has even higher attainment level?"

Actually, Fang Yuan was trying his best to conceal himself.

He pretended to be panting, like he was very tired.

But his acting was in reference to Chu Du and Not Immortal earlier. They had gone through this many times, they were experienced, they could maintain their composure.

Even though Fang Yuan showed a pathetic sight, he was just slightly weaker than them.

Eventually, Fang Yuan stopped at the twentieth step, smiling: "I am about the same as you, Brother Chu."

Chu Du looked at Fang Yuan with deep meaning: "Brother Liu, you have not gone all out."

Fang Yuan smiled bitterly: "I am barely holding on, if I continue, I will start spitting out blood!"

Chu Du's smile was even more bitter than his: "I will not lie to Brother Liu, the first time I came here, I started spitting out blood at the tenth step."

Chapter 1189: Huge Rise in Cultivation Level

Fang Yuan's heart jumped, he realized that his performance had gone overboard.

But this was just a small mistake, it was not a problem.

"Let's continue moving, we can set the alliance agreement before talking more!" Not Immortal smiled, his attitude was much warmer than before.

Fang Yuan's earlier performance made Not Immortal's evaluation of him rise by several levels.

The three traveled in the land of dao marks with much difficulty.

As they moved forward, dao marks were denser, the obstruction was greater.

Of course, this was referring to Not Immortal and Chu Du. But Fang Yuan also faced a lot of difficulty, having to pretend he was having a tough time, so that Chu Du and Not Immortal would not be suspicious of him.

The three immortals walked and rested, the short journey took them fifteen minutes.

Eventually, they came to a rock.

"A newcomer?" The rock suddenly spoke, as smoke rose up from the rock before vanishing.

The rock had turned into a skinny and short Gu Immortal.

He had a goatee, he was at the height of Fang Yuan's knee, and his tiny eyes were shining brilliantly.

"This is one of the Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics, wisdom path Gu Immortal Secret Schemer." Chu Du introduced at an appropriate timing.

Fang Yuan gasped in his mind: "This person is actually Secret Schemer!"

He concealed his expression perfectly, acting like he had heard it for the first time, immediately greeting: "Hello, I am Liu Guan Yi of transformation path."

A day later.

"Brother Liu, Brother Chu, you are leaving so soon, aren't you staying for a few more days?" At the first layer of Crazed Demon Cave, Not Immortal tried to ask them to stay.

"No." Chu Du smiled bitterly and rejected: "You also know about Northern Plains' situation, I recently created Chu Du and allied with Bai Zu tribe. Right now, the righteous path is targeting our lone cultivator sect, they cannot stand us, they are gathering members to deal with us."

Not Immortal sighed: "These are external worldly affairs, what is there that you cannot part with. Fame and reputation, will they still remain after death? In \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, after Verdant Great Sun died, his soul went to the door of life and death, he stayed in pacifying soul lake as reputation Gu left him. Only eternal life is the worthy goal and pursuit of us Gu Immortals."

Chu Du had a determined expression: "I will make sure strength path flourishes, this is a promise I made to someone, if I cannot achieve it, I will not live in peace!"

Fang Yuan could not help but look at Chu Du.

This was the first time he had heard Chu Du say his aspiration.

Chu Du's expression of sincerity did not seem to be fake.

"It seems that there is a story behind Chu Du cultivating strength path." Fang Yuan was thinking about this, when Not Immortal asked him.

"Brother Liu, you have a lot of potential, why don't you stay here?"

Fang Yuan smiled: "I came here this time to sign the Crazed Demon Agreement. Now that it is done, I have other matters to settle."

Not Immortal actually thought more highly of Fang Yuan.

Mainly because Fang Yuan's performance this time left a deep impression on him.

Fang Yuan was more confident than Not Immortal in this aspect.

He felt that he could even run freely in the third last layer's dao mark landscape.

But if he did that, it would be too shocking, the jaws of the Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics would drop!

"I have not seen the bottom and second last layers yet, I cannot assess them. But the third last layer is not a problem. Derivation Gu is at the bottom layer, but with the Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics guarding it, I cannot act alone." Fang Yuan felt it was somewhat of a pity.

One day, he would return to Crazed Demon Cave, using his advantage to explore the place.

But now was not the time.

He had to raise his cultivation level, that was the most important matter.

As for derivation Gu, even if Fang Yuan obtained it, what use would it have? It was a rank nine Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan thought back to wisdom Gu, he could neither use it, nor would he know how to, it would be a huge burden if he actually obtained it!

"Other than eternal life, everything else is temporary. Brother Liu, how long would you need?" Not Immortal asked. He did not want to let a useful person like Fang Yuan go.

Fang Yuan's gaze shined, looking at Chu Du: "Actually, I am a member of Chu Sect, right now the Huang Jin tribes are attacking Chu Sect, I need to help them."

Chu Du knew that Fang Yuan was using him as an excuse, but hearing this, he still felt warmed internally.

"Sigh, you guys... never mind." Not Immortal saw that he could not convince Fang Yuan and gave up.

Fang Yuan and Chu Du said goodbye to Not Immortal, before flying towards the sky.

On the way back, Fang Yuan asked Chu Du about the situation in Northern Plains, as well as the difficulties Chu Sect was currently facing.

Fang Yuan had also undergone the Crazed Demon Agreement, his relationship with Chu Du had deepened again.

Chu Du did not conceal it from him, he smiled bitterly: "Right now, I feel great pressure too. Even though Chu Sect allied with Bai Zu tribe, we are against an enemy with tens or hundreds of times our strength! But they are not unified and have their own territories, they can only deploy limited Gu Immortals. And they are in the righteous path, they talk about rules and reputation... we still have a chance."

"When are they coming?" Fang Yuan asked the crucial question.

Chu Du chuckled: "Far from now. Even though they are spreading news everywhere and saying harsh words, they are still far from setting off. These Huang Jin tribes have their own conflicts and disagreements, they need to consider a lot of things, things are not as simple for them as us demonic path members."

Fang Yuan nodded.

Chu Du's words made him gain even clearer insight and analysis of the current situation in Northern Plains.

Chu Du looked at Fang Yuan: "This might sound presumptuous, but Brother Liu, your transformation path has already reached great grandmaster attainment level?"

"What? Not yet." Fang Yuan replied.

"Even if you are not a great grandmaster, you are at least quasi-great grandmaster." Chu Du said with much self confidence.

Fang Yuan laughed, asking instead: "How did you know?"

Chu Du chuckled: "I deduced it from your performance with the dao marks. The higher your attainment level, the easier it is to explore Crazed Demon Cave. Not Immortal was shocked by my improvement, that was because I had recently attained a qualitative improvement in my strength path attainment level."

Chu Du stared at Fang Yuan, his gaze contained deep meaning.

Fang Yuan knew that he was trying to ask about the killer move immortal tribulation tempering aperture.

After all, Chu Du was only using calamity beckoning Immortal Gu to gain some benefits from Fang Yuan.

The core method that could draw out Reckless Savage's true meaning had been kept secret by Fang Yuan, he did not reveal any of it.

Fang Yuan knew what Chu Du was trying to ask, but he pretended not to know, saying: "Oh, I see."

After saying those three words, there was no follow up, they continued traveling quietly.

Disappointment flashed deep in Chu Du's eyes.

He had been desiring immortal tribulation tempering aperture all along, but in this situation, that was no longer the focus.

Thus, Chu Du asked very vaguely, he knew that a clever person like Fang Yuan would understand what he was trying to say.

But Fang Yuan replied with three words — oh, I see.

Chu Du immediately understood, Fang Yuan had rejected him.

Like how Chu Du asked very subtly, Fang Yuan's answer was the same.

"Oh, I see." It meant that Fang Yuan's method to draw out true meaning was not for sale, he rejected a transaction.

"I can only forget about it for now." Chu Du felt it was a pity, but he was very rational. In this situation, he had to deepen his cooperation with Fang Yuan, he could not worsen their relationship.

Fang Yuan did not return to Hei Fan grotto-heaven with Chu Du.

Halfway through the journey, he parted with Chu Du.

Fang Yuan flew towards the southwest direction, some days later, he landed on an ordinary looking mound.

"According to Xue Song Zi's memories, this is the place." Fang Yuan looked around, confirming that he had arrived at the right place.

He started to activate his Immortal Gu, after a while, the immortal killer move activated successfully, and he found the location of a blessed land accurately.

His Immortal Gu and immortal killer move were borrowed from Heavenly Lord Bai Zu. For this, he paid a huge price.

However, it was completely worth it for Fang Yuan.

"Found it!" Fang Yuan's eyes shined, he summoned the upper extreme heavenly eagle.

The upper extreme heavenly eagle carried Fang Yuan and flew in a circle a few times, before piercing through space and bringing him into a new blessed land.

The owner of this blessed land had cultivated earth path during his life, thus, this blessed land was covered in black rotten mud.

Many small mud monsters were rolling around here.

From time to time, a desolate beast giant mud monster would jump up from the soil, like a huge black tidal wave.

A small mudman with a green strand of grass coming from its head floated and came to Fang Yuan.

"Bababa." The small mudman spoke, talking to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan listened and understood what it was saying.

He could not help but look at the mud below him, muttering: "To become the owner of the blessed land, I need to defeat five desolate beast mud monsters at once? Heh, easy."

The acknowledgement requirement of this earth path blessed land was difficult for most rank sixes.

But for Fang Yuan, it was very simple.

Fang Yuan was not unfamiliar with earth path, in fact, due to his previous life's experiences, his earth path attainment level was at master level.

After annexing this earth path blessed land, his Mini Western Desert gained a huge swamp.

For the following month, Fang Yuan went around everywhere, finding blessed lands and annexing them.

The upper extreme heavenly eagle displayed immense value, Fang Yuan easily got into blessed lands to explore them.

The information of these blessed lands was basically obtained from the Gu Immortals souls that Fang Yuan captured.

Dong Fang Chang Fan, Zheng Ling, Xue Song Zi, and the nine Gu Immortals in Hei Fan grotto-heaven, as well as the countless Gu Immortal souls from the turbulent flow sea area, and of course, Hei Cheng who was alive.

Counting them all, Fang Yuan had a large number of Gu Immortal captives!

These captives had been soul searched many times, he obtained all of their intel.

Fang Yuan's cultivation level rose tremendously, he skipped calamities and tribulations time and time again. The space and resources in the sovereign immortal aperture also increased each time he succeeded, rising time and time again.

Fang Yuan had long since passed his first heavenly tribulation.

By the time Fang Yuan returned to Lang Ya blessed land, in this short period of time, he had already passed two heavenly tribulations, he was a rank six Gu Immortal who was only three earthly calamities away from his third heavenly tribulation!

Chapter 1190: Blood Plain Martial Competition

Northern Plains, Feng Xian grotto-heaven.

Rank eight Gu Immortal Prince Feng Xian was silently sitting with his eyes shut.

Flames were burning around him, like clothes fluttering in the sky, they were dazzling and brilliant, dancing like dragons or snakes, extraordinary.

Right now, Prince Feng Xian opened his mouth, spitting out small pearls of flame.

The pearls of flame grew with the wind, in a breath of time, they expanded to become orange-red fireballs with the size of a baby's head.

The fireballs circled around Prince Feng Xian's body, flying up and down, left and right.

Next, Prince Feng Xian opened his mouth again, spitting out another pearl of flame.

A while later, Prince Feng Xian already had eight fireballs around him, they were flying around, crashing into one another, they moved in a profound trail, circling around Prince Feng Xian endlessly.

Right at this time, Prince Feng Xian suddenly opened his eyes.

An unbelievably sharp light burst out from his eyes, it was extremely dazzling.

Bam bam bam...

The eight fireballs self-detonated one by one, turning into flickers of flames, dissipating.

"I failed again, I did not manage to deduce any trace of Fang Yuan." Prince Feng Xian's eyes were shining, he stared at the fireballs that were gone.

If his deduction succeeded, these flames would instantly draw Fang Yuan's location, as well as what he was doing.

Evidently, Prince Feng Xian had failed once more.

He learned nothing.

"I am not a wisdom path Gu Immortal after all, I was just mimicking wisdom path, I cannot deduce Fang Yuan's true location." Prince Feng Xian sighed.

He was tasked to capture Fang Yuan, but the problem was, he had hidden himself too deeply. Most of the time, he was inside a blessed land and did not come out. As long as blessed lands and grotto-heavens did not absorb fragments of the nine heavens, they would be a completely different world isolated from the five regions, even Fairy Zi Wei cannot deduce anything.

Prince Feng Xian primarily cultivated fire path, he naturally could not.

Of course, Fang Yuan would go outside as well.

But he had familiar face and dark limit Immortal Gu. Together with his dark path dao marks, Fang Yuan could conceal his traces every time he traveled.

"Lord Feng Xian, Gong tribe is here, they want to meet you." At this moment, a female Gu Immortal dressed in yellow came to the hall and reported.

She was beautiful like a flower, she had watery eyes and peach-like lips, she was one of Prince Feng Xian's two female Gu Immortal attendants — Le Yao.

"Gong tribe is here? Hmph." Prince Feng Xian frowned: "Not meeting them."

"But Gong tribe's Gu Immortal brought the Longevity Edict." Le Yao hesitated.

Prince Feng Xian smiled lightly: "So what if they have the Longevity Edict? It can control the Huang Jin bloodline, but I am not one of them."

Le Yao pouted: "But lord, did you forget, we are now spies inside Northern Plains. You are still a son-in-law of Gong Tribe on the surface, an external supreme elder. If you defy the Longevity Edict openly, would it not be a problem?"

"Hahaha." Prince Feng Xian laughed heartily: "Le Yao, you are only half right. Longevity Heaven is not to be underestimated, it is a rank nine grotto-heaven, it has Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's foundation, and is unfathomably deep. It is simply like Central Continent's Heavenly Court in Northern Plains! But this time, Longevity Heaven sent orders to unite the Huang Jin tribes, all of the righteous path super forces are to attack Bai Zu tribe. This is a unified battle of the Huang Jin tribes against outside forces. The collapse of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, the creation of Bai Zu tribe, as well as Chu Sect, have stepped on Longevity Heaven's bottom line constantly. This time, Longevity Heaven will definitely not ask for my help, Yao Huang is their only choice!"

Prince Feng Xian analyzed it perfectly, Le Yao's eyes shone, but she did not understand: "Then why did Gong tribe's Gu Immortal bring the Longevity Edict here personally?"

Prince Feng Xian's eyes shined with cold light: "These people from Gong tribe are trying to falsely use that authority, to use the Longevity Edict and deceive me into helping them. You also know about Gong tribe's objective, they are still dreaming of becoming the number one righteous path force."

"So that's it. Then we will not meet them!" Le Yao smiled, showing her pearly white teeth, she had a beautiful smile, like the image of spring.

It was all according to what Prince Feng Xian had analyzed, several days later, the Longevity Edict was passed on to all of the Huang Jin tribes, eventually ending up in Yao Huang's hands.

Yao Huang used his old hands to receive the Longevity Edict, sighing deeply to himself.

"This Longevity Edict still ended up with me after all."

To one who heard him mumbling, it may have seemed that Yao Huang was aware all along.

The truth was that it was an obvious situation.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was a rank eight Gu Immortal, if the Northern Plains righteous path forces wanted to deal with Bai Zu tribe, they would need to have a rank eight Gu Immortal to deal with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu.

On the surface, out of the rank eight Gu Immortals in Northern Plains, other than Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, Old Ancestor Xue Hu was in the demonic path, Five Elements Grandmaster was a lone immortal and had invaded Longevity Heaven, he was already trapped inside Calamity Luck Altar. Only Prince Feng Xian and Yao Huang were left.

Prince Feng Xian's identity was the biggest problem.

He did not have the Huang Jin bloodline, he was just a son-in-law of Gong tribe!

If they relied on Prince Feng Xian and defeated Bai Zu tribe, would that not prove Five Elements Grandmaster's point? The great Huang Jin bloodline, descendants of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, could not rely on themselves to defeat a strong foe?

Thus, for Longevity Heaven, there was only one person they could choose, the rank eight refinement path Gu Immortal Yao Huang!

In fact, Yao Huang really did not want to involve himself in this mess.

Currently, he was very busy trying to refine resurrection from the dead Immortal Gu!

He was severely interrupted, Yao Huang was in a bad mood.

Ping.

A soft sound echoed.

Yao Huang threw the Longevity Edict onto the table casually.

"I should go talk to Heavenly Lord Bai Zu first." Yao Huang sighed, storing his immortal aperture and going to the outside world of Northern Plains, flying into white heaven.

A moment later, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, who received Yao Huang's invitation, hesitated for a moment, before deciding to meet with Yao Huang and discuss the matter.

The two rank eight Gu Immortals met in white heaven and talked in secret.

In fact, they were friends.

Long ago, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had considered creating Bai Zu tribe, thus, as a lone cultivator, he got very close to Yao Huang.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu wanted to be in the righteous path, but there were only two righteous path Gu Immortals, Prince Feng Xian did not originate from the righteous path, he stayed by himself and his relationship with Gong tribe was not good.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu could only have a goal of getting close to Yao Huang.

Afterwards, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and Yao Huang had fought against Old Ancestor Xue Hu together. Even though they lost and caused Old Ancestor Xue Hu's reputation to surge, this matter had brought Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and Yao Huang closer together.

Thus, when they met, there was no animosity or anger.

"Friend, what do you think?" Yao Huang smiled and asked.

"Sigh, it has gotten to this point, I'll tell you the truth, I did not expect this." Heavenly Lord Bai Zu waved his hand, he also felt very gloomy about the situation.

His motive was very simple, he wanted to take down Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

But to think that Chu Du's battle strength and wits exceeded Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's expectations, it caused the situation to change and worsen, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu could not back out.

Among which, the rumors and threats regarding Heavenly Lord Bai Zu in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world were all spread by Chu Du and his subordinates.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was aware of this.

Anyone with a functioning brain knew.

But now, in fact, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and the culprit of the rumors, Chu Du had allied, to deal with the righteous path forces that he did not want to face.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was also very helpless in the progression of this matter.

Yao Huang saw Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's expression and deeply understood his feelings, Yao Huang pointed and smiled: "Old friend, do you understand now? It is not easy to be the leader of a righteous path force, in many situations, even as rank eight Gu Immortals, we cannot act freely."

"I used to envy your lone cultivator status, I also urged you not to create any righteous path force, do you feel it now?"

"I feel it. But I have worked hard for so long, it was not easy to get such results, I am not willing to give up just yet." Heavenly Lord Bai Zu said openly.

Yao Huang was silent, before saying: "I do not want to interfere in this matter either, but I cannot help it, Longevity Heaven's token is already in my hands."

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu sighed deeply, he felt gladness but also sorrow in his heart.

He was glad that his relationship with Yao Huang was close enough, but the sad thing was, he and Yao Huang were friends, but they had to fight. Even as rank eight Gu Immortals, they could not decide this for themselves.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu sighed deeply: "Then we can only fight now."

Yao tribe waved his hand: "This is an eventual matter, we are not in a rush now. Even though I am in charge of this matter, Yao tribe is just one of the righteous path forces, I still have Longevity Heaven overseeing it. They are watching patiently now, even if we fight, we cannot resolve this matter. In my opinion, we should let these juniors fight first, and rile them up."

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu pondered and nodded: "Then in that case, let's decide a date for a martial competition."

"Alright." Yao Huang thought: "Blood Plain is a good choice of location, how about there?"

"That is good." Heavenly Lord Bai Zu agreed instantly.

The two Gu Immortals talked for a while, deciding the matter of the Blood Plain martial competition, before leaving white heaven and going back to their tribes.

They gave their respective instructions on the Blood Plain martial competition.

At once, Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world went into commotion again.

A new storm was brewing, it faintly swept through the entire Northern Plains Gu Immortal world.

The Gu Immortals from the Huang Jin tribes were rubbing their hands together in anticipation, they felt that they had sufficient strength to suppress the allied forces of Bai Zu tribe and Chu Sect, they had high morale.

In terms of foundation, the allied forces of Chu Sect and Bai Zu tribe could not match the alliance of the righteous path forces, but they could seek help.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was from the lone cultivator faction, while Chu Du was a famous expert in the demonic path!

There was still some time until the competition. News of the Blood Plain martial competition had spread, even Central Continent and the other regions heard of it.

Both sides were gathering strength, the righteous path Huang Jin tribes were choosing carefully, only picking the elites, while Bai Zu tribe and Chu Sect started recruiting for experts to help them, making great preparations.

Chapter 1191: Begging

Central Continent, deep in Earth Abyss.

Delicious wine and food was set out in the garden.

"Come, Brother Shi, I have heard that you like delicious wine. I have purposely looked for these wines for you to taste." Gu Immortal Yang Feng sat upright as he stretched out his arm towards his esteemed guest.

This guest had short white hair and shining golden eyes with sharp light in them, he wore a tight martial uniform and had a blue silver belt, his forearms and knees had dazzling armor.

He had broad shoulders and a slim waist, he was emitting a valiant aura. But he was half-leaning on the wall and had a casual posture, it lifted a bit of the pressure that he was emitting.

Gu Immortal Yang Feng was a rank seven transformation path Gu Immortal, an expert in Ancient Soul Sect of the ten great ancient sects, but compared to his guest, he was inferior in fame.

Because this guest was Shi Lei, he cultivated earth path primarily and transformation path secondarily, he was at the peak of rank seven, he was an expert of Central Continent known as the Immortal Monkey King!

"Then I will not stand on ceremony." Shi Lei laughed, he stretched out his arm, lifting the wine vat on the table.

Breaking the seal, the smell of liquor burst out, it felt like an intense flame had started raging.

Instantly, in the huge garden, it was filled with the smell of thick alcohol.

The alcohol was red in color, the vapor gathered around the vat, resembling a bright cloud of flames.

Shi Lei saw this and became joyful, praising: "Good wine! So this is the legendary red emperor wine. Brother Yang Feng, you could actually get your hands on this, you are quite impressive."

Gu Immortal Yang Feng laughed loudly: "I'll not hide it from Brother Shi, I paid a huge price to obtain it from Ancient Soul Sect's treasury. Come to speak of it, this was thanks to our ancestor. Three hundred thousand years ago, a Gu Immortal from our sect became friends with a Gu Immortal of Eastern Sea, Wine Emperor, during the Gu refinement path convention, they competed in refining Gu and agreed that whoever won would obtain the loser's creation. They fought for eighty-one days, having their respective victories, they were closely matched. This red emperor wine was created by Wine Emperor, he had lost it to our ancestor."

Ancient Soul Sect of the ten great ancient sects had ancient in its name, true to its name, the sect was very old, having the longest history among the ten great ancient sects.

Three hundred thousand years ago, that was the Medieval Antiquity Era. Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable, and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable appeared in succession during this era. A female Gu Immortal, Shui Ni, founded water path and built Spirit Affinity House, it was also during this era.

"Oh?" Shi Lei was intrigued: "Wine Emperor, I know this person, he was a food path rank eight expert, he was very famous in human history. His entire life's effort was in the creation of his three sovereign five emperor wines. Legend says that by combining these eight wines, one can obtain the rank eight liquor worm Immortal Gu. Using this Gu, one can turn rank eight white litchi immortal essence into rank nine yellow apricot immortal essence. After this person died, he left his inheritance behind. Currently, there is the Eastern Sea Gu Immortal Zui Xian Weng, who became the one hundred and thirty-seventh inheritor."

"Brother Shi, you are so knowledgeable, I am impressed. Cheers!" Yang Feng raised his wine cup.

Shi Lei waved his hand instead: "Drinking with a cup is not satisfying enough, let's drink from the vats directly."

"Okay, Brother Shi, you are very direct, I will do the same." Yang Feng patted the table, replying.

But Shi Lei had just touched the vat when his movements paused, his expression changed as he looked outside.

An information path Immortal Gu had appeared in the sky above the garden, it was flying around but did not land.

Shi Lei's golden eyes shone: "This is an Immortal Gu from my sect, Brother Yang, please let it in."

This garden was not normal, it was exquisitely built, grand with white jade tiles, it was oozing with cold air, there were faint dragon roars heard occasionally, this was Ancient Soul Sect's Immortal Gu House, Frost Dragon Manor!

Yang Feng manipulated the Immortal Gu House, opening a path for the information path Immortal Gu to fly towards Shi Lei.

After inspecting it, Shi Lei's expression changed slightly.

Yang Feng could not ask about the sect matters, he raised his cup and savored the red emperor wine.

To think that Shi Lei took the initiative: "Northern Plains Gu Immortals are indeed battle maniacs, Hei tribe was just destroyed, and now they are starting to fight again. This time, the commotion is even bigger. All the Huang Jin tribes are ganging up to deal with the newly established alliance of Chu Sect and Bai Zu tribe."

"Chu Sect?" Yang Feng was confused.

"This is a newly created sect, do you know about Northern Plains' Chu Du?"

"I know a little, a strength path Gu Immortal, known as Domination Immortal."

"That's right, he created Chu Sect. This person is not to be underestimated, he used Hei Fan grotto-heaven to forcefully resist Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's invasion. He even nurtured many strength path Gu Immortals secretly, he has quite a force."

Yang Feng frowned, after absorbing this information, he said: "Strength path is like the setting sun, it is nothing much. But this Chu Sect is probably the first sect in Northern Plains, this Chu Du is so daring!"

"That's right." Shi Lei said: "This is a good show to watch. Both sides have agreed to hold a martial competition. Hehe, Northern Plains is really exciting, they are fighting all the time, why was I not born in Northern Plains."

"Cough, cough."

Shi Lei patted his own head: "Oh, I nearly forgot. Heavenly Court has orders, we are to go and attack Star Form blessed land now."

"Why, Heavenly Court has already confirmed that Fang Yuan will not come?" Yang Feng asked in surprise.

As it turned out, after Ying Wu Xie and the rest escaped from Heavenly Court, Fairy Zi Wei had never given up on searching for Fang Yuan's traces.

Fang Yuan's true body was not exposed yet, even Prince Feng Xian could not make any progress. But using some clues and her immense capabilities, Fairy Zi Wei managed to forcefully deduce the existence of Star Form blessed land.

Star Form blessed land was inside Earth Abyss, it was in Ancient Soul Sect's territory.

Fairy Zi Wei specially asked Gu Immortal Shi Lei to complete a task.

Shi Lei was a supreme elder of Combat Immortal Sect, Ancient Soul Sect sent Yang Feng to cooperate with Shi Lei.

Shi Lei was following orders, according to Fairy Zi Wei's plan, he was waiting in ambush. The moment Fang Yuan returned to Star Form blessed land, he would capture him immediately.

But after waiting for so long, Fang Yuan did not even appear once!

Not long ago, Star Form blessed land faced calamity, Fang Yuan made up his mind and ignored it.

Fairy Zi Wei noticed Fang Yuan's determination and deduced that if Star Form blessed land was kept intact, it would be of much help to Fang Yuan in the future.

Thus, she decided to go ahead and order Shi Lei to destroy Star Form blessed land.

Spirit Affinity House.

Lake Heart Mountain.

Feng Jin Huang's accommodations.

"Senior sister, you are amazing, you could refine even this type of Gu!" Qin Juan held the Gu with both hands as she cried out excitedly.

Feng Jin Huang had snowy skin, her eyebrows were long and golden, her lips curled up as she smiled: "This is nothing much."

She had dream wings Immortal Gu, her refinement path attainment was now grandmaster level. Refining a rank three mortal Gu was really nothing much.

"Senior, senior sister, oh no!" At this time, a Gu Master ran over with a flustered look on her chubby face.

Qin Juan was unhappy at her demeanor: "Sun Yao, you are an elite disciple of Spirit Affinity House, how can you be so panicky."

Feng Jin Huang smiled: "No need to worry, I am here. Tell me, what happened?"

Sun Yao breathed in deeply as she said: "That, that Zhao Lian Yun is coming!"

"What, Zhao Lian Yun?" Qin Juan's expression changed, she looked at Feng Jin Huang worriedly: "Zhao Lian Yun is an otherworldly demon, she has also inherited Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's true inheritance, since she joined the sect, she had been your opponent. Zhao Lian Yun wants to compete with senior sister over the next generation fairy position of Spirit Affinity House, why is she coming here to find you?"

Feng Jin Huang's smile gradually faded: "I am not sure either, go, let's meet her and ask, wouldn't that answer our questions?"

The three left the room, meeting a girl.

This girl was dressed in white, like a flower by the lake, she had long black silky hair with a worried look between her eyebrows, she had clear skin and pupils like they were fused with the night sky, expressing worry and anxiety.

Such beauty was comparable to Feng Jin Huang, it was Zhao Lian Yun!

"Junior sister Zhao, I wonder what business you have with me?" Feng Jin Huang was the first to ask.

Zhao Lian Yun hesitated for a moment, determination shone in her eyes.

Plop.

At the next moment, she knelt down.

Qin Juan and Sun Yao did not expect this, they gasped in shock.

Feng Jin Huang was also quite shocked: "Junior sister Zhao, why are you doing this?"

"I really have no other alternatives. Please, please save Ma Hong Yun!" Zhao Lian Yun said, as tears flowed down her smooth cheeks.

"Ma Hong Yun, who is he? He asked you to come and beg me? Come, you can get up and tell me, don't kneel." Feng Jin Huang quickly walked forward, stretching out her arms to help Zhao Lian Yun stand up.

She had the magnanimity of a senior sister.

Even though she and Zhao Lian Yun were fiercely competing for the position of fairy, now that Zhao Lian Yun was begging her, Feng Jin Huang did not look down on her, she offered to help her up instead.

But Zhao Lian Yun did not get up, she shook off Feng Jin Huang's hands, sobbing: "Right now, the only one who can help me is you, senior sister Feng Jin Huang!"

...

Southern Border, Gu Yue village.

Fang Yuan clenched his fists, gritting his teeth, he said to the two people sitting in front: "Uncle, aunt, you have already obtained the inheritance my parents left. Right now, I need some primeval stones, can't you help me?"

Aunt snorted, saying shrilly: "That is not right, we did not take your parents' inheritance, they are with your brother. Your brother has A grade aptitude, he has a far better future than you. I believe that your parents would do this too if they were still alive."

"Oh Fang Yuan." Uncle said in a calm and slow manner: "I know what you are thinking, you want primeval stones to buy Gu refinement materials and refine Gu. But do you know how hard it is to refine Gu? How big the risks are? You, oh, you are simply too young. Don't bear such unrealistic thoughts, just do your part properly. With your C grade aptitude, stop dreaming and live your life realistically."

It was winter now.

Inside the warm room, Fang Yuan's heart was ice cold.

He had been standing on the spot, after a short silence, he said: "I understand now."

He turned around and walked out.

Behind him, aunt criticized sarcastically: "Leaving like this? Not even saying goodbye, he is truly polite!"

Uncle was smiling, saying in a fake tone: "Oh Fang Yuan, don't be so anxious to leave, stay for dinner."

Fang Yuan did not stop, he walked even faster with firmer steps.

From his uncle and aunt's place, he went towards the streets with many people.

It was late at night now.

Even though there was no snow, the cold air gave Fang Yuan a bone chilling feeling.

Next, he looked up at the sky, clenching his fists.

In the sky, countless stars were shining brightly.

Starlight reflected in Fang Yuan's pupils, his eyes seemed to be shining with life.

"Since I transmigrated to this world, I must achieve something in life, so what if I have C grade aptitude, I can definitely succeed!"

Fang Yuan did not see that behind him, a figure was quietly tailing him, watching all the events unfold.

The stars in the night sky were shining even more brightly, this figure's appearance became clear.

It was another Fang Yuan.

But this Fang Yuan's appearance had changed completely, experience and maturity was also deep in his gaze.

Under his supervision, the entire night sky, the entire dream realm faded, as if there was a thick layer of fog in the sky, gradually, everything vanished.

In the real world, Fang Yuan opened his eyes slowly, muttering: "To think... that I could re-experience what happened in my previous life."

Chapter 1192: Concession

Central Continent, Spirit Affinity House.

"Zhao Lian Yun might be an otherworldly demon, but she has deep love in her." Feng Jin Huang's mother Fairy Bai Qing looked through the window, a very far distance away, focusing on Zhao Lian Yun, who was still kneeling in the courtyard.

Zhao Lian Yun approached Feng Jin Huang and begged her to help save Ma Hong Yun.

Feng Jin Huang was lost, after asking, she learned about Zhao Lian Yun and Ma Hong Yun's heart wrenching story.

Zhao Lian Yun was begging for help, but regardless of what Feng Jin Huang said, she seemed to be fixated on this, she refused to get up. Feng Jin Huang had no choice but to find her parents for help.

Her mother was a rank seven female immortal of Spirit Affinity House, Bai Qing, while her father was the famous Feng Jiu Ge!

Feng Jiu Ge walked towards Fairy Bai Qing, he did not look at Zhao Lian Yun, instead, he looked at the sky, saying plainly: "Dear, can't you tell? Zhao Lian Yun is guided by some people."

Fairy Bai Qing's gaze flashed: "Do you mean Xu Hao and Li Jun Ying?"

Places with people will have competition for benefits.

Spirit Affinity House had its internal conflicts too.

Feng Jiu Ge was powerful, in the absence of rank eights, he dominated the ten great ancient sects, nobody could rival him. But this did not mean he had no opponents.

Competition in this world did not just involve fighting and killing.

Xu Hao and Li Jun Ying were Feng Jiu Ge's main opponents in Spirit Affinity House.

The two of them were married too.

Among which, Xu Hao was a wisdom path Gu Immortal, while Li Jun Ying was known as the Illusory Fairy, her power was extraordinary.

In the previous life, when Feng Jiu Ge died inside the Thieving Heaven true inheritance's special space, these two immediately exerted pressure on Fairy Bai Qing and had a powerful stance. But afterwards, when Fang Yuan used Spring Autumn Cicada and ended up saving Feng Jiu Ge, history was changed.

Feng Jiu Ge's return caused great pressure on Xu Hao and Li Jun Ying, they were at a disadvantage.

However, using Zhao Lian Yun's influence, the two of them held their ground and were untouchable by even Feng Jiu Ge inside Spirit Affinity House.

Hearing Fairy Bai Qing mention their names, Feng Jiu Ge admitted: "It is them. This was my mistake, back then, I sent Xu Hao to complete the mission for the Thieving Heaven true inheritance, I wanted to push them aside, but to think they actually benefited from it."

"Huang Er wants to be the next generation fairy, she was originally unmatched, but now, Zhao Lian Yun appeared. As expected of an otherworldly demon, this woman is very intelligent and has a different perspective on many matters, yet she can get to the point and succeed in her unique methods, she is truly worthy of being Huang Er's opponent."

"This time, Zhao Lian Yun is kneeling and begging for help, Xu Hao probably instigated this. Zhao Lian Yun wants to save her lover, she has to fight for the position of fairy. That way, she would have enough authority to use Spirit Affinity House's power. If Huang Er gives in to her, she would give up being the fairy. But if she rejects her, it would breed trouble."

Feng Jiu Ge analyzed deeply, he easily exposed Xu Hao's schemes.

He was a sound path Gu Immortal, but he had incredible wits, he had a keen perception towards these internal conflicts.

Fairy Bai Qing rolled her eyes, saying playfully: "Dear, why would I not understand these? Our Spirit Affinity House's signature Immortal Gu is Love, our sect values moving people through love. Xu Hao asked Zhao Lian Yun to do this, he probably does not expect her to succeed. But after Zhao Lian Yun is rejected by Huang Er, others would sympathize with her."

"Hahaha, my dear, you are so smart, I was unduly worried." Feng Jiu Ge laughed.

Xu Hao was trying so desperately to make Zhao Lian Yun win and defeat Feng Jin Huang, and become the fairy of Spirit Affinity House. That way, he could use Zhao Lian Yun's power to ally with others and oppose Feng Jiu Ge together.

Xu Hao had a good plan.

All along, Zhao Lian Yun's identity as an otherworldly demon was her biggest obstacle in becoming Spirit Affinity House's fairy. Because people were more willing to believe in those who originated from a similar background.

Zhao Lian Yun, who came from another world, was ostracized and guarded against.

But after this matter, Zhao Lian Yun's image in Spirit Affinity House would completely transform in the eyes of everyone.

Even though Zhao Lian Yun was an otherworldly demon, she loved a man of the Gu world.

For this man, she fought for the position of fairy, she was not a vicious or ambitious person.

She was really pitiful, nobody was helping her. Her lover was in Northern Plains, he might die any time, these lovebirds might never get together again!

"This time, Xu Hao made a good plan. No matter what decision Huang Er makes, she would still lose. In fact, to compete for the position of fairy, she has to reject Zhao Lian Yun." Feng Jiu Ge said plainly.

"Then we let her continue kneeling here?" Fairy Bai Qing asked.

Feng Jiu Ge smiled: "No worries, she won't stay here for long, this is just a show."

But Fairy Bai Qing shook her head: "I do not agree with this. Did you not see Zhao Lian Yun's eyes, she is so determined and resolute, she is in deep agony. Do you think Xu Hao would tell her about the truth? At this moment, Zhao Lian Yun probably thinks that her only hope in saving her lover lies in Huang Er giving up this contest! She will definitely not give up, she will continue kneeling."

Feng Jiu Ge did not speak, he looked at the sky, he still paid no attention to Zhao Lian Yun.

Feng Jiu Ge was a little regretful now.

If he had known this, he would not have bought Zhao Lian Yun back in the Northern Plains auction.

Right now, she was Feng Jin Huang's greatest obstacle.

Parents in this world still had the same wishes, they wanted their sons or daughters to succeed in life.

Even Feng Jiu Ge with rank eight battle strength was no exception from this.

"Even your mother pities Zhao Lian Yun, oh Huang Er, we will not advise you this time, how will you deal with this?" Feng Jiu Ge was secretly anticipating as he waited.

On the road to Lake Heart Mountain.

Qin Juan kicked a rock along the path angrily: "This Zhao Lian Yun is so annoying! Is this how you beg someone? She wants you to give up the contest for the position of fairy, she has the nerves to say that! She is really shameless."

"But she really has no choice. She already explained that this is for the sake of her lover" Sun Yao mumbled.

"Yes but even so, she cannot do this. Kneeling on the ground, refusing to get up, does she want us to beg her to get up? Seriously, oh, I am so angry! She even caused senior sister's home to be surrounded by spectators, causing you to be unable to go home, and have to roam out here!" Qin Juan stomped, going crazy.

"However, she is really pitiful. I did not feel that last time, but hearing her words, I find that Zhao Lian Yun is really kind too..." Sun Yao shook her head.

"Hey, whose side are you on, you are speaking up for Zhao Lian Yun!" Qin Juan was furious as she pointed at Sun Yao: "Senior sister is the most qualified person to be Spirit Affinity House's fairy, Zhao Lian Yun is an outsider, how can she? And you, Sun Yao, correct your attitude. Did you forget about how senior sister has been taking care of us all along? You actually said such words, are you repaying kindness with enmity?"

"No, I have no such intentions. I just think that she is pitiful, no matter what decision senior sister makes, I will support her." Sun Yao waved her hand, explaining.

Qin Juan calmed down a little, she started worrying for Feng Jin Huang: "Senior sister must be troubled now. This Zhao Lian Yun really posed a good problem. If we agree to her demand, we will give up the position of fairy. But if we don't, people will say that senior sister is heartless, and people will sympathize for Zhao Lian Yun and acknowledge her. Most importantly, the contest for fairy is not just decided by our seniors, it also considers the view of our generation's disciples. Every generation's fairy in Spirit Affinity House has to be acknowledged by everyone!"

"Hehehe." Walking in front, Feng Jin Huang suddenly laughed lightly to herself.

She stopped walking, Qin Juan and Sun Yao realized that they were at the mountain slope that they usually went to.

Feng Jin Huang stood on the slope, raising her head as she looked at the stars in the sky.

Next, she spoke: "I will not concede."

Her tone was plain, but Sun Yao and Qin Juan could hear her unwavering determination.

Feng Jin Huang's clear eyes reflected the light of the stars in the sky. Winds of the night blew, caressing her face as her hair fluttered in the sky.

She continued: "Even though Zhao Lian Yun is pitiful, the title of the next generation fairy is my goal. This is the path that I have decided on, I will not change it for the sake of others!"

Northern Plains, Lang Ya blessed land, Fang Yuan was inside his own dream realm.

Inside Qing Mao Mountain again.

In Gu Yue village, a young Fang Yuan was standing in front of Gu Yue clan leader.

"You want me to give in to Fang Zheng tomorrow on purpose? And lose to him?!" Fang Yuan stared with wide opened eyes, growling.

Gu Yue clan leader sighed: "Fang Yuan, I understand that this is not your fault, Fang Zheng was the instigator. But you need to understand, he has been living under your shadow, unable to get free. He challenged you because his heart's inner desires are leading him to oppose you, to defeat you and break free from his childhood trauma, and obtain the heart of an expert."

Fang Yuan lowered his head, gritting his teeth: "Clan leader, since you looked for me in secret, that means I have the strength to defeat him."

"That's right, you took a debt and pawned all of your assets just to luckily succeed in refining that Gu. This greatly raised your battle strength. But Fang Zheng has A grade aptitude, he is taught by several elders, he has quite the skill, he just lacks some experience." Gu Yue clan elder said.

"A grade aptitude... hehe." Fang Yuan raised his head and looked at Gu Yue clan leader, smiling in a mocking manner.

"Your decision is?" Gu Yue clan leader was expressionless, looking down at Fang Yuan imposingly.

Fang Yuan turned around and walked away.

His figure faded into the shadows.

He left with one sentence: "I'll do it."

Gu Yue clan leader did not speak, his gaze became dark as he muttered to himself: "He conceded so easily, he must have other ideas. To play it safe, I should preemptively weaken him first."

Chapter 1193: Gong Wan Ting

Dawn.

When the first ray of sunlight shone, the flowers and grass were still wet with dew.

A blood thorn snake slithered out of its cavern after the unbearable cold night, greedily absorbing the warmth of the sunlight.

Ordinary snakes were cold-blooded, but the blood thorn snake's blood was warm.

As its temperature rose, it gradually regained its nimbleness. It stretched out its body and flicked out its tongue, as it started to look for food.

It needed to get enough food today and digest them to cope with the next cold night.

In this world, all living beings were struggling and fighting for every aspect of survival.

The appearance of the blood thorn snake was terrifying, but its nature was gentle. It did not eat meat and it fed on blood jaspers.

Its tongue darted in and out, and soon, it discovered its food.

Blood jaspers were translucent, like rose stones, hanging on the tips of stalks of grass. It was the dew from flowers and plants which had certain probabilities of transforming under the rays of dawn.

If this blood jasper managed to avoid the blood thorn snake's hunt and endure through the cold nights, after seven days and seven nights, it would transform into a small rank one blood jasper Gu.

The blood thorn snake quickly slithered over.

Rustle rustle....

The dense shrubs were shaking continuously, showing traces of a line. Within several breaths of time, the blood thorn snake crossed a thousand steps of distance and neared this blood jasper.

The snake's head rose and was about to devour this delectable food when suddenly, a loud explosion sounded from the horizon.

The blood thorn snake shook in fear, its whole body fell down to the ground without any trace of strength left.

Boom! Boom! Boom!

Explosions reverberated through the landscape like war drums.

An enormous hall moved through the clouds and descended above this grassland, like the ruler of the world.

This hall had a broad structure and magnificent appearance, with lightning snakes coiling around it and countless thunderbolts raining down beside it.

Inside the hall, Nu Er Gu laughed heartily: "Sure enough, Loud Thunder Hall is extremely powerful! In this blood battle competition, my Nu Er tribe has this hall to suppress the situation, we will definitely kill the enemies. Hahaha!"

He was a famous rank seven Gu Immortal expert of Northern Plains' righteous path, specializing in sound path and had impressive battle achievements. His battle strength stood at the same level as Guan Chou of Guan tribe, Unfettered Scholar and Pi Shui Han.

Nu Er Gu had a small head and big belly, his body was disproportional, his eyeballs were popping out, while his limbs were dry as twigs, he had pale skin resembling a sick person, without any hint of blood in his face.

Right now, Nu Er Gu was controlling Loud Thunder Hall, experiencing the overflowing strength of this Immortal Gu House.

He was extremely excited!

Along with Nu Er Gu were several of Nu Er tribe's Gu Immortals.

Among them, a girl did not conceal her frown, covering her ears as she shouted: "Alright, Nu Er Gu, stop using thunder sound. It is truly noisy, if you use it again, I will turn you into a toad."

Nu Er Gu who had been in high spirits, heard the girl's threat, his demeanor immediately disappeared without a trace.

"Great-aunt, I made a mistake!" He quickly turned around and bowed in apology.

The girl waved her hand: "Little Gu, you need to behave, we can't stand out in this blood battle martial competition. Yao tribe, Guan tribe and Liu tribe are the ones nearer to Chu Sect and Bai Zu tribe. If we put too much effort, they will just watch from the sidelines and reap the benefits."

"Yes, great-aunt, you are right. I shall listen to great-aunt's arrangement." Nu Er Gu quickly patted his chest and assured.

The other Nu Er tribe Gu Immortals almost could not hold back their laughter.

According to bloodline seniority, this Gu Immortal with the appearance of a little girl was indeed Nu Er Gu's great-aunt.

The crucial point was that she was very powerful and had a trump card immortal killer move, which she had tested on Nu Er Gu since he was young. The trauma on Nu Er Gu was extremely huge from this, and he had developed a fear of his great-aunt.

"Hmm? Gong tribe's people are also coming." The girl suddenly turned around, under the amplification of Loud Thunder Hall, her gaze easily pierced through an enormous distance, seeing another Immortal Gu House.

This Immortal Gu House was similarly a hall, it was Gong tribe's Golden Dawn Hall, shining with brilliant golden radiance.

When Nu Er Gu saw a female Gu Immortal standing at the entrance of the Golden Dawn Hall, he immediately frowned: "Why is it her?"

This woman looked to be in her late twenties, she was clad in dazzling palace attire with the lower hems touching the ground, her black hair was tied up high with jade and gold ornaments. Her skin was snow white, her eyebrows slender, her gaze sharp, and her chest was voluptuous and perky. She looked stately and beautiful, giving a feeling that she could not be offended.

"Gong Wan Ting?" Nu Er tribe's girl exclaimed in slight surprise, before quickly adding, "Come with me."

Nu Er tribe's Gu Immortals immediately flew out of Loud Thunder Hall and went up to the entrance of Golden Dawn Hall.

The girl greeted first in a cordial tone: "Elder sister Wan Ting, hope you have been well."

Gong Wan Ting lightly smiled: "Little sister Nu Er Qian, good day to you."

The two Immortal Gu House stopped above Blood Plain, this was a rare scene in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world.

Next, the third Immortal Gu House appeared, making this scene even more colorful.

Divine Light Hall!

Yao tribe's Immortal Gu House.

A Gu Immortal of Yao tribe, Yao Yuan Ying, flew out of the Immortal Gu House and greeted Gong Wan Ting first before greeting Nu Er Qian.

Nu Er Gu could not help but secretly transmit his voice to Nu Er Qian: "Great-aunt, it looks like Gong tribe came prepared this time. Sending Gong Wan Ting over, even the current holder of the Longevity Edict, Yao tribe, is overwhelmed."

Nu Er Qian transmitted back her reply: "Gong Wan Ting is Prince Feng Xian's official wife, who can dare to not respect her? Even if Yao Huang were to be present, he would also have to be somewhat courteous to her. But the person Yao tribe sent this time is actually Yao Yuan Ying. Her nature is gentle and she is not proficient in fighting and killing, but is specialized in healing. It seems Yao tribe also does not have the intention to put in much effort."

Just looking at these Gu Immortals, one could have some clues to the thoughts of each tribe.

Last time, Gong tribe had suffered the most in the battle at Iron Eagle blessed land, when Gong Er returned to the tribe, he had been punished. This time, Gong tribe wanted Prince Feng Xian to show up, but their ploy was seen through by Prince Feng Xian. Gong tribe could only choose the next best option, sending Gong Wan Ting.

She was Prince Feng Xian's wife, she had rank seven cultivation, with powerful battle strength, and was a genuine expert. Gong tribe's main objective this time was to revitalize their prestige.

Yao tribe sent Yao Yuan Ying, a healing Gu Immortal who was not good at fighting, and she had been appointed by Yao Huang. Yao Huang was friends with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, so he came up with the blood battle martial competition as an explanation to Longevity Heaven, his main focus was still on refining Gu. Some combative Gu Immortals of Yao tribe had been suppressed by Yao Huang, and could only grit their teeth with nothing they could do about it.

Nu Er tribe sent Nu Er Qian and Nu Er Gu as the main forces. Nu Er Gu's nature was erratic and was very aggressive, while Nu Er Qian was stable, experienced and very reliable. The main thing was that she could restrain Nu Er Gu.

However, Nu Er tribe also had the intention to forge ahead this time. So they did not stint on mobilizing the tribe's Immortal Gu House, Loud Thunder Hall.

But the final decision was in Nu Er Qian's hands.

Next, Huang Jin tribes appeared one after the other.

Liu tribe, Ye Lui tribe, Chanyu tribe, Meng tribe, Yuan tribe, Nian Er tribe, Murong tribe, Guan tribe.

A total of eleven Huang Jin tribes, super forces who ruled over territories, and had undisputed influence to Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world.

There had been two more tribes previously.

One was Dong Fang tribe, it was a pity, Dong Fang Chang Fan made it flourish, and it also was destroyed because of the failure of his plan to resurrect.

It could be said that Dong Fang tribe rose because of Dong Fang Chang Fan, and also suffered their downfall at Dong Fang Chang Fan's hands.

Another was Hei tribe. Hei tribe had many surviving Gu Immortals, but they were annexed by Bai Zu tribe, their tribe name was discarded and they no longer were acknowledged by other Huang Jin tribes, even being cast aside and disdained upon.

"Greetings to Fairy Gong Wan Ting." Like Yao tribe and Nu Er tribe, the Gu Immortals of different tribes also greeted Gong Wan Ting.

Gong Wan Ting's own battle strength made her an undisputed leader of the righteous path, and more importantly was her status, she was Prince Feng Xian's wife!

Even if she were a mortal, just this status alone was worthy for these Gu Immortals to have such an attitude.

"Gong tribe actually sent Fairy Wan Ting over, such a ruthless move, they clearly want to suppress Yao tribe."

"Gong tribe's people like to look down on others, to be honest, I like Yao tribe a bit more. After all, Lord Yao Huang is of our Huang Jin bloodline."

Each tribe's Gu Immortals acutely sensed the undercurrents in the righteous path forces, they were all secretly discussing, and looking forward to how Yao tribe would react.

"With Fairy Gong Wan Ting here, how could I, Yao Yuan Ying, command this edict?" Beyond most of the Gu Immortals' expectations, Yao tribe's representative Yao Yuan Ying directly handed over the Longevity Edict.

Gong Wan Ting, however, refused with a smile.

Yao Yuan Ying offered a second time.

Gong Wan Ting again refused, except her attitude had eased up by a lot.

Yao Yuan Ying offered the third time, and only then did Gong Wan Ting accept, looking like she was forced to.

And the moment she took it, she placed it at the center of the plaque on the entrance of Golden Dawn Hall.

Gong Wan Ting then continued: "Everyone, please come inside the hall. My tribe has already prepared some light wine and delicacies."

The immortals all accepted her invitation.

Previously, Gong Er had also invited others, but no one gave him face. Gong Wan Ting, however, was different, all the immortals knew that behind her was Prince Feng Xian. Even though the rumors of marital discord between them had spread for a long time, the immortals could not be careless.

Each tribe's immortals entered the hall.

Yao tribe was seated first from the left side, because left had the highest status, followed by right and center.[1]

Nu Er tribe was first from the right side because they had brought Loud Thunder Hall.

Other tribes were arranged according to the strength of the forces that they sent over.

Who could have thought such an arrangement would make one person extremely dissatisfied.

"Why is my Nian Er tribe last? Does Gong Wan Ting look down on us?" Nian Er Ping Zhi was outraged, as he transmitted his voice to the tribe's senior Gu Immortal beside him.

Right now, it was not just Nian Er Fu who came, but also wood path Gu Immortal Nian Er Yi Fang.

When he heard the words, he placed his aged hand on Nian Er Ping Zhi's shoulder, and spoke expectantly and with encouragement: "Ping Zhi, if you are dissatisfied, kill some opponents in the blood martial competition, at that time, when we mention changing our positions, no one will stop us, and it will also show our Nian Er tribe's prestige."

"Elder Yi Fang, you are right! I will do so then!" Nian Er Ping Zhi clenched his fists, his eyes brightened with a sharp luster.

From the main seat in the middle, Gong Wan Ting was secretly observing everyone, and when she saw Nian Er Ping Zhi's expression, she smiled lightly in her mind.

[1] Yeah don't question the Chinese rules. Back

Chapter 1194: Not Kneeling

The righteous path's immortals had just been sitting for a while, when lone and demonic immortals also appeared.

A huge grey cloud was flying over, upon which Domination Immortal Chu Du proudly stood at the front, behind him were two battle formations. On one side were Hao Zhen, Chou Lao Wu, Li Si Chun, Immortal Wang and others. On the other side were Bai Zu Ren, Bai Zu Ling as well as some familiar faces of Hei tribe, among which the four top supreme elders were also there.

The righteous path immortals' gazes went past the spacious entrance.

Their glances swept through the enemy group of immortals, before they fixed their gazes on Chu Du.

Several breaths later, a Gu Immortal laughed: "Our righteous path shall win this battle, no doubt. What Chu Sect and Bai Zu tribe, such a line-up dares to provoke our Huang Jin tribes?"

"Haha, that makes sense."

"The way I see it, we only need to be slightly on guard against Chu Du."

The immortals talked happily, the atmosphere in the hall becoming relaxed.

In contrast, Hao Zhen, Chou Lao Wu, Bai Zu Ren and others looked gloomy and worried.

One would just have to look at the situation and they would know it.

The righteous path had brought out three Immortal Gu Houses.

Loud Thunder Hall was to the right, Golden Dawn Hall was at the center, and Divine Light Hall was to the left.

In contrast, Chu Du's side only had a huge empty grey cloud below them. The stronger and weaker side was clear at a glance.

The righteous path immortals were resting at ease with wines and delicacies inside the hall. But Chu Du's side was standing amidst the wind, only able to watch.

The righteous path immortals talked and laughed, their morale was high. In contrast, Chu Du's side was silent.

Only Chu Du had a relaxed expression.

He had both brains and brawn, he was extremely shrewd, and had already anticipated such a scene before this trip. Right now, he was not anxious, he looked at a Gu Immortal beside him.

This immortal was tall and thin, folding his arms across his chest, he had white brows and white hair, and had an extremely cold and aloof expression.

Chu Du transmitted his voice to him: "Brother Xue, you have been in seclusion for a long time, tempering your abilities, and possess astonishing attainments, but you don't have reputation. Right now is the time to make your name known, I want to hand over the first battle to you. After this battle, I believe your name will not only be spread to the world, it will likely go down in history."

The Gu Immortal surnamed Xue heard this, and bright light shone in his eyes immediately.

"Last time, Brother Chu invited me to take action, but I was refining Gu and not able to come out. This time, I must make the world know of my, Xue Wu Hen's, name!"

The Gu Immortal named Xue transmitted his reply to Chu Du, and then flew to the sky before hovering between the two sides.

He still had his arms folded across his chest as he remained silent.

Inside Golden Dawn Hall, the immortals pointed at Xue Wu Hen and jokingly spoke: "They sent some nameless junior to his death."

Nian Er Ping Zhi was just about to stand up and take the fight, but was stopped by Nian Er Yi Fang: "Be patient, the enemy only has rank six cultivation and has no reputation. Killing him won't be enough to awe these immortals. No need to take this fight."

"Ah?" Nian Er Ping Zhi thought for a moment and realized it was true, and did not get up.

"Who wants to take the first battle?" From the main seat, Gong Wan Ting asked the group of immortals.

A young Gu Immortal stood up soon after: "I, Ye Lui Xiao Jin, am willing to take the fight!"

Gong Wan Ting hesitated for a moment.

She was inwardly thinking: "Domination Immortal Chu Du is an extraordinary person, he actually sent a nameless character for the first battle, they are definitely not someone ordinary. If our side gets careless and we lose the first battle, it won't be good."

Ye Lui Xiao Jin was also a young junior, and came to the blood battle competition under the company of his seniors. He was also like the enemy, he was still unknown and had not made a name for himself.

At this time, Ye Lui tribe's Gu Immortal Ye Lui Hui Hong smiled: "This junior might only be rank six, but he is talented in fighting and often pulls brilliant moves in battle. Even my tribe's first supreme elder has praised him repeatedly."

Gong Wan Ting heard Ye Lui Hui Hong, it was not good to contradict and disregard him publicly, so she agreed: "Then we shall see Ye Lui tribe's valiance."

"I heed the command!" This young Gu Immortal turned around and walked out.

When he passed by Nian Er tribe, he gave a deep glance at Nian Er Ping Zhi with his golden eyes.

"You!" Nian Er Ping Zhi was provoked, and almost jumped up.

But Ye Lui Xiao Jin had already walked out the entrance.

Nian Er Ping Zhi had made his name in the battle at Iron Eagle blessed land, but many young righteous path Gu Immortals were not willing to feel defeated, Ye Lui Xiao Jin was one of them.

This time, he also wanted to spread and establish his name through the blood battle martial competition!

The blood battle martial competition's first battle was about to unfold under both sides' gazes.

At the same time, far away at Southern Border.

"I have told you all the crucial information regarding Bai Xiang grotto-heaven. After a bloodline descendant of Bai Xiang becomes a Gu Immortal, this white form immortal snake can guide them to Bai Xiang grotto-heaven. But Bai Xiang grotto-heaven is filled with danger. Because Bai Xiang of the Heaven Surveying Five Xiangs is a demonic path Gu Immortal, you need to be very careful when doing this. According to the information my Shadow Sect has gathered, Bai Xiang was a man of his word, and hated people who went against his wish, and was extremely tyrannical in the way he did things. Only Gu Immortals whose battle strength met his expectations could talk and associate with him. You cannot stubbornly charge ahead in this trip, you need to remember when to yield."

Ying Wu Xie carefully instructed Bai Ning Bing.

Shadow Sect had already looked into the bet between the Five Xiangs for a long time, and wanted to meddle in it.

But inopportune time and coincidences made this plan progress very slowly. Naturally, the main reason was because Shadow Sect's full efforts were in refining sovereign immortal fetus Gu.

Shadow Sect recruited Bai Ning Bing because they wanted to hit two birds with one stone. On one hand, they wanted to exploit her identity as a fate-escapee, on the other hand, they were preparing to step into the bet.

Bai Ning Bing snorted: "I know what to do."

Ying Wu Xie was unfazed, still smiling: "Alright, go then."

Bai Ning Bing quietly took out white form immortal snake.

The white form immortal snake was slender and long, its whole body was covered in snow white scales and it had a graceful physique. Its eyes were like jade, and on the two sides of its head were a pair of long whiskers, floating like celestial ribbons.

It was a rank five mortal Gu and was very attached to Bai Ning Bing, which was likely because it was attracted by her Northern Dark Ice Soul physique.

Bai Ning Bing began to activate her phantom aperture.

The phantom aperture was illusory, but after it was activated, it turned from phantom to real.

Shadow Sect had stolen this method from Heavenly Court and had studied it until fifty to sixty percent completion, as such, it had many flaws.

Because of this, Bai Ning Bing could temporarily possess Gu Immortal strength without undergoing tribulation. So she was only a false immortal.

After leaving Shadow Sect for a period of time, she had not been able to maintain her phantom aperture, causing it to lose many of its effects and have limited periods of use.

Ordinarily, Bai Ning Bing would be in her mortal body, turning into a woman. After her phantom aperture was activated, she would turn into a temporary false immortal, the effect of the mortal Gu would be suppressed at this time and her body would return to that of a man's.

Sometimes a man, sometimes a woman, Bai Ning Bing him(her)self felt awkward.

However, among the immortals present, no one joked about it.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was kindhearted, Hei Lou Lan was fierce and ambitious, and did not care about these details, Shi Nu was actually rather nervous, after all, Bai Ning Bing's success or failure would be of huge influence to Shadow Sect's following actions.

Bai Ning Bing began to release his Gu Immortal aura, the white form immortal snake sensed this, its whole body jolted before it gave a long hiss towards the sky.

Its hissing was completely different from the sharp hiss of normal snake species, carrying a resounding and mighty aura.

Then, the white form immortal snake flew under Bai Ning Bing's feet of its own accord, carrying him and flying towards the sky.

Hei Lou Lan, Ying Wu Xie and the rest stood at their spots, looking at this sight.

They could not go as they did not have Bai Xiang's bloodline, and would only make things worse if they went. Everything now depended on Bai Ning Bing.

Fortunately, to raise Bai Ning Bing's success rate, Ying Wu Xie and the rest of the group had gone to Jade Pot Mountain and gave ice soul Immortal Gu to Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing had his first truly owned Immortal Gu.

He looked down while standing on the white form immortal snake's back.

However, when he saw the mountain ranges and the heavy fog, he suddenly recalled a scene back in Bai tribe.

That was his first encounter with the white form immortal snake...

The spirit spring was raging like boiling water.

All of a sudden, the spring water rose up like a tidal wave.

After it reached a certain height, the spirit spring scattered and splashed in all directions. The white form immortal snake flew out.

"I pay respects to Great Immortal!" Bai clan leader emotionally knelt on the ground, and at the same time anxiously urged, "Bai Ning Bing, why are you not kneeling down?"

"I will never kneel before a Gu!" Bai Ning Bing coldly snorted, his body standing upright and tall.

Although the white form immortal snake Gu released an ethereal cold grandeur with heavy killing intent concealed within, Bai Ning Bing was not the least bit afraid. His two blue eyes directly stared at its snake eyes...

"According to the clan's secret records, once a Gu Master obtains approval, the white form immortal snake Gu would fly with the inheritor and open a secret place in the sky."

"So, this so-called secret was Bai Xiang's grotto-heaven. And the condition to receive approval was to become a Gu Immortal."

The question from a long time ago finally cleared up at this time.

"Unknowingly, I have already reached this stage." Bai Ning Bing took a deep breath in, his blue eyes gazing high: "Success or failure does not matter, hehehe, I only hope Bai Xiang grotto-heaven won't be too boring, this trip should be splendid!"

Lang Ya blessed land, inside a secret room in a cloud city.

Fang Yuan lightly let out a breath of air.

In his hand was a dream path mortal Gu that had just been refined, and was still giving off warmth.

His cultivation was still at rank six second heavenly tribulation level and had stopped here for the moment, unable to be raised. Because he had almost annexed all the blessed lands in his memories. There were still some remaining, but he could not annex those blessed lands because of his attainment level.

Ever since he realized that dream realms provided incomparable help to this style of cultivation, he had immersed himself in refining dream path mortal Gu these last days.

These mortal Gu, when paired up with unravel mystery Immortal Gu, could form the immortal killer move unravel dream.

With this killer move, Fang Yuan could easily solve dream realms and unravel them, raising his attainment in many paths.

With unravel dream raising his attainment level, Fang Yuan could annex even more immortal apertures.

After annexing blessed lands, his cultivation level would soar up, causing his battle strength to surge.

After his battle strength surged, killing would become easier and he could obtain even more blessed lands.

It would then form a feedback loop of constant benefits.

Do not bother mentioning bullshit like whether killing is against morality or how it would influence one's reputation, demonic path Gu Immortals were direct and straightforward in this aspect!

Fang Yuan had never thought of himself as a good person.

"The blood battle martial competition should have begun... I should participate a few times, kill a few Gu Immortals and seize their immortal apertures, taking the final step to becoming a rank seven Gu Immortal."

"Although Eastern Sea has City Well, and there are many blessed lands in the well, it is too far away. Moreover, I have already been there once, heaven's will already knows of it."

"It is better to continue refining dream path mortal Gu while killing in the blood battle martial competition, it won't be too late to go after that."

With this idea, Fang Yuan once again entered a dream realm.

Verdant green trees grew in the rugged mountain path.

A merchant caravan was traversing on the mountain path with difficulty.

Fang Yuan was one of the members in the caravan.

In the end, he did not yield and wanted to prove that with his ability, he could defeat his genius A grade aptitude little brother.

He also needed such evidence for himself.

But Gu Yue clan leader did not give him this opportunity.

He personally schemed against Fang Yuan and used some sneaky moves, causing Fang Yuan to suffer an overwhelming defeat.

Finally, he became someone who overestimated his ability, being cast aside and troubled by everyone.

"C grade aptitude does not have any future."

"Even if you won against Gu Yue Fang Zheng, so what? He has A grade aptitude, the future of the whole tribe belongs to him. No, he is our tribe's future!"

"As an elder brother, you truly don't have even a little tolerance, you are actually making things difficult for your little brother."

Winner takes all.

Victory or defeat was decided, right or wrong was thus overturned, black and white was blurred.

Fang Yuan was on the verge of being exiled from the tribe, he could only join a merchant caravan, laboriously working while continuing his cultivation.

"Stop, stop, I am tired. This carriage is too bumpy, let's rest for a while." A young man's voice came from a carriage.

"But young master, we are still a long way from the next village. We have already rested three times on the way, if we rest again, we won't be able to walk out of this mountain before the sky gets dark." A steward of the merchant caravan stood outside the carriage, and spoke with a bowed waist.

Ping.

There was a sharp sound as a lightning whip instantly landed on the steward's body, sending him flying.

"What did you say?"

"This caravan is my clan's, I have complete management rights over it. You lowly servant, you dare to lecture me?"

The carriage's curtain was raised up, and a malevolent looking young Gu Master walked out from within.

"This servant deserves to die, this servant deserves to die." The steward kowtowed continuously.

The whole caravan stopped.

From ahead came questions: "What is happening behind?"

Questions came from behind as well: "What is going on ahead?"

Feeling countless gazes at him, the young Gu Master frowned, as he shouted: "What are you looking at, you bunch of lazy slaves, if you look at me again, I will dig out your eyes!"

Fang Yuan quickly lowered his head.

"You, yes you!" The young Gu Master suddenly pointed at Fang Yuan, "Come over, kneel down, be a stool for this master. This is your honor, I want to rest outside for a while."

Fang Yuan raised his head, staring at the young Gu Master with pursed lips.

"I won't kneel!"

"What?" The young Gu Master could not believe it, almost thinking he had misheard it.

"What did you say just now? You won't kneel?!" His finger that was pointing at Fang Yuan, was slightly shaking.

His expression was exaggerated, as if he had heard a joke.

"Haha, you won't kneel?! You are an ant-like slave, you still won't kneel?!"

He then heard Fang Yuan's words again——

"No, I won't kneel!"

Chapter 1195: Young

"Junior, take this move!" Liu Hui shouted, a powerful aura erupting from his whole body.

He raised his arms above his head, a grand radiance rose up from his body and rapidly condensed into a crescent moon in the air.

The crescent moon was thin and long, it was pale white but covered in a grey halo.

"Good! Elder Liu Hui finally got the chance to use his move, grey rock moon!"

"This move is a well known method of Liu Hui."

"That's right. Those that are struck by this move will start solidifying before finally turning into stone. Even their immortal aperture will also be contaminated, turning rocky, it is a truly troublesome move!"

Inside Golden Dawn Hall, righteous path Gu Immortals were discussing with smiles on their faces.

On the demonic path's side, Xue Wu Hen was only illuminated by the grey moonlight for several breaths of time before his expression changed greatly.

He immediately felt the power of this move, and did not dare to be rash as he quickly used an immortal killer move.

Strong cold aura coiled around his whole body, ice and frost attaching to his body. The grey moonlight turned the ice and frost to stone, but the ice and frost regenerated themselves, the grey moonlight was unable to penetrate through them and reach Xue Wu Hen's body.

"What? He actually used an offensive killer move on his own body?"

"Amazing! Xue Wu Hen handled such a complicated thing with ease, he is quite clever! For the moment, he has blocked Old Liu Hui's signature trump card!"

"Go, beat him!"

The immortals in Chu Du's side cheered and applauded loudly.

By contrast, the relaxed mood inside Golden Dawn Hall had now completely dissipated, and a bad feeling rose up in everyone's hearts.

"We are not going to lose to Xue Wu Hen again, right?"

"Even Elder Liu Hui cannot hold him down?"

"Xue Wu Hen is an unknown character, while Elder Liu Hui is a renowned rank six expert!"

As the immortals talked, Xue Wu Hen wore the heavy layer of stone and frost, and charged towards Elder Liu Hui.

"Old geezer, you are so old, what are you doing not resting at home? Just die!"

Xue Wu Hen pushed both his hands forward, instantly a wave of snow and frost rose up in the air.

The righteous path Gu Immortal, Elder Liu Hui, had to maintain the grey crescent moon in the sky, his hands were raised as if he was supporting the sky, he could not move and was directly submerged by this wave of snow.

Xue Wu Hen won!

Liu Hui died!

Everyone was surprised, they had not expected such an outcome.

"Before this battle, Xue Wu Hen had already won two consecutive battles, he was injured and not in his best condition."

"In the previous two battles, he battled against righteous path juniors, and could not kill the opponent. But now in this third battle, he killed Liu Hui."

"The grand Liu Hui actually died at the hands of a nameless demonic path minor character!"

"Heavens, this is unbelievable."

"This person might only have rank six cultivation, but he truly has rank seven battle strength. Where did this guy come from?"

"I can't help but think of Old Ancestor Xue Hu, this Xue Wu Hen is similarly of ice and snow path, he truly resembles Old Ancestor Xue Hu when he was young."

"He is still far from being qualified to compare to Old Ancestor Xue Hu. But three victories in three consecutive battles, his name will spread throughout the whole Gu Immortal world."

Whether it be the righteous path or Chu Du's side, they were both discussing Xue Wu Hen.

"Xiao Jin, don't put your loss to heart. This is not your fault, but the opponent being too strong. He actually killed Liu Hui! Sigh." Ye Lui Hui Hong consoled the young man beside him.

Ye Lui Xiao Jin felt his right arm.

His right arm was currently still in a frozen state, his whole arm had already turned black and blue from the cold, the intense chill was even affecting his bones and blood.

Ye Lui Xiao Jin felt such pain that after his defeat, he returned to the hall and had his head lowered the whole time.

As for Ye Lui Hui Hong's words, he did not seem to have heard them.

Ye Lui Hui Hong saw this, and sighed inwardly: "You are still young. But this setback will be beneficial to you. This shame will make you try harder, who can say what will happen in the future? Maybe your future achievements will be above them. The main thing is to not lose the confidence in yourself."

As he thought of this, Ye Lui Hui Hong gazed at Xue Wu Hen, who was standing alone in the air, and then at Nian Er Ping Zhi who was unable to stay still.

"Can I go fight now?" Nian Er Ping Zhi impatiently transmitted his voice to his senior, Nian Er Yi Fang.

However, Nian Er Yi Fang shook his head: "This person has won three battles, there are many injuries on him and his state is not at its peak. If you kill him, it would be nothing extraordinary, but if you can't kill him, it would instead weaken your prestige. Moreover, the other side is not foolish, why would they let Xue Wu Hen continue fighting?"

Sure enough, the next moment, Chu Du spoke, withdrawing Xue Wu Hen from the battle.

Nian Er Ping Zhi snorted: "Even if he does not battle, I will go up. He won three battles, I will win at least six battles!"

Nian Er Ping Zhi rose up and bowed to Gong Wan Ting: "I request to go to battle!"

Gong Wan Ting's frown relaxed a little.

The righteous path, which should have been victorious, was instead defeated thrice by a nameless character from Chu Du's side.

This was not only a heavy blow to the righteous path Gu Immortals, it harmed their reputation and was also damaging to Gong Wan Ting's prestige.

Gong Wan Ting knew Nian Er Ping Zhi was Nian Er tribe's current generation Sword Child, she naturally had no reason to not permit him.

Nian Er Ping Zhi took the stage, and shouted: "Who wants to die?"

The rising morale of Chu Du's side immediately stifled.

"Careful, don't be fooled by this kid's rank six cultivation, he can kill rank sevens."

"He made outstanding battle achievements in the battle of Iron Eagle blessed land, he is also extremely savage, killing multiple Gu Immortals."

"Even Old Monster Corpse Poison could not do anything about him."

"He is the current inheritor of Sword Saint Nian Er's true inheritance, he naturally is not ordinary."

Chu Du's side was silent.

Facing Nian Er Ping Zhi's challenge, there was actually no one who dared to accept for a period of time.

"Youngsters at the moment, each of them truly are fiercer than the other." Chu Du stroked his forehead.

"Big brother Chu, let me go handle him." Xue Wu Hen requested.

How could Chu Du permit it.

He already saw Xue Wu Hen's weak state, not only were there injuries on his body, many areas of his immortal aperture had even turned into rocks, causing losses to many resources, as a result of Elder Liu Hui's immortal killer move.

"Relax, I have already made arrangements to deal with Ping Zhi." Chu Du smiled, assuring Xue Wu Hen.

"Granny Yin, I will hand this battle to you." Chu Du spoke to a black robed Gu Immortal behind him.

This Gu Immortal with a hunched back was holding a walking stick, and had been silent the whole time.

Hearing Chu Du's words, terrifyingly bony hands stretched out of the wide sleeves and lifted up the hood, revealing an old, crooked face.

"Hehehe, let this old woman love you tenderly." Granny Yin flew to the battle, and stared at the young Nian Er Ping Zhi with her turbid yellow eyes, which flickered with dangerous light.

"What, she is the rank seven demonic Gu Immortal Granny Yin."

"Chu Du is shameless, our side's Nian Er Ping Zhi is only a rank six Gu Immortal, they are actually sending a higher rank expert famous in Northern Plains!"

"This won't do, call back Nian Er Ping Zhi." Nian Er Yi Fang was also very anxious.

Nian Er Ping Zhi was a future star of Nian Er tribe who was heavily nurtured, and Nian Er Yi Fang was in charge of his safety in this trip. If he died here, Nian Er Yi Fang would have greatly neglected his duty.

However, Nian Er Ping Zhi's fighting intent burned even stronger when facing a strong opponent.

He howled towards the sky, and disregarding the crazed voice transmission of Nian Er Yi Fang, he turned into an incomparably sharp sword light that charged towards Granny Yin!

Snowy Mountain, first peak.

"Now that I mention it, you need to be thankful to me. Haven't you discovered, your cultivation has risen and is going to reach rank five." Lady Wan Shou said to Ma Hong Yun, while holding a ball of lightning.

Ma Hong Yun shouted madly and hysterically: "You insane lunatic! You still want to shock me, you have tormented me so many times, you still want to continue! I don't want this cultivation, please let me go."

Lady Wan Shou sneered: "Impossible."

She then sent out the ball of lightning.

Crack crack crack!

Ma Hong Yun's whole body shook, his eyes rolled over, his mouth occasionally opened wide, occasionally pursed up and occasionally turned into 'O' shape, but all the time, he was shouting.

"Ahhh ooooohhhh arrghhhh..."

He screamed until the lightning completely dissipated.

"Failed again, this guy!" Lady Wan Shou's face looked extremely gloomy, she fiercely slapped Ma Hong Yun's cheek.

Ma Hong Yun instantly fainted from the slap.

Central Continent, Spirit Affinity House.

Heavy rain poured down, causing the sky to darken.

Zhao Lian Yun was drenched, her vision was blurry and intense dizziness was threatening to make her unconscious.

But she firmly held on, using every bit of strength in her body.

Although she was an otherworldly demon with memories of a previous world, she did not have much understanding of the upper levels of the Gu world, especially of the mindsets of Gu Immortals, whom she had rarely been able to associate with.

As far as she was concerned, this was the only way to save Ma Hong Yun.

"This otherworldly demon is indeed somewhat foolish." Li Jun Ying had been observing secretly.

Xu Hao shook his head: "I also had not expected her to be so persistent. It has already been over ten days now."

Li Jun Ying turned back and looked at her husband: "Have you thought about it, Feng Jin Huang can use this to make a countering scheme against us, requesting Zhao Lian Yun to give up on contending for the position of fairy, and then she will help save her lover?"

Xu Hao smiled: "How could that be? According to Feng Jin Huang's nature, she absolutely would not be able to do such a thing. These two are still young."

Inside a dream, Southern Border.

"Owww, it hurts, it hurts!" Fang Yuan screamed in pain.

"Kid, you know pain now? If you had knelt, you would not have had to experience this pain." A middle-aged man with a big beard was holding a Gu worm in his hand, healing Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan raised his head and clenched his right fist: "Uncle, what are you saying? A man only kneels to their parents, heaven and earth, how can we kneel at someone's order?! Even if I die, I won't kneel!"

"Not cherishing life, it seems healing you was completely in vain. I should not have done it." Big Beard suddenly became moody.

"Hmph, I didn't ask you to heal me!" Fang Yuan endured the pain and stood up, walking out of this tent without looking back.

However, he fell down to the ground after taking just a few steps. The intense pain sent him unconscious.

When he woke up again, he found he was still inside Big Beard's tent.

"Oh you, you are still too young." Big Beard took a gulp of wine: "I have healed half of your injuries, and have left the other half as a lesson."

Fang Yuan grumbled, weakly retorting: "Uncle, thank you. But I have told you, this is not about being young, this is a matter of principles!"

Chapter 1196: Sword Heart Clarity

Above Blood Plain.

Nian Er Ping Zhi and Granny Yin's battle had attracted everyone's attention.

Granny Yin was a veteran demonic path Gu Immortal, she cultivated soul path and possessed bewitching soul Immortal Gu, and her reputation had already been established long ago in Northern Plains.

She moved like a ghost, gloomy winds surged and vengeful souls moved around her, sending chills down people's hearts.

And Nian Er Ping Zhi was a shining member of the righteous path's younger generation, the current Sword Child of Nian Er tribe, his movement was quick and his sword moved like lightning.

Both sides had exchanged dozens of moves, at first they probed each other with mortal killer moves, then they used Immortal Gu, then immortal killer moves, and now the battle was at a very heated stage.

On the field, dark souls had covered most of the sky.

And the white sword light representing Nian Er Ping Zhi was already surrounded, despite it charging everywhere and the dark souls moving away, the overall flow of the battle was dictated by Granny Yin.

"Granny Yin is indeed a demonic path expert, the way she fights is steady and full of experience." Immortal Wang praised.

Chu Du, however, frowned, silent.

He was inwardly thinking: "Granny Yin is a rank seven Gu Immortal, but she was not able to immediately kill Nian Er Ping Zhi. Even though the situation looks more inclined towards her, Nian Er Ping Zhi's sword light is still rampaging around without the slightest of hesitation. He still is thinking of winning!"

Inside Golden Dawn Hall, seeing his tribe's shining hope, a sword path genius, falling into disadvantage, Nian Er Yi Fang was becoming nervous, staring at the battle without blinking.

If the situation looked bad, he would immediately make a move and save Nian Er Ping Zhi.

No matter the rules or reputation, as far as Nian Er tribe was concerned, Nian Er Ping Zhi being alive was most important!

"Hehehehe... such a tender body, you have nowhere to dodge now, accept your death!" A change suddenly happened at this instance.

Countless vengeful ghosts suddenly covered all directions, as they surrounded the sword light that Nian Er Ping Zhi had transformed into.

Then, Granny Yin revealed her true body from amidst the countless dark souls, stretching out her withered finger and pointing at Nian Er Ping Zhi from afar.

Immortal killer move — Bewitching Soul Art!

Nian Er Ping Zhi's eyes immediately lost their light, the freely moving nimble sword light completely dissipated and turned into his true body.

He was floating in the air like his mind had halted, not having the slightest bit of reaction to the charging Granny Yin.

"Hehehe!" Granny Yin laughed in satisfaction. She opened her mouth wide, revealing her sparse yellow teeth.

Her hand suddenly enlarged by many times, dark wind coiled around her five fingers, her nails as sharp as needles. The fan-like hand descended on Nian Er Ping Zhi's head.

If this attack were to land true, Nian Er Ping Zhi's skull would no doubt be crushed under his defenseless state.

"Stop it!" Nian Er Yi Fang shouted as he rushed out of Golden Dawn Hall.

However, Chu Du had already made prior arrangements.

He saw that Granny Yin was firmly grasping the battle situation, and had already considered if she were to make a killing strike towards Nian Er Ping Zhi, she would surely be obstructed by the righteous path Gu Immortals.

Therefore, he had already arranged his forces to lie in wait.

Sure enough, when Nian Er Yi Fang rushed out, Hao Zhen moved out shortly after.

"Shameless fellow, you are interfering in a one on one battle?" Hao Zhen shot out a bolt of lightning right at Nian Er Yi Fang's face.

Nian Er Yi Fang slightly shook, and emerald wooden armor appeared, covering his whole body firmly.

This wooden armor was Nian Er Yi Fang's immortal killer move, and it had extremely powerful defense. Regardless of how sharp Hao Zhen's lightning was, it could not even make a dent on the wooden armor, instead the wooden armor seemed to be rejuvenated as it produced fresh yellow and green leaves, like it had received many benefits.

Chu Du immediately gave out a light gasp.

He was surprised.

What made Chu Du surprised was not Nian Er Yi Fang's wooden armor, as his wooden armor was already famous in Northern Plains and was his self-created immortal killer move — Sick Tree Spring Armor.

Instead, it was that Nian Er Yi Fang had rushed out madly to save Nian Er Ping Zhi.

However, by using this move and blocking off Hao Zhen's lightning, he had missed the best opportunity to save Nian Er Ping Zhi.

Chu Du considered what he would do in Nian Er Yi Fang's position, his tribe's genius, a star of the younger generation, was at risk of losing his life, while he himself could choose to either block the lightning or move to protect Nian Er Ping Zhi's life.

But right now, Nian Er Yi Fang had chosen to protect himself. This action meant he did not feel it was urgent to save Nian Er Ping Zhi.

What was going on?

"Oh no!" Chu Du's heart suddenly jumped, and he quickly looked at the battle.

He was just about to warn Granny Yin, but it was already too late.

The sluggish looking Nian Er Ping Zhi suddenly let out extremely sharp, mysterious light from his eyes.

This change immediately froze Granny Yin's ecstatic laughter.

Granny Yin's mind sent out warnings of danger, she wanted to get back to defend herself but it was already late.

An extremely stunning sword light flashed!

Life and death, victory and loss, were determined within this moment of time.

The dark souls were still hovering around, but Granny Yin was already starting to fall down, cut into two by the sword light.

She was gazing at Nian Er Ping Zhi with an incredulous look on her face, unable to think of how he had suddenly gotten free from her signature trump card.

"Bewitching soul art is Granny Yin's proudest method, which she used when she roamed Northern Plains, but it was actually ineffective against Nian Er Ping Zhi?" Chu Du and his group of immortals paled in shock.

"What's going on?" Inside Golden Dawn Hall, the righteous path Gu Immortals were both surprised and joyous.

"This is sword heart clarity, it is an immortal killer move in Sword Saint true inheritance, especially used to restrict wisdom path and other similar methods. Few of the Sword Childs in history could use it." Nian Er Yi Fang laughed heartily, not giving up this chance to increase Nian Er tribe's prestige.

Ye Lui Xiao Jin could not help thinking: "Is he saying Nian Er Ping Zhi is outstanding even when placed among all the Sword Childs in history?"

He was a genius of Ye Lui tribe, but unfortunately had lost to Xue Wu Hen.

On the contrary, Nian Er Ping Zhi had killed the rank seven demonic path expert Granny Yin. Comparing the two, it was clear for everyone who was better and who was worse.

"This Nian Er Yi Fang is truly crafty. He clearly knew Nian Er Ping Zhi's situation was of no concern, but still pretended to rush out in panic to save Nian Er Ping Zhi." Chou Lao Wu mumbled behind Chu Du, feeling indignant.

One had to say Nian Er Yi Fang had acted really well.

Because of his acting, the Gu Immortals of both sides had subconsciously thought Nian Er Ping Zhi was in absolute danger.

Even Granny Yin was deceived.

"No, maybe it was Granny Yin who was too confident in her immortal killer move bewitching soul art." Chu Du assessed internally: "And this Nian Er Ping Zhi is also not just a brutish person, he actually pretended to be struck by the ability, deceiving Granny Yin. The killer move he used to kill Granny Yin is also not simple, it is terrifyingly powerful and also extremely fast, it is virtually impossible to guard against. It should be one sword life, an immortal killer move used by Sword Saint Nian Er in his younger days!"

"Come back quickly." Nian Er Yi Fang was in high spirits, but quickly and anxiously transmitted his voice to Nian Er Ping Zhi.

Nian Er Ping Zhi had killed Granny Yin, but he had also suffered heavy injuries.

He quickly retreated, but before leaving, he naturally brought the two halves of Granny Yin's body with him.

One half of the corpse had Granny Yin's immortal aperture.

This was Nian Er Ping Zhi's spoils of battle.

Chu Sect did not stop him, this was one of the rules stated in the competition agreement.

It was like when Xue Wu Hen who had stored away Gu Immortal Liu Hui's corpse.

However, Xue Wu Hen might have won three battles, but he only killed the rank six Gu Immortal Liu Hui. While Nian Er Ping Zhi might have only won one battle, but he took a rank seven demonic path Gu Immortal, Granny Yin's, life.

Thus, the righteous path's side was slightly leading.

Chu Du was feeling the pressure.

The slight dominance brought by Xue Wu Hen had now been balanced out by Nian Er Ping Zhi.

"Who should I send in this next battle?"

Chu Du was hesitating.

Soon, the result of this battle reached Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was still in Lang Ya blessed land, cultivating.

"Nian Er Ping Zhi killed Granny Yin?" Fang Yuan was only slightly surprised before he accepted this fact.

There were many genius experts who were able to achieve the feat of winning against rank seven with rank six cultivation.

But using rank seven cultivation to fight rank eight was extremely rare.

Nian Er Ping Zhi... Fang Yuan did not have any impression of this person in his memories. After all, in his first life, Fang Yuan was still a mortal around this time, and was not at all aware of the events in the Gu Immortal world or Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world.

What made Fang Yuan more interested was instead Xue Wu Hen.

Precisely speaking, it was the loot in Xue Wu Hen's possession — that Gu Immortal, Liu Hui's, blessed land.

"Gu Immortal Liu Hui is an earth path Gu Immortal who has gone through two heavenly tribulations, his blessed land is suitable for me to annex. With this, my cultivation can also rise and reach rank seven."

As he thought of this, Fang Yuan immediately wrote a reply.

He took the initiative to request for Chu Du's help in expressing his intention of buying the immortal aperture from Xue Wu Hen.

As for the invitation of Chu Du asking Fang Yuan to help, Fang Yuan used the reason of being in secluded cultivation to delay in a roundabout way.

"I need to raise my cultivation to rank seven first, it won't be too late to join this blood battle martial competition then."

Fang Yuan slightly shook his head, throwing the news of this blood battle martial competition to the back of his mind.

The Chu Sect alliance agreement he had was rather lenient. Even if Chu Sect was annihilated, Fang Yuan could choose not to show up and it would not be a problem.

Fang Yuan prioritized raising his cultivation, all the other things were secondary.

Chu Du received Fang Yuan's reply.

Fang Yuan did not come, which made Chu Du frown.

"Sigh, if Elder Liu Guan Yi could come, I would not be in this difficult spot." Chu Du heaved a sigh.

Xue Wu Hen was standing beside Chu Du, and curiously asked when he heard Chu Du: "Hearing Brother Chu's tone, it seems you hold this Elder Liu Guan Yi in high esteem."

Chu Du laughed: "He had mentioned you in his letter, hoping you can sell Liu Hui's immortal aperture to him."

Xue Wu Hen shook his head: "I could not get Liu Hui's Immortal Gu, but the resources inside the immortal aperture are my battle spoils. I don't know their value, so how can I sell them?"

His intention of refusal was extremely obvious.

Chapter 1197: Sword Dragon Transformation

Chu Du smiled.

Deep down, Xue Wu Hen was someone he wanted to recruit to his Chu Sect, so he had been giving him a lot of consideration.

However, Fang Yuan was his collaboration partner, later on he would have to get Reckless Savage's true meaning from Fang Yuan to raise his strength path attainment.

Chu Du was well aware of which was more important.

"In his letter, Liu Guan Yi entrusted me to accomplish this matter." Chu Du thought to himself, while transmitting his voice to Xue Wu Hen, "Brother Xue, collaborating with Elder Liu Guan Yi is probably your best choice to get the resources in Liu Hui's aperture."

"How so?" Xue Wu Hen asked doubtfully.

"Because Elder Liu has an upper extreme heavenly eagle. This eagle can go into blessed lands, it is better for you take away the resources in the immortal aperture and give the immortal aperture to Elder Liu, making him add on some resources as the price. Isn't this a win-win situation?" Chu Du replied.

Xue Wu Hen's eyes brightened.

"Upper extreme heavenly eagle?! I have also heard of this immemorial beast, I did not expect Elder Liu Guan Yi to have such a rare bird."

Pausing for a while, Xue Wu Hen continued his voice transmission: "I am willing to transact with Elder Liu!"

Right as Fang Yuan's plan was about to succeed, a change happened.

A Gu Immortal walked out of Golden Dawn Hall.

"It is a Liu tribe Gu Immortal, Liu Zhuan Shen!" Immortal Wang immediately recognized this person.

"He is coming down to fight?" Chu Du's side cast their gazes.

However, Liu Zhuan Shen did not go to the stage, instead stopped at the entrance of Golden Dawn Hall: "Lord Domination Immortal, my side is willing to use Granny Yin's corpse to exchange for Elder Liu Hui's corpse and soul."

Liu Hui's corpse had ended up in enemy hands, Liu tribe's Gu Immortals naturally were not willing to see such a scene.

The corpse was still alright, the main thing was the soul.

Liu Hui's soul had not been destroyed.

Therefore, Liu tribe's Gu Immortals wanted to get back Liu Hui's corpse and soul no matter what.

However, Liu Zhuan Shen did not have enough bargaining chips on him, and was also afraid that the other side would be very greedy and recklessly extort them, if so, then the situation would be quite awkward and they would be put on the spot.

So, Liu Zhuan Shen and the other Liu tribe Gu Immortals felt anxious, but did not make a rash move.

After Nian Er Ping Zhi killed Granny Yin, Liu tribe's Gu Immortals saw hope in this matter.

Liu Zhuan Shen had thus communicated with Nian Er tribe, and after giving up many benefits, had exchanged for Granny Yin's corpse.

An immortal aperture was inside Granny Yin's corpse, and for the moment, was unharmed.

It was only that Granny Yin's soul was already destroyed by Nian Er Ping Zhi. Nian Er Ping Zhi had a tough victory and simply was unable to hold back.

Granny Yin's soul was completely destroyed by the immortal killer move one sword life.

However, as far as Liu tribe's Gu Immortals were concerned, Granny Yin was rank seven while Liu Hui was only rank six, this transaction was very likely to be accomplished.

Chu Du's side heard these words, and there was immediately a stir among them, as they began to whisper to each other.

Chu Du inwardly exclaimed: "Amazing, this Liu Zhuan Shen has quite the ability, putting me in such a spot."

Chu Du did not have to turn around to sense the disturbance among the Gu Immortals behind him.

Granny Yin moved alone and had few relations with other Gu Immortals, most of her relationships were even hostile. Granny Yin had come this time only because of Chu Du's prestige and the rewards.

However, Chu Du knew these Gu Immortals behind him hoped the two sides could exchange the corpses.

The reason was that this blood battle martial competition had just begun, in the following battles, there might be Gu Immortals whose bodies and souls would perish in battle.

If that was the case, so be it, since there was no body nor soul.

But if they lost their life and their soul was left behind in the enemy's hands, what could they do?

Under such a situation, they could only rely on their side's Gu Immortals to help retrieve their soul.

"If I agree to Liu Zhuan Shen's request, I can stabilize these Gu Immortals' mindsets and lessen their worries. Otherwise, the morale will probably lower which can seriously impact the following battles."

Chu Du understood the importance of this matter.

Most of the members of Chu Sect and Bai Zu tribe were lone immortals or demonic cultivators. They were not well united to begin with, they only took this risk because of the reputations of Domination Immortal and Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, as well as the rewards.

If Chu Du were to refuse now, these Gu Immortals would probably be self-conscious and be on guard against each other.

Chu Du hesitated for a while, apologizing to Liu Guan Yi inwardly, before he spoke, agreeing to this transaction.

Liu Zhuan Shen was joyous, both sides exchanged the corpses.

Xue Wu Hen had lost a rank six earth path immortal aperture and Gu Immortal soul, but obtained a rank seven soul path immortal aperture. While Chu Du had also secretly made it up to him with some snow path killer moves.

So, he was quite happy with this result.

Anyway, even if he interrogated Liu Hui's soul and obtained earth path killer moves, they would be useless to him.

After both sides exchanged the corpses, Gong Wan Ting also saw the importance of this matter, and took the initiative to negotiate with Chu Du.

Because of this event, both sides had thus conveniently added a rule in the blood battle martial competition regarding the exchange of corpses and soul captives.

After a delay of half a day, both sides engaged in another battle.

Chu Du's side sent a Bai Zu tribe Gu Immortal, it was the previous Hei tribe supreme elder. The actual Bai Zu bloodline members were still being taken care of.

Before this trip, Chu Du had received Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's instructions to protect as many Bai Zu tribe descendants as possible.

Because of this setback, Fang Yuan's plan went down the drain.

Not long later, he received Chu Du's letter, the letter explained the reason in detail. Chu Du's tone was polite and even apologized to Fang Yuan for not fulfilling what he was entrusted with.

Fang Yuan understood Chu Du's difficulty.

He was standing in a Gu refinement secret room, mumbling to himself: "I don't have a use for a soul path immortal aperture. It seems I still have to make a move personally and seize the immortal aperture that I want, and advance to rank seven."

However, there were many forces in the blood battle martial competition, although Fang Yuan had familiar face, he still needed some new offensive methods.

After all, he had proclaimed to the outside world that he was a transformation path Gu Immortal.

"I have flying bear strength Immortal Gu, but the power of the flying bear transformation is quite poor."

"Fortunately, I have been considering this beforehand and have many possible solutions now!"

Fang Yuan's gaze landed on the dragon corpse in front of him.

This was a desolate beast.

Its whole body was shining with silvery light, its horn was sharp as a spear, its eyes were pure white, its fangs and claws looked fearsome, many layers of scales covered its body emitting metallic luster.

This was a silver colored dragon.

The whole body was twenty feet long, its body was slender and its shape was fluid and graceful. It was like a piece of art, but it emitted a dense cold feeling of sharpness, as if anyone who got close to it would be pierced through by the surrounding air.

This was not a false feeling, but it was because this silver dragon with two claws was originally a sword path desolate beast—— Sword Dragon.

Now, it was already dead, its sword path dao marks were gradually dissipating, merging into the surrounding environment.

This was the transformation Fang Yuan had prepared to cultivate ——Sword Dragon Transformation!

"The killer move sword dragon transformation needs dragon scale Gu, dragon horn Gu, dragon claw Gu, dragon eyes Gu, and so on. If any one of the Gu worms is an Immortal Gu, then it becomes an immortal killer move."

"But I have change form Immortal Gu, this Gu is one of the core essences of transformation path. Thus, I don't need to refine immortal level dragon scale Gu, dragon horn Gu, dragon claw Gu or dragon eyes Gu, and only need to refine the mortal Gu versions, and use change form Immortal Gu as the core, to form immortal killer move sword dragon transformation."

Transformation path killer moves were extremely simple.

It could even be said to be rudimentary.

This was one of the advantages of cultivating transformation path.

Immortal killer moves of other paths were not easy to deduce, but transformation path was completely different in this aspect.

Adding on that Fang Yuan himself was a wisdom path grandmaster, not only did he successfully deduced the contents of sword dragon transformation, but also improved on many aspects, making the transformation faster and nimbler.

Naturally, Gu Immortal Han Dong had a contribution in this.

He was a transformation path Gu Immortal who specialized in cultivating spirit snake transformation.

A dragon had a similar body shape and battle style. Although Han Dong died and his soul had dissipated, he had left behind a land spirit which retained some of Han Dong's cultivation insights, it was enough for Fang Yuan to take as a reference.

He started activating the Gu refinement formation and began to refine this desolate beast sword dragon.

The desolate beast sword dragon was full of sword path dao marks and in itself was an immortal material which could be refined into Immortal Gu.

However, Fang Yuan's refinement path attainment was not particularly high, and with just this sword dragon, the immortal materials to refine the relevant Immortal Gu were also not sufficient, so Fang Yuan was refining only mortal Gu to support change form Immortal Gu.

The refinement process went rather smoothly.

Fang Yuan himself was a Gu Immortal and was using precious immortal materials to refine some rank five mortal Gu, the success rate was naturally extremely high and could even be said to be quite easy.

Some days later.

Fang Yuan stood still and took in a deep breath, his mind was still. Suddenly, thoughts surged up like a storm, as Gu worms started activating one after the other.

In just a breath of time, Fang Yuan's whole body emitted piercing silvery radiance.

After the silver light dissipated, an elegant and exquisite silver sword dragon that was emitting a feeling of sharpness appeared.

The sword dragon's eyes were white, but they flashed with intelligence.

It was Fang Yuan!

"Immortal killer move sword dragon transformation has already been refined. Next..."

Fang Yuan began to get familiar with his body, brandishing his claws and fangs, or flying in the sky.

His practice drills went quite decently, it was because he had already begun cultivating transformation path. Not only the flying bear transformation, many times, he had used change form Immortal Gu to transform into all kinds of appearances, although they had not reached mastery, he could be said to be familiar with them.

After thoroughly getting familiar with this form, Fang Yuan began to test the might of this immortal killer move.

First was the expenditure of immortal essence.

Very little.

The expenditure of green grape immortal essence to maintain the sword dragon transformation was not high. After all, it only involved rank six change form Immortal Gu.

Next was his battle strength.

Fang Yuan had already arranged immortal materials in front of him.

First was a piece of hundred years profound ice, he swept at it with his claws, Fang Yuan felt like he had sliced into tofu, he easily smashed this profound ice into pieces.

Next, Fang Yuan moved to the subterranean adamantite and clawed at it!

Subterranean adamantite was among the hardest rank six immortal materials, it immediately showed a clear claw marking that reached a few inches deep.

Fang Yuan was immediately aware of the limit of the power of his dragon claws, he did not need to test it on the rank seven immortal material at the side.

Chapter 1198: Dragon Breath

Gu are the essence of heaven and earth, man is the spirit of all living beings.

Human intelligence was the highest among all the living beings. However, the way of heaven was to have balance, humans were highest in intelligence, but their bodies were extremely fragile.

Humans did not have sharp claws, fur, wings, or gills.

The strength of humans might not be the weakest but it was at the bottom tier. They were fundamentally unable to contest with typical desolate beasts.

Human skin was no different from paper compared to desolate beasts.

However, when Fang Yuan transformed into a desolate beast sword dragon, he obtained the qualities of a sword dragon. Although there was still a difference from a true sword dragon, he was already far beyond the limits of humans.

The initial concept when transformation path was created was —

Study all living beings and add the advantages of those beings to one's own body.

Humans did not have sharp claws, so transform human fingers into claws. Humans did not have fur, so transform one's hair into fur.

If one is without wings, then create wings, and fly like the birds in the sky. If one has no gills, transform into a fish, and swim in the depths of the sea.

Naturally, by the current era, the concept of transformation path was not limited to just this.

Using one path to project every path had become transformation path's main principle, imitating the advantages of other paths.

As time passed, there were bound to be improvements.

The wheels of history would keep on turning forward.

Ever since Reckless Savage Demon Venerable created transformation path, this path had not declined and was passed down throughout human history, moreover, new ideas replaced the old, causing it to thrive even now.

Fang Yuan lightly stretched out his dragon body, flying to the rank seven immortal material.

This was a giant dark inkstone, among rank seven immortal materials, it was considered very firm and had the characteristic of being difficult to process.

His dragon claws slashed at it, but were unable to leave any trace.

Fang Yuan had already expected this, thus he did not use only his claws, instead, he turned his body and suddenly whipped his tail!

Ping.

A sharp sound resounded as the dragon tail fiercely whipped at the dark inkstone.

Pain could be felt from the dragon tail, causing Fang Yuan to take a sharp breath of cold air.

While on the dark inkstone's surface, a thin crack appeared.

Just based on the dragon tail's whip, it was more menacing than the claws.

This was an attribute of the sword dragon.

Many dragons' characteristics differed in subtle aspects.

Some dragons had extremely sharp fangs, their strong bite power surpassing the power of their claws and tail. Some dragons were better at ripping, their claws were their most powerful weapons.

And the sword dragon was slender and nimble, the power of its tail surpassed its two small claws.

And above the power of its tail was the sword dragon's speed.

Fang Yuan had already practiced it, the sword dragon was not powerful in long distance attacks, but its burst of speed from an unmoving state was impressive.

Although it could not compare to sword escape Immortal Gu, it was not inferior to Fang Yuan's blood path movement killer move — Blood Torrent.

Moreover, because it was the sword dragon's own innate movement speed, Fang Yuan could change directions much more nimbly than blood torrent, and it was much easier to maneuver as well.

And the sword dragon's strongest weapon was its dragon breath.

Dragons could breathe out attacks.

This was almost an innate ability of any dragon.

It was like the upper extreme heavenly eagle, having the innate ability to penetrate space and enter blessed lands and grotto-heavens. It was just that the dragon's breath was a very common ability, while the upper extreme heavenly eagle's ability was rare.

Upper extreme heavenly eagles were very rare, rank eight Gu Immortal Hei Fan had also obtained one through a fortuitous encounter. Besides him, no one had obtained another upper extreme heavenly eagle in Hei tribe's history.

Whoosh!

Fang Yuan tested his dragon breath.

In an instant, a white light flashed and shot at the rank six immortal material subterranean adamantite.

The subterranean adamantite shook lightly before the dragon breath disappeared, the whole process was very fast, it was as if nothing had occurred.

But the next moment, changes started to slowly appear in the subterranean adamantite, a clear crack appeared on the subterranean adamantite, the whole crack was incomparably straight, going from top to bottom in a slightly inclined angle.

The subterranean adamantite was split into two by this thin crack. Then, due to the subterranean adamantite's enormous weight, the two halves fell down.

Bam bam, two consecutive muffled sounds echoed.

The boulder sized subterranean adamantite had split into two and fallen to the ground.

The cut surface was smooth, like it was directly split by the sharpest weapon in the world.

Fang Yuan's dragon claws could only leave behind marks a few inches deep. But his dragon breath was incomparably sharp, cutting down this giant subterranean adamantite into two!

It had to be known that subterranean adamantite was considered among the hardest rank six immortal materials.

The might of the sword dragon's breath could be seen from this.

Despite Fang Yuan being mentally prepared, upon seeing the two halves of the subterranean adamantite, he could not help slightly nodding his dragon head in satisfaction.

Next, he continued to test.

He used his dragon breath on the rank seven immortal material dark inkstone.

Dark inkstone was even firmer than subterranean adamantite, the dragon breath was like sword light, cutting open marks several inches deep on the dark inkstone.

Fang Yuan continuously breathed it out sixteen times before he reached his limit.

For a short period of time, he would not be able to send out his dragon breath, he felt like a traveler in a desert who had not drank water for over half a month, his throat was extremely dry. If he tried to use dragon breath any more, he had the feeling he would destroy his throat.

Consecutively using dragon breath sixteen times changed the appearance of the whole dark inkstone. There were sword marks everywhere on it, it looked somewhat scary.

After resting for some time, Fang Yuan felt he had recovered to some degree.

He breathed out again, sure enough, he used the seventeenth dragon breath!

Fang Yuan engraved this duration in his mind.

He was continuously estimating: 'With just my own strength, I can use dragon breath sixteen times in a row. After resting for about five minutes, I will recover and can continue to breathe it out. But it is just barely possible, and after breathing out the seventeenth dragon breath, I will once again fall into the previous plight and will still need to rest for five minutes of time."

"If I add some dragon breath mortal Gu in this, I should be able to increase the amount of times I can use dragon breath."

Fang Yuan had not yet combined dragon breath Gu in this sword dragon transformation immortal killer move.

Dragon breath Gu was quite difficult to refine.

This was because the material to refine this Gu worm was the breath of dragons.

This dragon Fang Yuan obtained was dead, he had waited for a long time in treasure yellow heaven before he found someone selling it, and he had to pay a considerable price to buy it.

Only a living dragon could send its breath out, which could then be used as material to refine dragon breath Gu.

Naturally, if the Gu recipe was modified and other materials were used to substitute for dragon breath, it could be done. But Fang Yuan clearly did not have such ability.

Besides a living sword dragon, other living dragons also could be used to refine dragon breath Gu.

However, such a dragon breath Gu might be the same in name, but would have some slight differences. Although it could be used, some other mortal Gu had to be added in to remove the differences.

Transformation path was somewhat particular about this aspect.

Thus, Fang Yuan had specifically refined all the required Gu like dragon scale Gu, dragon claw Gu and so on from the sword dragon's corpse.

By using these Gu worms, he could much more quickly and conveniently activate the immortal killer move, sword dragon transformation.

The testing of the killer move was finished, the results were in line with Fang Yuan's expectations.

He had pondered deeply about choosing sword dragon transformation, and he had deduced these results in detail prior to this.

"With just a rank six Immortal Gu as the core, sword dragon transformation has a certain level of battle strength, but it is still not enough against rank seven Gu Immortals."

Normally speaking, rank seven Gu Immortals had defensive methods that were stronger than dark inkstone.

Fang Yuan used the strongest weapon of his sword dragon transformation, dragon breath, but was only able to deform this dark inkstone.

This sword dragon transformation was not sufficient for display in the blood battle martial competition.

Fang Yuan was well aware of this.

He naturally had follow-up methods.

Cancelling his transformation, he flew out of his cloud city and soon arrived in front of Lang Ya land spirit.

Fang Yuan directly expressed his intent: "Greetings to first supreme elder, I am here to exchange for sect contribution points."

Lang Ya land spirit's eyes flashed with joy, he knew Fang Yuan had obtained Hei Fan grotto-heaven, had the status of an inheritor of Thieving Heaven, wrecked Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and definitely had many good things in his hands.

And for Lang Ya Sect to develop, it naturally needed better and more precious cultivation resources.

However, Lang Ya land spirit could not force other Gu Immortals to hand over their resources, this would conflict with their interests, and Lang Ya Sect would then fall apart.

"It is good you have such thoughts." Lang Ya land spirit was greatly interested, "What do you want to contribute to the sect this time?"

"First, take a look at this." Fang Yuan brought out an item.

"A Gu Immortal's soul?" Lang Ya land spirit frowned, souls of Gu Immortals could be treated as a type of immortal material, and had more value if they were of a soul path Gu Immortal. There was even more value in the cultivation memories in the Gu Immortal's soul.

Gu Immortal souls were naturally not common.

Many Gu Immortals had methods to detonate their soul, Shadow Sect were most adept in this. Back then, when Feng Jiu Ge had battled Qin Bai Sheng before he recovered his memories, he had sensed the latter had a powerful soul detonation method, and thus let go of Qin Bai Sheng, not willing to fight to such a desperate extent.

When Gu Immortals battle, it would not be easy for them to hold back. Just like when Nian Er Ping Zhi killed Granny Yin, he directly destroyed her soul.

Lang Ya land spirit accepted this Gu Immortal soul, but he found this soul was already tampered with by Fang Yuan and could no longer be soul searched, only being used as immortal material.

"Like this, this Gu Immortal soul can only exchange for a hundred contribution points." Lang Ya land spirit said with slight disappointment.

Fang Yuan, however, smiled: "No, I think the price can be slightly higher. We can place this Gu Immortal soul in Dang Hun Mountain and turn it into guts Gu. Gu Immortal souls are extraordinary, they are supreme goods, this will definitely turn into a large sum of guts Gu. Recently, we have not been able to increase the production of guts Gu, with this Gu Immortal soul, we can definitely satisfy the rockman tribe's requests."

Lang Ya land spirit came to a realization and nodded: "It is indeed true."

He estimated the price again and said: "This rank six Gu Immortal soul can be considered as two hundred and ten sect contribution points then."

Chapter 1199: Huge Sale

Fang Yuan nodded in agreement.

This price was fair, the value of the Gu Immortal soul had increased because of guts Gu.

Since the four races alliance was set, the rockman tribe below the northern icy plain requested for a large amount of guts Gu as they had an extremely urgent need for them.

However, guts Gu had always been sold at a fixed price in treasure yellow heaven. This price could not be reduced, after all, they had to consider the long term.

Currently, although the rockman tribe's relation with Lang Ya Sect was close, most of the guts Gu were still sold at treasure yellow heaven.

Because of the monopoly on guts Gu, they could not only exchange guts Gu for immortal essence stones, but also exchange for many immortal materials and other resources.

In the resource-scarce northern icy plain, the payment the rockman tribe could provide was not able to satisfy Lang Ya Sect's development requirements.

For the benefit of the whole sect, Lang Ya land spirit would not make the rockman tribe the main trade partner.

The rockman tribe was dissatisfied but had no choice regarding this.

In short, the production of guts Gu was far from enough to meet the demand in the market. Especially in regards to Southern Border, because of the righteous path Gu Immortals exploring the giant dream realm repeatedly, they had excessive demands for the guts Gu in treasure yellow heaven.

This even created a black market for guts Gu.

Some guts Gu were resold at a much higher price.

Lang Ya Sect had repeatedly raised the price of guts Gu, but the item was still extremely popular, the whole market was like an insatiable monster and even though Lang Ya Sect was already putting full effort in producing guts Gu, it simply was unable to satisfy the terrifying appetite of this monster.

Among Fang Yuan's revenue sources, the profits from the guts Gu trade had already soared far ahead, entering its own level.

Guts gu was the greatest contributor to Fang Yuan being able to repeatedly use rank seven Immortal Gu in battle and easily replenishing his reserves of green grape immortal essence at set intervals.

Lang Ya land spirit received this Gu Immortal soul and spoke: "Man is the spirit of all living beings, with this Gu Immortal soul, we can indeed increase the production of guts Gu to a huge degree next time. Unfortunately, Gu Immortal souls can only be found by fortunate circumstances and not sought out. In the future, the primary investment for this aspect is still in Tai Qiu. Fang Yuan, if you are free, make a few trips to Tai Qiu. Desolate beast and desolate plant souls might be far inferior to Gu Immortal souls, but we can offset it with quantity and the source is also stable. With you taking action, we should be able to develop even more quickly in Tai Qiu."

Lang Ya land spirit thought highly of Fang Yuan's ability.

However, Fang Yuan replied: "I will be going to take part in blood battle martial competition soon, I am afraid I won't have time to split my attention. This is a second Gu Immortal soul, I hope first supreme elder can verify its quality."

"Second?" Lang Ya land spirit raised his eyebrows, but was not surprised.

He knew some details about Fang Yuan, and was not surprised at Fang Yuan selling some Gu Immortal souls.

"This is a featherman Gu Immortal's soul." When Lang Ya land spirit inspected it, he was slightly surprised. Variant humans were suppressed, variant human Gu Immortals were extremely rare. He had not expected Fang Yuan to have a featherman Gu Immortal's soul.

"This is your kill?" Lang Ya land spirit casually asked.

Fang Yuan smiled: "Right."

This Gu Immortal soul was of a featherman, Zheng Ling, the previous soul was Xue Song Zi's.

Lang Ya Sect was a hairy man sect, regarding an unknown featherman Gu Immortal's soul, Lang Ya land spirit decided to take it and did not have the intention to investigate further.

Thus, Fang Yuan gained several hundred contribution points.

Immediately afterwards, he brought out a third Gu Immortal soul.

Lang Ya land spirit smiled: "It seems you intend to sell a lot today. Alright, just take out all the Gu Immortal souls you want to sell."

"Alright." Fang Yuan started taking out Gu Immortal souls one after the other.

He truly had many Gu Immortal souls.

There were souls of Dong Fang Chang Fan, Xue Song Zi, Zheng Ling and others from before. Later, in Hei Fan grotto-heaven, he killed a group. Then finally, he received even more souls in the turbulent flow sea area.

When Fang Yuan took out three Gu Immortal souls in a row, Lang Ya land spirit smiled.

When Fang Yuan took out six, Lang Ya land spirit was surprised, he subconsciously stood a little from his seat, as if he wanted to come closer to check.

When Fang Yuan took out the tenth Gu Immortal soul, Lang Ya land spirit's expression changed, he started pointing at Fang Yuan: "How did you kill so many people?"

Fang Yuan smiled: "It was just luck."

He then continued to take out Gu Immortal souls.

Finally, when Lang Ya land spirit saw Gu Immortal souls all around in the surroundings, he was extremely shocked.

"I finally understand why you are not able to blend in with humans and sided with us variant humans!" Lang Ya land spirit was left speechless.

"You only have rank six cultivation!" Lang Ya land spirit knew details about Fang Yuan, because familiar face was given to Fang Yuan by him.

"How long has it been since you became an immortal? You also still had to travel around here and there to revive yourself. Killing so many people, you are simply like Spectral Soul Demon Venerable when he was young."

Fang Yuan gave a forced smile when he heard the name Spectral Soul: "I am contributing all these souls to the sect, besides this, I also have many cultivation insights, Gu recipes of all paths, Immortal Gu recipes, killer moves and immortal killer moves. Even battlefield killer moves as well as up-to-date maps of each region, which will make it more convenient for my fellow sect members to move in the outside world."

Fang Yuan was undergoing a huge sale!

Lang Ya blessed land's history was extremely long, it had incomparably rich treasures which were even coveted by Heavenly Court and always in the minds of Shadow Sect.

But Fang Yuan had killed so many people, and the things he obtained from soul searching were also extremely abundant.

Most of the treasures in Lang Ya blessed land were payment received in the past by Long Hair Ancestor by refining Gu for others. While some were items purchased by Lang Ya land spirit through treasure yellow heaven.

Among these treasures, the former were stored ages ago, Long Hair Ancestor was a person from three hundred thousand years ago, a figure of the Medieval Antiquity Era.

And the latter could be sold at treasure yellow heaven, one could imagine that the top quality goods among them were sparse, although they would also have rare items.

As for these things Fang Yuan contributed, most of them were the entire foundation of the Gu Immortals, these things were as precious as life to them. Not to mention that they were new creations that would also not be sold for no reason in treasure yellow heaven.

In this regard, Lang Ya land spirit did not reject any offers.

He was different from the previous Lang Ya land spirit, the previous Lang Ya land spirit was only interested in refining Gu, while he was brimming with ambitions, creating Lang Ya Sect and wholeheartedly trying to make hairy men the rulers of the world, restoring their glory from the Immemorial Antiquity Era and Remote Antiquity Era.

Currently, Lang Ya Sect primarily used refinement path, most of the hairy man Gu Immortals cultivated transformation path as well.

Lang Ya Sect wanted to become a large sect, completing Lang Ya land spirit's ambition, for this they needed to incorporate various kinds of things and possess Gu Immortals of all paths. Like the great Huang Jin tribe super forces of Northern Plains, the ten great ancient sects of Central Continent and so on.

Fang Yuan's sect contribution points rose steeply.

In another cloud city.

Twelfth Hair was in the midst of refining Gu.

"Oh no, there is an error!" Suddenly, his expression changed as the fire he was controlling suddenly weakened.

He quickly activated Gu worms, spurting out blood into the fire.

Whoosh.

The fire burned high once again, Twelfth Hair was pale, his body shivering uncontrollably. He had just been injured by the backlash caused by failing in Gu refinement, blood was slowly seeping out of his seven orifices, causing the hair on his whole body to moisten with blood.

His wide-opened eyes were filled with traces of blood, as they firmly focused on the fire.

After a while, the burning fire suddenly erupted and disappeared.

The refinement path Gu formation opened up, revealing over a hundred self will Gu.

The hairy man Gu Immortals raised by the previous Lang Ya land spirit had extremely weak battle strength, but had strong Gu refinement ability.

These self will Gu were only mortal Gu but they were rank five. Twelfth Hair could refine over a hundred of these rank five self will Gu at once, revealing his extraordinary refinement path attainment.

Twelfth Hair thought to himself that it was a close shave, he rejoiced: "Fortunately, I sacrificed myself to make up for the mistake. Otherwise, these self will Gu would be destroyed, not only would it waste the effort I spent over these last few days to refine these Gu, I would also have to compensate for it with three times the refinement materials."

To increase the production of self will Gu, Fang Yuan not only used his sect contribution points to attract other hairy man Gu Immortals to refine them for him, he also supplied them immortal materials out of his own pockets, letting these hairy man Gu Immortals use these immortal materials to refine mortal Gu.

The hairy man Gu Immortals no longer had disdain and disgust towards Fang Yuan like before.

Fang Yuan possessed rank eight battle strength, causing these hairy man Gu Immortals to be filled with respect. Moreover, after such a strong financial ability was revealed, these hairy man Gu Immortals accepted the difference between them and Fang Yuan even more.

Strong dizziness assaulted Twelfth Hair's mind.

"Refining self will Gu eleven times without pausing is truly too consuming on the body and mind. The mistake just now is a warning that I need to rest. I need to quickly recover and accept some of these self will Gu refinement assignments later to earn more immortal essence stones."

Twelfth Hair had a bitter expression when he thought of immortal essence stones, heaving a deep sigh.

"Desolate beasts are not easy to raise."

"These desolate beasts all have great appetites, there is a huge burden on me every month to feed and raise them!"

"More importantly, beast enslavement Immortal Gu is only lent to me, every time I borrow it, I will have to pay with sect contribution points according to the period of time."

"Considering the long term, I definitely need to buy this beast enslavement Immortal Gu. But rank six beast enslavement Immortal Gu needs up to ten thousand sect contribution points..."

Twelfth Hair took out an information path Gu worm.

This Gu worm had one use, to display the sect contribution points of all Gu Immortals in Lang Ya Sect and rank them accordingly.

Simply put, it was Lang Ya Sect's contribution list.

Twelfth Hair looked into it with his consciousness and easily found his name in the upper half of the list.

Then he saw a series of numbers beside his name.

"Over six hundred sect contribution points, but I am still way too far from my target!" Twelfth Hair gave a bitter smile, feeling he had a long way to go.

"But the other hairy man Gu Immortals are also similar to me, some are even worse than me."

"My advantage lies in that I cultivate enslavement path as well, and now already have several desolate beasts with me. I can obtain sect contribution points more easily than others."

Chapter 1200: Dragon Breath Immortal Gu

"That's right, this is my advantage, I need to prioritize my strengths from now on and make full use of my talents in battle."

"I can use this to break the deadlock and drive up my cultivation speed."

"According to this development, my strength will continue to grow and the sect will need me more often. When I have strength like Elder Fang Yuan, the sect contribution points will be solely mine to take!"

"Cheer up, these days will keep on improving, Twelfth Hair, you need to continue working hard and reach your peak in life!"

Twelfth Hair's mood changed, and his fighting spirit gradually returned.

As he thought of Fang Yuan, he subconsciously glanced at the first name of Lang Ya Sect's contribution list.

Last time, because of the four races alliance, Fang Yuan had obtained a thousand sect contribution points which had caused the hairy man Gu Immortals' mouths to water in envy.

But recently, because Fang Yuan had issued large numbers of Gu refinement tasks, his sect contribution points had been continuing to dwindle, and quickly at that.

Fang Yuan's name still occupied first on the list, but the gap with the second ranked hairy man Gu Immortal was getting smaller and smaller.

A lot of hairy man Gu Immortals were waiting for the time when Fang Yuan's name was surpassed.

Fang Yuan was a human Gu Immortal possessing rank eight battle strength, surpassing him at the contribution list would give a different sensation to the hairy man Gu Immortals.

It would be an enormous glory!

However, the next moment, Twelfth Hair's whole body suddenly stiffened.

He remained still like a stone statue.

Because he saw the number behind Fang Yuan's name.

"Over fifteen thousand sect contribution points, how could it be?!" Twelfth Hair almost felt like he was hallucinating.

Ever since Lang Ya Sect was established, there had been no one who had obtained so many sect contribution points.

At most, at one time, Fang Yuan's sect contribution points had reached above two thousand, before it started rapidly falling.

Now, Fang Yuan's sect contribution points had passed fifteen thousand!

Unbelievable!

This was an unprecedented record!

Twelfth Hair's heart shook wildly, but the following scene made him even more shocked.

Fang Yuan's sect contribution points were continuously rising!

Fifteen thousand, eighteen thousand, twenty thousand, thirty thousand... fifty thousand, sixty thousand...

The number kept on rising steeply!

"It surpassed... eighty thousand!" Twelfth Hair was stupefied at the sight. What made him even more astonished was that Fang Yuan's sect contribution points still showed no signs of stopping!

When it reached over ninety thousand, suddenly, Fang Yuan's total sect contribution points decreased by over seventy thousand!

Only over ten thousand was left now.

"What is happening?"

"Could it be, I actually refined Gu so much that I am starting to hallucinate?"

"This, this is a dream?"

"Ah, no!"

Twelfth Hair suddenly shook and snapped back to awareness.

"Over seventy thousand sect contribution points suddenly disappeared, Fang Yuan definitely exchanged for an Immortal Gu. No, he did not exchange for my beast enslavement Immortal Gu, right?"

Twelfth Hair quickly took out another information path Gu worm and placed his consciousness in it.

After inspecting, he let out a heavy breath of relief: "So he did not exchange for beast enslavement Immortal Gu, but a rank seven Immortal Gu. It is good as long as it is not beast enslavement Immortal Gu."

That was seriously a huge scare!

Twelfth Hair patted his chest, his whole body easing up.

But the moment he relaxed, his eyes rolled backwards as he fainted on the spot.

He had suffered injuries during the Gu refinement process, and his mood had swung up and down at this moment, he naturally would fall unconscious after relaxing.

Achieving his target, Fang Yuan returned to his cloud city.

Inside a secret room, he took out a completely new Immortal Gu.

This Gu resembled light purple colored fog in the form of a dragon, it did not have a fixed shape and was floating around.

Rank seven Immortal Gu — Dragon Breath!

Fang Yuan had finally chosen sword dragon transformation because Lang Ya Sect's treasury had this Immortal Gu.

To exchange for this Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan had to sell all his Gu Immortal souls along with large amounts of cultivation information he had obtained from soul searching.

Naturally, Fang Yuan had withheld some of the contents. Like Dong Fang Chang Fan's wisdom path methods, Hei Fan true inheritance's important details, and so on.

This had sharply raised Fang Yuan's sect contribution points to above ninety thousand. In the near future, this amount would be Fang Yuan's peak, difficult to surpass.

Then, Fang Yuan used over seventy thousand sect contribution points to exchange for the rank seven transformation path Immortal Gu, Dragon Breath.

In just a short while, his sect contribution points had fallen to over ten thousand.

But he still occupied first place on the contribution list.

The second ranked Gu Immortal on the contribution list only had four digits in terms of contribution points.

The gap had been widened by a huge margin.

Fang Yuan's position was firmly in place like a mountain.

Naturally, Fang Yuan did not care about the sect contribution list.

He also did not know Twelfth Hair had received a great impact from this event and had fallen unconscious.

If he knew, Fang Yuan would think he was over-thinking it.

Not all Immortal Gu in Lang Ya blessed land could be exchanged. Beast enslavement Immortal Gu was on the exchange list, but Lang Ya land spirit had clearly left it behind for Twelfth Hair.

Even if Fang Yuan wanted to exchange for it, he would not be able to.

Besides this, rank seven Immortal Gu Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus was also not for sale.

This Immortal Gu was originally Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's Immortal Gu, later it was refined by Long Hair Ancestor up to rank eight and was merged into the rank eight Immortal Gu House Refinement Cauldron.

Some time ago, Shadow Sect had invaded Lang Ya blessed land, destroying Refinement Cauldron and seizing many of the core Immortal Gu. Although Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus remained, it had been damaged and had fallen from rank eight to rank seven.

If Fang Yuan wanted to exchange for this Immortal Gu, he would have to pay a very large price that could move Lang Ya land spirit's mind.

However, Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus would not be of much help to Fang Yuan. He had calculated that after he raised his cultivation to rank seven and his immortal essence started producing red date immortal essence, it would be sufficient.

It was not worth it to pay a greater price for just Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus.

Fang Yuan spent some time before he successfully integrated this rank seven dragon breath Gu into his immortal killer move, sword dragon transformation.

Transformation path immortal killer moves were essentially very simple. Dragon breath Gu was a natural component of sword dragon transformation.

What's more, Fang Yuan was a transformation path grandmaster.

With this rank seven dragon breath Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan simply did not need any dragon breath mortal Gu.

Like in Hei Fan's true inheritance, Hei Fan had really wanted to obtain immortal level day Gu and month Gu. Because then, when he activated days pass like years and similar immortal killer moves, he would not need to spend so many mortal day Gu and month Gu.

Having a relevant Immortal Gu made it extremely convenient.

It also reduced the difficulty of controlling the killer move.

Its effect would also have a large boost!

Taking a deep breath, Fang Yuan tried sword dragon transformation again.

Silver light burst out, shining towards the sky.

Just looking at this, Fang Yuan knew that sword dragon transformation's might had increased by multiple times.

From within the silvery light, a sword dragon revealed its figure. Its body was more than double the size of before, reaching over forty feet.

Its eyes were still white, its scales were much wider and thicker than before, there were now two more claws, reaching a total of four claws now. The dragon horn protruded out further, piercing towards the sky.

Fang Yuan inspected all over and saw that every aspect had received a huge boost in quality.

"After adding the rank seven dragon breath Gu, this is now an ancient desolate beast level sword dragon." Fang Yuan was well aware.

As such, this immortal killer move could be used at the blood battle martial competition.

The previous sword dragon transformation would not work.

It could only be used to bully some ordinary rank six Gu Immortals.

The current ancient sword dragon had the qualifications to match against rank seven Gu Immortals.

Next was the most important part.

Fang Yuan was unavoidably a little nervous.

He lightly stretched out his dragon body and flew to a completely new dark inkstone.

Dragon breath!

Fang Yuan opened his mouth and breathed out.

In that instant, a pure white sword light flashed past.

Crack, a crisp sound was heard, as the dark inkstone was cut in two.

Not only this, the sword light still had strength remaining to destroy the whole secret room.

Fang Yuan's cloud city shook intensely, giving off muffled noises as large numbers of Gu worms that formed the secret room died instantly.

"I have already controlled my strength, the dark inkstone already bore most of the dragon breath, only a small part of its power was leaked out." Intense joy flashed past the ancient sword dragon's eyes.

Fang Yuan had only displayed a small portion of his strength, but his surrounding environment actually was unable to endure it.

Although the cloud city's structure was exquisite and hairy man Gu Immortals had spent immense mental effort to make it, it was after all only a mortal Gu house, and could not endure the remaining power of the ancient sword dragon's breath.

Green grape immortal essence continued to be consumed to maintain the form of the ancient sword dragon.

Clearly, the immortal essence expenditure had increased by many times.

Where there are gains, there are losses.

After all, adding rank seven Immortal Gu dragon breath had increased the level of the immortal killer move, sword dragon transformation, immortal essence being expended rapidly was an inevitable outcome.

"I can no longer practice in the cloud city. Lang Ya blessed land has many observers, but if I go out of Lang Ya blessed land I will receive even more attention from heaven's will."

"It seems I still need to place my sovereign immortal aperture and properly test the limits of ancient sword dragon transformation."

"The dragon breath I send out has already reached rank seven battle strength, its effect is outstanding and the expenditure is still small. How powerful will it be when I use sword marks targeting death, dark assassination and triple layered sword wave in my ancient sword dragon form?"

Fang Yuan was feeling anticipation.

He resolutely took action, immediately flying out of the cloud city, going through the super Gu formation and teleporting to the outside world.

"Fang Yuan has left. He actually exchanged for dragon breath Immortal Gu, what is the reason?" Sixth Hair was secretly activating investigative methods, paying close attention until the super Gu formation activated and Fang Yuan's figure disappeared from his perception.

After Sixth Hair knew the change in the sect contribution points list, he was filled with unease.

Fang Yuan's development speed had surpassed his expectations again. Moreover, he did not understand the direction of Fang Yuan's growth.

"Fang Yuan naturally won't exchange for an Immortal Gu that has no use to him. No, I need to report this information to Lord Ying Wu Xie quickly." Sixth Hair was filled with worries.

Chapter 1201: Ye Lui Qun Xing

Sun was shining bright in the sky of Northern Plains, with no clouds to be seen in the surroundings.

However, at Blood Plain, starlight shone brilliantly, as if stars filled the sky.

Golden Dawn Hall was quietly floating in the air, it stood majestically, no matter how much turbulence was going on outside, it remained lofty and unmoved.

In contrast, the Gu Immortals on Chu Du's side were all standing on clouds, their expressions looking unsightly or filled with worries.

Chu Du was expressionless, but his gaze that looked at the battle was extremely heavy.

"Immortal Wang is going to lose." Chu Du sighed internally.

In the center of the battlefield, Immortal Wang was fighting with the righteous path Gu Immortal Ye Lui Qun Xing!

Immortal Wang had already transformed into a heaven swallowing hound, charging left and right with astonishing might.

The heaven swallowing hound was an immemorial desolate beast, but Immortal Wang was only a rank seven Gu Immortal, this transformation path immortal killer move also did not have a relevant rank eight Immortal Gu in it. So, this heaven swallowing hound's battle strength was only at rank seven level.

And Immortal Wang's opponent, Ye Lui Qun Xing, was tall and thin like a bamboo pole. He had three strands of hair as a beard and had a yellowish-white complexion. Right now, he was far away from the heaven swallowing hound, hundreds of star fragments were flying around him, shining with brilliant light, dying the sky a color of blue.

Immortal Wang's heaven swallowing hound transformation used all its strength to attack.

However, countless star fragments, big and small, tightly surrounded him.

Of these star fragments, small ones were the size of a lantern, while the big ones were the size of an elephant. They kept on flying around, a small portion were encircling Immortal Wang with dizzying speed, while the larger portion were encircling Ye Lui Qun Xing, moving slowly in a mysterious trajectory.

Plop.

A muffled sound echoed, a star fragment firmly collided against Immortal Wang's body.

The heaven swallowing hound's movement slowed, and exposed a flaw when it tried to dodge.

Boom boom boom.

Three muffled sounds resounded as this opportunity was taken, star fragments collided against Immortal Wang fiercely.

The heaven swallowing hound let out a low growl, coughing out a large amount of blood, its feet staggered and almost fell down to the ground.

Any Gu Immortal with eyes could see who was in control of the situation.

Immortal Wang was the one attacking, but was in an absolute disadvantage from start to finish.

And the defending Ye Lui Qun Xing was the one who held the upper hand, putting himself behind layers of defense.

This battle tactic was naturally a correct one.

One often had to choose long range battle when dealing with transformation path Gu Immortals.

Because the Gu Immortal that transformed into desolate beast, ancient desolate beast or even immemorial desolate beast, would have a strong and sturdy body, just relying on their transformed body's quality, their battle strength would increase to a terrifying level.

Gu Immortals of other paths mostly had human bodies. Their physical qualities were weak, even if they had powerful defensive methods, they did not want to put themselves in such a dangerous situation where they were fighting with their weakness against a transformation path Gu Immortal's strength.

The dominance was already clear, Ye Lui Qun Xing was in an impregnable position.

He spoke in a clear voice: "It is useless, Immortal Wang. My immortal killer move was created by taking Dong Fang Chang Fan's myriad star fireflies as a reference, the flying trajectory is extremely profound and inscrutable. Previously, six star fragments could completely obstruct you. Now, there are at least thirty-six star fragments around you, how will you break through?"

This Ye Lui Qun Xing was also a person with an interesting past.

He had challenged Dong Fang Chang Fan, and had suffered defeat after defeat, but had still persisted in challenging him. Dong Fang Chang Fan was a righteous path figure, the number one wisdom path Gu Immortal of Northern Plains who had single-handedly led Dong Fang tribe to prominence.

Ye Lui Qun Xing's defeats did not make Northern Plains' Gu Immortals feel he was weak.

Instead, they very much appreciated him fighting back despite the repeated setbacks, and his steady, unwavering spirit.

As one of the leading figures of the righteous path, Dong Fang Chang Fan could not lay a heavy hand on Ye Lui Qun Xing, who was similarly of Huang Jin bloodline.

There was even one time when after he defeated Ye Lui Qun Xing, he personally instructed him regarding some secrets of myriad star fireflies.

Ye Lui Qun Xing treated the guidance as a precious treasure, immediately going into closed cultivation.

Unknown to him, this was precisely Dong Fang Chang Fan's scheme.

Dong Fang Chang Fan had not only gotten rid of the annoying Ye Lui Qun Xing, this also expressed his goodwill to Ye Lui tribe, and had smoothly accomplished an instance of collaboration with Ye Lui tribe, gaining large amounts of benefits.

Ye Lui Qun Xing had originally felt that Dong Fang Chang Fan was a thorn in his eyes, but having obtained benefits from Dong Fang Chang Fan, he did not feel he could shamelessly challenge Dong Fang Chang Fan again. After coming out of his closed cultivation, he chose to focus hard on his own development and did not even find trouble with other Gu Immortals of Dong Fang tribe.

As such, this trump card killer move of his clearly bore resemblance to myriad star fireflies.

Myriad star fireflies was Dong Fang Chang Fan's killer move, which was famous throughout the whole of Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world.

Ye Lui Qun Xing's move, however, treated the star fragments as the main body, it could be considered as him creating his own unique method.

A real star was extremely huge, Fang Yuan had been using star eyes Immortal Gu up until now, and had only managed to refine one star.

Immortal Wang's heaven swallowing hound transformation kept on coughing up blood, and was struck by more and more star fragments. He could not even retort, he was dizzy and was heavily injured, moreover, his immortal essence expenditure had reached an enormous amount.

The immortals on Chu Du's side showed even more unsightly looks.

"If Immortal Wang is defeated, he would be the fourth person Ye Lui Qun Xing has defeated from our side!"

"His immortal killer move is truly too powerful, when it was just two or three star fragments, they can still be resisted. When fifteen star fragments appear and they work together as one, the difficulty to resist them increases by countless times. Right now, he already has a hundred star fragments, achieving complete dominance, this simply cannot be resisted."

Inside Golden Dawn Hall, the righteous path immortals had smiles on their faces.

Ye Lui Xiao Jin was watching the battle with excitement, Ye Lui Qun Xing was his senior, seeing this senior about to defeat his fourth opponent, Ye Lui Xiao Jin also felt excitement and pride.

On the other side, Nian Er Ping Zhi was still regulating his breathing.

One thing worth mentioning was that Nian Er tribe's position had already moved to the center.

This was because of Nian Er Ping Zhi's battle where he had killed the rank seven demonic path expert Granny Yin.

Many rank six geniuses and experts had the battle strength to go against rank seven. But being able to kill rank seven was a different level altogether.

Adding Nian Er Ping Zhi's young age to this battle achievement, this undoubtedly became even more rare.

By this time.

The allied righteous path forces, and the alliance of Chu Sect and Bai Zu, had already gone through over ten battles.

At the start, Chu Du had the discerning eye to send out the promising young Xue Wu Hen, who won three battles in a row, awing others.

Then, from the righteous path's side, Gong Wan Ting sent Nian Er Ping Zhi. Similarly a rising young genius, Nian Er Ping Zhi's battle result was even more brilliant, using the immortal killer move sword heart clarity and killing the renowned demonic path expert Granny Yin.

Afterwards, Gong Wan Ting negotiated with Chu Du, and the two sides temporarily stopped the battle, setting rules regarding exchange of corpses.

Then the battle began again, Yuan tribe of the righteous path, Meng tribe, and other tribe's Gu Immortals appeared one after the other, while Chu Du sent out Hao Zhen, Chou Lao Wu as well as some Gu Immortals of Bai Zu tribe to contest with them.

Perhaps it was because they were senior Gu Immortals, each side had their own victories and defeats, and suffered varying degrees of injuries, but there were no deaths.

Seeing the situation seemingly entering a stalemate, Gong Wan Ting pondered for a while before sending Ye Lui Qun Xing.

This person was a true main strength among Ye Lui tribe's force. He was an expert among rank seven Gu Immortals, although he had many losses among his battle achievements, they were against Dong Fang Chang Fan, naturally, no one would look down on him.

What made people especially admire him were his character and spirit. He had suffered many defeats from Dong Fang Chang Fan, but he always came back stronger.

Worth mentioning was that Ye Lui Hui Hong had the highest seniority, but his battle strength could not compare to Ye Lui Qun Xing.

The righteous path paid attention to seniority, unlike the demonic path which only looked at strength.

Finally, Chu Du spoke: "Alright, this battle is our loss."

Immortal Wang retreated with a shameful expression.

Ye Lui Qun Xing also did not forcibly go after his life, after all, Immortal Wang still had the ability to protect himself and it would give enough time for Chu Du to come help.

Immortal Wang was pale, his mood extremely complicated.

He was the fourth opponent of Ye Lui Qun Xing and had originally thought of having gotten an easy opportunity, but the result was that Ye Lui Qun Xing's battle strength had not fallen even after three battles.

Immortal Wang returned to his human form and walked towards Chu Du, saying in a heavy voice: "That Ye Lui Qun Xing's immortal killer move is extremely ingenious. His immortal essence expenditure is definitely small, and the star fragments have mutual attraction force between them, creating a good deal of starlight magnetic force, I am afraid it would not be easy to discern the mysteries of this killer move unless one is a star path Gu Immortal."

"The opponent would be implicated by these star fragments. These star fragments are very fast and sometimes they would suddenly form a formless force which skewed my direction, making me lose control over myself many times. Now that I think of it, Ye Lui Qun Xing was weakest in the first battle. Now, he has already released a hundred star fragments, forming an array for battle. The ones who will go later will lose many advantages, and would find it very difficult to go against this array."

Immortal Wang's tone was sincere, these were his sincere words, they were also reasons given to excuse himself and not be held at fault.

Chu Du nodded and patted Immortal Wang's shoulder: "No need to say much, it is good that you returned safely."

It was a simple action, but this action almost made Immortal Wang's eyes tear up.

"Who wants to come fight next!" At this time, Ye Lui Qun Xing called out.

"It seems this person still does not want to retreat and wants to fight his fifth battle!" Chu Du's expression slightly changed, killing intent flashing in his eyes.

The immortals behind him started whispering.

"He has already defeated four people in a row, he still seems to have strength remaining."

"Immortal Wang's strength is outstanding, he transformed into a heaven swallowing hound but was still unable to win, sigh!"

Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals were silent.

Bai Zu Wei was already dead, what they were good at was not individual battle strength, but Green City Rampage.

Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu's wind thunder roar was renowned throughout Northern Plains, it could be considered a trump card that could pressure the opponents and make them feel apprehensive. It was only that they had already battled separately and still bore some injuries.

When Gu Immortals were injured, because of the conflict of dao marks, they were very difficult to heal.

For a moment, Chu Du actually found that he had fallen into an awkward situation of having no experts to send.

Comparatively, in the righteous path, experts filled Golden Dawn Hall, while Chu Du's side was only an alliance of the newly established Bai Zu tribe and his sect, they indeed had few members and were seriously stretched out.

Chapter 1202: Arrogance Concealed Under Beauty

"Do I have to go myself?"

Facing the awkward situation of having no experts to send, Chu Du unavoidably had such a thought.

He could naturally take the stage and also had the confidence to win against Ye Lui Qun Xing.

But what would it look like when Chu Du, as the strongest expert on his side, took the stage? Would it not make their side look weaker?

Moreover, even after he wins against Ye Lui Qun Xing, the other side would definitely continue to send other Gu Immortals. Gong Wan Ting, Yao tribe's Yao Yuan Ying, Guan tribe's Guan Yang, Nu Er tribe's Nu Er Gu and Nu Er Qian, all of these people were experts who Chu Du needed to pay attention to.

Two fists cannot rival four palms.

Chu Du could win one battle, two battles, three battles, but could he guarantee he would win all the battles?

Chu Du fell into silence.

"What, no one wants to fight? We have just reached this stage and there is already nobody left?" Ye Lui Qun Xing did not let go of this chance to mock them.

Xue Wu Hen could not endure this provocation, he was a very prideful person. He requested to be sent by Chu Du: "Let me go deal with this Ye Lui Qun Xing."

However, Xue Wu Hen was only at rank six, how could Chu Du let him go? Xue Wu Hen might be able to battle rank seven, but the other party was an expert among rank sevens.

Chu Du slowly shook his head.

Right at this moment, his eyes suddenly brightened, because an information path Gu worm flew to his immortal aperture through treasure yellow heaven.

"Wonderful! Elder Liu Guan Yi's timing is perfect." Chu Du sent his consciousness into the Gu worm and after absorbing the information, his brows immediately relaxed.

He had confidence in Liu Guan Yi! He had always thought Fang Yuan's strength was only second to his in Chu Sect.

Especially when they made the trip to Crazed Demon Cave, Fang Yuan's performance had left a deep impression on Chu Du.

"Be patient. My Chu Sect's second supreme elder is about to arrive. Ye Lui Qun Xing, why are you in such a rush, enjoy your moment of victory for a while longer." Chu Du chuckled as he said in a plain tone.

"Chu Sect's second supreme elder?"

"Chu Du is the first supreme elder, doesn't it mean this second supreme elder is only second to him?"

"This person is very mysterious, no one knows where he comes from, and we have very limited information on him."

Both sides' Gu Immortals discussed.

The righteous path Gu Immortals in Golden Dawn Hall started discussing and exchanging information on Fang Yuan.

"Think about that Xue Wu Hen, what is strange about them having Liu Guan Yi?" Nian Er Yi Fang caressed his beard, speaking unconcernedly.

"So what if he is stronger? At most, he would have rank seven peak battle strength, our side is a gathering of experts and geniuses." Ye Lui Hui Hong laughed.

Gong Wan Ting spoke softly, her voice lingering around the whole of Golden Dawn Hall: "Chu Du is not blind, this person is placed above Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu. He is Chu Sect's second supreme elder, we should assume that he possesses an outstanding aspect."

Xue Wu Hen's eyes brightened, having many expectations regarding Fang Yuan.

"Elder Hao Zhen, how is Elder Liu Guan Yi's strength?" One Hei tribe Gu Immortal asked. Naturally, this Hei tribe Gu Immortal had now already changed his surname to Bai Zu. He had not participated in the battle of Iron Eagle blessed land, and it was not appropriate for him to ask Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals, Bai Zu Wei had died in the battle, and this had become almost like a taboo topic in Bai Zu tribe.

Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu were respectively Chu Sect's third and forth supreme elder. Actually, they were uncomfortable at being underneath Fang Yuan, but right now, they could not damage their own sect's reputation.

"He claims to be a transformation path Gu Immortal."

"But we have never seen him use any transformation killer moves. Even in Hei Fan grotto-heaven, when we resisted the attacks of Heavenly Lord, it was like that."

The surrounding Gu Immortals could not help but draw in deep breaths.

The words of Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu made people unavoidably think towards one aspect.

"It seems this Elder Liu Guan Yi is quite amazing! Even the invasion of Heavenly Lord Bai Zu did not make him use all his strength?"

"This was the person who first intruded Iron Eagle blessed land and seized almost all the eagle nests." A Gu Immortal of Bai Zu bloodline was feeling complicated at this moment.

"He has arrived." Chu Du suddenly spoke.

The immortals behind him followed Chu Du's movement and turned around, looking behind them.

Inside Golden Dawn Hall, the righteous path immortals also cast their gazes over.

A multicolored cloud was flying rapidly, upon which a young-looking Gu Immortal stood at the front with his head held high.

He wore a white robe, the wide sleeves constantly fluttered backwards due to the wind.

He had long black hair and a jade-like complexion, with sharp eyebrows and bright eyes, his nose bridge was tall, and his skin was white like snow. He had a light smile on his face, appearing relaxed and unfettered, and was extremely handsome, even a man would be moved by his appearance.

Just one glance at Fang Yuan left a deep impression on these immortals.

"Elder Liu, you have finally come." Chu Du smiled brightly, flying over to welcome him.

"Domination Immortal Chu Du personally went to receive him?"

Seeing this scene, many Gu Immortals were shaken, instantly, Fang Yuan's status had risen by multiple levels in their hearts.

"What are the origins of this Liu Guan Yi? What has he done to deserve such treatment from Domination Immortal?"

The righteous path Gu Immortals looked at each other, as they started to pay more importance to Fang Yuan's arrival.

"This information path Gu worm records the battle scenes from earlier, look at it quickly." Chu Du flew in front of Fang Yuan, and secretly handed an information path mortal Gu to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan silently accepted it.

Chu Du treated him as an equal, after the Crazed Demon Agreement, Chu Du's and Fang Yuan's relationship had become much closer.

The group of immortals subconsciously went silent, patiently watching Fang Yuan slowly fly towards the battle.

"This person is Ye Lui Qun Xing, he primarily cultivates star path. He has already defeated four people on our side, we need you to show your might and defeat him." Chu Du spoke softly to Fang Yuan as he pointed at Ye Lui Qun Xing, who was standing proudly in the air.

Fang Yuan inwardly thought: "I came over because of this person. A star path blessed land is suitable for me to annex. Moreover, this guy has rank seven cultivation, after I annex his immortal aperture, my cultivation will immediately soar and reach rank seven, I will start producing red date immortal essence."

Ye Lui Qun Xing was tense.

Ever since Fang Yuan had appeared, he had been paying close attention to him.

Fang Yuan's gaze was tranquil, he could not read his expression at all.

After some thinking, Ye Lui Qun Xing solemnly spoke: "I am honored."

The immortals quietly looked at Fang Yuan, awaiting him entering the battle.

Fang Yuan, however, internally was shaking his head.

He had already read all the information in the information path Gu worm, Chu Du had given him, and knew all the moves Ye Lui Qun Xing had shown before.

Fang Yuan had a clear estimation of Ye Lui Qun Xing's strength.

He was probably at the level of experts like Unfettered Scholar and Pi Shui Han, or maybe slightly weaker, all in all, he was an expert among rank sevens.

Above them would be people like Domination Immortal Chu Du and Immortal Monkey King Shi Lei.

And above Chu Du were Feng Jiu Ge and Qin Bai Sheng after regaining his memories.

It was fully achievable for him to defeat Ye Lui Qun Xing with ancient sword dragon transformation.

But killing him would be difficult with a frontal assault. Especially under the view of the crowd and their watchful eyes, everyone was on guard against each other.

Let alone when the opponent was Ye Lui Qun Xing.

The most important thing regarding this person was this immortal killer move, not only did it expend little immortal essence, it also had terrifying offensive and defensive properties.

Even more praiseworthy was his mental state and nature.

Losses could not defeat him and could only make him stronger.

If this kind of person was the enemy, the best thing was to kill them.

Even Dong Fang Chang Fan felt a headache because he could not kill him.

But how to kill him?

Fang Yuan estimated he did not have a high chance of killing Ye Lui Qun Xing. After transforming into an ancient sword dragon, Fang Yuan's battle strength would reach the level of Unfettered Scholar. However, Fang Yuan's ability to sustain a long battle was quite poor, after all, green grape immortal essence could not compare to red date immortal essence.

One hundred beads of green grape immortal essence could turn into one bead of red date immortal essence. But when using rank seven Immortal Gu, the effect that could be reached with one bead of red date immortal essence required at least one hundred and thirty beads of green grape immortal essence.

This created a phenomenon of intensifying expenditure.

Gu Immortals using higher rank Immortal Gu were like children waving around a sledgehammer, it was very difficult.

As he pondered this, Fang Yuan spoke: "I won't fight."

The immortals were stunned.

"Why won't you fight, are you afraid?" Immortal Wang's sneering voice came from behind.

Ever since the Iron Eagle blessed land's battle where Fang Yuan had treated him as a scapegoat, Immortal Wang had felt hatred towards Fang Yuan. The expectant gazes of immortals at Fang Yuan, made Immortal Wang very dissatisfied. He, himself, was defeated by Ye Lui Qun Xing, and the person whom everyone's expectations were placed on was his enemy. Such a feeling left a really bad taste in his mouth.

Fang Yuan did not respond.

Chu Du, however, immediately frowned, as he turned back and gave a fierce glare at Immortal Wang.

Immortal Wang quickly closed his mouth, beads of cold sweat starting to seep out of his forehead.

Chu Du inwardly shook his head: "Immortal Wang and these other Gu Immortals were all lone immortals or demonic cultivators, they are accustomed to being unrestrained. After joining Chu Sect, their awareness has not increased much. Right now, even if he has some dissatisfaction with Liu Guan Yi, how could he reveal the internal conflicts of Chu Sect in front of the public?"

At the same time, Chu Du looked at Fang Yuan, he did not speak but his gaze inquired: Why won't you fight?

Fang Yuan gazed at Ye Lui Qun Xing, sneering: "He is too weak, I can kill him with just my spit. Do we kill chickens with an ox-cleaver? Fighting him is an insult towards my status."

Arrogant!

Way too arrogant!!

For a moment, the stomachs of the immortals churned, as all kinds of thoughts surged in their minds.

Fang Yuan looked like a quiet handsome boy, who could have thought his first few words would reveal the astonishing arrogance within him.

"He actually said he can win against an expert like Ye Lui Qun Xing with just his spit? Even Domination Immortal Chu Du might not be able to do it!" Nian Er Ping Zhi was displeased.

"He is tooting his own horn too much." Xue Wu Hen looked at Fang Yuan with a dazed look. He had always thought he was a very prideful person, but he could not compare to this person before him.

Fang Yuan spouted a lot of nonsense right away. His arrogance caused many people to be dissatisfied.

The most dissatisfied person was Ye Lui Xiao Jin.

He was young and full of vigor, Ye Lui Qun Xing was his tribe member, humiliating Ye Lui Qun Xing was like humiliating him.

Therefore, this young Gu Immortal immediately stood up and shouted loudly: "You don't dare to show your skills, but you have quite the mouth! How can you estimate the skills of my tribe's Lord Qun Xing? You are not being proud, but are intentionally saying this because you are afraid!"

Chapter 1203: Shameless

"I don't know if you are afraid or not, but we can all see whether you dare or not." A Bai Zu tribe Gu Immortal sneered.

He had pure Bai Zu bloodline, behind him was Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, even Chu Du did not have a sway over him.

Fang Yuan lightly glanced at this person, the latter looked back without any fear.

Clearly, Fang Yuan stealing the eagle nests had caused the hatred with Bai Zu tribe to be big.

Fang Yuan swept his gaze around, the Gu Immortals all gazed back at him with doubts, curiosity, uncertainty, anticipation and so on. Especially, Xue Wu Hen who was beside him, his gaze was shining.

"Not fighting."

"What kind of person am I?"

"This weakling?"

"Hehe, not worthy of me making a move."

"In the future, when my biography is written, my first battle after seclusion is against Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, but the second battle is with this thing? There won't be any splendor even if I win against such a minor character of Ye Lui tribe."

No matter how open-minded Ye Lui Qun Xing was, his tone unavoidably had become colder from anger: "Hmph, so much nonsense! You have said so much, come fight me if you have guts!"

"You don't have enough qualifications." Fang Yuan held his hands behind his back, head raised and chest out, as he looked at Ye Lui Qun Xing with unconcealed contempt.

Many Gu Immortals' eyes widened.

They really wanted to ask: Ye Lui Qun Xing actually doesn't have enough qualifications, then who has the qualifications? What qualifications do you have? I really don't understand where you are getting such confidence from!

You are clearly a demonic path lone cultivator, who knows where you came from. Ye Lui Qun Xing fighting you is giving you face, giving you the chance to perform and gain some glory.

But the person involved, Fang Yuan, clearly did not have such a thought.

The immortals began discussing, the situation had become noisy from the clamor.

They were all talking about Fang Yuan, but Fang Yuan turned a deaf ear to their words.

After a while, Gong Wan Ting's expression turned cold, lightly calling out: "Enough, do you all want to make the grand blood battle martial competition into a joke?"

The righteous path immortals immediately turned silent.

Gong Wan Ting then looked at Chu Du: "Could it be that your side only has troublemakers remaining? Stalling for so long will only make others ridicule you."

Facing the overbearing Gong Wan Ting, Chu Du did not reply, instead looking at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan ignored Chu Du's gaze and slightly turned towards the side, pointing backwards: "You."

"Me?" A former supreme elder of Hei tribe, currently a Bai Zu tribe Gu Immortal, was completely stumped, not having expected Fang Yuan to suddenly point towards him.

"Go take the fight, if he can win against you, it means he has some qualifications for me to make a move once." Fang Yuan's tone was still very arrogant, even his own side's Gu Immortals felt their teeth itch from hearing him.

The immortals' gazes turned towards this unlucky person.

This Gu Immortal immediately felt huge pressure.

His anger was boiling: "Who did I provoke to suddenly send me to battle? Moreover, why the hell are you commanding me? I am a Bai Zu tribe Gu Immortal, even Domination Immortal Chu Du can only discuss with me. How can you, a mere second supreme elder, command me?"

This Gu Immortal had decided to refuse.

But then he heard the discussions of other immortals.

For instance —

"Ye Lui Qun Xing is so strong, he has already defeated four people in a row. Now, letting this person fight, isn't it letting the enemy gain more battle achievements?"

"Hmph, this person is only a minor character, Ye Lui Qun Xing can easily beat two of this guy."

"He is a Hei tribe Gu Immortal, although his surname has changed to Bai Zu, can he really fight to the death with a Huang Jin bloodline Gu Immortal?"

Wow!

When these discussions resounded in this Gu Immortal's ears, he immediately realized that he had no choice but to go to battle.

He fiercely glared at Fang Yuan, unfortunately, Fang Yuan had already turned around, facing him with his back.

The Bai Zu tribe Gu Immortal was furious and aggrieved, but could only give in and fly to the stage.

There was nothing unusual about the battle.

This Gu Immortal was clearly weaker than Ye Lui Qun Xing. After exchanging ten or so moves, he lost.

"I hope Elder Liu Guan Yi can fight now and enlighten us." This Bai Zu Gu Immortal carried his injuries back, and his first words were to sarcastically speak to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan snorted: "You are too weak."

The Bai Zu Gu Immortal suppressed his anger: "I am indeed too weak, elder should show his divine prowess."

Fang Yuan's following words almost made him flare up —

"Taking so long to fight with a weakling like you. I have to admit I had overestimated that Ye Lui Qun Xing. Now, I have no interest to battle with him at all."

"You!" The Bai Zu Gu Immortal was stifled to the point of being speechless.

The immortals' gaze towards Fang Yuan were also vaguely changing.

Xue Wu Hen's expression was even more blatant, he sized up Fang Yuan with intense suspicion.

"So it was like this. The so-called Chu Sect's second supreme elder is just a poser." Ye Lui Qun Xing scoffed, his scoff felt piercing to Chu Du's side's Gu Immortals.

"Lord Domination Immortal, have you ever seen him make a move?" Ye Lui Xiao Jin also added.

Chu Du was silent, he had sensed Fang Yuan's strange behavior but decided to wait and watch.

"Elder Liu Guan Yi, if you truly have skills, go kill him!" That Gu Immortal of Bai Zu tribe sneered.

Fang Yuan lightly shook his head, boasting shamelessly: "How can you comprehend my power? That's why you will never have the hope of becoming an expert like me."

Ye Lui Qun Xing flicked his sleeves and walked away. He knew Fang Yuan could not be forced to fight.

In truth, after fighting five people in a row, he was indeed feeling exhaustion. His immortal essence expenditure was still good, the main thing was that his mind had been taxed a lot.

Seeing him retrieve the star fragments and leave, many on Chu Du's side let out a sigh of relief.

Ye Lui Xiao Jin was also extremely happy, as he raised his head high and ran to the entrance of Golden Dawn Hall to welcome Ye Lui Qun Xing.

How could they have known Fang Yuan to speak: "Look, he is indeed afraid of me, even if I didn't enter the battle, he has been feeling frightened, now he is unable to maintain his cool any longer, having no choice but to leave."

Ye Lui Qun Xing's steps slightly paused.

Xue Wu Hen's eyes widened, as he gazed at Fang Yuan and thought: "There is actually such a shameless person in this world? It has really opened my eyes. Brother Chu actually gave this person the status of second supreme elder, perhaps his judgment has dulled."

Ye Lui Xiao Jin's mouth almost twisted from anger.

On the contrary, Ye Lui Hui Hong's expression slightly changed, he squinted his eyes and started looking at Fang Yuan.

Ye Lui Qun Xing shook his head, continuing to leave without even glancing at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan laughed loudly: "Ye Lui Qun Xing, f*ck your eighteen generations of ancestors!"

The whole scene was silent, before they suddenly burst into an uproar.

Where is your disposition? Where is it?

The Gu Immortals screamed internally.

Who could have thought the elegant looking Fang Yuan would swear out loud in public. Even if they were fighting for their lives, Gu Immortals always maintained their disposition, after all, they all praised themselves as being righteous. Cursing like this in front of everyone was really letting go of one's reputation.

"His good looks are wasted." A Gu Immortal gazed at Fang Yuan, shaking their head constantly.

No doubt, the favorable impression Fang Yuan gave to the immortals at first glance was already ruined.

Fang Yuan laughed sinisterly, suddenly walking to the battle stage: "Ye Lui whatever, I am here, didn't you want to fight with me?"

Ye Lui Qun Xing stopped and gazed back.

The atmosphere of the whole scene changed.

Inside Golden Dawn Hall, Ye Lui Hui Hong was sitting upright, his expression solemn: "Qun Xing, careful, this person is doing something underhanded. Come back."

Fang Yuan's earlier and later attitude made Ye Lui Hui Hong realize that something was fishy.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "Gutless rat, Ye Lui tribe is made up of cowards, you are a bunch of bastards..."

All kinds of derogatory terms were thrown out one after the other.

The immortals were stupefied as they listened.

Chu Du wanted to cover his face, Fang Yuan did not have even a bit of elegance, he was destroying the image of Chu Sect.

A piece of rat poop spoils an entire pot of soup!

It was the first time Chu Du reconsidered on his decision to draw in Fang Yuan, was it correct?

But no matter what anyone said, Fang Yuan's provocation was effective.

The righteous path was easier to deal with than demonic path and lone cultivators in certain aspects. Especially when the question was about reputation. When it involved the tribe and bloodline, even if one did not care on the inside and was willing to ignore the other's cursing, in front of the public, with so many outsiders watching fixedly, it became another situation.

The super forces which were held together by bloodline and blood relations protected and attached great importance to the reputations of their ancestors.

This was their basic moral philosophy!

"Qun Xing, come back. I will personally face the skills of this Chu Sect's second supreme elder." Ye Lui Hui Hong stood up.

Fang Yuan unavoidably felt disappointed inwardly, but laughed on the surface: "Ye Lui Qun Xing, it's time to scram."

Ye Lui Qun Xing waved his hand at Ye Lui Hui Hong, smiling at Fang Yuan, revealing his white teeth: "Since it is so hard to find a chance for you to fight, how can I avoid the battle and escape? It is just that I have fought hard for five battles, and need to rest for a while."

Such a request was completely fair.

Fang Yuan smiled, this Ye Lui Qun Xing could still be so cool-headed. But he also did not expect these words to be able to make these Gu Immortals lose their rationality from anger.

In truth, his pestering had already reached his target.

So, Fang Yuan immediately allowed: "Rest as much as you want, I will give you two or three days. If two or three days are not enough, then take two or three years, hahaha!"

"Hehe, an hour is enough." Ye Lui Qun Xing smiled with clenched teeth.

Fang Yuan was really detestable, Ye Lui Qun Xing was naturally very angry.

But he was also very aware of his own situation.

His immortal essence expenditure was not much and he still had a lot of reserves left. Resting for an hour was mainly to restore his mental energy. He had his own methods for this, and after an hour, he could completely recover to his peak state!

At that time, he will let this Liu Guan Yi taste his power!

This hour of time appeared somewhat unbearable as the Gu Immortals waited.

Finally, Ye Lui Qun Xing recovered and walked to the stage, standing opposite Fang Yuan.

"Liu Guan Yi, I..." Ye Lui Qun Xing was just about to speak when Fang Yuan's body suddenly erupted with dazzling silver light.

At the next instance, a silver colored ancient sword dragon shot out of the light.

It had a sharp dragon horn, its mouth was opened wide, revealing it to be densely filled with sharp fangs.

"So despicable!"

"He actually sneak attacked!!"

The righteous path's immortals scolded at once.

The ancient sword dragon had already neared Ye Lui Qun Xing.

Chapter 1204: How Could It Be Seen Through?!

Ye Lui Qun Xing had a great fright as he quickly retreated!

"This shameless guy!" He cursed inwardly, not having expected Fang Yuan's actions. Every time he felt that Fang Yuan was shameless, Fang Yuan's following actions would completely redefine shamelessness.

Fortunately, Ye Lui Qun Xing had been all the while and reacted in time.

One chased and the other escaped.

The distance between Fang Yuan and Ye Lui Qun Xing was rapidly shrinking.

The immortals held their breaths.

Ye Lui Xiao Jin also subconsciously stood up, looking at Ye Lui Qun Xing with worry.

Ye Lui Hui Hong, however, stood stably in his seat, he had a better understanding of Ye Lui Qun Xing's trump cards and did not think Ye Lui Qun Xing was in danger right now.

"So he cultivates ancient sword dragon transformation!" Chu Du thought.

"Ancient sword dragon, based on potential, it is still inferior to my heaven swallowing hound..." Immortal Wang had clenched teeth.

"He finally took action!" This was what many Gu Immortals were thinking.

"Go."

The retreating Ye Lui Qun Xing suddenly called out, pushing lightly towards the charging ancient sword dragon.

Immediately, his whole hand emitted brilliant blue light. A star fragment shot out from the blue light and collided against Fang Yuan with a speed like that of a meteor.

Fang Yuan roared towards the sky before suddenly moving, the whole ancient sword dragon made a beautiful arc in the air, as it nimbly moved past the incoming star fragment, almost brushing past it.

When the Gu Immortals saw this scene, despite having an extremely bad impression of Fang Yuan, many of them could not help but give praise internally, as they sensed Fang Yuan had already reached a proficient level at ancient sword dragon transformation.

Such control made Fang Yuan seem like he was an ancient sword dragon from the start of his life.

"Not good." Immortal Wang suddenly spoke.

Almost at the same time, Ye Lui Qun Xing saw Fang Yuan moving past this star fragment, and the corner of lips slightly raised up.

Ping.

A sharp sound echoed. Fang Yuan's dragon tail swung, directly smashing the star fragment he had brushed past.

The ancient sword dragon Fang Yuan had turned into had a more terrifying tail compared to its claws, its tail could directly smash dark inkstone, let alone this star fragment.

Such a response made even Chu Du pleasantly surprised.

He was happy inwardly: "The information path Gu worm I gave to Liu Guan Yi has records of all the battle scenes of Ye Lui Qun Xing. So Liu Guan Yi knows he absolutely cannot let Ye Lui Qun Xing have many star fragments under his control. The greater the number of star fragments he controls, the stronger he would become. Finally, it would form into an enormous advantage that managed to defeat five people in a row."

Ye Lui Qun Xing was slightly disappointed when he saw Fang Yuan responding in the wisest way, and quickly increased his retreating speed.

At the same time, he repeatedly clapped, layers of blue light covered his two hands, from which star fragments shot out one after the other.

At first, they were only thumb sized, but as they moved in the air, they returned to their original size and flew more rapidly, bringing in strong gusts of wind.

Boom boom boom.

Fang Yuan used his horn, claws as well as his body and tail to destroy all these star fragments.

He did not give Ye Lui Qun Xing any opportunity to accumulate power.

For a moment, star debris flew all around, turning into blue fragments like fog or sand, which scattered with the strong gale, creating a beautiful sight that was difficult to describe.

The silver scales of the ancient sword dragon also added to this beauty, as it moved along the star debris.

Chu Du slightly frowned.

Originally, Fang Yuan made a wise choice of smashing the star fragments, targeting the weakness of Ye Lui Qun Xing's immortal killer move. But also because of this, it led to a decrease in Fang Yuan's speed.

The distance between the two did not shrink much.

The advantage of the sneak attack before had already disappeared now.

Ye Lui Qun Xing had already stabilized himself.

He snorted, as he struck out with his hands rapidly, star fragments shot out everywhere, but not directly towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan fell into a difficult situation with two choices in front of him.

If he charged directly towards Ye Lui Qun Xing, the latter would retreat and he would not be able to forcibly close the distance, at the same time, the surrounding star fragments would keep on increasing, accumulating a great advantage for the latter.

If Fang Yuan dealt with these star fragments, he would have to keep on flying around, and would fall deeper into Ye Lui Qun Xing's scheme, giving the latter the initiative to more easily arrange the battle situation.

The ancient sword dragon slowed down its offense in its state of hesitation.

Sensing this, Chu Du's frown became deeper, while Ye Lui Hui Hong, inside Golden Dawn Hall, was starting to smile, taking a small sip of fine wine.

Despite Fang Yuan's hesitation not lasting for long, he had missed a good opportunity and there were now dozens of star fragments on the battlefield.

Ye Lui Qun Xing's advantage had started to accumulate.

Fang Yuan was surrounded by the star fragments, despite him not caring about his body, and engaging in even more crazed offenses, he was not able to break through the layers of encirclement.

Ye Lui Qun Xing relaxed, the star fragments continued to increase, not only surrounding Fang Yuan, some had also appeared beside him, orbiting around continuously.

"Liu Guan Yi, you acted arrogant and boasted shamelessly, it was to make me take back the star fragments so I would have to lay them out again."

"Your scheme was quite deep, almost letting others think you are wildly arrogant. Unfortunately, I am not the same person I was years ago."

"A few years ago, I already improved upon this weakness of my immortal killer move. It is indeed somewhat weak at the start, but your methods are not enough to restrain me."

"Now, what are you going to use to resolve this situation?"

A dragon's roar resounded, Fang Yuan moved his body, brandished his claws, and destroyed countless star fragments, star debris flew all around.

The dragon's might was powerful, its speed was especially astonishing.

Unfortunately, the spectating immortals sensed weakness within this strong momentum.

Fang Yuan was attacking wildly, but Ye Lui Qun Xing was far away, watching with arms folded in front of him, maneuvering the star fragments leisurely.

As time passed, there were more and more star fragments orbiting around Ye Lui Qun Xing.

"Liu Guan Yi has lost!" Immortal Wang spoke decisively at this sight.

Xue Wu Hen did not speak, inwardly thinking: "Based on strength, Elder Liu Guan Yi is indeed powerful, at the same level as Elder Hao Zhen and Elder Chou Lao Wu. But there is still a gap when compared to Ye Lui Qun Xing."

Chu Du was still frowning, the strength Fang Yuan displayed was not consistent with his expectations. But he still felt Fang Yuan had a trump card and was still confident in Fang Yuan, and until the end of the battle, he would choose to keep his expectations.

Ye Lui Xiao Jin laughed heartily at the entrance of Golden Dawn Hall, and shouted: "That Liu Guan or whatever, why are you not yelling now? Come on, continue boasting. Didn't you say my tribe's Lord Qun Xing could not compare to you? Didn't you say fighting him would lower your status? Why are you not speaking now? Only knowing how to yell, what do you want to vent out?"

The ancient sword dragon roared furiously, destroying the star fragments.

Sensing Fang Yuan's furious mood, Ye Lui Xiao Jin laughed again.

"Chu Sect's second supreme elder is only at this level."

"In all fairness, he does have some strength. Have you counted how many star fragments he has already destroyed?"

"But that is useless, Ye Lui Qun Xing's dominance is already increasing."

"Liu Guan Yi's hesitation earlier decided the battle. This was his only fault but it was perfectly used by Ye Lui Qun Xing."

"Thinking of it, it is also not strange. What is Chu Sect? How can they be on par with our great Huang Jin forces? Their second supreme elder has such battle strength, Chu Du cannot be considered to have made a bad judgment."

The righteous path Gu Immortals drank and rejoiced inside Golden Dawn Hall, the atmosphere was relaxed.

Ye Lui Hui Hong stroked his beard, the smile on his face had become brighter, but at the same time, he did not forget to speak and remind Ye Lui Qun Xing: "Be careful of his dragon breath. The ancient sword dragon's strongest weapon is its breath. Until now, he still hasn't breathed out once."

Ye Lui Qun Xing slightly nodded.

Even without Ye Lui Hui Hong's reminder, he had already been concerned about this.

Experts!

They were not decided with just strength, but also their mental state during battle.

No doubt, Ye Lui Qun Xing who had suffered numerous defeats, had an extremely good mentality. He was an expert that had gone through painstaking training, setbacks and defeats.

His foundation was extremely solid and stable.

However, Ye Lui Qun Xing did not retreat.

Right now, he was quite far away from Fang Yuan, almost at the opposite end of the battlefield.

Ye Lui Qun Xing looked at the star fragments orbiting around him, and thought: "I have a hundred star fragments protecting me. Even if Chu Du personally comes, I can resist for a while, let alone this Liu Guan Yi. Dong Fang Chang Fan, you might have passed away, but let me sustain the reputation of myriad star fireflies for you. After all, my immortal killer move had received your guidance."

Right as most of the Gu Immortals felt the battle was decided, there was a sudden change!

Sword escape Immortal Gu!

Suddenly, Fang Yuan activated rank seven sword escape Immortal Gu.

Right now, he had transformed into an ancient sword dragon, his transformation path dao marks had turned into sword path dao marks, adding on to his cultivation of sword eyebrows Immortal Gu, his sword path dao marks had already reached a number of ten thousand.

A thousand dao marks could double an Immortal Gu's power.

Ten thousand dao marks could add ten times the power!

Sword escape Immortal Gu was already an exceptional movement Gu worm among rank seven Immortal Gu. Now, ten times its power was added!

At the same time, the ancient sword dragon's own speed also had to be calculated.

Sword dragons did not have strong long range attacks, but their burst of speed from a stationary state was astonishing.

Ancient sword dragon, sword escape Immortal Gu and ten thousand sword path dao marks, when stacked together, allowed Fang Yuan to instantly disappear from his spot.

Before any immortals had reacted, he had already flown through the whole battlefield and appeared in front of Ye Lui Qun Xing!

At this moment, Ye Lui Qun Xing's expression was still paused on a strategic and victorious smile. But his pupils had shrunk to needle-sized, as he looked, with extreme fright, at a gigantic sword dragon head that filled his whole vision!

He only had one thought in his mind —

"Impossible! My star fragments' flying trajectories are extremely profound and takes reference from myriad star fireflies, how could he see through it?!"

This was Ye Lui Qun Xing's final thought in life.

Chapter 1205: Be Careful of Liu Guan Yi

Everything happened too quickly!

At the previous moment, the ancient sword dragon was still tightly surrounded by star fragments. It was charging here and there, roaring repeatedly but unable to do anything.

At the previous moment, Ye Lui Qun Xing was still at the other end of the battlefield, star fragments were orbiting around him like he was the lord of stars.

At the previous moment, almost all the Gu Immortals felt Ye Lui Qun Xing already had victory in his grasp and the battle was decided. Because they were very much familiar with the scene that was unfolding in front of them.

Before this, the five Gu Immortals Ye Lui Qun Xing had defeated in succession were all in this situation.

Although there was no study of 'subconscious bias' in this world, these Gu Immortals' thought processes were almost the same at this moment.

Then, at the next moment!

Fang Yuan suddenly used sword escape Immortal Gu, instantaneously bursting out with an extremely terrifying speed.

At the next moment, the ancient sword dragon had destroyed all the obstructing star fragments in its path, and arrived in front of Ye Lui Qun Xing.

He opened his mouth and breathed out.

Dragon breath!

While Ye Lui Qun Xing was still confident in his defensive methods, his whole head had instantly been sliced off.

The human body was weak and had many fatal areas. One the head was cut off, they would die. Even if they turned into an immortal zombie, their head was still a weak point.

Ye Lui Qun Xing immediately died!

Fang Yuan smoothly grabbed his body.

A portion of Ye Lui Qun Xing's soul was also cut and before it could escape from his physical body, Fang Yuan had already stored it inside his immortal aperture.

The whole process went extremely quickly.

Fang Yuan had already been plotting for a long time!

Activating Sword Escape, charging in, using his dragon breath and retrieving the corpse. The whole process involved four actions.

But even so, after Fang Yuan finished these four actions, his whole dragon body had already charged out of the battlefield, reaching several li away.

One could feel how terrifying his speed was!

If it were a human body, it might have already burst from the enormous pressure brought by such intense speed.

Fortunately, Fang Yuan had transformed into a dragon.

But even with this, Fang Yuan felt quite a bit of pressure when he had charged.

His vision had already turned blurry.

If he had human eyes, they would not have been able to keep up with such speed. But Fang Yuan's eyes were dragon eyes now, even so, it was difficult for his eyes to cope with this speed.

At this speed, even Fang Yuan felt like he could not sustain it.

"If I am to move with this speed, I must use all my energy and concentration in controlling my body."

"Otherwise, if there is any deviation in my direction, who knows whether I crash into peaks or the ground at the next moment."

"This speed is too fast, one moment I am still in the air, and the next moment I am already several li away!"

Fang Yuan thought in his mind.

He thought of when he had first gotten the sovereign immortal aperture and practiced colliding into Southern Border's mounds, besides knocking himself dizzy, the whole mound and even the veins underneath had been destroyed.

This speed was quite suitable for a momentary burst, but in truth, it was not highly practical during battle.

Once Fang Yuan used his fastest speed, he would have to use all his energy and concentration in controlling the ancient sword dragon body. As such, he could only perform some simple actions, or maybe rely on the transformed sword dragon body.

If so, it would be quite dangerous.

Because although Fang Yuan would have a sturdy and strong body in ancient sword dragon form, the sovereign immortal body's characteristic of non-conflicting dao marks would still exist.

"Ancient sword dragon transformation is a classic case of strong offense and weak defense, moreover, there is an extreme imbalance between its offense and defense."

"Fortunately, I actually succeeded this time and killed Ye Lui Qun Xing. My luck is pretty good!"

"First, I need to find a place to annex this immortal aperture before I think of anything else."

Fang Yuan did not return, directly flying away from Blood Plain.

The Gu Immortals of both sides watched his figure dazedly, until he disappeared into the horizon.

The immortals looked at the messy battlefield with countless star debris as well as many star fragments still flying in the air, only then did they come to a sudden realization!

"Liu Guan Yi, he killed Ye Lui Qun Xing!"

"Unbelievable! This is like a dream."

"Too fast, we simply cannot react to such speed."

Regardless of the righteous path or Chu Du's side, they were both clamoring in discussions. Gu Immortals did not transmit their voices secretly, but directly spoke out, as if they could only release the doubts in their hearts by speaking up.

Ye Lui Xiao Jin was standing, dumbfounded, at the entrance of Golden Dawn Hall, like a statue.

Just moments before Ye Lui Qun Xing was killed by Fang Yuan, he had still been shouting and mocking Fang Yuan.

Now, these words he spoke out, as well as his actions, seemed to be like slaps that struck his face repeatedly and resoundingly.

He was shaken and shocked, unable to believe this fact!

Ye Lui Hui Hong also stood from his seat, his hand was still holding a wine cup and his beard was wet from the spilling of the wine.

Just the moment before Fang Yuan killed Ye Lui Qun Xing, he had been sitting and moving the wine cup to his lips.

But after the matter occurred, Ye Lui Hui Hong subconsciously stood up from shock, not caring about the wine cup in his hand, letting the wine spill on his beard, neck and clothes.

Ye Lui Qun Xing was dead!

An expert of Ye Lui tribe, a famous Northern Plains Gu Immortal, Ye Lui Qun Xing was dead.

His death was so sudden that there had been no signs at all.

If Ye Lui Xiao Jin was said to be a future hope of Ye Lui tribe, then Ye Lui Qun Xing was a current pillar of the tribe.

But he had died.

His life had ended here!

This was an extremely heavy impact to Ye Lui Hui Hong and Ye Lui Xiao Jin!

And to the whole of Ye Lui tribe as well, this was an extremely big loss!

"Terrifying, too powerful."

"He is indeed the second supreme elder of Chu Sect, such astonishing battle strength."

"Chu Du really has an eye for talent, I had been looking down on Liu Guan Yi just before, my insight is still too superficial."

The Gu Immortals on Chu Du's side were all showing happy expressions.

Despite them not liking Fang Yuan, the battle achievement was displayed in front of them, Fang Yuan had resolved their difficult problem, Ye Lui Qun Xing, permanently.

From now, there would be no such person in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world!

"Amazing. Elder Liu put on a pretentious appearance to incite the other side, then during the battle, he lured the enemy into having a false sense of security step by step. He clearly has such strength, but he restrained himself until the last moment, when he dealt the fatal blow!" Xue Wu Hen heaved a long sigh.

He was thoroughly convinced.

Such a turn of events made him fully admire Fang Yuan.

"How laughable I was, I had still been thinking Elder Liu was nothing impressive. Sigh, if I was Elder Liu's enemy, I might have died without knowing how I died. I am still too inexperienced!"

"Everyone needs to pay attention, this Liu Guan Yi is extremely crafty, be vigilant when you encounter him in the future." Inside Golden Dawn Hall, Nu Er Gu spoke with a grave expression, breaking the long silence.

Right now, as they thought back to Fang Yuan's performance, they all felt Fang Yuan was extremely insidious and sly.

The arrogance before the battle and the weak display during the battle were just disguises so he could strike with the most fatal attack at the end.

He did not make a move carelessly, but when he moved, it shook everyone!

"Ping Zhi, if you run into this Liu Guan Yi alone in the future, it would be best for you to avoid him and retreat." Nian Er Yi Fang looked at his tribe's future hope, and spoke with worry.

Nian Er Ping Zhi nodded: "Yes! I understand. I am only a Sword Child right now, when I become a Swordmaster in the future and cultivate to rank seven, I will definitely have a proper fight with this Elder Liu Guan Yi."

The righteous path Gu Immortals spoke to each other.

"Ye Lui Qun Xing died a miserable death. The whole battle was in Liu Guan Yi's grasp, what we and Ye Lui Qun Xing felt and saw, was all just his facade."

"Sigh, who could have thought he had such strength."

"Elder Ye Lui Hui Hong, don't blame yourself. We will definitely take revenge for Ye Lui tribe in the coming battles!"

Ye Lui Hui Hong had already snapped back to awareness.

There was one thing he did not understand in his mind — how was Liu Guan Yi able to easily penetrate through the heavy lines of defense from Ye Lui Qun Xing's numerous star fragments!

He had sparred many times with Ye Lui Qun Xing and was very clear on how much power the defensive lines held.

This doubt was shrouding over Ye Lui Hui Hong's heart, like a heavy dark fog.

He took two large breaths, his face was still pale, but he forcibly calmed down because right now, he represented the whole of Ye Lui tribe.

If his performance was not good, the whole of Ye Lui tribe would be disgraced!

"Lady Gong Wan Ting." Ye Lui Hui Hong took a deep bow to the main seat, "My tribe's Ye Lui Qun Xing is of pure Huang Jin bloodline, sacrificing his life here is also a glory for him, he is a hero of our Huang Jin bloodline. But now, his corpse is still in his killer's hands, his soul also might still be alive. I sincerely request to come forward and recover Qun Xing's corpse and his soul."

"Of course." Gong Wan Ting softly agreed, her attitude was straightforward and clear.

According the rules set by both sides previously, they could exchange corpses.

But right now, Fang Yuan had already raced off to who knows where with Ye Lui Qun Xing's corpse. Even if the righteous path Gu Immortals wanted to chase him, they were too late.

Thus, Gong Wan Ting directly asked Chu Du.

Chu Du was also surprised at Fang Yuan's direct departure, and had already sent a letter to ask. Fang Yuan had such strength, Chu Du still needed to rely on him.

Just as Gong Wan Ting had asked, Chu Du had coincidentally received Fang Yuan's reply in his immortal aperture —

"I have great use for Ye Lui Qun Xing's corpse! Brother Chu, if you have no choice, just expel me from Chu Sect."

These were two simple sentences, but they expressed Fang Yuan's firm and unrelenting attitude.

Chu Du frowned, but spoke calmly to Gong Wan Ting: "Fairy, you can rest at ease, Ye Lui Qun Xing's corpse will definitely be guarded properly. I have already notified my sect's second supreme elder. But to exchange for the corpse, your side will have to pay a price."

"Everything can be discussed." Ye Lui Hui Hong immediately agreed, his stance was clear.

Chapter 1206: Becoming Rank Seven!

Fang Yuan had already thrown the matter of the blood battle martial competition to the back of his mind.

He absolutely would not let go of Ye Lui Qun Xing's immortal aperture. Even if he could not annex it right now, he could do so in the future.

As for the righteous path's demand for Ye Lui Qun Xing's corpse and soul, Fang Yuan thought about it and was willing to satisfy a portion of the request, regarding the body.

His focus was the immortal aperture, Ye Lui Qun Xing's soul also could not be transacted, he could soul search and obtain many of Ye Lui tribe's secrets. After the soul search, he could still hand over this Gu Immortal soul to Lang Ya Sect and earn sect contribution points.

"The urgent matter right now is to test whether I can annex this immortal aperture or not."

Fang Yuan flew rapidly.

He took twists and turns, guarding against heaven's will.

A few hours later, he arrived at Tai Qiu.

Tai Qiu was not too far away from Blood Plain.

If looked from Northern Plains' map, Blood Plain would be at the left side and Tai Qiu would be at the right side, the territory in between was Hei tribe's Iron Eagle blessed land.

Blood Plain, Iron Eagle blessed land and Tai Qiu, if these three were connected in two lines, they would form an irregular V shape.

Entering Tai Qiu, Fang Yuan changed his appearance and sneaked inside.

He was familiar with the route, and soon, he arrived at the super Gu formation he had arranged previously.

Through the super Gu formation, he arrived at Lang Ya blessed land.

"Fang Yuan has returned!" Sixth Hair immediately paid close attention to Fang Yuan's every move.

"Ever since he left after exchanging for dragon breath Immortal Gu, this is the first time he has returned. What did he use dragon breath Immortal Gu for?" Sixth Hair was constantly guessing.

He did not know that hours ago, Fang Yuan had used ancient sword dragon transformation to kill a rank seven Gu Immortal expert, Ye Lui Qun Xing.

This person was at the same level as Pi Shui Han and Unfettered Scholar.

Fang Yuan's strength was now already able to compare favorably to these characters.

Since the failure at Yi Tian Mountain, Shadow Sect was in an extremely disordered state, Sixth Hair might very well be the only survivor of Shadow Sect left in Northern Plains, his information gathering was much slower than before.

But the news of Fang Yuan killing Ye Lui Qun Xing could not be covered up. This news was too shocking and would soon spread throughout the whole of Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world, and even Central Continent's Gu Immortals would hear of it.

After all, Central Continent's ten great ancient sects were also paying attention to this blood battle martial competition.

"Eh? Fang Yuan is leaving again?" Sixth Hair was astonished.

The super Gu formation flashed again as Fang Yuan left.

Sixth Hair did not know what Fang Yuan was doing, coming and going in such a hurry. But he intuitively felt something amiss, and was somewhat panicked. He felt Fang Yuan was going to obtain enormous benefits at this time.

Fang Yuan's growth rate was increasing rapidly, and to Shadow Sect, this was very bad news.

Fang Yuan used Lang Ya blessed land to teleport.

He wanted to annex the immortal aperture, for that, he had to first place the aperture.

He could not place the immortal aperture in Blood Plain, the commotion would be huge and it would attract countless gazes, and that was not good for Fang Yuan.

"It was not easy to obtain this rank seven star path immortal aperture, I naturally want the process of annexing it to go without any mishaps!"

When Fang Yuan appeared in the other Gu formation outside, he was already very far away from Blood Plain.

He had already planned his actions, and had already chosen a location.

Exiting the teleportation Gu formation, he hid his tracks and flew rapidly, arriving above ordinary grassland not long later.

After inspecting and not finding anything wrong, Fang Yuan took out Ye Lui Qun Xing's corpse.

The pitiful fellow's head had already been sliced off entirely.

Fang Yuan used temporary measures to handle the headless corpse, ensuring the immortal aperture would still exist.

This method had its own history.

When Fang Yuan had seen Blazing Heaven Demoness' method of retrieving apertures, he had also inquired her for some research results of Old Immortal Kong Jue. Adding on to Fang Yuan's methods from his first life, he had created his own method in preserving an immortal aperture.

Ye Lui Qun Xing's soul was already taken out by Fang Yuan and sealed properly.

The situation was a little troublesome.

Ye Lui Qun Xing's soul had similarly suffered from his dragon breath and its injuries were not light. Fortunately, Fang Yuan had guts Gu.

Although this Gu worm was only a mortal Gu, it was created from a secluded domain of heaven and earth, and was among the best methods of soul strengthening in this world. Fang Yuan was the owner of Dang Hun mountain, thus he had large reserves of them with him.

After using many guts Gu, despite Ye Lui Qun Xing's soul being on the verge of dissipation, it was finally rescued.

Fang Yuan released the seal he laid out and threw the corpse onto the grassland.

The mighty Ye Lui Qun Xing, who had enjoyed boundless glory while alive, was treated so casually after dying. If Ye Lui tribe's Gu Immortals were to see this, they would definitely jump out in anger to stake their lives against Fang Yuan.

Several breaths later, there was turbulence in heaven and earth qi.

The immortal aperture began to land on the ground, causing a huge commotion.

Fortunately, Fang Yuan had Dog Shit Luck and was not as unlucky as before, when it seemed like he might even die from choking when drinking water.

Without any surprises, the immortal aperture's entrance opened in front of Fang Yuan.

Despite having the upper extreme heavenly eagle, he still took the chance to enter Qun Xing blessed land through the entrance.

Ye Lui Qun Xing's blessed land was rather peculiar.

The sky was a scene of darkness, but the ground below emitted dim blue light.

The moment Fang Yuan glanced, his mind shook.

He discovered, the ground of this blessed land was actually covered with countless star fragments. The large ones among these star fragments were as big as shells, while the small ones were the size of pebbles, and they gave a rustling sound when stepped on.

The blessed land seemed endless in size, its surface was vast and its terrain was level.

Fang Yuan wanted to fly, but felt a powerful magnetic force that firmly kept him to the ground.

The ground suddenly protruded up, then a basin sized star core floated in front of Fang Yuan.

This azure star core was like a dark blue crystal ball, it was this blessed land's land spirit.

It was bright and colorful, and was slowly revolving on its own axis, emitting all kinds of light rays, making Fang Yuan mentally associate them to the rays of light in those perfect diamonds back on Earth.

Amidst soundless communication, Fang Yuan learned about this blessed land's ownership condition.

To ordinary Gu Immortals, this condition was quite difficult.

Because the land spirit's request was to show the true, complete version of the immortal killer move, myriad star fireflies, to it.

While alive, Ye Lui Qun Xing had all along been pondering on myriad star fireflies. The immortal killer move he created also imitated myriad star fireflies heavily.

His obsession was about this.

After death, his obsession combined with the heavenly power in the immortal aperture, to form this land spirit.

"My luck is overflowing, it cannot be stopped, hahaha." Fang Yuan immediately took out the whole contents of myriad star fireflies and gave it to the land spirit.

He was the killer of Dong Fang Chang Fan and had searched Dong Fang Chang Fan's soul countless times, sometimes also torturing him. In the end, he had handed Dong Fang Chang Fan's soul to Lang Ya land spirit like it was rubbish, and exchanged it for sect contribution points.

After a while, Fang Yuan became this blessed land's master.

"Now is the most crucial moment. Let's see if I can annex this blessed land."

Fang Yuan rested for a while before beginning.

Immortal apertures could annex one another, and summarizing the experiences of predecessors, there were three main conditions for this.

First, annexing an immortal aperture required specific attainment level.

Second, a smaller immortal aperture could not engulf a bigger one.

Third, dead apertures could not be annexed.

Fang Yuan already satisfied two conditions for annexing Qun Xing blessed land. But there was still one condition left which was somewhat ambiguous.

A smaller immortal aperture could not engulf a bigger one. The question here was, what was small and what was big?

If it was cultivation level, rank six immortal apertures were small and rank seven immortal aperture were big, then Fang Yuan would not be able to annex this Qun Xing blessed land.

If it was based on the immortal aperture's foundation and so on, Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture absolutely surpassed Qun Xing blessed land, and could devour it.

Fang Yuan had already wanted to test this and verify it.

The regretful thing was that there were very few rank seven immortal apertures among the immortal apertures he knew of, and he was also unable to fulfill the attainment level conditions.

Until now, when Fang Yuan seized Qun Xing blessed land.

Fang Yuan had both skills and boldness, he began to test; with the land spirit's help, he began to annex Qun Xing blessed land.

The process was smooth beyond expectations.

He simply did not encounter any obstacles!

The test succeeded!

After annexing Qun Xing blessed land, not only did the sovereign immortal aperture have an enormous star fragment plain, more importantly, many of Fang Yuan's calamities and tribulations were passed, letting him officially ascend to rank seven from rank six.

Rank seven Gu Immortal!

"From this moment on, I am a rank seven Gu Immortal. I have finally become a rank seven..."

Fang Yuan was filled with emotions.

In the five hundred years of his first life, he had only been at rank six second heavenly tribulation level. Naturally, the current Fang Yuan knew that heaven's will had intentionally suppressed his cultivation level.

Heaven's will required an otherworldly demon as a tool to deal with Shadow Sect. Fang Yuan was chosen by heaven's will, naturally it carved and sculpted Fang Yuan to make him a qualified chess piece. At the least, his cultivation level could not be too high, if he was too strong, heaven's will would find it more difficult to control Fang Yuan. He also could not be too weak, otherwise, even with rebirth, he could not be of any use. Rank six was just right.

This was a long term plan of heaven's will!

But at present, because of all kinds of fortuitous encounters as well as his own efforts and perseverance, Fang Yuan had finally broken through heaven's will's restrictions and charged to rank seven.

Its significance was huge!

Rank six Gu Immortals were considered bottom tier, they were numerous.

Rank seven Gu Immortals were mid-tier, they were the elites among Gu Immortals and had high statuses.

Rank eights were rare, their every move could create a storm in a region.

Reaching this level, Fang Yuan had already become an elite among Gu Immortals, an expert. If a rank six saw him, they would have to detour around him. Even among rank seven Gu Immortals, Fang Yuan was only wary of Ye Lui Qun Xing, Unfettered Scholar, Nu Er Gu, such characters of this level.

Chu Du? Fang Yuan estimated he was still somewhat below him. Fortunately, Chu Du was currently his ally.

At this moment, the sovereign immortal aperture began to produce red date immortal essence.

Shortly, Fang Yuan would possess his own red date immortal essence.

At the same time, he could also merge his accumulated green grape immortal essence and turn them into red date immortal essence.

One hundred beads of green grape immortal essence could merge into a bead of red date immortal essence.

"I need to merge them!"

"If green grape immortal essence was used to activate rank seven Immortal Gu, there would be at least thirty percent additional expenditure. After merging them into red date immortal essence, there won't be any meaningless loss in this aspect."

"Once some time passes, I will have reserves of red date immortal essence and will no longer have to fear battles of attrition. The difficult situation when Heavenly Lord Bai Zu attacked Hei Fan grotto-heaven will be completely behind me!"

Chapter 1207: Doing Something Bad

"Hah!" Hao Zhen flew to the sky and spat out a thunderbolt.

This thunderbolt shrunk into a ball, with the color of lapis lazuli, and charged towards Hao Zhen's opponent with a speed that seemed to be slow but was actually fast.

His opponent was a Gu Immortal of Murong tribe who had a burly stature, with muscles that were like layers of rocks, he had a wide nose bridge, large chin, and small forehead, making his head look like a triangle.

Seeing the thunderbolt approach him, he actually did not dodge and let the thunderbolt land on his body.

Boom.

The thunderbolt exploded, lightning splashed out everywhere, dazzling the spectating immortals' eyes for a moment.

After the lightning dissipated, the Murong tribe Gu Immortal was standing on the same spot without even budging.

There was a patch of burnt color on his chest from which white smoke was still rising.

But, the effect was only that.

"This is your strongest attack? Hmm, you have burned some of my hair, it is a little more powerful than before." This Murong tribe Gu Immortal spoke in a tranquil tone without a hint of frustration.

"You!" Hao Zhen's eyes seemed to spout fire from anger, but he was not able to retort.

His strongest killer move had no effect on this opponent.

"Wonderful!"

"He is indeed the Gu Immortal famous for his defense in Northern Plains."

"Murong Gang... this guy has not attacked at all and is only taking the beating passively. Elder Hao Zhen's offense actually could not show any results."

Both sides' Gu Immortals exclaimed in surprise.

Fang Yuan killing Ye Lui Qun Xing had been an extremely heavy blow to the righteous path.

To turn the tide of the situation and raise morale, Gong Wan Ting immediately took measures to make Murong tribe's strongest expert among their current group take action.

It was this burly man who seemed to be forged from steel — Murong Gang!

Chu Du was frowning again.

He sighed internally: "Just now, Ye Lui Qun Xing was killed, now there is Murong Gang. These Huang Jin tribes are indeed the overlords who have ruled Northern Plains for so many years, their accumulation is truly powerful."

At this moment, Hao Zhen admitted his defeat and returned with a pale expression: "I am ashamed, I could not live up to your expectations."

Chu Du consoled him with a few words.

Fang Yuan had not left for long, and he had fallen into the same awkward situation like before.

He looked at the immortals behind him, but found he had no capable people to send.

"In my opinion, the strongest person among us is you, supreme elder. But, you cannot easily take the stage, I think you need to call back Elder Liu." Immortal Wang suggested.

His suggestion was immediately approved by many Gu Immortals.

"Right, Elder Liu's strength is unfathomable, he can kill Murong Gang!"

"Elder Liu killed Ye Lui Qun Xing easily, killing Murong Gang won't be a problem for him."

"Elder Liu's ancient sword dragon breath is too powerful."

Even Murong Gang spoke: "Domination Immortal, don't send other minor characters. Besides you, the only one who can enter my, Murong Gang's, eyes, is Liu Guan Yi. Bring him out, I would like to experience the power of his dragon breath."

"Damn it! He is actually looking down on us." Chou Lao Wu was furious.

Hao Zhen clenched his fists: "If it were two on two, we could use wind thunder roar and wipe them out!"

After seeing Fang Yuan's power, Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu had no more dissatisfaction towards their position of third and fourth supreme elders.

Hao Zhen was only saying this to retain some face.

Actually, he was aware that his and Chou Lao Wu's wind thunder roar was powerful, but it was not easy to use it and it required a safe environment.

Like before, when Heavenly Lord Bai Zu attacked Hei Fan grotto-heaven, they were able to use wind thunder roar because they were protected by other Gu Immortals.

Everyone was anticipating Fang Yuan's reappearance.

Chu Du's side hoped Fang Yuan could raise their might again.

The righteous path's side hoped they could kill Fang Yuan. Avenging Ye Lui tribe was secondary, the main thing was that they wanted to kill this person to salvage their face!

Chu Du naturally also hoped Fang Yuan would take the stage again.

But Fang Yuan had not given any reply.

Chu Du could only smile bitterly at this, and could do nothing about it.

His and Fang Yuan's relationship was of mutual benefits and they held equal status.

Lang Ya blessed land, inside a secret room in a cloud city.

Fang Yuan was sitting cross-legged on a prayer mat, his divine sense entering his immortal aperture.

He was merging green grape immortal essence and refining them into red date immortal essence.

This merging method was widely popular and was not anything new.

Countless mortal Gu was moving on their specific trajectories, some were standing still, some emitted light, while some flew continuously.

Under the effect of these Gu worms, beads of green grape immortal essence were slowly but surely merging together.

Tens of thousands of green grape immortal essence were piled in this enormous mortal Gu formation.

With Fang Yuan's continuous effort, there were already two beads of red date immortal essence produced at the bottom of the green grape immortal essence.

"Hmm? Chu Du sent a letter again, it is still that Murong Gang... this is already the sixth letter." Fang Yuan's attention slightly diverted.

Shortly afterwards, he threw this information path mortal Gu aside, having no interest to even reply.

What blood battle martial competition, I don't give a f*ck!

Screw off.

In any case, Fang Yuan's agreement with Chu Sect was extremely loose. Besides some fundamental interests and principles, even if he suddenly did not want to do a task, or his interest waned, or he betrayed the sect, or he voluntarily left Chu Sect, he would receive no backlash.

What was the nature of this blood battle martial competition?

Fang Yuan knew it was a political compromise.

This was a stage which Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and Yao Huang, two rank eights, had discussed and created. It was to restrict the scope of the conflict between one another. The basic purpose was to ensure both sides' interests did not suffer loss beyond their bottom-line.

Yao Huang knew clearly that since Bai Zu tribe was already established, it could not be destroyed. At least, he alone was not able to do it.

Because on the opposing side was a rank eight Gu Immortal, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu. As long as he existed, Bai Zu tribe was as stable as a rock.

Unless Longevity Heaven sent a powerful reinforcement, for example, a rank eight Gu Immortal.

When he received the Longevity Edict, he was already reluctant. All he needed was to provide an explanation to deal with Longevity Heaven.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu did not want to provoke trouble, he had just created his tribe and wanted everything to move smoothly. However, the situation did not permit it. He could only swallow the bitter pill and face the Huang Jin tribes' allied offense.

Just this competition would do. They would not truly fight to the death!

Chu Du had seen through these two sides' thoughts, and because he was coincidentally squeezed in between, he took a huge step forward and established Chu Sect, using Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's might to test the response of Northern Plains' righteous path. If it was accepted, he could expand Chu Sect, if it was not accepted, he would disband Chu Sect. The losses wouldn't be huge and were of no concern.

From Longevity Heaven's standpoint, they naturally did not like seeing other bloodlines mixing in among the righteous path. All along, Northern Plains had been the world of the Huang Jin tribes. They were even more unwilling to see Chu Sect's existence! The master-disciple relationship, compared to the bloodline system, were two different ideologies. Systems based on either one were always sensitive and on guard against the other.

Longevity Heaven's Gu Immortals were clear that once the master-disciple system was spread, it would greatly shake their tribal forces and benefits.

Central Continent was a clear example and the best evidence of this.

"But Longevity Heaven is dreaming if they want to rely on just the Longevity Edict to destroy the alliance between Chu Sect and Bai Zu tribe."

"Unless they become more resolute and send out rank eight experts to kill Heavenly Lord Bai Zu!"

"This world is all about strength."

"Hei tribe did not have a rank eight Gu Immortal to suppress the situation and had also lost their Immortal Gu House, with just some excuses, their fellow Huang Jin tribe members destroyed them."

"Bai Zu tribe is an outsider and not of Huang Jin bloodline, but there is Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, making it a completely different situation."

"Strength... strength..."

Fang Yuan's thoughts lingered over this word.

Rank seven cultivation level.

This was an accomplishment, but to him, it was only another starting point.

"The blood battle martial competition does not match my interests."

"I have the sovereign immortal aperture and can annex other immortal apertures, skipping calamities and tribulations to raise my cultivation and strength. This is a shortcut for cultivation, filled with slaughter and blood. But... I like it."

"I want chaos, the more chaos, the better!"

"But the five regions chaotic war is still over four hundred years later! It is too far away, I can't wait that long."

"I need to think of a way to make them fight. The blood battle martial competition is too gentle, how many can be killed? If there are no deaths, there won't be blessed lands."

"There is also Lang Ya Sect and the four races alliance, hehe, if I let Northern Plains' human Gu Immortals know of them, what will their response be? Regretfully, I am bound by alliance agreements. Although there is 'Do Not Care', it cannot resolve the underlying problem!"

Fang Yuan's only worry was that the world wouldn't be chaotic, sinister and dangerous thoughts started to rise up in his mind.

He did not intend to go to Blood Plain.

The sect's enthusiastic anticipation and the enemy's provocation, what value did they have?

Fang Yuan had to spend all his effort to kill Ye Lui Qun Xing. If his actions had slightly slowed, he would have lost the opportunity. Would those three Immortal Gu Houses just stay there like decorations?

Especially that Murong Gang, he was a tough foe, it would not be easy for Fang Yuan to defeat him, let alone kill him.

Since the start of the battle, Chu Du's side had lost many times, while the righteous path had not even lost one-third of the time.

Hehe, there definitely would be some internal conflicts of the sect involved in this.

This was a trick righteous path Gu Immortals liked to play.

Fang Yuan had first thought of going to Southern Border.

Over these last days, he had adjusted his cultivation plan, using almost all his time and energy in refining dream path mortal Gu.

It was all preparation for that giant dream realm in Southern Border.

But he thought and thought, and felt the opportunity at this blood battle martial competition was truly too rare.

Adding on that on Southern Border's end, it was occupied by the righteous path whom had arranged a super Gu formation to tightly defend the giant dream realm, Fang Yuan felt it would be very difficult for him to meddle in and did not have any opening currently.

Thus, after Fang Yuan refined all the green grape immortal essence into red date immortal essence, he quietly left Lang Ya blessed land and arrived at Liu tribe's territory.

He was going to do something bad.

Chapter 1208: With the Murder Weapon in Hand, Killing Intent Surges

Northern Plains, Bone Burial Field.

This was a place filled with white bones, countless piles of skeletons were together.

There were some huge skeletons resembling hills, and also small skeletons unassumingly situated by the side.

Most skeletons were pale white in color, under the corrosion of nature in the sun and wind, their flesh had already decomposed, only these strong and tough bones of the desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts remained.

But there were also some bones with special colors. Some were yellow and shining brightly, some were purple and alluring, emitting poisonous gas.

Gu Immortal Liu Yong was paying close attention.

He had the Huang Jin bloodline, he was a rank six enslavement path Gu Immortal of Liu tribe.

Right now, he was manipulating six desolate beast bone armor hounds as he traveled in Bone Burial Field, searching for his target.

The formation of Bone Burial Field had several possible rumored origins.

Some said that during the Olden Antiquity Era, two enslavement path great experts engaged in a life and death battle here, resulting in the deaths of many desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts.

Some said that this was a graveyard of bone monsters. Countless bone monsters felt that their lifespans were ending, so they came here and buried themselves.

Some even speculated that this was a Gu refinement ground created by a refinement path great grandmaster during ancient times, after countless years had passed, it reached this present state.

But no matter what, Bone Burial Field contained large numbers of desolate beast and ancient desolate beast corpses.

Liu tribe controlled this place and developed it wholeheartedly, trying to turn this into a production base for bone path Gu worms.

And every year, Liu Yong would borrow the use of this place, to pick suitable bones for his bone armor hounds and replenish their bone armor.

"This white bone seems like a snake bone, it is soft and cannot be used. If it is eaten, the bone armor would be soft and have no defensive properties."

"This is a poison Gu, bone armor hounds do not have high resistance against poison, they will die if they eat this."

"This bone is not bad, it seems to be a desolate beast steel skin giant lizard's bone. Even though it is not the hardest, it is good enough, especially when it can endure heavy weight."

Liu Yong inspected for a moment, discovering more and more loot.

Eventually, he placed his beloved hounds, the six bone armor hounds, at six different locations.

He himself was lying down on a huge skull, looking at the sky.

"Today has good weather, it is sunny with gentle breeze." He looked at the blue sky, there were no clouds anywhere, and the sunlight was not intense, wind blew on his face mildly, he felt very comfortable.

Looking at the empty sky, Liu Yong felt really bored.

"Hmm? The tribe has sent an information Gu here?" Suddenly, his brows rose as his eyes shone with light, he sensed that something interesting was coming.

His mind quickly entered his immortal aperture, as his consciousness entered the information path Gu worm.

The contents of the Gu worm spoke about the advancements and developments that Liu tribe had made in the last few months.

Next were some rumors, and the actions of experts recently.

Finally, the most important point, it talked about the developments of the blood battle martial competition.

"Murong Gang defeated eight people in a row, impressive!"

"However, between every battle, he has to recover for two hours. He is unlike Ye Lui Qun Xing, he could fight consecutively."

"I heard that Murong Gang has strong defensive methods, but his immortal essence expenditure is huge as well!"

"Sigh, speaking of Ye Lui Qun Xing, it was really a pity. He was actually killed by Chu Sect's second supreme elder in a sneak attack, that was really despicable!"

Liu tribe was a Huang Jin tribe, a righteous path force, when spreading the information, they naturally placed it from their own perspective for their political benefit.

Even though the information was not wrong, the way it was written would give others a different feeling when reading it.

For example, 'losing repeatedly' and 'fighting on despite repeated setbacks', between the two phrases, they would provide different impressions.

All in all, it talked about how strong Fang Yuan was, and the facts about his ancient sword dragon transformation, the information also emphasized on how shameless he was, and how devious and scheming he acted.

The 'Liu Guan Yi' identity that Fang Yuan was using had definitely became (in)famous after this battle, nobody in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world did not know of him, even Prince Feng Xian and Heavenly Lord Bai Zu learned of him, even in the other regions, like Central Continent, they heard about Liu Guan Yi.

After expressing his anger and disdain towards Fang Yuan, Liu Yong thought about himself, sighing.

"I cultivate enslavement path, I am not suited to one-on-one fights."

"When can I gain such fame at the blood battle martial competition too?"

"Maybe one day, I can defeat Liu Guan Yi and challenge Domination Immortal Chu Du! Wouldn't that be really cool!"

Liu Yong was thinking about this when suddenly, there was a huge explosion.

Rumble!

The entire ground was shaking intensely.

"What, what is going on?!" The giant skull below Liu Yong had fallen off the neck of the skeleton due to the tremors.

Liu Yong quickly got up as he floated in the air, staring widely in bewilderment: "This defensive Gu formation is being attacked, someone is attacking here? This is the territory of my Liu tribe!"

Thinking of this, Liu Yong felt that it was unimaginable.

My Liu tribe is a great righteous path force, a Huang Jin tribe, we are a domineering force in the whole of Northern Plains.

Especially recently, their long-time enemy, Hei tribe, was gone, and Chu Du was also being targeted, the future looked promising and they were currently in high spirits, someone was actually attacking Liu tribe's territory now?

Who gave them the guts?

Their dog guts were truly rivalling heaven!

Liu Yong was furious, and also slightly glad: "Thankfully, I came here to pick up bones and feed my bone armor hounds, heh, the attacker is really unlucky to have encountered me... eh?!"

At the next moment, Liu Yong saw the invader.

Or rather, a dragon.

An ancient sword dragon!

It had pale white eyes, a sharp horn that extended to the sky, its scales were shiny and thick, its claws were sharp and powerful, it had a muscular tail, and its teeth gave off a chilly feeling, Liu Yong shuddered upon seeing it.

"Oh? It seems that a member of Liu tribe is here, my luck is pretty good." The ancient sword dragon spoke human words, as its dragon eyes emitted strong killing intent.

"Liu, Liu Guan Yi?!" Liu Yong was stunned.

At this moment, he wanted to cry.

His heart was pounding intensely, his body was uncontrollably shaking as Liu Yong screamed internally to himself: "Stay calm, quickly calm down, Liu Yong! You can do it."

Another voice in his head was resounding: "Calm down my ass, he is Liu Guan Yi, even Ye Lui Qun Xing died at his hands. He is scheming and shameless, unscrupulous and shrewd, I am just a tiny rank six Gu Immortal."

"Calm down, calm down! Right, right! Liu Guan Yi is the second supreme elder of Chu Sect, isn't Chu Sect a righteous path force? Then Liu Guan Yi is a righteous path Gu Immortal! As a righteous path member, how can he attack us for no reason? Attacking us for wealth, that is a demonic path act." Liu Guan Yi calmly analyzed.

At the same time, another voice screamed in his head: "Then tell me, why is Liu Guan Yi not participating in the blood battle martial competition, but here instead? He destroyed our Liu tribe's defensive Gu formation, his evil intentions are apparent! What else could he want?!"

Even though Liu Yong's name had 'courage'[1] in it, at this moment, he was completely gutless, he stammered as his tongue was shivering: "Liu, Lord Liu, why are you here at my, my Liu tribe..."

"Of course it is to..." Fang Yuan purposely dragged his words out.

"Is, is to what?" Liu Yong asked.

Fang Yuan's reply was not in words, it was his dragon breath.

This was the ancient sword dragon's breath, having the rank seven dragon breath Immortal Gu in it, the speed was fast like a flash of white light!

Liu Yong's upper body blew up.

Fresh blood spewed out, scattering on the pale white bones, detailing the sadness and pathetic state of a weakling.

The two halves of his body landed on the ground, his expression before death was still frozen on his face, his eyes were staring wide open.

"Useless fellow. But it is not strange... all of the Huang Jin tribes have been in power for too long, there is unavoidably some rot on the inside. Just like the ten great ancient sects." Fang Yuan analyzed internally.

The bigger the tree, the more leaves it would have, and unavoidably, it would have some rotten wilting leaves as well.

Woof woof woof!

The six bone armor hounds barked at Fang Yuan angrily.

Their owner was dead, but they still feel attached to him, they all ran over, guarding their master's corpse, defending it loyally, as if hoping that it would revive.

Seeing this, Fang Yuan's evaluation of Liu Yong rose by a bit: "It seems that he is passable in raising desolate beasts, unfortunately, they do not have the wisdom of Gu Immortals, what can these six beasts do?"

Fang Yuan sneered as he flew down.

This battle had no unexpected surprises.

An hour later, six fainted bone armor hounds were lying in Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture.

These desolate beast hounds appeared at a good time, Fang Yuan was about to buy some desolate beast dogs and use their faeces to feed dog shit luck Immortal Gu.

There were also a vast amount of desolate beast and ancient desolate beast corpses, they had extremely high value.

Fang Yuan placed them in his sovereign immortal aperture, temporarily storing them somewhere.

And finally, Liu Yong's corpse, his immortal aperture was still hidden in his stomach, Fang Yuan sealed it for now.

This enslavement path immortal aperture was suited for Fang Yuan to annex.

And also, Liu Yong's soul.

After being hit by Fang Yuan's dragon breath, although extremely weak and at Fang Yuan's mercy, it was still alive.

Fang Yuan quickly thought of the reason: "This Liu Yong was an enslavement path Gu Immortal, enslavement and soul path are related, to manipulate desolate beasts, one must have a sufficiently strong soul foundation."

Fang Yuan quickly left the scene of the crime.

He moved very quickly.

Only a tattered defensive Gu formation was left, and the empty Bone Burial Field, as well as the upper body of Liu Yong.

"The next location, Liu tribe's jade light pit."

Fang Yuan licked his lips, showing excitement in his eyes.

He had just committed murder, but now he was not going to retreat, he was going to attempt another crime!

As the saying goes — With the murder weapon in hand, killing intent surges.

Fang Yuan was a rank seven Gu Immortal with ancient sword dragon transformation, his battle strength had risen immensely, he was starting to become somewhat unrestrained.

[1] 刘勇: the character 勇 means courage Back

Chapter 1209: Looting Another Place

Whoosh!

A figure flew in the sky, tearing across space as a shrill sound could be heard.

It was Fang Yuan.

Right now, he was still in the ancient sword dragon form, he was using sword escape Immortal Gu and flying rapidly.

This speed was terrifying!

Back then when he killed Ye Lui Qun Xing, almost none of the Gu Immortals managed to react.

Of course, his burst of speed at that time was shocking! But now, Fang Yuan was traveling a long journey, his speed was lower now, compared to his peak burst of speed.

Even so, he was very fast.

"My speed is top tier even in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world. Of course, I cannot compare to Hui Feng Zi. Chu Du's body strength travel is far below me now."

Hui Feng Zi was most skilled in speed, he was known as the fastest person in Northern Plains. Disregarding any hidden cultivators, Hui Feng Zi was truly worthy of this. Because there was once a rank eight Gu Immortal who chased him but failed to capture him.

Fang Yuan was still far inferior compared to him.

This was the case for both straight distance travel and nimbleness.

But Chu Du's body strength travel had indeed been faster than Fang Yuan's sword escape Immortal Gu in terms of straight distance travel.

Now, Fang Yuan turned into the ancient sword dragon, his original flying speed with his dao mark amplification caused Fang Yuan's speed to surpass Chu Du.

Not to mention that Chu Du's immortal killer move, body strength travel, had a major flaw, it could only fly straight, it could not turn and had low nimbleness.

"If compared to rank eight Gu Immortals, how would I fare?" Fang Yuan had a question in his mind.

Immediately, he shook his head.

Rank eight Gu Immortals were all unfathomable, if they wanted to pursue Fang Yuan, he would be in danger. His initial burst of speed might surpass them and pull some distance, but in a long distance chase, he would definitely become slower.

And pursuing methods were not just about speed. Rank eight Gu Immortals had a wide variety of methods, they could do other things like Gu formations, teleportation, long range attacks and others.

"I have just destroyed Liu tribe's Bone Burial Field, and even killed an enslavement path Gu Immortal of Liu tribe, Liu Yong. When he was alive, he had already informed his tribe, as a super force, Liu tribe will definitely send Gu Immortals to pursue me."

"However, Liu tribe's available fighters are all at the blood battle martial competition. The remaining Gu Immortals are at the resource points, or have missions to attend to, it is not easy to send people out, especially people who are able to deal with the expert Liu Guan Yi, time is needed."

"After they get to Bone Burial Field, they will still need some time to chase me. They would not think that instead of retreating, I actually went to the southeast direction and plan to rob the jade light pit next. In this case, these Liu tribe pursuers might waste even more time."

"With all this wasted time, I can definitely devour the whole of jade light pit."

Fang Yuan had been collecting information about the outside world while he was cultivating.

Liu tribe was big and eye-catching, a lot of their resource points in the outside world were known to all. Sometimes, in order to display their own strength and foundation, Liu tribe's Gu Immortals would expose intel about these places themselves. For example, the Bone Burial Field's production of mortal Gu, and how many profits they derived.

Fang Yuan had been very interested in Liu tribe's jade light pit.

Because of attitude Gu.

To feed attitude Gu, he needed a vast number of flowing light fruits.

The higher the rank of the Immortal Gu, the longer the interval of feeding, and the greater amount eaten each time.

Fang Yuan had already bought a lot of flowing light fruits in treasure yellow heaven earlier, he had planted them in sovereign blessed land, using fruits to bring about more fruits.

Right now, he needed huge amounts of dazzling light Gu between his flowing light fruits to increase the amount of light. With intense light, brand new flowing light fruits would form.

This method was not only efficient, it was simple and easy for Fang Yuan to control.

And inside the jade light pit, there were all sorts of light Gu. For example, jade light Gu, reflect light Gu, borrow light Gu, return light Gu, all sorts of colored light Gu, like blue light Gu, red light Gu, black light Gu, and others. Dazzling light Gu was one of them.

Fang Yuan raced against time, right now, they were already alerted, his time was very precious.

"There is a cloud layer in front." Joy flashed across the ancient sword dragon's eyes.

At this time, he was already near the jade light pit, a huge cloud layer was able to conceal Fang Yuan's traces.

"I am quite lucky, to think there was a cloud layer here. If the Liu tribe Gu Immortal defending the jade light pit is careless, I might even be able to sneak attack!"

Fang Yuan carried anticipation as he rushed into the cloud layer.

The thickness of the cloud layer completely concealed the ancient sword dragon's body.

But the truth was not as nice as Fang Yuan had hoped.

In the jade light pit, Liu tribe Gu Immortal Liu Luo felt something, she stared with wide opened eyes: "An enemy!"

This Liu Luo was nearly two hundred years old, but she had the body of a young child, her eyes were watery and bright, her petite body was so cute and delicate, people would want to protect her.

She was the Liu tribe Gu Immortal guarding the jade light pit, she was very alert now.

All because of Liu Yong's report, all of Liu tribe's Gu Immortals were notified, they were all on guard.

The jade light pit's defensive Gu formation did not have any Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan's transformation, the ancient sword dragon, easily tore the defense and got in.

"It is Liu Guan Yi indeed, he did not escape, he is here to attack my jade light pit!" Seeing the ruthless ancient sword dragon, Liu Luo was furious and shocked.

"I cannot escape, my speed is not as fast as the ancient sword dragon."

"Thankfully I planted many seeds here! I can only persevere and wait for reinforcements."

"Brother, save me quickly..."

Liu Luo quickly analyzed, at the same time, she muttered as the ground of the jade light pit tore open, dozens of vines resembling dragons or pythons drilled out.

Next, countless trees expanded like jade umbrellas, becoming larger and larger until a huge forest was formed!

Liu Luo hid herself in the forest and vanished.

"It seems that they are on guard." Fang Yuan took a glance and saw Liu Luo, before she vanished from his perception.

"Rank six wood path... but this forest was meticulously created, it is quite troublesome to deal with." Fang Yuan was strong, but this was a tough nut to crack.

Because this forest was an immortal battlefield killer move.

Liu Luo was a rank six Gu Immortal, but she had an immortal battlefield killer move, this was atypical.

But Fang Yuan felt no surprise.

From Liu Yong's soul, he obtained a lot of information. Liu tribe had Liu Chang and Liu Luo, these two siblings, because of their father's protection, both of them became Gu Immortals.

Liu Chang was a rank seven Gu Immortal, his battle strength was not lower than Ye Lui Qun Xing. But this time, to get rid of the mud monster group in Liu tribe's great mud pit, he could not spare any time outside.

Liu Chang had great battle strength and status, especially when Liu tribe had no rank eight Gu Immortals.

Liu Chang doted on his little sister Liu Luo since a young age, he even gave her lifespan Gu.

This wood path battlefield killer move was obtained by Liu Chang for Liu Luo to have a strong trump card defending her.

Fang Yuan thought about it, he did not deal with this forest, he charged straight for the Gu worms in the pit.

Countless Gu worms were taken by him, kept into his immortal aperture.

Liu Luo watched with much fear, gritting her teeth. This Liu Guan Yi was robbing her in her face, this proud female immortal felt extremely humiliated and angry.

"This Liu Guan Yi is truly too daring!"

"He dared to kill my Liu tribe's Gu Immortals and even steal our cultivation resources!"

"It is a pity I do not have enough strength, otherwise, I would make you pay the consequences."

Liu Luo hid inside the battlefield killer move and did not dare to show herself.

Even after Fang Yuan left, she did not reveal her traces.

Not long after, there was white light in the sky.

The light was painful to the eyes, it suppressed even the sun's radiance.

As the white light charged down, it formed into a male Gu Immortal.

He had a skinny body and a sharp face, he had bean-like eyes, and showed anxiety and rage on his face.

"Brother!" Liu Luo saw this person and immediately appeared between the trees, feeling elated.

"Sister, you are safe!! I was so worried about you!" The person who came was Liu Chang, he saw that Liu Luo was fine and calmed down, the anxiety on his face turned into joy.

Liu Luo was also overjoyed, but she was still very cautious: "Brother, let's match our secret code, before I let you in."

There was no issue, Liu Chang entered the battlefield killer move and the siblings hugged each other tightly upon meeting.

"Sister, you must have been shocked, right? Don't worry, brother is here."

"Brother, that Liu Guan Yi is so terrible, he took away all of the Gu worms inside the jade light pit, not a single one is left. I failed to defend them, the tribe is definitely going to punish me."

"No need to worry, no need to worry, with me here, I will protect you. Don't be afraid, cheer up, I will back you up no matter what." Liu Chang doted on his sister, even though she was actually nearly two hundred years old.

He touched Liu Luo's head as he consoled: "Brother will go kill this bad person and avenge you, sister."

In fact, he was sent by Liu tribe to capture Fang Yuan to begin with.

Liu Chang's battle strength was not inferior to Ye Lui Qun Xing's. He cultivated light path and was specialized in speed and movement, he could retreat or advance easily.

Between Gu Immortals, once one party had advantage in speed, they would gain initiative in the battle. Whether they fought or retreated, it would be up to them.

While the siblings interacted, more Liu tribe Gu Immortals arrived.

Just now, Fang Yuan killed Liu Yong and took Liu tribe's resources, the entire tribe was furious!

Not only did they send Liu Chang, they also sent two more Gu Immortals to assist him and ensure that they succeeded.

"My goodness, our tribe's jade light pit was completely robbed by Liu Guan Yi!"

"KIll him, we have to kill him, otherwise, our Liu tribe's anger will not be appeased!!"

The two new Gu Immortals who arrived screamed.

"Stop screaming, you are so loud, what if you scare my sister?" Liu Chang raised his head and yelled back.

The two Liu tribe Gu Immortals knew about Liu Chang and quickly lowered their volume.

Among them, one used an investigative method and quickly found traces of Fang Yuan: "He escaped there, let's chase him!"

"You guys go first, I will escort my sister back." Liu Chang said.

The other two Gu Immortals were dazed: "To and fro, how long would you take? If we do not start chasing now, we will not catch up to him."

"Then what if we leave and Liu Guan Yi comes back and harms my sister? If anything happens to my sister, I will take it out on you both!" Liu Chang shouted loudly.

"Brother is the best." Liu Luo was joyous.

The two Liu tribe Gu Immortals looked at each other, they could see the bitterness in each other's faces.

Chapter 1210: Wanted by the Entire Righteous Path

"According to what Liu Yong said, if Liu tribe wants to capture me, they will send that Liu Chang. But he is a light path Gu Immortal, even if I kill him, I cannot annex his immortal aperture for the moment. Why would I take a risk then?"

Fang Yuan was still in his ancient sword dragon transformation as he flew towards the west.

As he flew, he searched Liu Yong's soul.

Right now, Fang Yuan was going to retreat.

If he continued, there would not be enough time, he did not need to fight with Liu tribe's Gu Immortals, if he did that, the risks were great with minimal benefits.

As he flew, Fang Yuan continued using sword escape Immortal Gu.

Undoubtedly, red date immortal essence was truly durable. If it were like before, would Fang Yuan with only green grape immortal essence dare to sustain such expenditure for so long?

But it was out of Fang Yuan's expectations that while he retreated, he did not see a single trace of Liu tribe's Gu Immortals.

He did not know that Liu Chang had delayed a lot of time in escorting his sister back, he could no longer make it. As for the other two Liu tribe Gu Immortals, they did pursue him, but they could not catch up.

After Fang Yuan entered Tai Qiu, these two Liu tribe Gu Immortals could only watch without entering.

Through the Gu formation, Fang Yuan returned to Lang Ya blessed land.

"Fang Yuan is back!" Sixth Hair immediately got news of it.

He had a complex feeling.

Because right now, he had already known that Fang Yuan had killed Ye Lui Qun Xing. Most importantly, Fang Yuan had used ancient sword dragon transformation, he used his own strength, instead of relying on the upper extreme heavenly eagle!

"How did his battle strength surge so quickly? And recently, he has been very busy, going in and out of this place, what is he trying to do?"

Sixth Hair was very uneasy.

Seeing Fang Yuan's busy schedule, he felt like he was looking at Fang Yuan's back, seeing him sprinting ahead rapidly.

Sixth Hair really wanted to trip Fang Yuan and halt his progression, but there was nothing he could do.

Whenever he thought of Fang Yuan's upper extreme heavenly eagle, he became dejected.

Rank eight battle strength!

Sixth Hair did not know the truth, he could only hope that Fang Yuan had few heavenly crystals and could not feed the upper extreme heavenly eagle.

"I hope this upper extreme heavenly eagle dies of hunger!" Sixth Hair could only hope for this.

"I have insufficient heavenly crystals indeed." Fang Yuan returned to his cloud city, after inspecting his immortal aperture, he sighed deeply.

Sixth Hair's hopes were not groundless.

Heavenly crystals were rank eight immortal materials, they were rarely sold in treasure yellow heaven.

In this aspect, Fang Yuan did not have enough heavenly crystals to begin with, the majority were obtained by trading resources with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu.

The upper extreme heavenly eagle had been growing all the while, his heavenly crystal storage was depleting.

"It doesn't matter, I will use my sect contribution points to exchange for a batch and use my immortal killer move on the upper extreme heavenly eagle to delay its growth."

Hei Fan's true inheritance could accelerate the upper extreme heavenly eagle's aging and cause it to mature rapidly, he naturally had a method to do the opposite.

However, Fang Yuan only spent some sect contribution points to exchange for heavenly crystals, he did not use any immortal killer move.

Fang Yuan was still not familiar with this killer move, he needed to practice it many times or the activation would fail. Not only would Fang Yuan be injured, the upper extreme heavenly eagle would be hurt as well. Secondly, this immortal killer move needed three days to activate, Fang Yuan did not have enough time.

Fang Yuan left after returning.

Using the super teleportation Gu formation, he went to another corner of Northern Plains.

Undoubtedly, Lang Ya land spirit's super Gu formation was simply too useful. Fang Yuan lost Fixed Immortal Travel, but using this super Gu formation, Fang Yuan could still enjoy the effects of Fixed Immortal Travel.

Choosing a location without anyone nearby, Fang Yuan tossed out Liu Yong's corpse.

Placing his immortal aperture, Fang Yuan went inside.

Liu Yong had a land spirit left behind, it was a black hound, the condition it had was: collect twenty desolate beast hounds for this blessed land.

Fang Yuan easily completed it.

A few days later, he successfully annexed this blessed land and the sovereign immortal aperture gained some new territory.

Speaking of which, Fang Yuan had annexed many immortal apertures recently.

The entire space in the sovereign immortal aperture had increased slightly.

But because the sovereign immortal aperture was just too large, the increase in size was not significant.

There was also another change, the land spirits.

Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture already had more than ten land spirits. There was a snake, star core, black hound, land spirits in all sorts of forms were scattered in different locations over the sovereign immortal aperture.

They all controlled an area and Fang Yuan provided them immortal essence and Gu worms.

A lot of the immortal essence was left behind by their main bodies before death, it was not Fang Yuan's own green grape immortal essence or red date immortal essence.

Other people's immortal essence was also known as foreign immortal essence, they had limited use.

The biggest use was to activate Immortal Gu Houses.

In the past, Fang Yuan obtained a huge amount of Giant Sun's immortal essence, he used almost all of it to activate Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage, and used it extensively in Yi Tian Mountain. Next, he used Change Soul and the remaining amount of Giant Sun's immortal essence went to Ying Wu Xie.

It was necessary to mention that Immortal Gu House had fixed abilities, but their strength depended on the immortal essence that was expended, they could either be stronger or weaker.

After absorbing Liu Yong's enslavement path blessed land, Fang Yuan realized that his count of calamities and tribulations had only moved forward by one!

"It seems that with rank seven cultivation level, annexing a rank six blessed land has negligible effects. The truly effective ones are rank seven immortal apertures!"

Fang Yuan realized this and his gaze turned pensive.

"It is slightly difficult."

In the five regions' Gu Immortal world, rank six Gu Immortals were the most commonly seen. Rank sevens were rarer, their quantity was far lower than rank sixes. And rank seven blessed lands could only be annexed by those with grandmaster attainment level in that path.

Fang Yuan only had five grandmaster attainment level paths. Among which, rank seven Gu Immortals who cultivated strength path, blood path, and wisdom path were few. Star path and transformation path were still available, but this way, Fang Yuan's options were far fewer, he could not annex rank seven blessed lands as casually as rank six ones.

But Fang Yuan had a solution for this problem.

He directed his gaze far away.

In the direction of Southern Border!

"How can I make my way in? Just familiar face alone, even though I can conceal myself, if I interact with them, I will be full of flaws, this is a headache."

Fang Yuan had no idea on what to do.

He did not leave Northern Plains urgently.

He was waiting to see everyone's responses.

Liu Guan Yi had an infamous reputation now, he suddenly assaulted Liu tribe and killed Liu Yong, he looted Bone Burial Field and the jade light pit, news quickly spread in the Northern Plains Gu Immortal world.

The righteous path forces were furious, Gong Wan Ting also changed her attitude after hearing this, she questioned Chu Du and blamed the Domination Immortal.

Over at Chu Sect, they were also surprised and shocked.

They held great anticipation towards Fang Yuan, but he ignored the blood battle martial competition and went to loot Liu tribe alone.

So daring!

So unrestricted in his actions!

Liu tribe was Chu Du's enemy, back then, it was because of Chu Du and Liu tribe's conflict that he gained great reputation and became known as the Domination Immortal.

But now, even though Liu tribe suffered a loss, Chu Du was unhappy.

"This Brother Liu is too uncontrollable!!" Chu Du's good feelings towards Fang Yuan vanished without a trace.

He did not want any Gu Immortal under him to do this.

Fang Yuan did this and broke all of the rules, he destroyed the tacit understanding between both sides.

Chu Du was quite angry.

Yao Huang and Heavenly Lord Bai Zu also felt the same.

Even Ye Lui Qun Xing's death could not cause any sorrow or concern in these two rank eight Gu Immortals. But after hearing news of Fang Yuan attacking Liu tribe, they frowned in unison.

"A piece of rat poop spoils an entire pot of soup!"

"Liu Guan Yi... is not a member of the righteous path."

The two rank eight Gu Immortals gave their verdict on Fang Yuan immediately.

Both sides had agreed to hold their bottom line during this conflict. It was like two kids fighting, they would agree beforehand that they could attack anywhere, except the face.

Fang Yuan did this, he not only slapped their face, the vile consequences were something that the righteous path Gu Immortals did not want to see.

Immediately, Chu Du declared: Liu Guan Yi's actions were purely his own, he was not asked to conduct them. To express his innocence, as well as Chu Sect's standpoint, Chu Du announced on the scene that Liu Guan Yi would be expelled from the sect, he would no longer be Chu Sect's second supreme elder.

"So resolute." Fang Yuan noted as he held Chu Du's letter Gu.

In the letter, Chu Du was very polite, he expressed his helplessness, the situation was very urgent at that time, he had to expel Liu Guan Yi immediately. He expressed that on the inside, he had wanted Fang Yuan to stay, and hoped that in the future, they could still cooperate.

Be it Fang Yuan's immortal tribulation tempering aperture or the Crazed Demon Agreement, Chu Du had reason to continue cooperating with Fang Yuan secretly.

But publicly, the two were enemies.

At the same time, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and Yao Huang sent orders denouncing Fang Yuan's demonic acts, they were putting up an arrest warrant for Fang Yuan, so that he would receive judgment.

This was how the righteous path worked, they did not want demons to wreak havoc.

The three sides immediately kicked Fang Yuan out.

Even though Fang Yuan's battle strength was something Chu Du needed.

Fang Yuan's plan of disrupting Northern Plains failed. Not just that, Liu Guan Yi was now wanted by everyone.

"Chu Du, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, Yao Huang, they are truly not easy to scheme against."

Fang Yuan smiled, he was unphased.

Not to mention Liu Guan Yi was just a randomly created false identity for himself, even if it was real, so what?

His main connections in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world were the variant humans.

At the same time, he was planning to go to Southern Border now.

Although Fang Yuan would still pay attention to the developments of Northern Plains, his focus was now shifting towards the giant dream realm.

"Southern Border, oh Southern Border, I am coming back."

"As a rank seven Gu Immortal..."

"Is this considered to be returning with glory?"

Fang Yuan had a complex smile on his face.

Chapter 1211: Stepping Into Southern Border

Wind was blowing around him.

The grassland below was rapidly moving in Fang Yuan's vision as he flew past it.

After more than ten days of traveling, the huge green regional wall appeared in front of Fang Yuan.

Suddenly, Fang Yuan's expression changed.

He sensed that dark limit Immortal Gu's power was rapidly weakening.

"Someone is deducing about me again!" Fang Yuan realized.

He quickly used dark limit Immortal Gu, resisting the deduction's power.

Fang Yuan had already encountered this problem many times. Recently, Fang Yuan killed Ye Lui Qun Xing and plundered two resource points of Liu tribe, not only did he empty them out, he even killed a rank six enslavement path Gu Immortal, Liu Yong.

Thus, while Fang Yuan was leaving Northern Plains, he encountered many deductions about himself, the frequency was much higher than before.

Thankfully, Fang Yuan had wisdom path grandmaster attainment level, and also dark limit Immortal Gu to defend himself.

But dark limit Immortal Gu had a flaw, every time it was activated, it would need to rest for a long time before it could be used again.

Fang Yuan needed to consider this point, and avoid a situation where he had to use dark limit Immortal Gu but it was not ready for use.

Nurture, use, refinement — the mastery of Gu was deep and profound, there were many things to take note of depending on different Gu worms.

Liu tribe.

Three Liu tribe Gu Immortals were in the Gu formation, consuming their immortal essence as they maintained the operations of the Gu formation.

A moment later, the Gu formation stopped, the three Gu Immortals took their rest.

"Failed again?" Outside the Gu formation, rank seven light path expert Liu Chang shifted his feet as he spoke in a disappointed tone.

"We have failed Lord Liu Chang's request, we are extremely ashamed." The three Liu tribe Gu Immortals sighed as they lowered their heads, having ugly expressions.

Liu Chang snorted coldly, looking at the three immortals unhappily, but his tone had calmed down: "Forget it, our Liu tribe do not have any wisdom path Gu Immortals, this Gu formation can only achieve the effects of a wisdom path deduction. I will go and find Tian Xia Xin for help now."

"Pardon me for saying this, Lord Liu Chang, but we failed to deduce it not because our formation is weak, but because the enemy has very strong defensive methods that prevent others from making deductions about him." The leader of the three Gu Immortals said.

"That is the case?" Liu Chang's expression became darker.

He muttered to himself: "The other party is a transformation path Gu Immortal specialized in ancient sword dragon transformation, how can he have such methods? But who knows, transformation path is said to project all paths. But the higher possibility is that this demon Liu Guan Yi has helpers. Domination Immortal Chu Du... even though he expelled Liu Guan Yi, I do not believe that he would do nothing. These demonic path or lone immortals are nothing good!"

Saying this, Liu Chang gritted his teeth, his expression became ruthless.

Liu Guan Yi plundered two of Liu tribe's important resource points, and even killed a Gu Immortal from Liu tribe, how could they take this lying down?

Liu Chang was ordered to kill Liu Guan Yi, but after so many days, he had not made any progress.

Earlier, for his sister's safety, he did not chase after Fang Yuan. This matter caused a bad reaction in the tribe, right now Liu Chang was enduring huge pressure, he wanted to find Fang Yuan at this very moment.

"Liu Guan Yi, you coward, where are you?" Liu Chang felt extremely stifled.

He had no idea that he was going to be even more stifled from now on. Because Fang Yuan had already left Northern Plains, going to other regions.

Ye Lui tribe was similarly as troubled as Liu Chang.

Ye Lui Qun Xing died at Fang Yuan's hands, Ye Lui tribe was definitely going to seek revenge. And now, Fang Yuan was expelled from Chu Sect, Ye Lui tribe immediately took action to investigate and pursue Fang Yuan.

The Gu Immortals that they sent were not weaker than Liu Chang. Unfortunately, Fang Yuan had already left Northern Plains.

Fang Yuan successfully passed the licorice regional wall.

This mystical regional wall that surrounded Northern Plains was filled with green fog. Grass was growing wildly in the fog and was constantly twining and twisting, like a sea of snakes or hair.

Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture could pass through without any obstruction.

After passing the licorice regional wall, Fang Yuan got into the blue water regional wall of Eastern Sea.

When he passed the blue water regional wall and reached Eastern Sea, his aura had completely changed, it was that of an Eastern Sea Gu Immortal.

This was one of the special attributes of the sovereign immortal body.

Everywhere Fang Yuan went, he would perfectly integrate into the environment, like he was born and bred there.

It was unlike other Gu Immortals, their external region aura was very obvious. Undergoing tribulation was also very troublesome, they had to return to their region to do it, otherwise, taking in another region's heaven and earth qi would cause a lot of problems.

After entering Eastern Sea, Fang Yuan did not travel in a rush, he went to Qing Yu blessed land and rested for a while.

This blessed land was left by Gu Immortal Liu Qing Yu.

After Fang Yuan killed him, the duck land spirit was successfully controlled by Fang Yuan.

Meeting Fang Yuan again, the duck land spirit was excited, it quacked and jumped up and down.

Fang Yuan said comforting words to it as the duck land spirit shed tears of joy: "Quack quack!"

"I knew that master did not abandon me!"

Sadly, Fang Yuan's attainment level was too low, he could not annex this rank seven blessed land.

Fang Yuan rested for a while, waiting for dark limit Immortal Gu to recover. Because this blessed land was a small world, during this period, anyone who deduced things about Fang Yuan would fail, it would not expend dark limit Immortal Gu's power.

By the time dark limit Immortal Gu could be used again, Fang Yuan did not hesitate to use it on himself.

After this replenishment, Fang Yuan left Qing Yu blessed land, going to the turbulent flow sea area.

The troublesome path in the chaotic currents wasted multiple days, but he eventually got into City Well.

There were many immortal apertures inside City Well.

Fang Yuan used the upper extreme heavenly eagle, entering and annexing a portion of the blessed lands.

Fang Yuan progressed by two calamities and tribulations again, the effect was not good. The remaining immortal apertures were mostly water path, but Fang Yuan's water path attainment level was just ordinary.

After leaving, Fang Yuan did not rush ahead once again. He went to Qing Yu blessed land and waited for dark limit Immortal Gu to recover before leaving for his destination.

After leaving Northern Plains and going to Eastern Sea, the deductions from Northern Plains became extremely weak. Each deduction expended less of Dark Limit's concealment power.

Fang Yuan was much different from before now.

Not only was he aware about heaven's will, he knew how to guard against it, he even had dark limit Immortal Gu and many wisdom path methods to protect himself. Of course, most importantly, his cultivation level and battle strength had risen greatly as well.

Compared to the time after the battle of Yi Tian Mountain, when Fang Yuan went from Southern Border to Northern Plains, there was an evident contrast.

Right now, if Fang Yuan met a group of ancient cloud beasts, he would not be chased around, the ones in danger would not be Fang Yuan but the ancient cloud beasts instead.

Thinking about it, Fang Yuan felt deeply: After gaining the sovereign immortal body, his cultivation level was rising at a shocking speed. It was worthy of the ultimate product created by Spectral Soul, Shadow Sect, and Zombie Alliance, after spending a hundred thousand years of time and effort!

Of course, the stronger the sovereign immortal body, the greater the enmity between Fang Yuan and Shadow Sect was.

This irreconcilable feud made Fang Yuan 'deeply concerned' about Ying Wu Xie and the rest.

Unfortunately, Ying Wu Xie and the others were crafty, Fang Yuan could not find their locations. Otherwise, he would rather give up on the annexing of blessed lands and get rid of these threats first!

Tens of days later, Fang Yuan finally got through Eastern Sea's blue water regional wall, and Southern Border's miasma regional wall, officially stepping into Southern Border.

Interestingly, be it Fang Yuan or Ying Wu Xie, they did not know that the other party was in the same region.

"I have heard long ago that the location of Yi Tian Mountain has been sealed with a huge defensive Gu formation made by the righteous path Gu Immortals together. I should go and check out the situation first." Fang Yuan had no idea how to enter the giant dream realm now.

He decided to gather intelligence first.

He flew southwest.

The flying journey was filled with lots of detours, of course.

Considering heaven's will, if Fang Yuan flew straight, that would be giving heaven's will a chance to set up trouble.

"Hmm? Someone is deducing about me?" While flying, Fang Yuan felt dark limit Immortal Gu's power weakening and found it laughable.

Southern Border, Northern Plains, they were separated by two regional walls, Fang Yuan's danger of being deduced was extremely low.

As expected, in Northern Plains' Myriad Bean Garden, Gu Immortal Tian Xia Xin returned half of the payment to Liu Chang.

Liu Chang had an ugly expression, and disbelief in his eyes: "What? Even you could not deduce it?"

Wisdom path Gu Immortal Tian Xia Xin smiled bitterly: "Wisdom path deductions are not all-powerful. I have tried my best, I am deeply sorry."

Liu Chang flew away from Myriad Bean Garden at a slow speed.

He was very troubled.

And very lost.

If the current number one wisdom path Gu Immortal in Northern Plains, Tian Xia Xin, could not deduce Liu Guan Yi's location, who could?

"Liu Guan Yi, you had better pray that you never bump into me ever!" Liu Chang swore, he had deep killing intent in his icy cold eyes.

No matter how deep his killing intent was, Fang Yuan was living a good life.

"Oh, they stopped deducing. Hehehe, when these people pay an even bigger price and obtain no results, they should stop." Fang Yuan laughed.

Northern Plains, Snowy Mountain.

Ma Hong Yun looked at Lady Wan Shou who was approaching as he stared angrily: "Go ahead, you vicious woman!"

Lady Wan Shou snickered, she pressed the lightning ball into Ma Hong Yun's chest.

Crack crack crack!

Ma Hong Yun's body trembled intensely, he was emitting smoke due to the lightning.

Guh.

Lady Wan Shou spit out a mouthful of blood, she had a pale expression: "Why did I fail again?"

Her eyes were blood red, after failing so many times, her elegant demeanor was gone.

Ma Hong Yun forced himself to stay conscious, he said weakly: "How would I know? I don't want it to fail. Just succeed, if you succeed once, I'll die. Death will end it, I will not undergo such torture again!"

Saying so, Ma Hong Yun could not stay awake anymore, his eyes revolved backwards as he fainted.

Chapter 1212: Burning Soul Bursting Luck!

"Chirp chirp!" A yellow haired female monkey pranced around, running towards Fang Yuan with nimble steps.

The yellow haired monkey stood in front of Fang Yuan, offering its peach to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan received it wordlessly, before tossing it below the tree.

The female monkey was shocked, it waved its arms as it jumped around Fang Yuan, it yelled and caused the branch that Fang Yuan was standing on to shake, the leaves were rustling as some fell to the ground.

Fang Yuan covered his face with his hands, sighing as he lowered his head.

The female monkey approached Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan kicked, sending the monkey down the tree.

The female monkey fell off the tree, it gritted its teeth in pain, looking at Fang Yuan on the tree, the attraction in its eyes turned into fear, it quickly escaped while limping.

Fang Yuan's appearance now had changed, his entire figure had turned from a human to a male monkey.

Precisely so, he attracted the affection of that female monkey.

This was the peak of a nameless mountain.

Fang Yuan came here, disguised as a monkey, he had been here for half a month already.

He concealed his identity, his focus was on observing the super Gu formation.

That's right, in front of him was the super dream realm.

Unfortunately, the giant dream realm was completely concealed by the righteous path's Gu formation, with the naked eye, one could only see the scene of a verdant green mountain.

Even if Fang Yuan used his methods, he could only see past the surface, the inside of the Gu formation was still very blurry.

"Unfortunately, my strongest investigative method is three breaths future vision, it cannot deal with this super Gu formation. There must be many Immortal Gu inside this super Gu formation."

"The one who arranged this Gu formation is Chi clan's first supreme elder, Chi Qu You. This person is a formation path great grandmaster, the strongest Immortal Gu formation he has ever made is called three tune nine pool formation. His Chi clan descendant Gu Immortals had used this formation during the five regions chaotic war and killed many Central Continent Gu Immortals. This formation was made during Chi Qu You's later years, he is still far from dying now. But maybe I can deduce it from this super Gu formation in front of me, it has the style of three tune nine pool formation, formations inside formations, overlapping in layers."

"Right now this Gu formation has only used a portion of its power, it has not even activated Immortal Gu, after all, that would consume immortal essence."

"Even so, with my observations these last days, just I alone cannot destroy a Gu formation of this level. Not to mention that inside, there are at least thirteen righteous path Gu Immortals!"

There were thirteen super forces in Southern Border's righteous path.

The super Gu formation here was made through everyone's efforts. To defend their own interests, each clan had sent at least one Gu Immortal to defend it. These Gu Immortals were elites of their own clans, otherwise, they would not be able to control the situation.

"The defense is too tight, if I want to get in, and use unravel dream, forcing my way through is impossible, I need to plan wisely." Fang Yuan shook his head internally.

But what plan should he use, Fang Yuan did not know.

There were no clear options.

Because this problem involved the entire Southern Border righteous path. These righteous path forces had worked together, they were united, their distribution of benefits was also very reasonable.

Fang Yuan was all alone, even though he had rank seven cultivation level, against such a huge force, there was nothing he could do.

These righteous path forces could stay in power until today and dominate most of Southern Border's cultivation resources, there was a good reason for it.

Like before, Fang Yuan attempted to disrupt Northern Plains, in the end, the righteous path forces and Chu Du resisted him.

Fang Yuan had been reborn, but because of heaven's will, the advantage of his rebirth was quite small.

Most crucially, this giant dream realm also had Gu formations that were not used in his previous life. Thus, Fang Yuan's understanding of it was minimal.

"What should I do?" Fang Yuan was troubled.

Bai Ning Bing, who was inside Bai Xiang grotto-heaven, stared at the land spirit with an equally troubled feeling.

"I broke through the thirty halls and cut down all my obstacles, I finally met you but you refuse to acknowledge me as your master?" Bai Ning Bing stared at Bai Xiang heavenly spirit, he had an icy expression.

Bai Xiang heavenly spirit was an old man.

He smoked his cigar as he sat on the steps, he looked at Bai Ning Bing and breathed in deeply, before puffing out deeply: "Oh, young people these days, they are so hasty. When you came here, I said that if you get through the thirty halls, I will meet you. I did not say that I will acknowledge you as master. Getting here just means that you have the initial qualifications to accept the following test."

"What is the following test?" Bai Ning Bing asked coldly.

"Bring back an immortal material." Bai Xiang heavenly spirit looked at Bai Ning Bing, chuckling with a creepy look.

"What immortal material, where?" Bai Ning Bing asked.

"Do you see that hole at the top of the hall?" Bai Xiang heavenly spirit pointed up and said.

"I saw it the moment I came here, it is too eye-catching." Bai Ning Bing said plainly.

Bai Xiang heavenly spirit sighed again: "The greatest use of this Immortal Gu House, Thirty Heavenly Halls, is to store large amounts of immortal materials. But a few thousand years ago, one immortal material at the highest layer broke through the ceiling and flew away."

"What?" Bai Ning Bing was surprised.

"Don't looked so shocked, young man, this world is huge beyond your imagination. The profundities of all life forms, you will encounter it in the future, and feel for yourself the grandness of heaven and earth..." Bai Xiang heavenly spirit sighed.

"Stop prattling, get to the point." Bai Ning Bing interrupted mercilessly.

"Oh! Youngster, you have no patience, listening to an old man's words is good for you." Bai Xiang heavenly spirit sighed.

Bai Ning Bing was silent, only staring at Bai Xiang heavenly spirit with his blue eyes.

Bai Xiang heavenly spirit smoked another puff as he said: "Alright, I'll tell you. I want you to subdue that flame. It is hidden deep in the sea to the west. Normally, you cannot find it because it can fuse with sea water completely, but once in a while, it will float to the surface and frolic around. That is your best chance to catch it."

Bai Ning Bing followed Bai Xiang heavenly spirit's guidance, arriving at the western coastline.

The sea was wide and vast, there were many waves on the surface, it was a magnificent sight.

Bai Ning Bing had hidden here for more than ten days, he finally found the chance that Bai Xiang heavenly spirit had mentioned.

Swish swish swish!

Countless waves appeared on the surface of the sea, causing tides that were more than a hundred feet tall to form.

The calm and silent sea had at this moment, turned into a roaring brute, the sea was fierce and magnificent, Bai Ning Bing, who was witnessing this for the first time, had deep emotions seeing it.

Next, he flew to the sky, seeing that immortal material which Bai Xiang heavenly spirit was talking about.

It was a small lump of flames.

The flames were orange-yellow, round and the size of an adult's fist.

It burned and emitted light, it formed into the shape of a flying dragon as the orange flames continued to fly around randomly.

Bai Ning Bing, who was usually expressionless, showed shock on his face.

"Light of dao marks, and so lively, this is a rank nine immortal material!"

Rank nine immortal materials were extremely rare.

They were special materials in the world that could refine rank nine Immortal Gu.

Bai Ning Bing did not expect that Bai Xiang heavenly spirit was asking him to retrieve a rank nine immortal material!

This was out of his capabilities, Bai Ning Bing had to take a risk and use the Immortal Gu inside him to activate a special method, communicating with Ying Wu Xie outside.

"Didn't I tell you not to contact me, if Bai Xiang heavenly spirit finds out, it will be troublesome." Ying Wu Xie said.

"I encountered trouble, I need to retrieve a rank nine immortal material, it is a lump of orange-yellow flames..."

Hearing Bai Ning Bing's thorough description, Ying Wu Xie's expression changed: "You say that the light from its dao marks resemble flying dragons? The surrounding seawater is rushing outwards, as if it is afraid of this fire?"

"That is indeed so, around the fire, there is a huge empty space without any water in it. I can see the water level at the bottom of this, the empty space is still continuing to expand." Bai Ning Bing added.

Ying Wu Xie's expression changed again, his answer this time was a little shaky: "You must have read \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, recorded inside were the three unique flames of heaven, earth, and human respectively, this is the human flame — Raging Wave Rising Dragon Fire!"

"Raging wave rising dragon fire?!" Bai Ning Bing heard this answer and became tongue-tied.

After a short pause, Bai Ning Bing asked: "Then what should I do?"

Ying Wu Xie sighed: "It is very hard. With your cultivation level, there is almost no hope in subduing wild flames. However, this flame is not wild, it was once subdued by Bai Xiang, there is some chance. I have three methods for you, you can try them all."

"How big are my chances?" Bai Ning Bing asked.

Ying Wu Xie smiled bitterly: "I am not sure, they all have a possibility of success, but the chances are slim, it will depend on your luck."

Both of them conversed in a short time, in order to avoid getting caught, Ying Wu Xie was the first to cut the connection.

Ying Wu Xie was not optimistic, his thoughts were shrouded in darkness.

"The human flame among the three flames of heaven, earth and human... I am afraid only my main body after revival can have high hopes in succeeding."

"It seems that I need to help Bai Ning Bing, if he fails, it will be troublesome for my future plans."

Ying Wu Xie decided to do something.

Even though he was far away from Bai Ning Bing, the latter was in Bai Xiang grotto-heaven and was under the surveillance of Bai Xiang heavenly spirit, Ying Wu Xie had many methods to help Bai Ning Bing.

First, there was luck!

Ying Wu Xie's immortal killer move — Burning Soul Bursting Luck.

He used this killer move again. The last time he used it was in the super Gu formation inside Central Continent's Earth Abyss. Back then, Ying Wu Xie planned to refine Fixed Immortal Travel, he burned his own soul to raise his luck sharply!

Eventually, his Gu refinement still failed.

But this was because Heavenly Court had already refined Fixed Immortal Travel before him.

Immortal Gu were unique, even if his luck was overwhelming, Ying Wu Xie could not refine a second Fixed Immortal Travel in this world.

Before Bai Ning Bing set off, Ying Wu Xie had already used connect luck Immortal Gu to tie their luck together.

Right now, Bai Ning Bing was trying to subdue the rank nine immortal material raging wave rising dragon fire, he could not avoid this, Ying Wu Xie could only use luck to help Bai Ning Bing!

On the other hand, near the giant dream realm.

"Oh? Something's happening!" Fang Yuan, who had turned into a monkey, quickly hid behind the branches.

Two Gu Immortals appeared, standing below the tree Fang Yuan was in.

The peach that Fang Yuan had thrown out earlier was by the feet of a Gu Immortal.

"Brother Luo, thank you for this." A Gu Immortal said.

"I can bring you in, but if anything happens and you get discovered, it has nothing to do with me." The other Gu Immortal replied.

Chapter 1213: Immortal Opportunity Business

"What?" Hearing the conversation of the two Gu Immortals, Fang Yuan's ears stood up.

He jumped out of the tree, landing above the two Gu Immortals as he hung himself on the branch.

It was a normal reaction for the type of monkey that Fang Yuan had transformed into to behave curiously like this.

The two Gu Immortals did not even raise their heads.

But Fang Yuan was well aware that these two Gu Immortals had already activated their investigative methods, they also found Fang Yuan. But Fang Yuan's familiar face was a rank eight immortal killer move, it was beyond their methods.

The two immortals had no suspicions, they continued talking.

One of them said: "Brother Luo, don't worry, I also gained interest after hearing Lady White Rabbit's words, I want to interact with the rumored dream realm, and test the opportunity for myself. Even though I, Jiao Lei Zi, am a mere lone cultivator, I hold my promises. Since I promised you and made an information path agreement, I would not do something out of line."

"Precisely because of your reputation, Jiao Lei Zi, us brothers agreed to meet you. Otherwise, you would not even see our shadows. Follow me, when you enter the formation, say that you are a member of Luo clan, and are here to bring an Immortal Gu to my brother." The Luo clan Gu Immortal walked as he explained.

At the side, lone cultivator Jiao Lei Zi was following after him, listening attentively.

Fang Yuan sat on the branch as he watched them leave, he even followed them, brazenly jumping from tree to tree.

Only after the two Gu Immortals vanished did he stop moving, he looked around, screeching in confusion.

His disguise was extremely convincing, displaying the might of a transformation path grandmaster.

From start to finish, these two Gu Immortals had no suspicions.

"Interesting." Fang Yuan went back to the trees, his eyes bright as excitement rose in him.

He had accidentally encountered two Gu Immortals' secret deal.

These two had coincidentally chosen this mountain peak to meet, and right in front of Fang Yuan as well.

This luck was amazing!

Hearing their conversation, evidently, a righteous path Gu Immortal who was part of the defensive Gu formation had gone ahead and done a secret deal with the lone cultivator Gu Immortal, Jiao Lei Zi.

The righteous path Gu Immortal led the way for Jiao Lei Zi, letting him enter the defensive Gu formation and find his own opportunity.

Fang Yuan scoffed at Jiao Lei Zi's idea.

"You really think the dream realm is this easy to interact with... Opportunity? Without specialized dream path methods, what opportunities can there be?"

"And that righteous path Gu Immortal called himself Luo, he must be from the super force Luo clan."

Southern Border's righteous path had thirteen super forces, they had their respective territories in the entire region, Luo clan was one of them.

"Can I use this chance to get into the defensive Gu formation and interact with the dream realm?" Unavoidably, Fang Yuan had such a thought.

He took a final glance at the formation before leaving.

The monkey that Fang Yuan had turned into jumped from tree to tree, climbing mountain cliffs, and continuing to travel. After half a day, he finally left the original mountain.

Continuing on and getting past some mountain peaks, Fang Yuan got rid of his transformation and returned to normal.

He had a vigilant nature, if he used an immortal killer move close to the super Gu formation, he might draw the attention and wariness of the righteous path Gu Immortals.

"This distance should be safe." Fang Yuan estimated internally.

He was not certain, because he had no understanding of this super Gu formation.

However, even if the righteous path Gu Immortals found his traces, there were no issues.

"I do not believe that after the righteous path super forces made this super Gu formation, the demonic path and lone immortals did not come to probe it!"

Fang Yuan guessed correctly.

The battle of Yi Tian Mountain was like a ball of lightning, from the calm lake that was Southern Border's Gu Immortal world, it caused a massive tide that has risen with ferocity.

The battle of Yi Tian Mountain, it involved the Immortal Gu House Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage, all the major forces in Southern Border and countless Gu Immortals paid attention to it.

Later on, the righteous demonic battle also affected the whole of Southern Border's Gu Immortal world.

But eventually, that huge battle at Yi Tian Mountain destroyed everything, all of the Gu Immortals that were involved died. And in place of them at Yi Tian Mountain, there was a gigantic dream realm that manifested out of nowhere.

This made the Southern Border Gu Immortals unable to even investigate Yi Tian Mountain. The parties involved, Shadow Sect, Heavenly Court, and Fang Yuan, were keeping very quiet about it, these Southern Border Gu Immortals were all kept in the dark.

Ever since the righteous path went ahead to encircle the giant dream realm, and created this super Gu formation, the demonic path and lone immortals were very unwilling to give in, many of them wanted to investigate this Gu formation.

The righteous path Gu Immortals often found traces of these people, but as long as they did not charge into the Gu formation, they turned a blind eye.

Fang Yuan chose an ordinary mountain cave and stayed for a few days.

He waited for Jiao Lei Zi to leave the defensive Gu formation.

Jiao Lei Zi's movement was not concealed, he left on the same way as he went in.

"Since Jiao Lei Zi disguised as a Luo clan Gu Immortal, when he left, he had to be open and nonchalant, otherwise, it would be suspicious." Fang Yuan stared fixedly at Jiao Lei Zi, seeing him fly away, Fang Yuan followed after him closely.

The two flew for a while, Jiao Lei Zi's speed suddenly slowed down, he stopped at the peak of a nameless mountain.

He turned around and looked at Fang Yuan: "Friend, you have been following me for so long, is anything the matter?"

Jiao Lei Zi did not have a confrontational attitude.

Because Fang Yuan had purposely revealed his traces to Jiao Lei Zi when following him.

He also used attitude Gu to express his goodwill, Jiao Lei Zi could sense it.

Jiao Lei Zi thus did not speak to Fang Yuan in a bad tone, but he was still very guarded.

"I am truly sorry for troubling you." Fang Yuan greeted as he expressed his intention politely.

Jiao Lei Zi heard Fang Yuan's following words and his expression soothed.

The reason was, Fang Yuan called himself a wandering lone cultivator, he was curious about the dream realm. But he had heard that Jiao Lei Zi had a way to bribe the righteous path Gu Immortals and get inside the defensive Gu formation, to personally interact with the dream realm, he wanted to see if he could find any opportunities.

Fang Yuan thus waited outside for a long time, only following Jiao Lei Zi after he came out.

"So news have already spread, even an outsider like you has obtained information about it." Jiao Lei Zi was not suspicious, he smiled helplessly.

"Come with me, it is normal that you want to enter the dream realm to find your immortal opportunity. However, I am not a key middleman, I will bring you to Lady White Rabbit." Jiao Lei Zi was very enthusiastic.

He might not know Fang Yuan, but his Southern Border Gu Immortal aura could not be false.

Furthermore, Southern Border was the region with the most secluded cultivators in the five regions. This was Southern Border's trait, many Gu Immortals would not be known by people from the time of their ascension until their death.

With less than a day's journey, Fang Yuan met with Lady White Rabbit thanks to Jiao Lei Zi.

This female Gu Immortal had the appearance of a woman in her twenties, her eyes were red like rubies, she had a cute round face and shiny big eyes. Her lips were lush, she spoke very quickly, words came out of her mouth like firing a Gatling gun.

The scene of meeting with Lady White Rabbit made Fang Yuan quite surprised.

Because this Lady White Rabbit directly placed a mortal Gu House at a mountain peak, many demonic path and lone immortals were entering and exiting this house.

"We only do dream realm business here, you came to the right place!"

"If you want to enter the dream realm, I have many reliable ways, it will depend on what price you can pay."

"The bigger the price you pay, the faster you can enter the dream realm, perhaps you might be able to find your own immortal opportunity!" Lady White Rabbit said this as she pointed her thumb at the wall behind her while facing Fang Yuan.

There were all sorts of small boards there, people's names were written there.

"There are five more people in queue." Jiao Lei Zi saw this and sighed.

"You must know the importance of the immortal opportunity!" Lady White Rabbit stared at Fang Yuan as she spoke, listing many examples in history before she added: "The Prophecy of Three Venerables, you must know about it. Dream realm, this is the immortal opportunity that concerns Great Dream Immortal Venerable! Think about it, if you can become Great Dream Immortal Venerable in the future, what would happen? Even if you only get one small opportunity, your situation will change. If you do not try this, how would you know if you are able to succeed?"

"That's right. Even if you know you cannot succeed, you can ensure that you have no regrets in the future." Jiao Lei Zi added at the side: "A precious dream realm that even the righteous path Gu Immortals are coveting, it is so rare that we can have this chance!"

"That's right, now is just the start. Thus, the righteous path is not very strict yet." Lady White Rabbit continued, purposely telling Fang Yuan: "After a while, it will be different. This business will not last long, the opportunity will depend on whether you can grab hold of it!"

"What price do I have to pay?" Fang Yuan pretended to hesitate.

Lady White Rabbit said a sum.

Fang Yuan showed a look of hesitation: "I will consider it first."

"Of course, consider it well!" Lady White Rabbit smiled, her attitude was still very polite.

At this time, a female Gu Immortal came to the counter, Lady White Rabbit's smile became more sincere, she disregarded Fang Yuan as she went over: "Sister Miao Yin, you are here to try to find an opportunity again?"

That female Gu Immortal nodded, saying: "I feel that if I change to another location and enter the dream realm, I will have different gains."

There were many Gu Immortals inside the mortal Gu House, Lady White Rabbit was not the only intermediary, from time to time, new boards were hung on the wall.

Fang Yuan walked out of the mortal Gu House, saying goodbye to Jiao Lei Zi.

"You can consider this again, but in my opinion, you should decide it as soon as possible. It cannot be dragged out. You can see the situation for yourself, the longer you think, the longer the queue of Gu Immortals become, there is no time to waste." Jiao Lei Zi said before leaving.

Fang Yuan expressed his gratitude as he left.

"Well, has he not made up his mind yet?" Lady White Rabbit finished attending to her Sister Miao Yin as she asked Jiao Lei Zi.

"He said he needs to think about it, sigh, I thought that I could earn a sum of recommendation fees to replenish my losses." Jiao Lei Zi smiled bitterly.

"Jiao Lei Zi, you are so affluent, why are you acting poor to me?" Lady White Rabbit laughed: "However, this person that you brought is likely a wandering secluded cultivator, he is poor and does not have resources, otherwise, why would he leave? Those with some funds would at least stay and interact for a while before leaving."

Jiao Lei Zi laughed bitterly: "How am I affluent? I thank Lady White Rabbit for the praise. To speak the truth, this price is really expensive, even I feel great loss."

Lady White Rabbit smiled, showing her pearly white teeth: "This business relies on both parties' wishes, it is pricey because it is worth the cost, this is an opportunity involving Great Dream Immortal Venerable after all, right?"

Jiao Lei Zi nodded, making up his mind, saying: "I will pay a sum of resources, I want to try again."

Chapter 1214: Situation of Southern Border

Looking at the clouds in the sky, Fang Yuan's expression was dark.

He thought about the scene earlier.

Out of his expectations, that immortal opportunity business, as it was known, of the dream realm was extremely popular. The involvement was far bigger than he had predicted earlier.

Looking at the situation inside the mortal Gu House and Lady White Rabbit's tone, evidently, whether they were demonic path or lone cultivators, as long as they could pay the price, anyone could enter the righteous path's defensive Gu formation and interact with the dream realm.

"This is slightly above my expectations, but thinking about it, I understand why."

Dream path.

At this time period, it was very empty.

Even though many super forces were researching on it, their gains were little.

Fang Yuan had the killer move unravel dream, he was a leading figure in the current five regions. Of course, Ying Wu Xie's lead soul into dream was also very unique, it was an ability that surpassed the current era.

Lead soul into dream had displayed incredible might during the battle of Yi Tian Mountain, the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals had suffered due to it.

And Fang Yuan's killer move, unravel dream, also gave him great gains, and immense profits.

"The righteous path Gu Immortals might have encircled this dream realm, but they have no way of excavating the treasures inside. In fact, a while later, they lost many members, among which were rank seven Gu Immortal experts holding great authority! Luo clan even lost their third supreme elder..."

Such information could not be hidden, it was widely spread in the Southern Border Gu Immortal world, Fang Yuan could easily obtain this information.

"The righteous path suffered a lot, they know the power of the dream realm, it is not possible to explore it randomly, so they used this method to scam the demonic path and lone cultivators' resources. And if any accidents happen, they would not need to waste any of their members to deal a huge blow to these non-righteous members, it is truly killing two birds with one stone."

"To be able to make this immortal opportunity business so popular and at such a huge scale but still have the ability to remain intact, evidently, the righteous path have come to a consensus, Lady White Rabbit's mortal Gu House is backed by Southern Border's righteous path Gu Immortals. One clan is not enough, there are at least six or seven clans working together to result in this fearless stance."

Fang Yuan was an old schemer, because of the experiences in the five hundred years of his previous life, he could clearly deduce all of the details regarding this immortal opportunity business.

This way, even though he could use this method to enter the righteous path defensive Gu formation, and interact with the dream realm, he could not satisfy his own needs.

What were Fang Yuan's needs?

Firstly, he needed time and opportunity to interact with the giant dream realm for an extended period of time.

Secondly, he needed an identity to protect himself, even if anything happened to the dream realm, he could continue staying there.

Just one or two trips into the dream realm, what could Fang Yuan get?

Just the cost involved was extremely high.

But the Prophecy of Three Venerables had deeply affected everyone, countless Gu Immortals were still going ahead with it.

The righteous path Gu Immortals had already tasted suffering, by the time these demonic path and lone immortals realized the futility, their enthusiasm would fade.

Furthermore, even if Fang Yuan did this and unraveled the dream realm, gaining an increase in his attainment level.

It would trigger a change in the dream realm.

At least, the dream realm would shrink by an amount.

If other righteous path Gu Immortals realized this situation, what would they do?

By then, Fang Yuan would be inside the Gu formation, like fish on the chopping block. Even with the upper extreme heavenly eagle, Fang Yuan had no heavenly crystals to feed it.

"If I cannot do this, what should I try? Kill a righteous path Gu Immortal and use familiar face to disguise myself before going inside?"

Fang Yuan thought about this, he shook his head, discarding this unrealistic idea.

Firstly, Gu Immortals from righteous path forces would use methods like life tablet Gu, soul lantern Gu or blood rope Gu.

These methods allowed their clans to easily inspect if the Gu Immortal was dead or alive. Furthermore, they could use these life tablet Gu, soul lantern Gu, or blood rope Gu to deduce the exact location of these Gu Immortals with great ease.

Once Fang Yuan kills these Gu Immortals, the clan would react immediately. Unless Fang Yuan had information path methods that could deceive these Gu worms.

Fang Yuan had always been weak in terms of information path.

Furthermore, familiar face might be a rank eight killer move, but it was not flawless. For example, back in Eastern Sea, Ying Wu Xie could use luck inspection Immortal Gu to find out Fang Yuan's identity.

Finally, once a long time passes, even if Fang Yuan used familiar face, lots of minute details or habits of the Gu Immortal would slowly become flaws that allow others to realize a problem.

Thus, killing someone and replacing them was not feasible.

Fang Yuan thought from all angles, he could not think of any good ideas.

Even if Fang Yuan had rank eight battle strength and attacked the Gu formation forcefully, he might not be able to succeed. Even if he broke the Gu formation, there were still many rank eight Gu Immortals in Southern Border.

By that time, when rank eight enemies encircle him, Fang Yuan would be able to explore any dream realms.

He could not find a solution, Fang Yuan was quite helpless.

He thought about it and returned to the mortal Gu House.

Lady White Rabbit's eyes shone, she greeted Fang Yuan: "Have you considered it, you want to find your own immortal opportunity?"

Fang Yuan smiled bitterly: "Fairy White Rabbit, I am but a secluded wanderer, I have not interacted much with the outside world, this price will cost me almost all my assets, I need to consider it. I am here this time to get some information from you, and understand matters in Southern Border's Gu Immortal world."

Fang Yuan said this as he handed Fairy White Rabbit a rank six immortal material.

Fairy White Rabbit was slightly surprised, even though this immortal material was very common, Fang Yuan's request was not hard. These days, she had been managing this business, she interacted with all sorts of Gu Immortals, she had a good understanding of the Gu Immortal world's current situation.

"Let's talk using this." Fairy White Rabbit gave Fang Yuan an information path mortal Gu.

...

Super dream realm, righteous path Gu formation.

"We meet again, Fairy Miao Yin, do you remember me?" A Qiao clan Gu Immortal led a female Gu Immortal as they entered the Gu formation.

Even though he was a righteous path Gu Immortal, he had a fawning tone.

Because this Fairy Miao Yin, although from the demonic path, was extremely beautiful, she inherited a predecessor's blessed land and was extremely affluent, she was publicly known as one of the three great fairies in Southern Border's Gu Immortal world.

The two entered the Gu formation, this was seen by the two righteous path Gu Immortals at the center of the Gu formation.

"These people are becoming more daring! They used to come once every seven days, but now, they come every one or two days, bringing all sorts of people in here."

"The two Gu Immortals from Luo clan are still fine, they bring in people with good reputations and clean records. But Qiao clan's Gu Immortals have no restraints, they are very greedy. This Miao Yin is a demonic path member, in the past, she had destroyed two important resource points of my Ba clan, and even injured four Ba clan Gu Immortals who chased her!"

Gu Immortal Ba Quan Feng said angrily.

Beside him was another Ba clan Gu Immortal.

This person was very tall, nearly three meters, he had an old fashioned appearance, his beard and hair were connected, his dark green beard hung down to his waist, while his jade green hair extended to the back of his waist.

He had a large mouth and broad nose, his eyes were covered by a black cloth, covering them completely. He had a strong body with broad shoulders and chest, his skin that was not covered looked like thousand year old tree bark, there was even green moss growing on it.

He was thousands of years old, his cultivation level was stuck at the final step before reaching rank eight.

He had rank seven peak battle strength, publicly recognized in Southern Border's Gu Immortal world as the number one person under rank eight — Old Treeman Ba De!

Ba De spoke slowly: "Little Feng, don't be anxious. Even though Qiao clan is weak, at the bottom of the righteous path forces, they are backed by Wu clan. Qiao clan and Wu clan have been linked by alliance marriages for tens of thousands of years."

Ba Quan Feng heard about Wu clan and the anger on his face faded, but he still continued : "Qiao clan is a righteous path force, but for the last few thousand years, they have been at Wu clan's beck and call, they are just a dog raised by Wu clan!"

"This Wu clan is too overbearing! With two rank eight Gu Immortals in the clan, they act fearlessly. This time, they actually cooperated with six other clans, using this dream realm to make their immortal opportunity business. What do they think of the remaining six clans not involved, us included? This super Gu formation was made by all of us, we created it with all of our Immortal Gu!"

"Hehehe." Ba De laughed: "Little Feng, you are thinking that everyone should have a part of the profits?"

Ba Quan Feng's thoughts were exposed, his face turned red: "Hehe, I could not hide it from you, lord."

Ba De shook his head: "Wu clan's actions will attract even more clans to join in. After all, we have already realized that now is not the time to explore the dream realm. This method can give us greater profits, it is good for us."

"But our Ba clan cannot join in."

"Ah, why is that?" Ba Quan Feng asked quickly.

"There are advantages and disadvantages in this. Even though they gain many cultivation resources, we gain a hold on them in return. With enough evidence, in the future when we argue over it, my Ba clan will have the advantage. When we split the dream realm, we will get a bigger portion. Little Feng, look forward, the dream realm cannot be explored now, but what about the future? The dream realm is the true treasure." Ba De sighed.

"But, Wu clan is so domineering, they have two rank eight Gu Immortals while we only have one, by then, if they keep a strong stance, we cannot stop them." Ba Quan Feng said angrily.

"We cannot stop Wu clan, but what about the other clans? Furthermore, Wu clan's first supreme elder is close to dying, Wu clan will soon be in unrest for a long time. With just one rank eight Gu Immortal left, can Wu clan still be the number one righteous path force?" Ba De smiled with deep meaning.

Ba Quan Feng stared with wide eyes: "So the rumors that Wu clan first supreme elder's lifespan is depleted are not false? Impossible, they are a huge force, how can they not have lifespan Gu stocked up?"

"Wu clan's first supreme elder had used other lifespan extension methods when she was young, there were problems left behind. Right now, lifespan Gu has no use to her." Ba De sighed:" With her death, the entire situation in Southern Border will change, by then, we'll see if Wu clan can control the situation, our clans will have a chance to strike. After all, all these years, Wu clan has occupied too many resources."

Chapter 1215: Wu Clan's Conflict

Wu Du Xiu slowly opened her eyes.

"A brand new day." She thought to herself.

A rank eight Immortal Gu was flying around in this average sized house.

Food path Immortal Gu — Medicine Fragrance!

This was a healing Immortal Gu, it filled the entire house with a thick fragrance of medicine. But Wu Du Xiu's own rotting smell was intense, the medicine fragrance could not conceal it.

The two smells mixed together, even Gu Immortals could not stand it.

Another passing day meant one less day left.

Wu Du Xiu knew that she was very close to dying.

At this moment, she was lying in her bed, looking at the scene outside her room, her heart was filled with tranquility.

Long ago, when she was still a rank six Gu Immortal, she fell in love with a demonic path Gu cultivator, and was punished by the clan.

She was locked in this house for fifteen years.

To think that this was her fortuitous encounter.

It turned out, inside this house, there was an inheritance of a Wu clan ancestor. Wu Du Xiu obtained it and cultivated in secret, her strength rose rapidly and drastically.

She even used the great expert's blessed land to meet with her lover in secret. Wu clan's Gu Immortals did not expect that Wu Du Xiu was openly breaking the clan rules under their watch.

Those were Wu Du Xiu's happiest years, she was immersed in unparalleled bliss.

Back then, she was just a young, beautiful and silly girl, she did not know the vicious nature of people, she could not tell that her lover had ulterior motives.

Time passed.

Thousands of years later, Wu Du Xiu returned to this house.

She was close to dying, her lifespan was running out, she had days left.

This old woman was filled with experience and fatigue, her murky gaze seemed to have crossed thousands of years, back to the past when she spent her happiest times laughing in this house, all of her memories were surfacing in her mind.

These memories were forever painted in a rosy light.

The windows of the house were opened, a gentle breeze carrying the fragrance of flowers and grass entered her room.

A young lady with a beautiful appearance, youthful with eyes clear as water, greatly moving. She was singing in the house, cleaning up the place and doing a lot of mortal chores, yet she was extremely happy and lively.

At that time, happiness was so easily obtained. But as she grew older, this simple bliss left her.

As for that lover, Wu Du Xiu's first love, she had already forgotten him.

His image was blurry.

The pain that he had caused Wu Du Xiu caused her to grieve terribly, the hatred that tortured her tired soul had faded with the wind.

Creak.

With a soft sound, the door of the house was opened by someone.

Wu Du Xiu turned her head with difficulty, through the curtains, she saw a familiar figure.

She was not surprised, she had allowed this.

She was Wu clan's first supreme elder, a person who was in power for thousands of years, without her permission, who could enter this house?

"You are here." Wu Du Xiu spoke faintly with much difficulty.

But the person who came was very well-mannered, he knelt on the ground and bowed deeply: "I am here to meet you, mother."

This person was a middle aged man with an ordinary appearance, he had a strong body and sharp eyebrows, giving him a dark and hazy aura.

Wu Du Xiu spoke: "I called you here to tell you something. You have a younger half-brother, he was born in Eastern Sea. I will pass everything in Wu clan to you. And my own inheritance will be left to him, do you understand?"

The middle aged man lowered his head until it touched the ground: "This child understands."

"You may leave." Wu Du Xiu paused for a moment before saying.

"I will take my leave!" The middle aged Gu Immortal said carefully, he slowly got up and moved back a few steps before turning around and leaving the house, softly shutting the doors.

He did not dare to even breath loudly, he had an expression of reverence that never changed, only after he left and passed several large mountains, reaching his own Immortal Gu House, did his expression change.

"Mother is muddleheaded!"

"Before dying, she actually wants to bring back that illegitimate son!"

"That bastard, can't he stay in Eastern Sea for good? Why must he return and fight with me over the inheritance?"

The middle aged Gu Immortal flew into a rage.

"Master, don't be angry, mind your health." A rank seven Gu Immortal with a hunched back quickly urged.

The middle aged Gu Immortal kicked him away, roaring: "Mother's abilities come from her wind path Immortal Gu. She wants to hand these Immortal Gu to that bastard, without these Immortal Gu, with just my rank eight cultivation level, what can I do? We would still be bullied by Ba clan, Tie clan, and Shang clan!"

"Saying that she will leave everything in Wu clan to me, hmph! Why do I want these resources for? I want her rank eight Immortal Gu, I want battle strength! With strength, what can I not get?"

The middle aged Gu Immortal got angrier as he spoke, he paced around in the Immortal Gu House.

"Master, we could also just finish him off!" The rank seven hunched back Gu Immortal walked forward and chopped downwards with his hand.

The middle aged Gu Immortal stopped walking.

He frowned deeply, turning to ask the rank seven Gu Immortal: "You mean to say..."

"That's right, first supreme elder only has two sons, other than you, there is only the Eastern Sea illegitimate son. If we kill him, then all of first supreme elder's inheritance will be yours, right?" The rank seven hunched back Gu Immortal smiled sinisterly.

The middle aged Gu Immortal blinked rapidly as sweat appeared on his forehead.

"No."

"If mother finds out, I will be finished!" Thinking about his mother's methods, even though the middle aged Gu Immortal had rank eight cultivation level, he could not help but tremble.

"Forget it, he is only rank seven, what can he do even if he returns?" The middle aged Gu Immortal sighed deeply.

But the hunchback Gu Immortal did not give up, he continued to speak: "Oh master, you cannot think like that. He already has rank seven cultivation level, what will happen when he gets first supreme elder's Immortal Gu?"

The middle aged Gu Immortal snorted, regaining some of his defiance: "Even if he has rank eight Immortal Gu, his dao mark accumulation cannot compare to mine. He is not my match. It is a pity regarding those two rank eight Immortal Gu, however. Sigh..."

The hunchback Gu Immortal smiled sinisterly: "Master, you are just hesitant because you are afraid of failure and causing first supreme elder to punish you. Actually, we do not need to act ourselves. Other than us, there is Ba clan, Tie clan, Chi clan, and others, they are all after our clan's status, they want to displace us. As long as we release information about his traveling route, we can lure them to attack. By then, we will benefit from it greatly."

The middle aged Gu Immortal heard and his eyes shone, he praised: "Good plan, good plan, Xu Tuo, you are indeed my greatest aide. When I become first supreme elder, I will not mistreat you."

"Master, it is my job to solve problems for you, it is my honor." The hunchback Gu Immortal's eyes were turning red as he choked, holding back a sob.

The middle aged Gu Immortal patted Xu Tuo's shoulder, he did not speak, he only showed happiness on his face.

Inside the Immortal Gu House, both master and servant had a lightened atmosphere.

"Master, there is no time, should I go prepare now?"

"Yes, go ahead, I am assured if you are handling it."

After leaving the Immortal Gu House, Xu Tuo's eyes flashed with a sharp and dark light.

"Hmph! After spending so much effort, I finally managed to convince this Wu Yong, this way, even if I expose information about this illegitimate son, and get hunted down by others, I will be safe under Wu Yong's protection! My true identity will not be exposed."

Xu Tuo's true identity was not just simply Wu Yong's servant, the truth was, he was a Ba clan Gu Immortal. He was a spy planted into Wu clan, he had the highest authority among the spies.

The situation in Southern Border was very different from Northern Plains and Central Continent.

Among the righteous path forces in Southern Border, Wu clan was the domineering one. In history, at their peak, they had three rank eight Gu Immortals! And across history, Wu clan always had at least one rank eight Gu Immortal to hold the fort in their clan.

Wu clan had always been strong. Wu Du Xiu's life was ending, while Wu Yong was not talented enough, even though he was rank eight, compared to the other righteous path rank eights, he was not impressive.

Wu Du Xiu's illegitimate son, Wu Yi Hai, had incredible talent according to some information. Even though he was a lone cultivator in Eastern Sea, he had formidable battle strength, he was quite famous even in Eastern Sea's Gu Immortal world.

Killing Wu Yi Hai could not only weaken Wu clan, it can also attack Wu Yong's reputation, and send Wu clan into chaos and suspicion internally.

Xu Tuo went with much hope.

Some days later.

Three Gu Immortals were passing through the miasma regional wall.

"Young master, we are almost through the miasma regional wall. This is the final hurdle, once we are out of the regional wall, they will have fewer chances to attack us." An elderly Gu Immortal said solemnly.

Wu Yi Hai suddenly said: "Uncle Zhang, you mean that the following part of the journey is the most dangerous!"

"That's right." The elderly Gu Immortal nodded seriously.

Another young looking Gu Immortal said: "But as long as we get through this, we will be completely free. As long as you can meet your mother, all of the hardship and suffering on this trip would be repaid by hundreds or thousands of times!"

Hearing about his mother, Wu Yi Hai had complex emotions.

He sighed: "Oh! What rewards, I am not thinking about them. I just want to see my birth mother, she was the one who abandoned me, but she also got Uncle Zhang to lead me on the road of cultivation. I want to meet her personally, and for the first and final time, before leaving. I am an Eastern Sea Gu Immortal, I became immortal in Eastern Sea."

Uncle Zhang smiled: "Young master, don't worry, first supreme elder had long since thought of this, she prepared everything for you. Even though you became immortal in Eastern Sea, we have an immortal killer move to cleanse your heaven and earth qi, to turn you from an Eastern Sea Gu Immortal to a Southern Border Gu Immortal. From now on, you can undergo tribulations in Southern Border, taking in heaven and earth qi without any problems."

"Oh? There is such a way..." Wu Yi Hai heard this and became overjoyed.

Even though he had some fame in Eastern Sea, he was just a lone cultivator, he knew the pain and weakness of cultivating alone. If he had a super force to rely on, Wu Yi Hai would be glad about it.

He was just thinking about this, when suddenly, dragon breath resembling sword light assaulted his face!

Chapter 1216: Regional Wall Ambush

This dragon breath was extremely sharp, before it even hit, Wu Yi Hai already felt like there were needles poking into his face.

He was extremely shocked, he had no time to dodge.

Clang!

With a sharp metallic sound, a small, round and golden shield appeared in front of Wu Yi Hai at the moment of life and death.

The dragon breath made of sword light landed on the golden shield, in the blink of an eye, this shield broke as the remaining power shot towards Wu Yi Hai's face.

But with this golden shield, Wu Yi Hai gained a precious amount of time to save his own life.

He was a renowned rank seven Gu Immortal in Eastern Sea indeed, he called out as he activated his transformation path killer move.

Light shone, Wu Yi Hai vanished on the spot, a huge tortoise appeared in his place.

The huge tortoise's four limbs, head, and tail were kept inside a shell.

The dragon breath landed on the huge tortoise's shell, causing a deep mark to form.

"What amazing dragon breath! The horned divine tortoise that I transformed into is an ancient desolate beast, it has a tough shell, it is top ten even among Eastern Sea's ancient desolate beasts." Wu Yi Hai was very shocked: "It seems that the enemy is stronger than all the earlier ambushes! Now, it will depend on Uncle Zhang and Brother Leng."

Wu Yi Hai was a transformation path Gu Immortal, but the horned divine tortoise he turned into was huge and had good speed when traveling underwater. On land, it was far slower.

Its battle strength also fell by a lot, Wu Yi Hai was merely using the horned divine tortoise's strong defense.

High defense and low offense, even though Wu Yi Hai protected his life, he lost all initiative in this battle.

He had other methods to turn into other lifeforms as well, but do not forget about the major weakness of transformation path Gu Immortals.

That was: They could not transform casually. When changing to different forms, time needed to be spent. Gu Immortals had to remove the temporary dao marks on them first before transforming again.

Fang Yuan had the sovereign immortal body, that was a special case. Qi Zai had once mistaken that he had obtained Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's true inheritance, which allowed him to casually change forms.

Thus, after Wu Yi Hai became a horned divine tortoise, even though he saved his life, for the short term, he could not counter attack.

But Wu Yi Hai did not panic.

He knew that there were two rank seven Gu Immortal experts with him.

One was Uncle Zhang, the other was Brother Leng, Wu Yi Hai did not know their full names, but he knew that these two were sent by his mother, bodyguards to escort him to Southern Border!

On the previous parts of this journey, these two Gu Immortals displayed incredible strength, they were reliable and had helped Wu Yi Hai to get through many hurdles.

Wu Yi Hai placed his hopes in Uncle Zhang and Brother Leng, but Uncle Zhang was spitting out blood.

He had to.

Because his golden shield was broken by that sword light dragon breath.

This was Uncle Zhang's defensive killer move, after it was broken, Uncle Zhang suffered a backlash, he immediately spat out blood.

Similar to Wu Yi Hai, Uncle Zhang was very shocked.

"Inside this miasma regional wall, all immortal killer moves are weakened by the miasma. This dragon breath penetrated the miasma and broke my defenses, it even left a mark on the horned divine tortoise shell, how strong is that dragon breath!"

Uncle Zhang was spitting blood, Brother Leng was flying forward.

The two worked with coordination.

This young Gu Immortal knew that Uncle Zhang needed to rest after his defensive killer move was broken.

He charged fiercely and imposingly.

In the blink of an eye, he turned from a human into a lightning flash giant wolf.

The lightning flash giant wolf was an ancient desolate beast, it was covered in blue fur, the tips of the fur was all covered in mysterious blue crystals, they gave off weak sparks.

Once the lightning flash giant wolf appeared, it brightened up the dark purple miasma in the area.

It followed the path formed by the dragon breath, and charging forward.

Its four limbs moved, its muscles pushed with strength, giving this Gu Immortal incredible speed.

At the same time, countless strands of lightning resembling snakes appeared on this lightning flash giant wolf's body.

The lightning snakes gathered into a stream that shot forward from the lightning flash giant wolf's head.

This was the Gu Immortal's immortal killer move.

Seeing this, Uncle Zhang relaxed his mind.

In a few breaths of time, he suppressed his injuries as his body shone in a bright light.

In the blink of an eye, he turned into a golden sword teeth tiger, his size was twice as large as the lightning flash giant wolf.

As it turned out, he was also a transformation path Gu Immortal.

This was Wu Du Xiu's purposeful arrangement.

Because the regional walls of the five regions were very special. Between different cultivation paths, there was no difference in terms of passing through them, but if they fought inside, transformation path Gu Immortals had an advantage.

Inside the regional wall, when Gu Immortals use their immortal killer moves, their immortal apertures would shake and they would get injured before even harming the enemy.

But if they turned into a fierce beast, fighting with just their physical body, this weakness would be avoided, and they would have a sustainable source of battle strength.

Uncle Zhang took a look behind, he knew of the horned divine tortoise's defense, he instructed Wu Yi Hai before following after the lightning flash giant wolf, charging forward.

Soon, Uncle Zhang saw the lightning flash giant wolf running back!

Behind the lightning flash giant wolf, there were streams of dragon breath made of sword light shooting towards him, inside the thick dark purple miasma, dragon roars could be heard.

"What is going on?" Uncle Zhang was shocked, he knew that the Brother Leng was very courageous in battle, he would not retreat without a reason. There has to be a reason why he was running!

"Don't fight, retreat." Brother Leng saw the golden tiger and spoke human words.

Uncle Zhang was even more shocked now, why did Brother Leng want to avoid battle.

He was about to ask, when he finally saw the culprit that attacked them.

A sword dragon penetrated the dark purple miasma, appearing before them.

Many layers of silvery white dragon scales, pale white dragon eyes, a dragon horn that pierced towards the sky, and four sharp and dangerous dragon claws, dragon teeth that were shining with sharp light, as well as the aura of many Immortal Gu in its body!

"Is this a wild ancient sword dragon?!" Uncle Zhang opened his eyes wide, unable to believe it.

But the truth was right in front of him, he had to accept it.

At this moment, he understood why the Gu Immortal who usually felt no fear in any situation would retreat so suddenly.

Because he encountered a wild ancient sword dragon, this sword dragon did not come from the five regions, it lived in either white heaven or black heaven.

Why was Uncle Zhang so sure?

Because this ancient sword dragon could move freely in the regional wall, its movements were so fluid, as if it did not feel any resistance or pressure.

For Gu Immortals, they were differentiated by regions, when they enter regional walls, they would be greatly affected.

Only life forms that lived in the ancient white heaven or black heaven would be able to move freely in the five regional walls.

Uncle Zhang did not hesitate, he turned around and fled.

Being unaffected by the regional wall, this advantage was huge. Gu Immortals in the regional walls could display only about fifty to sixty percent of their strength.

Even in the outside world, against an ancient sword dragon with multiple wild Immortal Gu, Uncle Zhang did not have confidence. Not to mention right now, when they were inside a special environment like the regional wall?

"Why are we so unlucky? So coincidentally, we encountered a wild ancient sword dragon, roaming in the regional wall?"

"I am guessing that this ancient sword dragon is likely to have been lured here by certain Gu Immortals, to obstruct us!"

While escaping, Uncle Zhang and Brother Leng conversed.

Soon, they met with the horned divine tortoise that Wu Yi Hai had turned into.

Wu Yi Hai was informed of the situation as well, he quickly transmitted: "Try not to fight with this ancient sword dragon, it might have been lured here, with the purpose of draining our immortal essence and battle strength as we fight it!"

"Then what do we do?"

"Retreat, leave the ancient sword dragon alone and try not to aggravate it, but we also have to display great strength. Wild beasts have little intelligence, but if it knows that the prey is powerful, it will give up."

The three Gu Immortals quickly decided on a plan.

Less offense and more defense, they allowed the ancient sword dragon to trail behind them, using its sword light dragon breath.

The three Gu Immortals retreated, they were on the back foot against the dragon breath, unable to raise their heads.

"What do we do, this ancient sword dragon seems to be locked onto us!"

"Maybe I aggravated it earlier when I used a lightning path killer move."

"I have an immortal killer move that can reduce the anger of this fierce beast, but I need to change my killer move."

The three immortals quickly discussed, they soon decided that Brother Leng and Uncle Zhang would defend while Wu Yi Hai would change his transformation to appease the ancient sword dragon.

Wu Yi Hai carefully changed back to human form.

He hid behind the two immortals, using his methods to get rid of the dao marks on him, before using another transformation.

As a wild beast, the ancient sword dragon would have little intelligence, it constantly attacked the huge wolf and golden tiger instead.

Uncle Zhang and Brother Leng thus endured the attacks of the ancient sword dragon, defending with much difficulty. They were both injured, but to chase this ancient sword dragon away, they did not use their offensive techniques, to prevent the situation from worsening and falling into their enemies' trap.

"It is almost ready, my immortal killer move is... uh!" Wu Yi Hai's joyous tone turned into a shocked gasp.

Because he saw that the golden tiger that Uncle Zhang had turned into had its head pierced by an immortal killer move, dying on the spot.

Sword path killer move — Dark Assassination!

It was so sudden, without any warning.

Next, that ancient sword dragon burst out with unparalleled speed in an instant, flying forward like a silver bolt of lightning, leaving behind vague silhouettes in the immortals' eyes as it vanished on the spot.

Brother Leng was shocked!

"We fell for their trap! Oh no!!"

He turned around, only to see that Wu Yi Hai's head was shattered into pieces, his white brain matter was flowing out. His headless corpse was grabbed by the ancient sword dragon, stuffed into its immortal aperture.

Chapter 1217: Cultivation Level Rises Again

Seeing this, the poor Brother Leng's eyes were almost popping out.

"How can this be? This ancient sword dragon has an immortal aperture, it is not wild, it is a Gu Immortal's transformation!"

"This should not be! If it is a transformation path Gu Immortal, why is it not affected by the regional wall?!"

Brother Leng screamed crazily in his mind!

This went against the common sense of the cultivation world!! How could this happen?

The ancient sword dragon roared as it charged at him.

Blood flowed out of the eyes of the lightning flash giant wolf, Wu Yi Hai was dead, everything that he did earlier was for nothing.

Brother Leng tried to defend himself, in order to save his own life.

The ancient sword dragon craftily dodged all of his immortal killer moves, spitting out streams of dragon breath at the lightning flash giant wolf as it flew around it.

The lightning flash giant wolf could barely move in the regional wall, like an old man. But the ancient sword dragon was unaffected, it moved smoothly and could retreat and advance with ease, it held the initiative.

The lightning flash giant wolf could only take a beating, even if it used immortal killer moves to retaliate, the ancient sword dragon easily dodged them.

A moment later, the ancient sword dragon found a flaw and sent dragon breath at the lightning flash giant wolf's stomach.

The lightning flash giant wolf's defenses crumbled, its stomach was penetrated, its intestines and blood flowed out of the huge wound that was created.

The ancient sword dragon attacked using this chance, even though the lightning flash giant wolf dodged left and right, it could not resist the attacks of the ancient sword dragon, it fell on the ground with many holes in its body, it turned back to human form and died in a pool of blood at the hands of the ancient sword dragon.

The ancient sword dragon quickly cleaned up the battlefield, moving with great familiarity, as if it had gone through this countless times.

Soon, Uncle Zhang and Brother Leng's corpses were stuffed into the immortal aperture, before it destroyed the battlefield entirely and flew away.

The ancient sword dragon did not turn around and return to Southern Border, instead, it flew towards the east, going through the miasma regional wall and blue water regional wall to reach Eastern Sea.

It searched for a nameless sea area before placing Wu Yi Hai in it.

After the blessed land was formed, the entrance was opened, and the ancient sword dragon flew in using the opportunity.

Wu Yi Hai's blessed land was an ocean. The types of lifeforms inside mainly were sea turtles and tortoises, corals, and seagulls.

Inside, there were desolate beasts, and even ancient desolate beasts.

Like three ancient desolate beast horned divine tortoises, a field of ancient desolate plant silent corals, and six desolate beast white letter blue feather seagulls.

Not long after, the land spirit appeared before the ancient sword dragon.

This was a land spirit in the shape of a sea turtle, it gave a rather difficult acknowledgement requirement.

The ancient sword dragon could only leave this blessed land temporarily.

After returning to the outside world and confirming its safety, the ancient sword dragon turned back to human.

Who else could it be but Fang Yuan?

As it turned out, he had learned a lot of intelligence about Southern Border from Lady White Rabbit, he knew about Wu Yi Hai's matter.

This was Wu clan's internal conflict, but it involved Wu Du Xiu, naturally it escalated into a huge matter.

Wu Yi Hai's route was widely spread, Fang Yuan sensed acutely that this was a major chance!

Evidently, Wu Yi Hai was very suitable for Fang Yuan to disguise as and replace.

Firstly, he was Wu Du Xiu's illegitimate son, he did not have any life tablet Gu or soul lantern Gu, otherwise, he would not be an illegitimate son but the second young master instead.

Thus, when Fang Yuan killed him, there was little chance that Wu clan found out.

Secondly, Wu Yi Hai had always been staying in Eastern Sea, cultivating as a lone cultivator, he had basically zero interaction with Wu clan's Gu Immortals. Most of Wu clan's Gu Immortals did not even know what his appearance was, especially the details regarding his habits and the way he spoke, nobody knew about those.

Thus, once Fang Yuan used familiar face to disguise as Wu Yi Hai, for a long period of time, there was little chance of him getting exposed.

Wu Yi Hai's blessed land was not obtained, but Fang Yuan did not panic.

He found a deserted island and rested in it.

On one hand, he was waiting for blood asset Immortal Gu to recover, on the other hand, he was trying to modify an immortal killer move — Blood Light Spirit Suppression.

Ever since blood asset Immortal Gu was injured, Fang Yuan had been healing it, paying great attention to it, it had almost recovered fully already.

Thus, in a few days, Fang Yuan got back his blood asset Immortal Gu in perfect condition.

But Fang Yuan continued to cultivate, deducing blood light spirit suppression.

Finally, he got what he wanted, a simplified version of blood light spirit suppression using blood asset Immortal Gu as the core!

Matters became simpler now.

Fang Yuan used the upper extreme heavenly eagle to enter Wu Yi Hai's blessed land, after getting close to the land spirit, he suppressed it with blood light spirit suppression.

Next, because the land spirit had no resistance anymore, Fang Yuan spent a lot of effort to successfully annex this blessed land, making it a part of the sovereign immortal aperture.

This allowed his calamities and tribulations to move ahead by a large number.

After all, Wu Yi Hai was a rank seven Gu Immortal, he was different from those at rank six.

As for Wu Yi Hai's sea turtle land spirit, under Fang Yuan's careful preservation, it did not vanish, it entered Fang Yuan's immortal aperture along with the blessed land.

But it did not listen to Fang Yuan, it cried all the time.

Fang Yuan wanted to get rid of it, but after realizing that it did not have the intention to harm the blessed land, he gave up that idea.

"Maybe when I fulfill the ownership requirement, I would be able to truly subdue this land spirit."

After this matter was settled, Fang Yuan immediately traveled across the regional walls, going back to Southern Border.

Once he entered Southern Border, he flew straight towards the central region of Southern Border, placing the immortal apertures of Brother Leng and Uncle Zhang and annexing them after they formed blessed lands.

"Hmm, this way, I have already passed one grand tribulation." Fang Yuan inspected, he found that after annexing three rank seven Gu Immortals' blessed lands, his cultivation level rose sharply, he was a rank seven Gu Immortal who had passed one grand tribulation already.

Rank seven Gu Immortals faced an earthly calamity every ten years, a heavenly tribulation every fifty years, and a grand tribulation every one hundred years. After three hundred years, after passing three grand tribulations, they would become rank eight.

"But the might of the grand tribulation gets stronger each time, by tens or hundreds of times. Southern Border's top rank seven Gu Immortal, Old Treeman Ba De, is stuck at the final grand tribulation, he does not dare to undergo tribulation."

His gains this time were out of Fang Yuan's expectations.

Not only did he annex three rank seven blessed lands, it even caused his cultivation level to rise sharply, such cultivation speed was scary even for him.

Fang Yuan could not help but gasp at his good luck!

"Dog shit luck Immortal Gu, worthy of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's vital Gu. I wonder what will happen when I elevate it to rank eight, how would it compare to fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu?"

Fang Yuan subconsciously looked above his head, even though he had no luck inspection Immortal Gu.

He did not know that the entire matter went so smoothly largely because of Ying Wu Xie, he had used the immortal killer move burning soul bursting luck.

Especially when he fought against the three Gu Immortals including Wu Yi Hai, they actually misunderstood Fang Yuan as a wild ancient sword dragon.

One one hand, ancient sword dragons truly could be unrestricted by regional walls, they could not help but think of it like that.

On the other hand, Fang Yuan had used attitude Gu and disguised himself, the three Gu Immortals were just rank seven, they fell for it without realizing.

Thus, when fighting, Fang Yuan had an easy time, the three Gu Immortals defended more than they attacked, they chose to take a beating.

Later on, Wu Yi Hai thought the ancient sword dragon had low intelligence and actually spoke, saying that he was going to attempt to change into another form.

Hearing this, the two immortals naturally relaxed their minds.

Fang Yuan saw this massive opportunity and activated the killer move that he had prepared long ago, dark assassination, killing Uncle Zhang. Next, he attacked at lightning speed, eliminating Wu Yi Hai, in the blink of an eye, only Brother Leng was left. At that point, Fang Yuan's victory was assured.

In this battle, Fang Yuan gained immensely.

The only drawback was, these three transformation path Gu Immortals' immortal apertures had shaken intensely, a lot of resources were lost.

There was no helping it, they were attacked many times in the regional walls, it was impressive to have lasted until then.

Next, Fang Yuan did not go to Wu clan immediately.

He soul searched Wu Yi Hai as he tried to understand his entire life.

During this period, Fang Yuan was not cultivating in seclusion, he went to Lady White Rabbit for more intelligence.

Wu Yi Hai's disappearance was known to the whole of Southern Border.

It was unknown if he was alive or dead, Wu clan chose to remain silent. The forces had their guesses, although they were inclined to believe — Wu Yi Hai was dead, but it was unknown who did it.

There were many forces who acted in the dark, most of them were righteous path forces, this matter was known to everyone.

These forces were not going to foolishly admit they were the ones who killed Wu Yi Hai, of course.

Regarding this problem, there was a rumor that was entering everyone's ears.

That was — the true culprit who murdered Wu Yi Hai was none other than Wu clan rank eight Gu Immortal Wu Yong!

There were many versions of this rumor, but the central claim was, Wu Yong wanted to take Wu Du Xiu's inheritance for himself, thus, he went ahead to murder his half-brother.

Undeniably, this was a severe blow to Wu Yong.

Demonic path Gu Immortals did not care, while it varied from person to person for lone immortals, but righteous path Gu Immortals placed a lot of emphasis on and treasured their reputations.

Wu Yong also chose to remain silent, he did not clarify anything.

"Interesting." Fang Yuan could feel many hidden undercurrents in this matter, countless forces and Gu Immortals were secretly exerting force, creating this contest that was carefully hidden from view.

Wu Du Xiu was about to die, Wu Yong, who had always lived in his mother's shadow, had rank eight cultivation level, but his abilities were widely questioned.

"If I appear at this time, what would happen?" Fang Yuan had just thought of this when he felt a cold chill running down his spine.

Chapter 1218: Du Xiu, Yong

Fang Yuan looked over the situation, he knew that now was not the time for 'Wu Yi Hai' to show up.

Firstly, he had not completely searched Wu Yi Hai's soul yet, his preparations were not complete.

Secondly, Wu Du Xiu was not dead yet.

If Wu Du Xiu did not die, Fang Yuan could not safely appear as Wu Yi Hai.

Rank eight Gu Immortal!

Who knew what methods Wu Du Xiu had to ascertain if 'Wu Yi Hai' was her own son?

Even though 'Wu Yi Hai' would lose a lot in this case, Fang Yuan only really wanted the identity of 'Wu Yi Hai'.

That was his original motive. If his disguise failed because of some greed, he would lose this rare opportunity, that was the biggest loss to him, he would slap himself endlessly.

Finally, there was danger lurking in all righteous path forces, the same went for even Wu clan.

There was no smoke without fire.

Wu Yong indeed had the motive and was likely to deal with Wu Yi Hai.

If Fang Yuan appeared too early, he might get killed by Wu clan secretly.

"Speaking of which, Wu Yi Hai's identity is quite troublesome. But thankfully, I have future memories, I know what happened in the five hundred years of my previous life, this can help me analyze the situation."

Just like this, Fang Yuan continued to cultivate.

He continued to soul search Wu Yi Hai while collecting information about the outside world.

Wu Du Xiu's condition was getting worse every day, the entirety of Southern Border was in a commotion.

Over in Northern Plains, the blood battle martial competition was still ongoing. Without Liu Guan Yi, Chu Du's side was completely suppressed. But soon, the situation changed, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu personally invited three rank seven lone immortals and they won consecutively, helping Chu Du's side reach a deadlock with the righteous path alliance.

Liu tribe Gu Immortal Liu Chang had been announcing that he wanted Liu Guan Yi to fight him, otherwise, he was a coward, a chicken and more.

Not only was Liu Chang seeking to trouble Fang Yuan, the same went for other forces like Ye Lui tribe. But Liu Guan Yi had vanished without a trace, as if this person had never existed in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world!

These pursuing forces were bound to fail, but over in Central Continent, many Gu Immortals had worse fates.

Defy!

This underground organization created by Shadow Sect's Gu Immortals had been eradicated completely by Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals as well as the ten great ancient sects.

Other than that, many of the people on the Demon Judgment Board had been captured, blood path demonic immortals were killed, while some other demonic path or lone immortals had less severe crimes, they were taken away by the ten great ancient sects and turned into slave Gu Immortals.

On a certain day, half a month later, Wu Du Xiu summoned Wu Yong and several other Wu clan supreme elders to her house.

At her dying moments, Wu Du Xiu spoke with unprecedented clarity, she said: "I have three regrets in life."

"The first regret is that I failed to exterminate the Seven Fierce Gorge Ghosts, I only destroyed their den."

"The second regret is that I did not managed to find enough dry clear qi to refine eight-faced prestige wind Gu."

"The third regret..."

Saying this, Wu Du Xiu paused.

"Is that I did not get to see my son Yi Hai. Back then... I hated his father, I killed him, but I should not have placed that hatred and anger on a pure and innocent child, he is blameless. I want to make it up to him, but it is too late."

In the house, nobody made a sound, it was silent.

Wu Du Xiu sighed, sitting up on her own.

She got into a half sitting position with much difficulty, leaning on the head of her bed, she waved to Wu Yong weakly.

Wu Yong understood her intention, he quickly pulled the curtains apart and stepped forward, getting to Wu Du Xiu and kneeling down reverently.

Wu Du Xiu looked at her eldest son and smiled after a long time: "Yong Er, you are good, I am not disappointed."

Wu Yong's body shuddered, he raised his head, his eyes were red, tears were sprinkling down.

At this moment, he was expressing his true emotions, this old woman in front of him was his mother after all!

"I am handing Wu clan to you, I can rest assured." Wu Du Xiu continued to say.

"Mother." Wu Yong opened his mouth, his voice was hoarse, tears were streaming down his face.

Wu Du Xiu continued: "My child Yi Hai was unable to come here, that is fate. Forget it, I will hand these Immortal Gu to you. You cultivate wind path as well, I hope you can cherish them and put them to good use."

"Mother, I don't want your Immortal Gu, I just want you to live!" Wu Yong sobbed.

"Silly child, who can avoid dying? Even Immortal Venerables and Demon Venerables with immense strength die in the end. Eternal life is but a fantasy of fools."

Saying this, Wu Du Xiu's Immortal Gu flew out of her immortal aperture, going towards Wu Yong.

The Wu clan supreme elders on the other side of the curtain watched this quietly.

The transfer was smooth.

Aura of Immortal Gu faded into Wu Yong's body one by one.

Wu Du Xiu looked outside the window.

The sunlight was bright, through the small window, it entered the room.

In a daze, Wu Du Xiu could almost see a figure in the sunlight.

That figure was neither her father or mother, it was also not the man who she had once loved in her life, it was herself.

That young version of herself, the lady whose smile was as bright as the sun.

Wu Du Xiu.

Wu Du Xiu.

"Hehe." Wu Du Xiu muttered her own name twice, before laughing lightly.

Her body began to shine with white light, countless white specks were flying out of her shriveled old body.

The specks of light were the dissipation of her soul and body.

A moment later, there was nobody left on the bed, the reputable and powerful rank eight Gu Immortal, Wu Du Xiu, a legendary person who had exerted her influence on Southern Border for thousands of years, had at this moment, vanished from this world.

She did not leave behind her body or her soul.

"First supreme elder—!"

Outside the curtain, Wu clan's supreme elders cried out with sorrow.

Cries filled this small house without any owner.

Incredible anguish was vented through crying.

Wu Yong cried quietly, he knelt on the ground, lowering his head and not moving, like a statue.

Long after, he slowly raised his head, he no longer cried, his expression was as firm as steel.

He stood up.

Next, he looked at the Wu clan supreme elders through the curtain, they were sprawling on the ground, crying painfully without any of their usual demeanor.

"Everyone, hold in your sadness. Mother is gone, but we have to continue enveloping Southern Border with Wu clan's glory!" Wu Yong's plain tone carried extraordinary authority.

The supreme elders gradually stopped crying.

Wu Yong pulled the curtain aside, walking out.

The supreme elders had already stood up, they realized something.

The atmosphere had become heavy, these Gu Immortal elders paid their respects towards Wu Yong, they said together: "We pay respects to first supreme elder!"

The legend of a generation, Wu Du Xiu had died, as her son, Wu Yong with rank eight cultivation level became the next first supreme elder of Wu clan.

After news got out from Wu clan, it spread through the entire Southern Border Gu Immortal world at lightning speed!

Southern Border was in a commotion.

Wu Du Xiu had finally died, many Gu Immortals and forces let out sighs of relief.

Wu clan originally had two rank eight Gu Immortals, but now only one was left, could it still remain as the number one righteous path force?

Wu clan seemed to have too many resource points under its control.

Wu Du Xiu was gone, only Wu Yong, who had insufficient talent and abilities, was left, could he truly lead Wu clan on a path of glory?

Not only were the Gu Immortals outside of Wu clan thinking about this, even within Wu clan, many members were doubtful towards the abilities of this new first supreme elder.

And also the rumors of Wu Yong killing his half-brother Wu Yi Hai, at this moment, they were spread around fiercely, like the surface of boiling water, bubbles were emerging fiercely.

Qing Yang Mountain.

Qiao clan's headquarters were here.

Two Gu Immortals of Qiao clan were standing at the peak, looking in Wu clan's direction.

The two immortals could see many layers of clouds, mountains winds were blowing and causing their sleeves to flutter.

Qiao clan's first supreme elder sighed: "Wu Du Xiu is dead, Wu Yong has just taken over her position, but he is already plagued by the rumors of killing his brother, hehe, this is a good opportunity for our Qiao clan. Everyone thinks that we are Wu clan's lackey, but the truth is, we were just trying to survive. With Wu clan's commotion, we can finally have a chance to take action. Compared to other clans, we have better reasons to do this because of our long term marriage alliances with Wu clan!"

"Wu Yong seems ordinary, but I feel like he is not so simple. Even if he is not talented, he is still a rank eight Gu Immortal." The other Gu Immortal spoke.

She looked like a woman in her twenties, she wore a green dress that could not conceal her alluring body shape. Her skin was white as snow, her eyes were concealed by her long eyelashes, they seemed clear as water.

She was Qiao clan's pride, a genius that was the hope for the future, as well as one of the three great fairies of Southern Border — Qiao Si Liu.

Qiao clan's first supreme elder laughed:" Oh Liu Er, this is the reason why I asked you to talk to me. We are going to continue our marriage alliance with Wu clan."

Qiao Si Liu's body shook: "I understand, I am willing to contribute to the clan."

"Very good, the clan did not raise you in vain." Qiao clan's first supreme elder was very glad.

"But if I marry Wu Yong, I might not be able to control him. He is a rank eight Gu Immortal, he even has authority over the entirety of Wu clan..." Qiao Si Liu hesitated.

"Not with him." Qiao clan's first supreme elder smiled.

"Then who else?" Qiao Si Liu was visibly confused.

"Wu Yi Hai."

"Wu Yi Hai?"

"That's right, he approached us a few days ago."

Seven days later.

Wu clan held a grand funeral on Divine Wind Mountain.

All the righteous path forces, as well as many lone immortal experts, even certain special demonic path Gu Immortals were invited for the funeral.

In front of everyone's eyes, Wu Yong suddenly erupted: "Men, take down this traitor of the clan!"

"What?!" Xu Tuo was shocked, he wanted to resist but it was too late.

"Master, what are you doing?! I am your most loyal and dedicated servant!" Xu Tuo screamed loudly.

"Hehe." Wu Yong chuckled, he pointed at Xu Tuo as he shouted: "You are a loyal and dedicated servant indeed, Xu Tuo! To think I trusted you so deeply, yet you harmed me, leaking the travel route of my brother, and causing countless fiends to attack him. My poor brother, I have not even met him, but he was already killed by you bunch of evil fiends!"

Saying this, Wu Yong sighed at the sky, tears flowing down his face.

Xu Tuo looked on, dumbfounded.

The shock inside him could not be expressed with words.

He wanted to deny it, but Wu Yong tossed out a bunch of evidence!

The evidence could not be overturned.

Xu Tuo had no way of rebutting, he realized now that Wu Yong had found out his identity long ago, he endured all this while, until today!

Wu Yong made use of him to exterminate his brother Wu Yi Hai, and also fully obtaining the inheritance. He became Wu clan's first supreme elder, and shattered all of the rumors regarding him on this very day.

Xu Tuo was the sacrificial pawn that he discarded.

"Today, I will win everything!" Wu Yong laughed in his mind, but he pointed at Xu Tuo, ordering: "Drag him away!"

The righteous path representatives were uneasy, even those demonic path and lone immortals showed shock on their faces.

Wu Yong looked around, feeling extremely satisfied.

But just as he was about to speak, Qiao clan's first supreme elder stood up: "I have good news for Lord Wu Yong. Your brother Wu Yi Hai did not die, not only did he survive, he has arrived here with the help of my Qiao clan."

"What?"

Chapter 1219: Fang Yuan versus Wu Yong

Fang Yuan took large strides, walking out of the group of Qiao clan Gu Immortals.

At once, everyone's focus was gathered on him.

Fang Yuan instantly became the center of attention.

Seeing his face, multiple supreme elders of Wu clan gasped: "They are really alike."

Fang Yuan's appearance, no, Wu Yi Hai's appearance, was very similar to his birth mother Wu Du Xiu. This was an undeniable point, it was Fang Yuan's advantage.

Wu Yong was different, he resembled his father, he had complementing eyes and brows, he looked very ordinary, he had a natural unremarkable aura.

But Wu Yi Hai was different.

He was handsome and muscular, he stood out from the crowd like a spear stabbing at the sky. Even though he lived in Eastern Sea, his traits were very similar to Wu clan Gu Immortals, especially his nose, it was wide and tall, at a glance, people could tell that this person was very extraordinary, he had a firm personality and could not be looked down upon.

Of course, the reason why Fang Yuan could give off such an impression was highly attributed to his appearance.

The real Wu Yi Hai did not have the traits of a Wu clansman.

Rank eight immortal killer move — Familiar Face!

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's signature method, it was displaying its worth right now, all of these Gu Immortals were deceived, none of them could tell that Fang Yuan was an impostor.

The truth was, even Wu clan's Gu Immortals were seeing Wu Yi Hai for the first time.

Undoubtedly, Fang Yuan's prior preparation and hard work was rewarded now. When Wu clan's Gu Immortals looked at him, they held some good feelings towards him.

Because Wu Yi Hai looked like Wu Du Xiu.

Wu Du Xiu was not beautiful, she had features that suited a man, if she were a male, she would be a grand hero that could rival heaven.

Wu Yi Hai bore seventy percent resemblance to her.

Wu Du Xiu died, Wu clan was in a commotion, the clan's Gu Immortals were all in remembrance of Wu Du Xiu's achievements and glory.

After all, humans were like this, they did not feel much attachment towards people when they were still alive, but the moment they were gone, they would want to cherish and appreciate them.

Fang Yuan appeared at this juncture, it made good use of the immortals' mental state.

Of course, this was part of Fang Yuan's calculations.

"Alike, they really look alike." Even other clans' Gu Immortals were sighing.

Fang Yuan sensed sharply that the gazes on him were changing slowly.

In the five hundred years of his previous life, he did not have the achievement of high cultivation level, but he had gone through five hundred years of life, he had nurtured an unfathomably deep ability to observe situations, and an acute perception towards the changes of emotions in the Gu Immortals near him.

He sensed that the gazes of Wu clan's Gu Immortals were welcoming, while Wu Yong's gaze carried animosity in it.

Wu Yong was indeed shocked.

Fang Yuan had disguised as 'Wu Yi Hai' and appeared, this greatly affected his plans and arrangements.

What made Wu Yong alarmed was that Fang Yuan and Qiao clan's Gu Immortals were together, he felt a sense of wariness.

The truth was, Wu Yong hated this younger brother of his in the deepest part of his heart.

Even though both sides were meeting for the first time.

Wu Yong did not like Fang Yuan at first sight.

Because Wu Yi Hai looked too much like his mother Wu Du Xiu.

So many years.

Wu Yong had followed by Wu Du Xiu's side, growing under her protection.

Wu Du Xiu was a giant tree, the leaves of the tree protected the entirety of Wu clan, including Wu Yong himself.

Wu Yong felt like he was constantly lowering his head, the shade of the tree was a type of shadow that loomed over his life.

He was Wu Du Xiu's son, but do not forget, he was a man.

Men naturally sought strength, having an intense desire towards authority.

But all along, Wu Yong was under Wu Du Xiu's shadow, her strength, her abilities, as well as her identity, Wu Yong could not resist her, he had to lower his head.

Wu Du Xiu passed away, Wu Yong was naturally very upset and grieved, but at the same time, unavoidably, he felt freedom, he felt... joy.

This joy was something that Wu Yong did not dare to admit he felt.

But now, when Wu Yong saw this Wu Yi Hai who resembled Wu Du Xiu, he unavoidably felt some feelings of dislike.

Fang Yuan sensed Wu Yong's ill intent and animosity, even though he disguised himself well.

Fang Yuan knew on the inside: "The first step of showing myself succeeded, but the second step of interacting with Wu clan and getting them to acknowledge me is the crucial one."

"Being accepted by Wu clan means getting Wu Yong, this rank eight Gu Immortal, the first supreme elder of Wu clan's acknowledgement!"

Thus, when Fang Yuan stepped into the limelight, he bowed deeply towards Wu Yong: "Wu Yi Hai pays respects to elder brother."

Wu Yong had an agitated but hesitant expression: "Are you really my brother Yi Hai? Alike, you really look like mother, except that your eyes are blue, we don't usually have that eye color in Southern Border."

That sentence had deep meaning.

Wu Yong did not directly acknowledge Fang Yuan's identity, instead, he pointed out the Eastern Sea Gu Immortal identity of 'Wu Yi Hai' seemingly unintentionally.

Fang Yuan answered solemnly: "Reporting to brother, I had black eyes before, but some accidents occurred when I cultivated transformation path. Right now, I returned due to mother's arrangement. Unfortunately, I met with many attacks along the way, Uncle Zhang and Brother Leng, who traveled with me, died on the battlefield while protecting me as I escaped."

"Both Zhang and Leng were simply attendants of my mother, but they made great contributions to Wu clan. Pass my orders, we will give them a grand burial, according to the rules of how we treat external supreme elders. Their descendants will also be taken care of, and be treated as equals in our Wu clan." Wu Yong instructed.

The supreme elders quickly responded.

Fang Yuan heard this and snickered internally.

This Wu Yong refused to give up any chance to show off his wise image, but hearing his words, he did not accept Fang Yuan's identity. He avoided the important topic, taking about Zhang and Leng and ignoring the important point — his brother Wu Yi Hai.

Wu Yong ignored this part, but Fang Yuan was not helpless.

This could not stop him.

Fang Yuan bowed as he said: "I hope brother can allow me to pay respects to our mother!"

Wu Yong's brows tightened.

Fang Yuan's words were very logical, as a son, his mother had passed away, how could he not pay respects to her?

This was an extremely reasonable request, especially in a clan system where bloodline was crucial in maintaining relationships, even Wu Yong could not stop him.

If he said no, outsiders would react badly to it, his new image that had been painstakingly created would be completely ruined.

But if he did not refuse Fang Yuan's request, then that would mean that Wu clan was acknowledging Fang Yuan's identity, that he was a member of Wu clan!

As a matter of fact, Wu Yong did not want that.

Wu Yong disliked Wu Yi Hai's appearance.

Wu Yi Hai's identity was a headache to Wu Yong.

Wu Yi Hai came here with Qiao clan, it was a huge warning to Wu Yong!

"This Wu Yi Hai should go back to where he came from. Isn't he an Eastern Sea Gu Immortal? Then let him develop in Eastern Sea, even if I have to spend some resources to get him to leave."

This was the best result for Wu Yong.

In fact, Fang Yuan's performance and the Qiao clan Gu Immortals' testament made Wu Yong not suspicious towards Fang Yuan's true identity.

"Wait, what if I get rid of this Wu Yi Hai?"

"I could not do it earlier because mother was around. But now, I am first supreme elder, this is my territory, in time, I will gain control of the clan, I can make arrangements in secret and execute him, wouldn't that end my troubles?"

"Even if he is in Eastern Sea, it is a problem. If he is not in Eastern Sea and stays in Southern Border, the problem is even bigger."

"I might as well agree to his current request. Eventually, I can go through some arrangements and demonstrate him to be a fake, I will be able to openly get rid of him!"

Thinking of this, Wu Yong felt intense killing intent surging in him.

He was about to speak, and directly agree to Fang Yuan's request, when suddenly, a supreme elder of Wu clan said: "Pardon me, but is everyone forgetting to confirm second young master Wu Yi Hai's identity. I am not suspecting him, or suspecting anyone from Qiao clan, but for him to come back to the clan, that is a necessary procedure!"

Wu Yong heard this and his brows tightened again.

He looked at the Wu clan Gu Immortal who spoke deeply, it was Wu clan's third supreme elder, Wu Qiao[1].

The gazes of Fang Yuan and Qiao clan's first supreme elder met secretly, he thought: "It was right to contact Qiao clan, but I did not think that Qiao clan had infiltrated Wu clan so deeply, reaching up to the third supreme elder, Wu Qiao."

Qiao clan's first supreme elder looked at Fang Yuan, thinking about the scene in which they schemed and collaborated...

"As long as I appear during the funeral, Wu Yong would be in a passive position. Even as a rank eight Gu Immortal who can easily kill me with his strength, he cannot do anything to me there. Hehehe."

Fang Yuan laughed as he continued: "He will not attack or kill me. Because he is Wu clan's first supreme elder, he is not a lone cultivator or a demonic cultivator. By then, if I request to pay respects to our mother, what can Wu Yong do to stop me?"

"Hahaha, brilliant, truly brilliant!" Qiao clan's first supreme elder gave a thumbs up: "Privately acknowledging your heritage is too dangerous. If we do this, it is brilliant, even if Wu Yong disagrees, what can he do?"

Fang Yuan said seriously: "Thus, we must undergo the acknowledgement during the funeral. If we miss this chance, it will be difficult. Not only would the risks be higher, Wu Yong would not even give us any opportunity."

"Don't worry, by then, I will speak up and suggest this." Qiao clan's first supreme elder smiled.

"No, no, no." Fang Yuan shook his head: "It is unsuitable for you to suggest it, you are an outsider, how can you interfere in Wu clan's business?"

Qiao clan's first supreme elder fell into silence.

Fang Yuan's words directly addressed his biggest concern. This was a huge problem he was facing. If this was not solved, he could not cooperate with 'Wu Yi Hai'.

Fang Yuan's arms were behind his back, he raised his head and looked outside the window: "Therefore, I need a supreme elder from Wu clan, he can openly suggest this, and steer the situation towards the heritage acknowledgement."

Qiao clan's first supreme elder was a bit troubled: "This..."

[1] The Qiao in his name (樵) is different to the Qiao in Qiao clan (乔) Back

Chapter 1220: Presence in Southern Border

Fang Yuan continued to say: "This supreme elder should have some status, and he needs to have a firm attitude! Because during this period, Wu Yong is likely to side with me, acting as if I am already confirmed to be his brother to deny this suggestion. Thus, the person we choose needs to be able to stand the pressure of a rank eight Gu Immortal!"

Qiao clan's first supreme elder shrugged: "This is too difficult. After all, Wu Yong is not only a rank eight Gu Immortal, he is also Wu clan's first supreme elder, he inherited Wu Du Xiu's Immortal Gu."

Fang Yuan did not even turn around, he still looked outside.

His words turned cold and firm: "Don't tell me Qiao clan does not have such a person. If you don't, why do you have ambitions towards Wu clan? Just give up and sleep, you might have more success in your dreams. I, Wu Yi Hai, will not cooperate with such a clan!"

Qiao clan's first supreme elder was slightly stunned, he assessed Fang Yuan again.

From his angle, he could only see Fang Yuan's side view.

Outside the window, the rays of the setting sun shone on Fang Yuan's face, like a layer of blood.

Fang Yuan's expression was firm like steel, his blue eyes were brimming with life.

"This man... hehe, interesting. As expected of Wu Du Xiu's son." Qiao clan's first supreme elder sighed to himself internally, before agreeing: "We will go with your idea."

...

Even though Wu Du Xiu was dead, at her funeral, there was a peculiar and interesting scene.

Wu Du Xiu's illegitimate son from Eastern Sea, Wu Yi Hai, had appeared, wanting to pay respects to his mother.

All of the Gu Immortals from different forces watched quietly without interfering.

After all, these were Wu clan's internal affairs.

Among them, many Gu Immortals could see some things beyond the surface.

But when Wu clan's third supreme elder, Wu Qiao, spoke, multiple gazes landed on him.

Wu Qiao seemed unfazed, showing an attitude of being impartial and upright. He was Wu clan's third supreme elder!

Qiao clan could infiltrate Wu clan to this extent, Fang Yuan was shocked.

Of course, he was one of the parties involved, he knew more and had clearer judgment. People not in the know, without knowing the reasons behind this, would not be able to tell what Wu Qiao's stance was.

Was he siding with Wu clan or Qiao clan?

Even though Wu Yong noticed this possibility, he could not ascertain the facts.

Wu Yong spoke: "Alright, we will hold the acknowledgement of my brother's heritage here at my mother's funeral. I am sure that my mother would be very glad to see this happen."

He did not rebuke them, he directly agreed to it.

Fang Yuan looked at Wu Yong deeply, this person was not simple!

Qiao clan's first supreme elder was also slightly surprised by Wu Yong's reaction, his evaluation of Wu Yong rose by a level.

Evidently, Wu Yong had noticed that he could not stop Fang Yuan from the acknowledgement of his heritage. If he continued to reject it, he would lose his reputation and image, he might as well agree and allow this matter.

"All of the immortals here can bear witness to it, bring the Immortal Gu!" Third supreme elder Wu Qiao stood up, he needed to be the host of this event, to prevent Wu Yong and the rest from tampering with it.

Soon, Wu clan brought the Immortal Gu.

Wu Qiao stood before Fang Yuan, holding an Immortal Gu in his hand, saying: "This is a rank seven blood path Immortal Gu, Bloodline, my Wu clan obtained it from killing a blood path demonic immortal, it is our trophy of victory, it can be used to certify second young master's identity."

As he said this, the Gu Immortals present internally rolled their eyes.

Blood path was not tolerated, it was too dangerous.

But the truth was, every righteous path force was secretly researching it. Because blood path could increase one's battle strength the quickest.

Evidently, this bloodline Immortal Gu was the product of Wu clan's research, but they called it their loot from battle.

"Second young master, please provide a drop of blood!" Wu Qiao said.

Fang Yuan was tense.

It was a rank seven blood path Immortal Gu!

This was out of his expectations.

A drop of blood was different from examining his body, it was hard to tamper with.

Under everyone's supervision, Fang Yuan followed what he said and squeezed out a drop of blood to Wu Qiao.

Wu Qiao used the Immortal Gu and aimed towards the blood in his hand, as a dark red light shone.

There were no issues.

Fang Yuan let out a sigh of relief.

"Thankfully, blood asset Immortal Gu recovered, and I added it into familiar face to disguise my bloodline. Last time, I deceived measures in Hei Fan's true inheritance, while this time, I got past the rank seven blood path Immortal Gu Bloodline."

Thankfully, it was only rank seven, if it were rank eight, he might not be able to deceive it.

Fang Yuan was quite lucky in this aspect.

Of course, Wu clan was not going to be so wasteful as to raise a blood path Immortal Gu to rank eight.

Refining a rank eight Immortal Gu had too high of a cost, it could dry up a super force's assets without assurance of success.

But this was not all.

Next, Wu Qiao asked Fang Yuan many crucial questions.

Some of these questions, Fang Yuan knew the answers, while some he did not, he answered honestly.

Among the questions, some were traps, events that had never happened were used to trick him.

But Fang Yuan had searched Wu Yi Hai's soul, he could deal with these questions.

The true danger was the rank seven Immortal Gu Bloodline, he had already passed that, there was little difficulty left.

Hundreds of questions were asked, Wu Qiao was still expressionless.

But the other Wu clan supreme elders nodded, some of them were smiling, looking at Fang Yuan, showing that he had already passed the test.

"Actually, we also had to inspect your soul and bones, but Lady Wu Du Xiu has passed away, we will skip that." Wu Qiao said, making Fang Yuan feel extremely glad.

Thankfully, he was not greedy regarding those rank eight Immortal Gu.

If he was questioned by her in person, his soul path and bone path methods were not impressive, there was a high chance of him showing a flaw.

"I heard that when Wu Du Xiu died, her body turned into specks of light, none of her body remained. Even her hair and other things left behind had dissipated as well. She really died completely without leaving a trace, it is a good death!" Fang Yuan was overjoyed at his luck.

Next, Wu Qiao reported his findings to Wu Yong.

Needless to say, everyone had already seen the result.

Wu Yong nodded, while the other Wu clan supreme elders also agreed.

Thus, Wu Qiao took out life tablet Gu and soul lantern Gu, asking Fang Yuan to refine them. These Gu worms would be left in Wu clan's ancestral hall, they were the symbol of Fang Yuan's acknowledgement into the clan.

After all this, Fang Yuan had finally used Wu Yi Hai's identity to step into Southern Border's Gu Immortal world.

After paying respects to Wu Du Xiu, Fang Yuan cried profusely, showing off a fantastic performance with incredible acting.

As it was now Wu Du Xiu's funeral, Wu clan could not hold a banquet. But after the ceremony ended, Fang Yuan interacted with many Wu clan Gu Immortals, even though they only drank tea and talked for a while, Fang Yuan benefited greatly.

Of course, Gu Immortals asked to spar with Fang Yuan, but he rejected them all.

His status was very high now!

He had rank seven cultivation level, he was the brother of Wu clan's first supreme elder, the rank eight Gu Immortal Wu Yong.

Even though these brothers were of separate minds, on the surface, it seemed that their bloodline bonded them together.

Seven days later, the funeral ended, Fang Yuan stood beside the Wu clan Gu Immortals, sending off the guests who came, like he was an important part of the clan.

These Southern Border Gu Immortals remembered Fang Yuan well.

Many of them listed him as someone they could not trifle with, not because of Fang Yuan's cultivation level, but because he was blood related to Wu Yong.

Wu Yi Hai's name spread in Southern Border. Even though it could not be said that everyone knew about it, he was not far off.

Three days later.

Dawn, the sun rose slowly in the sky.

Fang Yuan was standing on the peak of Bear Mountain, quietly looking at the beautiful sunrise.

After the acknowledgement of his heritage, he was assigned by Wu clan to live on this Bear Mountain.

This was not within the blessed land serving as Wu clan's base, Fang Yuan claimed that he wanted to live outside as well. Bear Mountain was a well known place, there were large numbers of wild beasts on this mountain, all sorts of bears were living here.

Wu clan directly gave this mountain to Fang Yuan, from now on, this was Wu Yi Hai's territory.

But Wu clan did not assign Fang Yuan any relevant roles.

Wu clan's Gu Immortals were all supreme elders, Wu Yong was the first supreme elder, followed by the second supreme elder, third supreme elder, and so on. They had different positions, and differing authority and power.

In this aspect, Qiao clan's first supreme elder was very anxious and concerned about it.

Because Qiao clan helped Fang Yuan in order to get him to become an authoritative figure among the higher-ups of Wu clan. So that he could contest for Qiao clan's benefits.

For this purpose, Qiao clan needed Fang Yuan to gain more power in Wu clan, that way, he could speak up for Qiao clan and make firm decisions.

Qiao clan's help was not for free, Fang Yuan had already made alliance agreements with Qiao clan's first supreme elder secretly.

But Fang Yuan was not in a rush.

He pretended to look at the sunrise, but he was actually thinking about the giant dream realm.

He had already obtained his righteous path identity, how could he enter the super Gu formation openly now, and use the giant dream realm to raise his attainment level?

Fang Yuan was thinking of this problem, when an information path Immortal Gu flew towards him, bringing Wu Yong's summons.

Right now, Fang Yuan had perfectly assimilated into the clan, the process was seen by countless Gu Immortals in Southern Border, Wu Yong could not harm his life anymore.

The ship had set sail, it was far too late now.

Especially when he was inside Wu clan's territory, Wu Yong needed to protect this 'younger brother' of his.

Fang Yuan followed the instructions of the information path Immortal Gu and met with Wu Yong in a hall.

Wu Yong said: "You are my younger brother, you have just returned to the clan. According to our clan rules, every newly advanced rank six Gu Immortal may pick a rank six Immortal Gu. After becoming rank seven, they may pick a rank seven Immortal Gu. Bring along this information path Immortal Gu with you and go to the clan's treasury to choose your two Immortal Gu."

Chapter 1221: Love Comes!

Hearing that his 'brother' was arranging for him to claim Immortal Gu from the treasury, Fang Yuan smiled.

In his case, he did not lack Immortal Gu. Forget about rank six Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan even had many rank seven Immortal Gu. As for rank eight, Fang Yuan had attitude Gu, years flow like water Immortal Gu, and wisdom sword Immortal Gu. Right now, the most important one was attitude Gu. Wisdom sword Immortal Gu needed rank eight immortal essence, while Years Flow Like Water had a huge drawback of attracting immemorial year beasts.

But in terms of numbers, Fang Yuan had more rank eight Immortal Gu than Wu Yong.

He even had rank nine wisdom Gu.

Although, strictly speaking, wisdom Gu did not belong to Fang Yuan.

Inside Wu clan's treasury, there were indeed many useful or powerful Immortal Gu, and there was a high chance that many Immortal Gu suited Fang Yuan's needs.

But deep down, Fang Yuan clearly understood — At this juncture, there was one thing that he needed the most.

Dream realm!

As long as he could enter the dream realm, Fang Yuan could use unravel dream to rapidly raise his attainment levels.

When his attainment levels rise, he would be able to annex more immortal apertures.

Unlike now, he was restricted by his attainment levels, he could not annex many blessed lands.

There were relatively few Gu Immortals.

In a single region, there were merely several hundred Gu Immortals, most of them were rank six, few were rank seven, and rank eight Gu Immortals were usually the ones at the peak.

Among these Gu Immortals, Fang Yuan could only annex some of the rank six and seven immortal apertures. And among these, only those which he had suitable attainment levels could be annexed. He could not go to Central Continent. As for the other four regions, there were many Gu Immortals that Fang Yuan could not touch. Like those with close relationships to rank eight Gu Immortals, or those who were hard to find, or people like Feng Jiu Ge and Shi Lei.

Therefore, at the end of the day, Fang Yuan did not have many immortal apertures to annex.

Earlier, he could annex a lot and raise his cultivation level, on one hand, it was Fang Yuan's accumulation, he had killed many Gu Immortals and obtained a lot of information, but on the other hand, Fang Yuan had sufficient luck.

Raising his attainment levels in all the different paths had great benefits for Fang Yuan.

It increased the range of his choices drastically.

He would be able to annex even more immortal apertures.

"Earlier, I annexed immortal apertures and raised my cultivation level from rank six to seven. But after reaching rank seven, annexing rank six immortal apertures to skip calamities and tribulations has a far smaller effect."

"My cultivation level is rising at an unavoidably slower speed. But after raising my attainment levels in different paths, my rank seven cultivation level would start to climb up rapidly again. The speed would not be as fast as before, after all, rank seven immortal apertures are very rare, but compared to normal cultivation, it is still extremely shocking!"

Of course, Fang Yuan could not estimate the actual speed.

Because it depended on the situation.

If he was lucky enough, he would be able to annex many rank seven blessed lands at once. With enough of them, he would rise to rank eight, it was not impossible.

This was the power of the sovereign immortal aperture.

Spectral Soul had spent a hundred thousand years, sacrificing Shadow Sect and Zombie Alliance to create this Immortal Gu, there was good reason for it.

For ordinary Gu Immortals, this cultivation method was impossible.

"However, there are not many rank seven blessed lands even if I add up all five regions, I can forget about advancing to rank eight for now."

Fang Yuan thought about it, the chances of becoming rank eight immediately were too slim.

He had a clear mind.

Fang Yuan was not overly greedy, he knew what was important, and what was less of a concern.

Thus, facing Wu Yong, he said: "I do not need to go to the treasury, I know what I want."

"Oh?" Wu Yong was surprised.

Next, Fang Yuan said the names of two Immortal Gu, one was rank six, the other was rank seven.

Wu Yong was even more surprised now, he looked at Fang Yuan deeply, having understood what he wanted. But he still pretended to be unaware: "These two Immortal Gu are part of the super Gu formation, they have been used already to encircle that giant dream realm. Are you sure you want them?"

Fang Yuan nodded without any hesitation, showing that he had made his decision.

In order to create the super Gu formation and protect the dream realm, the righteous path forces in Southern Border had contributed both manpower and resources. Wu clan put in six Immortal Gu, there was no need to conceal this information.

Fang Yuan had learned about it from Qiao clan's Gu Immortals.

As for why he chose these two Immortal Gu, it was because they were extremely crucial to the operations of the super Gu formation.

One could say, if Fang Yuan became the owner of these Immortal Gu, he would have the biggest say in the super Gu formation.

Fang Yuan continued to speak earnestly: "Brother, you have been in the clan since your were born, you have the support of Southern Border's strongest super force. But I am different, I grew up in Eastern Sea without anyone's help. I am a lone cultivator, you have never been a lone cultivator, you will not know our pain."

"Therefore, this time, I thought of coming to Southern Border, to join Wu clan, I do not want to go back to Eastern Sea anymore."

"I admit that I have my ambitions, but which Gu Immortal has no ambition?"

"Brother, I will speak the truth. You are a rank eight Gu Immortal, you have rank eight Immortal Gu, you are the first supreme elder of Wu clan, you live freely in Wu clan. As for me, I came from Eastern Sea, I only have rank seven cultivation level, I have some transformation path methods, but how can I compete against you? I have never thought of fighting with you."

"I merely want my cultivation journey to continue. Qiao clan has an alliance agreement with me, therefore they supported me to come here. I was forced to, without Qiao clan's help, I could not even attend mother's funeral."

"But I am still a Wu clansman, Wu clan's bloodline flows within me. My mother might have left me when I was a baby, but she had asked me to return in her final days. No matter what she thinks, she is still my birth mother all along."

"These last few days, I have been thinking, the dream realm's location is where I want to go. I am willing to leave Wu clan and cultivate there forever. All I want is some support from the clan, so that I would not be without cultivation resources. That way, I will be satisfied."

Fang Yuan spoke with sincerely, it was a moving speech.

Towards the end, his eyes even turned red, he bowed deeply to Wu Yong.

Wu Yong was moved.

He left his seat, going towards Fang Yuan and grabbing his shoulders.

"My brother!" He spoke, his voice was trembling, his expression was agitated.

"You are my younger brother, we have the same mother."

"I understand your intentions. I understand your hardships, and I am glad that you understand my difficulties."

"Since that is so, I will agree to your request. Do not forget what you said today!"

"Elder brother!" Fang Yuan choked, tears falling down from the corners of his eyes: "I will not forget today's words! Brother is granting my wish, I will support you fully. In the future, unless brother agrees, I will not act on my own and step into Wu clan's headquarters at all. I will also not interact with Wu clan's Gu Immortals excessively."

Wu Yong grabbed Fang Yuan's hands, patting the back of his hands: "You will not let me down, and I will not let you down!"

A moment later, Fang Yuan left the hall.

"Finally, I can go to the super Gu formation and openly explore the dream realm." The excitement in his heart could not be described to others.

Meanwhile, Wu Yong sat down on his seat, having a deep gaze in his eyes.

"My younger brother knows what's best for him, he is clear of the current situation. Not bad, not bad indeed."

"He did not mention the Immortal Gu inheritance at all, and even volunteered to leave Wu clan's headquarters. With his absence, I will be able to control the clan as rapidly as possible."

"The dream realm is also very useless. Current methods cannot excavate this mountain of treasures. As long as he guards the super Gu formation quietly, and cultivate in peace, without trying to gain authority in Wu clan, so what if I have to give him many more times the cultivation resources he is asking for?"

"The dream realm is like this now, but the future is not certain. After all, this is a prophecy regarding Great Dream Immortal Venerable... Hehe, speaking of which, my younger brother's ambitions are not small."

"However, just as he said, who has no ambitions? It is not scary to have ambitions, it is scary if your ambitions are so big you cannot recognize your own limits, and do something stupid beyond your abilities. For example, Qiao clan... hmph!"

Central Continent, Spirit Affinity House.

Zhao Lian Yun knelt on the ground like a statue.

The house in front of her was shut tight, there was no disturbance.

Feng Jin Huang no longer lived here.

Zhao Lian Yun knew this, but she still continued to kneel here.

Because she knew that this was her only hope! She had to grab onto it, because other than this, there were no other options.

At this moment, Zhao Lian Yun's legs were numb, she was so tired she felt dizzy, in her daze, memories of the past surfaced in her mind.

There was a grassland with budding wild flowers.

"This flower is for you, Lady Xiao Yun, they say that women love flowers." Ma Hong Yun brought a bunch of flowers with him as he stood in front of Zhao Lian Yun, smiling sheepishly.

"It stinks!" Zhao Lian Yun covered her nose, saying in disgust: "What flowers did you pick? These smelly fly flowers only grow on top of animal faeces. Take them away, take them away from me."

Ma Hong Yun was stunned, he answered: "Precisely because they grow on faeces, they are big and strong."

Zhao Lian Yun was rolling her eyes, she stepped on Ma Hong Yun's leg angrily: "Get lost! Fool! Why are you finding me flowers, you should think of how to please your young master! You idiot!!"

Ma Hong Yun was jumping from the pain, he said meekly: "I wanted to thank you, thanks for lying for me, otherwise, I would have been executed for stealing shoes."

Scenes of the past faded gradually, Zhao Lian Yun returned to the cold hard reality.

"Big fool!"

"But, what am I doing now, I seem like a fool too huh."

"To think that I, Zhao Lian Yun, would act so foolishly as well!"

"You always do foolish things, but the results always end up good. I am not you, but, this is the only thing that I can do... I am just a normal person."

Thinking of this, tears rolled down Zhao Lian Yun's eyes, the grief and agony in her heart could not be described with words.

At this time, in her blurry vision, she saw a Gu.

Rank nine —

Love Gu!

It was flying in front of Zhao Lian Yun.

Chapter 1222: Current Generation Fairy, Zhao Lian Yun?

Rank nine love Gu.

Zhao Lian Yun did not recognize this Gu worm, but that did not stop her from noticing this Gu worm's uniqueness.

Because in her vision, this Gu worm had become the center of the world, its body was glowing with multicolored lights, the entire Gu worm seemed to be the hottest flame burning in the universe. All of reality would be overturned, everything in this world would revolve around it.

"Is this... a miracle?" Zhao Lian Yun's face was covered in tears, a final thought was produced in her mind.

Next, she fell onto the ground, falling unconscious.

Spirit Affinity House was in a commotion!

Love Gu, it was the signature Immortal Gu of Spirit Affinity House.

It flew out of its resting place to Zhao Lian Yun's side. Most importantly, when Zhao Lian Yun was unconscious, it did not fly away, it remained on her shoulder.

That night, Spirit Affinity House recalled all of the Gu Immortals in the sect, holding an emergency meeting to discuss this matter.

Spirit Affinity House's first supreme elder, second supreme elder, and third supreme elder, Feng Jiu Ge, Fairy Bai Qing, Xu Hao, Li Jun Ying, and the others had gathered, the auras of immortals mixed together, the highest number of Gu Immortals from Spirit Affinity House had gathered together for the first time in hundreds of years.

"Everyone, we know about the rules of the sect. Now that love Gu has acknowledged Zhao Lian Yun, she is the sect's current generation fairy!" Xu Hao spoke expressionlessly, but intense joy could be felt from his tone.

Back then, he had advised Zhao Lian Yun, he was just trying to target Feng Jin Huang and damage her reputation, to elevate Zhao Lian Yun's own prestige.

He did not think that Zhao Lian Yun would be so stubborn, continuing to kneel there without giving up.

Xu Hao was helpless about this.

He nurtured Zhao Lian Yun and used her as a chess piece to deal with Feng Jin Huang. His real goal was to attack Feng Jin Huang's father — Feng Jiu Ge.

A place with people interacting would have internal and external conflicts.

When an organization is big, there would be many factions in it.

Right now, the Feng faction with Feng Jiu Ge at the lead had the greatest authority in Spirit Affinity House.

Xu Hao, Li Jun Ying, and the others were suppressed by theFeng faction, unable to lift their heads. Thankfully, Spirit Affinity House's two rank eight Gu Immortals, first supreme elder and second supreme elder, were impartial, they did not side with anyone, only looking at the benefits of Spirit Affinity House, this allowed Xu Hao and Li Jun Ying to remain as part of the sect's core authority, despite the Feng faction's power.

Zhao Lian Yun knelt and begged Feng Jin Huang, most people could only see the surface of the matter, only a few understood that this was a political conflict in Spirit Affinity House.

Zhao Lian Yun was a mere mortal, but after inheriting the Thieving Heaven true inheritance, she was qualified to compete with Feng Jin Huang for the position of Spirit Affinity House's fairy.

Xu Hao made Zhao Lian Yun his political tool.

Originally, Xu Hao was thinking that he could not let Zhao Lian Yun kneel anymore. In his opinion, as a political performance, it was already enough. If Zhao Lian Yun continued kneeling, she would be like an idiot, there were no gains for her.

But several hours ago, when Xu Hao heard that love Gu had stayed by Zhao Lian Yun's side of its own accord, he was stunned.

After his heavy shock, he felt intense joy!

He acutely sensed that this was a godsent opportunity. This gift was too precious, he almost fainted from happiness.

This was an unbelievably rare chance.

He needed to use this opportunity to make Zhao Lian Yun Spirit Affinity House's fairy!

Then on this basis, he would retaliate against the 'Feng faction', this was an unprecedented opportunity for Xu Hao in the sect! As long as he made use of this chance, his future in the sect would change drastically for the better.

Xu Hao did not doubt this.

Thus, he was the first to stand up and support Zhao Lian Yun for the position, to become Spirit Affinity House's current generation fairy!

He spoke: "Our sect rules are clear, in choosing the fairies, first, we listen to the masses, then we look at aptitude, finally, we look at the preference of higher-ups."

The meaning was: They would first see what the people in the sect thinks, before looking at the aptitude and talent of the participant, and finally, it would depend on who suited the preferences of the higher-up Gu Immortals more.

Xu Hao continued to speak: "Right now, in terms of the masses, Zhao Lian Yun might be an otherworldly demon, but she has love and loyalty, in order to save her lover, she knelt down to her opponent. The entire sect knows about her character, and in terms of aptitude, it is not important, as long as we are willing, we can raise a mortal's aptitude easily. I believe that everyone has heard of her experiences in Northern Plains, she is an elite in terms of talent. And finally, everyone's preferences. I greatly acknowledge Zhao Lian Yun, I express my support towards her in becoming our fairy."

"I concur." Xu Hao had just said that when Li Jun Ying added this.

She was Xu Hao's wife, they had the same opinion in this.

This was not strange.

But the following scene was shocking to others.

"I agree with Xu Hao."

"I approve of Xu Hao's perspective."

"Even love Gu acknowledged Zhao Lian Yun, what else do I have to say?"

...

At once, five to six Gu Immortals agreed with Xu Hao's words.

Fairy Bai Qing could not stand it anymore.

She felt: It seemed that everyone here agreed with Xu Hao, they felt that the position of Spirit Affinity House's fairy should go to Zhao Lian Yun.

Fairy Bai Qing was a Gu Immortal of Spirit Affinity House, but more than that, she was Feng Jin Huang's mother.

The position of fairy in Spirit Affinity House was very special.

She was the cultivation seed that was chosen by the entire Spirit Affinity House, even the mortals were part of the selection process. Next, they would invest heavily in her and nurture her to become immortal. Every generation's fairy would be Spirit Affinity House's representative when they fully matured.

Spirit Affinity House was an organization, and organizations not only needed old experts, but also new Gu Immortals, to inject fresh blood and keep the system going smoothly.

Fairy Bai Qing herself was a fairy of Spirit Affinity House. She had felt for herself the experience of having an entire sect support her cultivation.

Even though Feng Jiu Ge and Bai Qing were both Gu Immortals and could totally fund their daughter, Feng Jin Huang, for her immortal ascension easily, this type of support paled in comparison to the funding of the entire sect.

Fairy Bai Qing did not want to see her daughter lose.

But she understood deeply: Right now, the situation was very disadvantageous for her!

Because the sect rules were, in choosing a fairy, other than 'listening to the masses, looking at aptitude, and the higher-ups preference', there was also an important part, that was —

Once love Gu acknowledged someone, no matter how disliked they were, or now bad their aptitude was, or even how badly received they were by the Gu Immortal higher-ups, they would become the current generation fairy, regardless of the situation, or whether they were male or female!

Because of this rule, after Xu Hao finished speaking, he gained the approval of many Gu Immortals, they expressed their support.

In fact, Xu Hao's own political force was not strong. Normally, he would not garner such support.

"Even though the sect rules are as such, it is not a hopeless situation. Because in our sect's history, there was a fairy that was promoted because of this rule, and in the end she..."

Fairy Bai Qing thought of this and was about to speak.

But at this time, Feng Jiu Ge pressed down on her hand softly.

"Don't be anxious."

"I know, you want to mention Mo Yao, right? Back then, she was just an inkman slave, but she gained the acknowledgement of love Gu and was funded by the entire sect to become a Gu Immortal, and even managed to reform Bo Qing. But in the end, she betrayed the sect, she defied Heavenly Court."

Feng Jiu Ge transmitted.

Fairy Bai Qing nodded, replying to him secretly: "That's right, this is Huang Er's only hope. As long as we use this point and continue arguing, using the strength of Feng faction, we might be able to get the sect to change this rule. After all, rules are made by people, isn't that right? This sect rule does not make sense!"

But Feng Jiu Ge shook his head.

He rejected Fairy Bai Qing's idea: "Xu Hao is a wisdom path Gu Immortal, why did he not mention the sect rules in his earlier speech? He only talked about the first three conditions, and seemingly forgot about this sect rule that was most advantageous for him."

Fairy Bai Qing was slightly stunned.

Feng Jiu Ge continued: "This is his scheme, his trap. If you talk about it, you will fall into his plot. Even though Bo Qing and Mo Yao had caused such a situation, the sect rules did not change. After the battle of Yi Tian Mountain, our sect suffered a lot of pressure, but our rules had not changed either. This is a very deep issue, there is more than meets the eye. If you want to use Feng faction's power to challenge it foolishly, wanting to change this rule, we will lose miserably. We would suffer heavy losses while Xu Hao would be completely intact, that is what he wants to see."

Fairy Bai Qing's body was covered in cold sweat.

"I was rash." She quickly calmed down, after a while, she thought about why she made such a mistake.

"Because it involved Huang Er, I became confused due to love. No, there is another reason, I became a rank seven Gu Immortal and gained rank seven Immortal Gu, compared to before, I was overconfident. Because I am in the righteous path, battle strength is not everything. If hubby did not remind me today, I would have committed a huge mistake."

Thinking of this, Fairy Bai Qing unconsciously looked at Feng Jiu Ge.

She felt a strong feeling of protection from him. Even though Feng Jiu Ge was from the demonic path, after all these years he had demonstrated his skills, being in the sect did not require just battle strength, his political abilities were also far superior to her, otherwise, how could his Feng faction have such brilliance today?

"Since you can expose Xu Hao's trap, I will entrust this matter to you." Fairy Bai Qing transmitted secretly, there was sweet affection in her tone.

Feng Jiu Ge smiled bitterly: "This matter, I am not going to interfere. Because interfering is of no use."

"What do you mean?" Fairy Bai Qing was stunned.

Feng Jiu Ge did not speak, he looked at the sky.

"He did not fall for it..." Xu Hao was originally waiting for someone to jump out, but nobody objected to his words, even Feng Jiu Ge was keeping silent, he felt that it was a pity.

But he quickly collected his thoughts, feeling confident inside: "Forget it! Since nobody objected, this matter is decided."

But first supreme elder suddenly said: "I have understood everyone's stances. But Zhao Lian Yun has a special background, she is an otherworldly demon. I will report the result of our discussion to the higher-ups, they will decide themselves."

"What?" Xu Hao was completely stunned.

Chapter 1223: Entering The Gu Formation Openly

Southern Border.

The remains of Yi Tian Mountain.

"Lord Wu Yi Hai, this way please." Wu An bowed as he led the way.

Fang Yuan nodded, in front of him, an entrance opened in the super Gu formation.

"Please, lord, enter first." Wu An gave way as he smiled affectionately.

Wu Yi Hai's identity was now known to almost everyone in Southern Border's Gu Immortal world.

Fang Yuan arrived directly and became Wu clan's person-in-charge for the super dream realm. Wu An with only rank six cultivation level was his direct subordinate, he had to curry favor.

Fang Yuan had yet to take over the role, but Wu An had already flown out of the super Gu formation, staying at a mountain for two days and two nights a hundred li away, just to receive Fang Yuan when he arrived.

When he saw Fang Yuan, he immediately lowered himself and stuck to Fang Yuan like a fly. Whatever he was asked, he answered to the best of his abilities. If Fang Yuan wanted to kick his butt, he would definitely move his butt over to Fang Yuan's leg so that he could kick it more conveniently.

But this was exactly why he gave Fang Yuan a good understanding of all the Gu Immortals who were here from different clans defending the super Gu formation, as well as this current situation.

Fang Yuan did not stand on ceremony with Wu An, he entered first as Wu An followed after him, smiling and lowering his head.

Many Gu Immortals were looking at this scene secretly.

"Wu Yi Hai is here, not long ago, he used Wu clan's immortal killer move and got rid of his status as an Eastern Sea Gu Immortal, he is now a true member of Southern Border." Ba Quan Feng said as he observed the expression of the Gu Immortal beside him carefully.

It was none other than the publicly recognized strongest rank seven expert in Southern Border's Gu Immortal world, Old Treeman Ba De.

Ba De retracted his gaze, saying plainly: "Let's observe for now."

Saying this, he turned around and left.

It seemed like Wu Yi Hai's appearance was just an insignificant matter to him.

Ba Quan Feng was disappointed.

He wanted to see Ba De's reaction, Wu Yi Hai was here but he was a newbie, be it in the super Gu formation, or in Southern Border's Gu Immortal world, he was a newcomer.

Wu Du Xiu died, Wu clan only had one rank eight Gu Immortal left, Wu Yong, their strength had fallen drastically, many clans were waiting to strike. Especially the strong Ba clan.

In the past, when Wu clan was strong, Ba Quan Feng had many opinions about it. Now that one of Wu clan's rank eight Gu Immortals was dead, and a newcomer, Wu Yi Hai, was here, he unavoidably had some notions of suppressing him to vent his frustration.

Unfortunately, Ba De said that they would observe for now.

After all, nobody knew about Wu Yi Hai's strength and methods.

Ba De was a dependable and experienced old schemer.

If Wu Yi Hai was naive or had low strength, he would not mind making Ba clan the main controller of this super Gu formation!

Inside the super Gu formation, there was space inside, that surrounded the entire super dream realm, forming something like a giant city.

Each segment was guarded by one clan, the thirteen righteous path forces split the space in this super Gu formation into thirteen portions.

The space that Wu clan occupied was huge, it was one of the largest among the thirteen. The only clan that was comparable to them was Ba clan. Even Tie clan and Shang clan were inferior.

Fang Yuan entered it and because he had information provided by Wu clan, and he had his lackey, Wu An, he did not lose his way.

Soon, he found his way to the core, and met with another Gu Immortal from Wu clan, Wu Liao.

This person had broad shoulders and a thin waist, he looked very brave and heroic, there was a needle-like beard under his chin, he greeted Fang Yuan without any tone of submission: "Greetings to Lord Wu Yi Hai. Please pardon me for not receiving you, I was tasked to stay here."

His tone was calm, pride was rooted in him.

Fang Yuan felt very amused, Wu An and Wu Liao, they both had rank six cultivation level, but their attitudes were a stark contrast.

Now that Wu Yi Hai was here, all of Wu clan's stationed Gu Immortals were here in the super Gu formation.

Originally, there was a rank seven Gu Immortal.

But since Fang Yuan came, he was sent off elsewhere.

Wu clan was huge, it was the number one force in Southern Border's righteous path, but it did not have many Gu Immortals that could be used. Every Gu Immortal was a portion of strength that needed to be used wisely and carefully, in the right areas.

"Let's solve the main issues first. I am sure you know about our clan's orders. Bring me to refine my two Immortal Gu." Fang Yuan said.

This was the first important mission.

Wu Liao saw that Wu Yi Hai worked at a rapid speed, he felt a sense of acknowledgement towards him.

Wu An quickly ran to Fang Yuan's side, smiling in a fawning manner: "Lord, this way please, I will bring you there now."

A moment later, Fang Yuan successfully refined the two Immortal Gu.

Refining other people's Immortal Gu was not easy. But with Wu clan's cooperation, it was a different story.

Fang Yuan finally let out a sigh of relief.

He knew: Wu clan's treasury definitely had Immortal Gu that were better or more suited for himself. But he still chose these two Immortal Gu regardless.

He did this because he had his own considerations.

With these two Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan could plant his roots into this super Gu formation.

From now on, even if Wu clan wanted to move Fang Yuan away, they had to consider this point!

This super Gu formation was already established, every Immortal Gu was tightly linked, changing a single one would adversely affect it. Every Immortal Gu that each clan controlled was also the investment that the clan was putting into the giant dream realm, it affected the distribution of power and authority that the respective clans had in this place.

"Lord, I have prepared some supper for you to eat." After Fang Yuan refined the Immortal Gu, Wu An quickly came over and said this to him in a subservient manner.

Fang Yuan was expressionless, he responded with a grunt.

Wu An suddenly seemed like he had heard some heavenly music, he quickly led the way joyfully: "Lord, this way please."

Wu Liao snorted coldly, showing disdain in his eyes, he did not like Wu An's fawning.

But Fang Yuan said: "Wu Liao, follow us, I have some things to ask you two."

"Yes, lord." Wu Liao replied respectfully.

The banquet was indeed not bad, the dishes and wines were very delicious.

Fang Yuan sat at the main seat while Wu An and Wu Liao sat on his left and right.

Fang Yuan knew that there was a possibility of bias and misinformation, he could not listen to Wu An's words alone. Thus, during the banquet, he asked the two of them many questions.

Wu An and Wu Liao answered respectfully.

After the banquet ended, Fang Yuan gained an even clearer understanding of the situation at the super Gu formation, there was a vivid picture in his mind.

In Fang Yuan's plan, for a long time in the future, he was going to cultivate here secretly.

He had to be clear of the environment here.

The righteous path and demonic path was different, the demonic path acted freely while the righteous path talked about rules. What were the rules of the righteous path? It was nothing more than just customs created over a long period of time, rules of a game that involved the distribution of benefits.

Fang Yuan understood that since he came here using Wu Yi Hai's identity, he had to settle matters using righteous path methods. If he used demonic path methods here, his enemies would laugh happily, and his clan would distance themselves from him. Even if Wu Yong sides with his brother, he would not be able to endure the pressure, for the sake of the clan, he would need to move Fang Yuan elsewhere.

After all, Wu clan was led by Wu Yong.

Wu clan was once the dominant clan, but Ba clan, Shang clan, and Tie clan were not willing to be under Wu clan. Qiao clan was Wu clan's most loyal ally.

But after Wu Du Xiu's death, the situation had changed greatly. Ba clan was stirring and ready to strike, especially when Old Treeman Ba De was the one sent here to guard the dream realm.

With just this, Fang Yuan could acutely sense that from now on, Ba clan was going to be his main competitor.

As for Qiao clan...

Fang Yuan felt somewhat of a headache.

He came here, he had gone against the agreement with Qiao clan. As for what Qiao clan's attitude would be and how much support they would give him, Fang Yuan was uncertain.

After the banquet, Fang Yuan sent Wu An and Wu Liao away, resting alone.

Before leaving, Wu An wanted to say some things, but he was very hesitant about it.

Wu Liao left quietly, he had an improving opinion of Fang Yuan after this. During the banquet, he asked very precise questions, even though Wu Liao had difficulties answering them, he felt confident in Fang Yuan's abilities as a result.

For righteous path Gu Immortals, their own strength was the foundation, but it was not enough, they needed to be skilled in political methods as well.

However, after the banquet, for the next few days, Fang Yuan did not show up in public, he was hiding in his own room, cultivating.

"Is this Wu Yi Hai really just a lone cultivator?" Fang Yuan's actions were very much resembling lone cultivators, this made many Gu Immortals who were observing him secretly make such a guess.

Wu Liao was a bit disappointed, he wanted a superior that could suppress the situation, not someone who was purely cultivating.

Wu An felt very uneasy.

These last days, he had invited Fang Yuan with all sorts of reasons. But Fang Yuan rejected them all, he even said that he should not be disturbed if there were no important matters.

Wu An could not tell what Fang Yuan's thoughts were, as time passed, his anxiety turned into fear.

And behind Wu An, there were also Gu Immortals from other clans, they were also very anxious.

The reason was simple.

The immortal opportunity business.

Back then, they could do the immortal opportunity business because Wu clan had led them, colluding with several clan's Gu Immortals to undergo this trade secretly.

The original Wu clan rank seven Gu Immortal left, Wu Yi Hai was moved here.

The immortal opportunity business thus had to stop, because the person in charge of Wu clan over here was Wu Yi Hai. Most importantly, he controlled two Immortal Gu!

Wu An was fawning over Fang Yuan so desperately, other than wanting to gain his protection, he also wanted to salvage the immortal opportunity business.

Wu An obtained a lot of benefits from this, without these benefits urging him, he would not have been so enthusiastic towards Fang Yuan.

Initially, interactions between Fang Yuan and Wu An were developing well. But soon, Fang Yuan acted abnormally, Wu An was at a loss.

The immortal opportunity business could not be exposed, if it was known publicly, they would be held responsible. This was an act of corruption, it was information that could be used against them.

Without dragging Fang Yuan into this, Wu An felt uneasy.

Gritting his teeth, he decided to take a risk!

Chapter 1224: White Rabbit's Seduction (1/2)

"This servant greets Lord Wu Yi Hai." The female Gu Immortal knelt down before Fang Yuan's feet.

She wore a white fur coat, it only wrapped around her chest and lower body, a large portion of her snow white skin was exposed. Her ears were like rabbit ears, her eyes were red like rubies, her nose was small and delicate, she had an extremely cute appearance. In terms of beauty, she was only inferior to Shang Xin Ci and Feng Jin Huang.

At this moment, this female immortal was kneeling on the ground, her forehead was touching the floor. Her huge chest was squeezed by the floor, experiencing a change in form. And her butt was high in the sky, attracting people's gazes.

She was none other than Lady White Rabbit.

Right now, she was pure yet wild, she was cute and embarrassed. Especially with her subservient attitude, when men see her, they would feel something emerging in their crotches, they would want to hug her tightly and give her some well deserved love.

Fang Yuan was feeling strange.

Not long ago, he had offered this woman some cultivation resources in exchange for information on the Gu Immortal world. To think that now, this woman would be kneeling before his feet, subjecting herself to whatever he wanted to do.

"This is an attempt to seduce me!"

"This Wu An took a risk and lied to me, saying that some important person wanted to report matters to me, therefore enabling Lady White Rabbit to meet me."

"It seems that these last few days, I had been secluded for too long, they are anxious now. They even used this method."

"The method is old and cliched, but it is very effective."

Fang Yuan smiled, standing up from his seat, slowly walking towards Lady White Rabbit.

Lady White Rabbit's forehead did not leave the concrete floor.

With Fang Yuan's sharp eyes, he could see that Lady White Rabbit was trembling.

She was nervous.

Fang Yuan thought: He had interacted with Lady White Rabbit before, and with his five hundred years of cultivation, he could tell that this woman was a pure lone cultivator. To think that she would offer her own body, this must be her first time doing this.

Of course, Fang Yuan's judgment could be wrong, but there were likely to be few people in the five regions who could deceive him this thoroughly.

Lady White Rabbit was indeed very nervous.

She was nervous, her body was trembling, her heart was pounding.

Even though she knew that she had to be calm and follow Wu An's words, she could not do it.

Knowing was easy, doing was hard.

"Turns out seductions are not so easy after all." Lady White Rabbit sighed internally.

Other than this, she felt some shame and anger, as well as disbelief.

"I, I am actually doing something like this? Why am I doing this? I am trying to seduce a man I have never even met before!"

Lady White Rabbit felt very strange, this was not something she would normally do.

Before this, she was a pure lone cultivator, having no conflicts in the world, she cultivated in peace and quiet. If anyone told her that she would be on her knees doing this in the future, she would definitely fight that person without doubt!

"Why did it come to this?"

Lady White Rabbit thought about it: She had good connections with people, so one day, Wu An came to her and said that he had a huge fortune to share with her.

Back then, Lady White Rabbit was very wary and suspicious, why would something so good come to her? She felt that maybe Wu An was trying to cheat her money and body?

But no.

Lady White Rabbit managed the immortal opportunity business, she became the middleman, both demonic path and lone immortals had basis to trust her.

Of course, the initial business was not good. But afterwards, when word got out, the Gu Immortals gradually understood this business, and people started to flood towards her endlessly.

After every business transaction, Lady White Rabbit would take a cut of the profits.

Very soon, her total wealth had reached the level of her accumulation in the last tens of years.

Lady White Rabbit was shocked and joyful.

The business was getting better, she felt that each new day would be brighter.

But an unexpected mishap came both suddenly, and not suddenly.

Not suddenly because Lady White Rabbit knew about the matter entirely. Rank eight great expert, Wu Du Xiu, of Wu clan, passed away, her illegitimate son from Eastern Sea, Wu Yi Hai was returning to Southern Border, and was attacked by many forces. In the end, Wu Yi Hai survived the attacks and successfully returned to the clan, becoming a Southern Border Gu Immortal.

But it was sudden because Lady White Rabbit did not expect that this matter, which involved the entire Southern Border Gu Immortal world, would implicate her. Wu Yi Hai, who was far apart, having a high status, had actually come over here and became the person-in-charge of the super Gu formation on Wu clan's side.

The immortal opportunity business had to stop!

Because this business could not be exposed. Originally, Wu clan's rank seven Gu Immortal was the person manipulating it in the background.

Now that he was gone, Wu Yi Hai came.

Wu An and the rest were beneficiaries of this, but they had no ability to continue this business.

Because they were not qualified to.

They could not bypass Fang Yuan and continue the business either.

Because this business only involved seven clans, Ba clan, Tie clan, and Shang clan were not participants. They needed a strong background to support them.

Stop it here?

No, of course not!

All of the Gu Immortals involved in the immortal opportunity business had experienced great gains and benefits, they still wanted to continue!

Thus, roping Fang Yuan in was the most important matter.

Wu An was tasked with this important mission, Wu Liao could not be relied on, this Gu Immortal seemed young, but he was very conservative and strict with rules, he had always objected intensely to Wu clan doing the immortal opportunity business.

Wu An was very enthusiastic and attended to Fang Yuan meticulously, but he suddenly went into seclusion.

This made Wu An and the Gu Immortals with him extremely anxious.

The situation with the demonic path and lone cultivators was terrible now.

Suddenly, they could not enter and interact with the dream realm. This made the Gu Immortals feel that something was wrong, were these righteous path members trying to take their cultivation resources and not holding their side of the deal?

Large numbers of Gu Immortals surrounded the mortal Gu House on the mountain peak. They could not find the righteous path Gu Immortals, they could only surround Lady White Rabbit and shout loudly, sending threats as they demanded answers!

At this moment, Lady White Rabbit realized that she was in extreme danger!!

If the immortal opportunity business could not continue, not only would she not have a bright future, she would be torn to shreds by these wolves, her end would definitely be miserable.

In this situation, Wu An came and spoke with a glib tongue, finally convincing Lady White Rabbit.

Lady White Rabbit was forced by the situation, she had no choice but to dress up like this and meet Fang Yuan, using her beauty to seduce this Gu Immortal from Wu clan, so that he could come out and manage the immortal opportunity business!

"Raise your head." At this time, Lady White Rabbit heard Fang Yuan's order.

Lady White Rabbit's body shook, her heart almost skipped a beat.

She breathed in deeply, she raised her head, looking up at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan looked down imposingly at this beautiful girl, she was sprawling on the ground, raising her head to look at him. Her eyes were large and round, her skin was white like a boiled egg, and her lips were pink and delicate, soft as flowers, it made people unable to resist the urge of exploring how they tasted, especially the exquisite pink tongue that was inside, what flavor would it have?

"Stand up." At this moment, Fang Yuan spoke.

Lady White Rabbit was like a wooden puppet, obediently standing up.

She had an exquisite and busty figure, her chest could barely be contained, but her height was only at Fang Yuan's chest level, she was like a neighbor's cute daughter.

The two were less than five meters apart.

Lady White Rabbit's heart was pounding fiercely, her breathing was rough, she was almost gasping. Next, she remembered Wu An's instructions, she stepped forward and hugged Fang Yuan.

She used her jade-like arms to wrap around Fang Yuan's waist, using a seductive tone as she said: "Mas... master, please, please forcefully ravage this servant!"

She stammered as she said that, she wanted to die from shame and embarrassment!

Even though she had cultivated for many years, Lady White Rabbit was still very ignorant about male and female relationships. Her only guidelines were Wu An's suggestions.

"White Rabbit, oh White Rabbit, how can you say such shameful words? You really said it!"

Her face was bright red, she was asking herself this on the inside, she found it hard to believe that this was actually her.

Elsewhere, outside the place that Fang Yuan lived in, Wu An was pacing around uncertainly.

He was anxious, he walked around as he rubbed his hands, they formed into fists at times. From time to time, he stopped walking, turning around to look at the tightly shut door, thinking about what could happen inside.

If the immortal opportunity business stopped, and Fang Yuan refused to take over, that would mean that he did not like this idea, he would expose it.

This was very possible, Wu Yi Hai was very young and had just joined Wu clan, he needed to prove himself to the clan.

His brother was Wu Yong, he definitely had no lack of cultivation resources. For the moment, benefits were less important to him than reputation.

This way, Lady White Rabbit would be done for, even if she did not die, she would be wanted by the righteous path. She would turn from a lone immortal to a demonic path Gu Immortal.

Even though Wu An would not die, because Wu clan had limited Gu Immortals, he would definitely need to give up the benefits that he had obtained. He would also be punished by the clan, he would be sent away and his bright future would be completely ruined due to this business.

At this time, footsteps could be heard.

Wu An turned and look, only to see that this person was standing straight like a spear, he footsteps were like the wind as he emitted an imposing aura all over his body.

Wu An had a bad feeling: "Wu Liao, why are you here?"

Wu Liao snorted coldly at him: "Why else? Someone was shameless and wanted to seduce Lord Wu Yi Hai into committing a grave mistake! I am here to tell lord everything that you have done. I want him to know your schemes and ill intentions."

Wu An was so angry he was about to explode, he pointed at Wu Liao as he gritted his teeth: "Wu Liao, you dare to do so?!"

He had tried to bribe Wu Liao.

But Wu Liao refused to accept it, he did not find it little, it was just his personality.

Among Wu clan's Gu Immortals, who would not know about Wu Liao's personality?

Chapter 1225: White Rabbit's Seduction (2/2)

Wu Liao ignored Wu An, he bowed towards the door deeply as he shouted: "Wu An has ill intentions, Wu Liao seeks an audience with lord, I want to report him!"

Wu An's heart was frozen at this point.

He was scared, he was fearful.

He was afraid that at the next moment, this door would abruptly open and Lady White Rabbit would be thrown out with tears in her eyes.

Then he, Wu An, would be done for.

But no.

The door remained shut, as if Fang Yuan heard nothing.

But how could this be possible?

This was not an ordinary location, it was the internal space of the super Gu formation, a huge group of palaces had formed that could accommodate people.

Fang Yuan controlled two crucial Immortal Gu, he was fully aware of everything going on in Wu clan's territory inside the formation.

Wu An and Wu Liao's actions were extremely clear to Fang Yuan.

How could he not hear what Wu Liao had shouted earlier?

Impossible!

Seeing that Fang Yuan was ignoring him, Wu Liao, who was extremely confident, was stunned.

He knew that Wu An had been trying all kinds of ways to meet Fang Yuan, Wu Liao knew the purpose of his request.

Wu Liao did not obstruct him, because he knew that humans were greedy and selfish, many people were different from him, for example, the previous rank seven Gu Immortal from Wu clan.

But afterwards, Fang Yuan did not meet Wu An once.

Realizing this, Wu Liao was extremely happy.

He thought of it in his own perspective, since Fang Yuan rejected Wu An, he was definitely unhappy with the immortal opportunity business.

"Indeed! How can someone of Lord Wu Yi Hai's status be after such small gains? He has just entered the clan, he must be concerned about his reputation, and how he would develop as a Wu clan higher-up in the future." Wu Liao guessed.

Having such thoughts, he came to meet Fang Yuan, hopeful that Fang Yuan would receive him.

But now?

The hall's door was shut, like a wall or a tall mountain that was blocking Wu Liao's heart.

Wu An laughed heartily.

He wiped the sweat off his forehead, his mind returned to a calm state.

Wu Liao's request to meet was the best probe.

Wu An instantly thought that he had understood Fang Yuan's intention.

Wu Liao did not believe it, he shouted again, but the doors remained shut, there was no response.

Wu An laughed even louder now, feeling very confident.

He spoke: "Wu Liao, stop screaming. Lord has important matters to attend to, is it nice to disturb him like this?"

Wu Liao's expression was dark and ugly.

Wu An sneered, shaking his head.

Wu Liao looked down on Wu An, while Wu An felt that Wu Liao was too obstinate, he was not reasonable in how to deal with people and relationships.

"Now it seems, even though I took a risk, it paid off well."

"It is understandable, after all, Lady White Rabbit has a great appearance. When I first saw her in that attire, my heart almost jumped out of my mouth. I wanted so badly to cuddle her and rub all over her body!"

"Seeing a beauty like Lady White Rabbit, as long as one is a man, they would be tempted! Lord Wu Yi Hai is a young and vigorous guy, he has just gotten some authority, and a beauty comes to him immediately, it can satisfy his ego. Furthermore, he was an Eastern Sea lone cultivator, while Lady White Rabbit is also a Southern Border lone cultivator, between lone cultivators, they can understand each other and feel for each other. And the rarer thing is that Lady White Rabbit is a real virgin, when a man and woman meet, they would be like the fusion of fire and ice... hehehe!"

While he was thinking that, at the next moment, something happened that caught Wu An off guard.

Only to see that the doors opened, Lady White Rabbit stood at the door, appearing before the two Wu clan Gu Immortals.

"What happened? She came out already? Why has it been so little time?" Wu An was extremely surprised.

"Lord must have heard my words and sent this female immortal out." Wu Liao was overjoyed, but when he saw Lady White Rabbit, his gaze froze.

Even though he felt a little disgusted earlier, seeing Lady White Rabbit's divine beauty made his heart shook, he could not help but admit that Lady White Rabbit was beautiful.

"Such a short time has passed, did she not succeed?!" Wu An's heart sank to rock bottom, he was in a daze, his throat went dry.

But soon, he saw that Lady White Rabbit had changed her clothes, it was no longer the white fur coat from before.

Also!

What attracted Wu An's attention more was that Lady White Rabbit was wearing a pair of jade earrings, they were ball shaped and extremely thick.

This was Southern Border's custom.

When a woman marries and loses her virginity, she would wear such earrings, to show that she had successfully become one with her man.

Wu An was overjoyed, he was extremely happy!

Wu Liao's expression was pale, his eyes were sharp, he had already seen Lady White Rabbit's jade ball earrings.

"Did, did you succeed?" Wu An came forward and asked carefully.

Lady White Rabbit had an odd expression, but she nodded and did not speak.

Wu An let out a breath of turbid air, he shut his eyes as pressure left him, he could not adapt to this feeling and nearly fell down.

"But, why was it so fast?" Wu An had a thought: "This shouldn't be, don't tell me that Lord Wu Yi Hai is... a two pump chump in that aspect? Such a situation is not rare in Southern Border, there are many guys who had cultivate until this happened to them. Hehe, if that is the case, I can offer many useful Gu worms to lord in the future. But Lord Wu Yi Hai is already a rank seven Gu Immortal, with so many dao marks in him, these Gu worms might not be effective."

"These jade pearls were given to me by Lord Wu Yi Hai. He has instructed me to tell you, from now on, he will mainly focus on cultivating, you can carry on with your duties, do not disturb his cultivation." Lady White Rabbit said.

After she said that, Wu An looked at Wu Liao smugly with the expression of a victor.

Wu Liao's body shook, he took a step back, looking at Wu An angrily as he turned and left.

"Lord Wu An, let's leave too." Lady White Rabbit said.

"Don't call me lord, how can I, Wu An, be any lord. Just call me by my name." Wu An showed a sincere expression, as well as a courteous smile.

Right now, Lady White Rabbit's status had changed.

Not only did Wu Yi Hai take Lady White Rabbit's virginity, he had given her jade pearl earrings, he acknowledged her status as his concubine.

Lady White Rabbit felt Wu An's change in attitude, she had a complex feeling inside her.

She spoke: "Actually, Wu An, Lord Wu Yi Hai has some words especially for you."

"Lady, please tell me!" Wu An quickly turned solemn.

Lady White Rabbit said some shocking things: "Actually... Lord Wu Yi Hai did not copulate with me."

"What?!" Wu An's expression turned into shock.

The earlier scene appeared in Lady White Rabbit's mind again.

When she went ahead to hug him with an extremely flustered feeling, a pair of strong hands grabbed her shoulders.

Next, strong force was emitted in these warm hands, without allowing for any resistance, Lady White Rabbit was pushed away from Fang Yuan's body.

Lady White Rabbit's expression turned pale, instantly, she felt that she failed.

But at the next moment, she heard Fang Yuan's voice: "When I was in Eastern Sea, I was a lone cultivator. I know the pain of a lone cultivator clearly. Some things are sweet, but you will have to pay a price if you swallow them. I am sure that now, you understand why. However, I do not want to take advantage of someone in dire straights."

Saying this, Lady White Rabbit saw that a hand had stretched out towards her chest, it was holding a Gu worm.

"This is a clothing Gu, wearing it before talking to me." Fang Yuan's voice could be heard again.

Lady White Rabbit obeyed him, the clothing Gu turned into clothes that covered her body.

When she raised her head again, she saw Fang Yuan smiling lightly at her: "Even though I joined Wu clan, I am still a lone cultivator at heart, it will never change. You can consider this Gu worm a gift from a fellow lone cultivator, I suppose."

Lady White Rabbit's heart jumped, she felt an indescribable sensation, she was extremely touched in both body and soul.

At once, she started sobbing, tears formed in her eyes as her vision turned blurry.

But in her blurry vision, Lady White Rabbit could feel that Fang Yuan's smile was so warm and gentle, it was like the rays of the morning sun, shining into her heart, providing warmth and protection to her.

"However, if you leave like this, you might not be able to answer for the consequences. I am clear about you and Wu An's intentions in coming here. Thus, bring this with you." Fang Yuan said, taking out a pair of earrings.

With his abilities, creating such mortal objects would only take a thought.

Lady White Rabbit received this pair of jade earrings with tears in her eyes.

"From today onwards, you are my attendant and mistress." Fang Yuan smiled and said.

Lady White Rabbit acknowledged his words, slightly nodding.

"Go ahead with the immortal opportunity business. But I will not take over, if anything happens, I can help out secretly, but I will not step up officially."

"This is a matter that violates the interests of the other righteous path clans. After all, the entire super Gu formation was created with everyone's effort."

"I have just arrived in Southern Border, I have yet to establish myself, I do not need these meager gains."

"You are so intelligent, you understand what I mean, right?"

"Yes, I understand." Lady White Rabbit quickly answered with a shaky voice.

"Go back, and convey my message to Wu An and the people around him. My portion of the profits will go to you." Fang Yuan sent her off.

Lady White Rabbit mustered up her courage, wanting to take another look at Fang Yuan.

But she did not manage to do so.

She lowered her head as she walked out. The moment her back faced Fang Yuan, tears fell down her cheeks.

The situation was much better than she had thought.

The name of Wu Yi Hai was engraved into the deepest part of her soul.

"I understand now, I understand now!" After hearing Lady White Rabbit's recollection, Wu An's forehead was full of sweat, his smugness was completely gone by now.

He subconsciously looked towards Fang Yuan's residence, wariness and even more so, admiration and respect was hidden in his gaze.

Chapter 1226: Rules of the Righteous Path

On his bed, Fang Yuan slowly opened his eyes.

He let out a breath of air, realizing that he was still in his bed, the surrounding arrangements were all intact.

This was the defensive Gu formation that Southern Border's righteous path forces had created together, it was very safe. But Fang Yuan was vigilant to the core, he always considered the many possible outcomes before he did anything.

Ever since rebirth, he had been cultivating endlessly, he exerted all of his effort without wasting a moment of his time on useless aspects.

This sleep was the same.

Fang Yuan entered his own dream realm, getting materials from his dream realm, he obtained the Gu materials for many dream path mortal Gu.

"If I refine them, I can get five to six dream path mortal Gu." Fang Yuan assessed.

His improvement in dream path was evident.

In the past, after one dream, he would only obtain a few Gu materials, to refine one or two dream path mortal Gu. But now was different, his gains had risen sharply, his efficiency in getting dream path mortal Gu also rose by many times.

Of course, there was an important element, his soul.

When exploring dream realms, the soul would weaken.

Thus, the stronger the soul, the longer one could explore the dream realm, and the greater the backlash that they could endure from the dream realm.

What was worth mentioning was: No matter how strong the soul was, it was just a basic condition for exploration. A strong soul could not allow one to freely move in the dream realm.

There was a somewhat unfitting analogy for souls and dreams.

The dream realm was like a desert, when souls explore it, they are like lost travelers inside the desert. The stronger the soul, the stronger the traveler's constitution, they could endure hunger and stay inside the desert for a longer time.

But that did not mean that he could walk out of the desert. He did not know what direction it was, he could not create food and water inside the desert, he could not shrink the desert or leave it freely.

But clear directions, creation of water and food, and modifying the desert, all of these could only be achieved by dream path at this period of time.

Why 'this period of time'?

Because when all the paths reach a certain attainment level, they can mimic other paths and attain their effects.

In the future, fire path, earth path, and others can also create their own immortal killer moves that mimic dream path effects.

However!

There was a huge condition.

That was, dream path had to be developed further as a path, and the Gu Immortal trying to mimic its effect needed to be familiar with dream path and have high dream path attainment.

Right now, dream path had just started being researched, all the forces and Gu Immortals were suffering from exploring it, they did not have many useful gains.

Even though there were quite a few dream path Gu worms and even wild dream path Immortal Gu, dream path as a path itself was still very far from actually being created.

It was not even properly created yet, not to mention completed.

Creating a whole new path was not so easy.

There were many water path Gu worms, during the Immemorial Antiquity Era, Remote Antiquity Era, and Olden Antiquity Era, there were countless wild water path Gu worms, there were even people who created new water path Gu worms. But only until the Medieval Antiquity Era did Spirit Affinity House's founder, Shui Ni, finalize the path after considering all aspects, formally creating water path.

Thus, Gu Immortals in the five regions could do nothing about dream path, they knew that it was extremely valuable, but they had no way to gain from it.

Many Gu Immortals died in dream realms.

This situation was happening everywhere, and some time ago, Southern Border's Gu Immortals had suffered massive casualties from this.

Precisely so, Southern Border's righteous path Gu Immortals noticed the fact and had to slow down their exploration of the dream realm, moving forward with steady steps, carefully progressing slowly.

Many Gu Immortals were still very wary of the dream realm, they started to have different ideas, thus, the immortal opportunity business was born as a result.

If the righteous path Gu Immortals had ways to explore the dream realm, how could they give up this immense profit to the demonic and lone immortals?

Thinking of the immortal opportunity business, Fang Yuan sat up on his bed.

The immortal opportunity business had to exist, but at the same time, he could not be involved in it excessively.

The immortal opportunity business had many uses.

On one hand, it could give Gu Immortals immense benefits. On the other hand, it could greatly reduce the conflict of the righteous path, demonic path, and lone cultivators.

If the righteous path Gu Immortals defended the super dream realm forcefully, what would these demonic path and lone immortals in Southern Border think?

"The righteous path definitely obtained a lot of benefits, but they are keeping it for themselves. If time passes, the righteous path will get stronger, while we get weaker, how can we live? These are the cultivation resources of Great Dream Immortal Venerable, who does not want to become Great Dream Immortal Venerable? Why is the righteous path allowed to hog it for themselves, without any for us?"

This would be their mentality.

It was extremely dangerous.

Southern Border's righteous path forces knew that if these people were forced, the demonic and lone immortals would join up and result in another battle of Yi Tian Mountain, or result in the blood battle martial competition of Northern Plains.

With this immortal opportunity business, the lone and demonic immortals would realize: Oh, the dream realm is so dangerous, there is nothing to gain from it. At this moment, the righteous path can do nothing to it, otherwise, why would there be this business? Are they letting us experience the dream realm on purpose?

Creating this dream realm business was the idea of the rank seven Gu Immortal from Wu clan, he was very astute. Unfortunately, Fang Yuan was stronger and used his brother's influence to chase this rank seven Gu Immortal away.

Fang Yuan needed stability.

The more stable the better!

He needed a stable environment to explore the dream realms here.

Thus, preventing the attacks of both lone and demonic path immortals here meant that it was necessary to continue the immortal opportunity business.

But Fang Yuan could not participate.

Because not all the righteous path clans were participating.

This was a crucial point!

Put simply, the loot was not distributed evenly.

Wu clan and six other righteous path clans were getting the benefits, while the other half of the clans were not participating.

This was very reasonable.

Gu Immortals were moved by benefits, the fewer people who joined, the more they would gain, right?

Thus, the result was — once the immortal opportunity business was exposed, all of the Gu Immortals involved would not be able to get away. They would definitely be punished severely, because this was the rule of the righteous path!

Fang Yuan could not step into this trap.

Wu An and the rest wanted to rope him in, but Fang Yuan knew that once this was exposed, even if he was the owner of two Immortal Gu in here and was the brother of Wu Yong, it was impossible for him to stay here.

Fang Yuan was not going to take the risk.

He went through all kinds of methods to infiltrate here, what was it for? It was for the dream realm!

Especially when Wu Yong was not someone who favored his 'brother' Wu Yi Hai. His attitude would depend on the circumstances.

But as long as Fang Yuan did not commit a mistake, and was the owner of the Immortal Gu here, Wu Yong would be less likely to send him elsewhere.

Fang Yuan could see all these details clearly.

Thanks to the five hundred years of his previous life.

Even though his cultivation level was not high, he had been in the righteous path, demonic path, and even was a lone cultivator, he had incredibly rich life experiences.

This allowed him to be in the righteous path while not being restrained by Wu Yi Hai's lone cultivator upbringing. He was clear about the political situation here, he knew what to do as a righteous path Gu Immortal, and how to play this game of life.

Thus, he recruited Lady White Rabbit.

At the crucial moment, he could use her as scapegoat, saying that he did not know the matter.

The immortal opportunity business' profits that were for him were all given to Lady White Rabbit as well.

He could not take the profits.

Unlike demonic path or lone cultivators who would crazy after seeing some resources, the righteous path could not do this, some benefits could be gained, but certain benefits were untouchable.

But what if he rejected her? What if he gave Lady White Rabbit and Wu An the cold shoulder?

That was worse.

If Fang Yuan did that, even though there would not be a crisis after getting exposed, he would make enemies with six clans of Gu Immortals. These people were beneficiaries, if Fang Yuan did not lead them, they would not dare to undergo this business. These people would definitely have poor feelings towards him.

Fang Yuan would have just arrived at the super Gu formation, and he would have already offended all of the political allies of Wu clan.

And all those who did not participate in the immortal opportunity business, like Ba clan, Tie clan, or Shang clan, would be greedily eyeing up Fang Yuan.

If he did that, he would be crippling his own network, it was an extremely stupid idea.

The arrangement now was good.

The immortal opportunity business continued, his political allies were happy, Ba clan and the rest were watching but could not do anything to Fang Yuan, who had no exploitable weaknesses.

In the future, if this matter was exposed, Fang Yuan would push Lady White Rabbit into the spotlight, sacrificing her and saying that he was doting on her, but to think that she would do something like this behind his back. He was completely kept in the dark and ignorant.

All in all, Fang Yuan had leeway to retreat or advance.

As for those profits, Fang Yuan could only give up on them.

He did not lack resources now, the sovereign immortal aperture's cultivation resources would put most rank seven Gu Immortals to shame!

"Next, I can officially start exploring dream realms!" Fang Yuan prepared to move.

At the same time, in Northern Plains.

The blood battle martial competition was reaching its end.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and Yao Huang did not appear from start to finish, but their influence was heavily affecting the competition.

Chu Du had an ugly expression.

The situation was not in his favor.

Hao Zhen had lost, he was holding his left shoulder with his right arm. His injuries were severe, his left arm was completely chopped off, the injury area was covered in dao marks, it was hard to heal.

"Northern Plains' righteous path truly has a deep foundation." Chu Du sighed, he was in an extremely awkward position of having nobody to send out.

Hao Zhen had an angry expression, he spoke with unwillingness to give up: "Lord Chu Du, I have a friend who is stronger than me, but they are a secluded cultivator and have little fame."

Chu Du was joyful and suspicious: "Oh? Why did you not recommend them earlier?"

Hao Zhen had a difficult expression, he transmitted carefully: "There is one bad point, they cultivate blood path."

Chu Du's expression turned solemn, he rejected it without hesitation: "Absolutely not! Any blood path Gu Immortal is a demonic path Gu Immortal. This blood battle martial competition is a competition between righteous path forces, how can this blood path demonic immortal take part?"

Once they were involved, the other party could slander Chu Du's side for being demonic path members.

Chu Du's hard work would completely go down the drain.

This was the rule of the righteous path!

Chapter 1227: Dragonman

"Our Combat Immortal Sect is one of the ten great ancient sects. Lad, since you were recommended by my senior brother, you must know about the selection rules of Combat Immortal Sect, it will depend on your combat results."

In Fang Yuan's vision, a Gu Master was looking down imposingly at him, saying: "If you want to officially become a disciple of Combat Immortal Sect, you have to put up a good fight and be one of the ten people left out of a hundred people, to be qualified to join the sect."

"Combat Immortal Sect..."

"Why is it this kind of dream."

"Spectral Soul Demon Venerable didn't seem to have joined Combat Immortal Sect during his life?"

"It seems that he absorbed many souls in the door of life and death and obtained lots of cultivation experiences. This is why it formed like this?"

Fang Yuan speculated inwardly.

At this time, the Gu Master took out three Gu worms.

This first Gu worm looked like a caterpillar, it was light blue and the size of an adult's thumb, the head had a small horn on it.

The second Gu worm was a butterfly with red patterns, emitting a warm aura.

The third Gu worm was a toad, it seemed like a grey rock.

Inside the dream realm, the Gu Master spoke: "These three Gu worms are water arrow Gu, fire cloak Gu, and spirit saliva Gu. You are a rank one Gu Master, choose one."

"I can only choose one?" Fang Yuan asked.

"Everyone can only choose one." The Gu Master in charge said expressionlessly.

Fang Yuan nodded, he assessed carefully: "Water arrow Gu is for attacking, but it is not good among offensive Gu. Fire cloak Gu is a defensive Gu, it grants me a cloak of fire that can burn enemies mildly, and spirit saliva Gu can be used to heal Gu Masters."

"If I can choose all of them, so be it. But if I can only choose one, it means this task needs cooperation. The earlier Gu Master said that there are a hundred people but ten spots. To explore this dream realm, I probably need to go ahead and get one of the ten spots."

"I choose fire cloak Gu." Fang Yuan thought, answering soon after.

He needed to race for time.

His dream realm exploration time was very precious. The soul would continuously be expended when exploring dream realms, once it weakens to a certain level, Fang Yuan's cognitive abilities would fall drastically. He would be unable to differentiate between reality and the dream, he would not know that he was dreaming. Eventually, his soul would be trapped in the dream, until he died, Fang Yuan would only have his body left in this world, like those pitiful Gu Immortals of Southern Border earlier.

Exploring dream realms was dangerous.

Especially when Fang Yuan was exploring it alone, without anyone around to take care of him. If any problems occurred, he would be unable to save himself, that would be terrible.

But who could Fang Yuan truly trust?

To grow his attainment level, Fang Yuan had to pay a price and take some risks.

"Of course, I have my trump card, I am not recklessly charging around like other Gu Immortals, needing to test their luck." Fang Yuan thought of this and immediately used an immortal killer move — Unravel Dream!

Large numbers of dream path mortal Gu were expended, a mystical power was displayed before Fang Yuan.

A Gu Master suddenly appeared.

The Gu Master from earlier was shocked, he asked the new Gu Master: "Senior brother, why are you here?"

The senior brother said: "I came to take a look, junior brother, give the spirit saliva Gu to this child."

"But senior brother, this is cheating, if it is discovered..." The junior brother was troubled.

The senior brother laughed: "Don't worry, spirit saliva Gu cannot be detected on the outside if it is used secretly. This child also chose fire cloak Gu, when he is concealed by it, who can see that he is healing himself?"

The junior brother nodded: "Since senior brother is saying that, I have nothing else to say. Take it."

Saying so, he tossed two Gu worms at Fang Yuan, fire cloak Gu and spirit saliva Gu.

Fang Yuan had just received them when the surrounding dream realm faded, becoming the second scene.

Unravel dream's effect would change to fit the dream realm, creating effects that would benefit the user.

Thus, unravel dream's actual effect would vary from dream realm to dream realm.

"But this time, after using unravel dream, I only obtained one extra mortal Gu in the dream. Unravel dream is an immortal killer move, this effect was rather small."

Fang Yuan thought about it, when he was exploring Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream realm, unravel dream had immediate results, like untying the wind knot grass instantly, it was direct progress of the dream realm. Unlike here, after using it, he only gained one more mortal Gu.

After all, Fang Yuan's cultivation level was rank two in this dream realm, he had limited primeval essence, he could not use Gu worms many times. Even though he obtained a second Gu, he had to use his primeval essence wisely, the actual help was not very big.

"Don't tell me that because this dream realm is too big, the rules of the dream realm are also stronger. Thus, external influences are less effective? In the five hundred years of my previous life, a batch of Gu Immortals also agreed with this point..."

Regardless of Fang Yuan's thoughts, the second scene had started.

Fang Yuan found that he was in dusty fog, the road in front of him seemed to be at level ground.

"This is the internal space of a Gu formation, it can accommodate a hundred people to fight, the Gu Masters controlling the Gu formation can also observe our situation, huh..."

Fang Yuan analyzed as a young man in the fog approached him.

Fang Yuan thought quickly, he called out: "Don't attack, friend, so many people are participating, we can ally first."

"Ally? You offended Young Master Long, you want others to ally with you?" The young man snickered as he shot out a water arrow.

Fang Yuan's figure shifted, he nimbly dodged it, before pouncing.

Seeing that Fang Yuan was getting close, the young man panicked, he used a second water arrow and tried to force Fang Yuan away.

But Fang Yuan was experienced, seeing the young man raise his hand, he knew where the arrow was heading.

Fang Yuan moved his feet and charged even quicker as the second water arrow missed him narrowly.

The youngster quickly moved back, retreating while firing arrows.

Fang Yuan observed patiently, even though he had a chance to get close, Fang Yuan purposely dodged instead. After a while, the young man was out of steam.

Fang Yuan smiled, slowly walking forward: "Right now, I can disqualify you easily, how about it? Join me and we can work together to deal with the others, I am very sincere!"

"Hmph!" The young man snorted: "Just the two of us against ninety-eight people, you are dreaming. You offended Young Master Long, you wanted to snatch his woman, and you still want to get into Combat Immortal Sect, you are simply dreaming! I would rather give up here than offend Young Master Long foolishly!"

Fang Yuan's heart sank.

In this case, wouldn't he have to deal with the other teenagers in this test alone?

This Young Master Long was truly a problem.

"No wonder earlier, Southern Border's righteous path Gu Immortals suffered heavy losses. This dream realm is too difficult. It is harder than even Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream realm!" Fang Yuan retreated, realizing that he was surrounded by thirty youngsters who had ganged up together, encircling him all around.

Bai Xiang grotto-heaven.

"I succeeded." Bai Ning Bing said plainly.

His gaze was still cold, he had a normal expression, but his appearance was quite tattered, he was charred black, like lamb on a barbecue rack, having been roasted for a long time.

When he spoke, smoke was coming out of his throat.

Bai Xiang heavenly spirit looked at him, nodding: "You used your own body to contain the fire, subduing the raging wave rising dragon fire. Do you know how dangerous this is, there is only a small chance of success, if you fail, your entire body will turn into ash."

"Regardless, I succeeded." Bai Ning Bing was still holding on desperately, when he spoke, each word was said with much difficulty, he was relying solely on his willpower.

Bai Xiang heavenly spirit chuckled: "Since you succeeded, you are now the new owner of this grotto-heaven. Greetings to young master."

Bai Ning Bing nodded, he did not say anything, he felt like he would faint if he uttered another word.

But if he fainted, according to Ying Wu Xie's words, he would be unable to control the raging wave rising dragon fire in his body, he would be burned to a crisp instantly.

At this time, Bai Xiang heavenly spirit said: "Young master, you are in a dangerous situation now, if you are careless, you will die completely, not even your soul will survive. If you were the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance Physique, it would be better, but you had to be the Northern Dark Ice Soul Physique. I have a cultivation method that suits your current state. This Gu refinement method uses the Gu Immortal themselves as Gu material, together with the raging wave rising dragon fire, you will be refined together, young master will leave the human race and become one of the variant humans — a dragonman."

"Dragonman?" Bai Ning Bing stared with wide eyes, thinking: "\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> has no mention of any dragonman. There is such a variant human race?"

Bai Ning Bing did not speak, but Bai Xiang heavenly spirit knew his doubts.

The heavenly spirit continued: "It is indeed not inside \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, because the variant human dragonman was created by a human great expert, Duke Long, the original intention was to prolong lifespan."

"Duke Long is a Heavenly Court Gu Immortal, he has extremely high battle strength, like Sword Immortal Bo Qing in the past. He brought about the method of humans alike dragons[1], he fused refinement path and transformation path, to create a brand new variant human race, the dragonman."

Bai Ning Bing's shock increased a bit more, he thought: "Who is this Duke Long? Even though I only became an immortal recently, knowledge is not my weakness, I know much more than ordinary Gu Immortals. Duke Long is someone on par with Bo Qing, how could he not be in historical records, is there no such person recorded in Gu Immortal history?"

"Is Bai Xiang heavenly spirit speaking rubbish?"

[1] Like the saying dragon among men, dragons are considered superior humans in Chinese belief, with humans being the descendants of dragons. Back

Chapter 1228: Duke Long

Bai Ning Bing knew that a land spirit or heavenly spirit was formed by the Gu Immortal's obsession fused with the immortal aperture's heavenly power, it was a mystical existence.

Because of the obsession, land spirits and heavenly spirits had an ownership acknowledgement requirement, and they could not lie.

But although land spirits and heavenly spirits could not lie, that did not mean they could not spout nonsense.

If land spirits or heavenly spirits obtain wrong information, but they think it is real, when they say it, it is not a lie.

Bai Xiang heavenly spirit's words were quite unbelievable.

Bo Qing was Bo Qing because he was a type of person rarely seen in human history.

What was Bo Qing's title?

The pseudo-Immortal Venerable who split the five regions with his sword, it was fortunate for the people in the world that love changed him!

He was publicly recognized by all Gu Immortals across different eras that he was at a level second to only rank nine Gu Venerables.

Such a person was extremely dazzling, like the moon in the night sky, even over the span of history with countless geniuses. If this Duke Long was a great expert at the level of Bo Qing, how could he not be in historical records?

Bai Ning Bing was full of doubts.

But at this time, Bai Xiang heavenly spirit did not answer his doubts, he asked: "Young master, your life is in great danger. We can only use the humans alike dragons Gu refinement method to turn yourself into a dragonman and resolve your crisis."

"However, this method is rather dangerous."

Bai Xiang heavenly spirit said this as he frowned, sighing as he said: "You must know that Gu refinement has very strict requirements towards the materials. A proficient refinement path expert would consider all of the dao marks that were inside each Gu material."

"And the humans alike dragons Gu refinement method uses the Gu Immortal themselves as the immortal material. But immortal materials like these vary from person to person. Every Gu Immortal has different number of dao marks of differing paths. Thus, this Gu refinement method has a low chance of success."

"If young master had the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance Physique, or if you cultivated transformation path or refinement path, there is a greater chance. But you are on the other extreme, being the Northern Dark Ice Soul Physique!"

"Sigh... if you use this method, the chance of surviving is extremely minute. During the Gu refinement process, all of your dao marks will be affected. Young master, all of the ice and snow path dao marks in your body might vanish completely."

Bai Ning Bing's eyes shined brightly instead!

"My ice and snow path dao marks will vanish, does that mean the information path alliance agreement on me, and the transformation path dao marks, will also vanish?"

He was very stirred up.

All along, what troubled him most were the transformation path dao marks.

Back then, in Southern Border's Qing Mao Mountain, because of yin-yang rotation Gu, he turned from a guy to a girl. Now, once he used the phantom aperture, he would turn into a Gu Immortal, his transformation path dao marks would be suppressed and he would become a male again. If he did not use the phantom aperture and turned back to a mortal, his transformation path dao marks would turn him into a girl again.

Of course, the dao marks from Shadow Sect's information path alliance agreement were Bai Ning Bing's biggest restraint at the moment.

Was Bai Ning Bing someone who would submit to others?

All along, he merely had no methods or ways to break free.

"Use, this, method!" Bai Ning Bing did not hesitate, he struggled intensely and uttered three words.

Central Continent, Heavenly Court.

A female immortal was holding an information path Gu worm and inspecting it carefully.

She had a graceful figure with hair that extended to her waist, and was adorned in a beautiful purple robe. Her eyes were like deep pools, with a sense of sorrow shrouding her face.

It was the wisdom path great expert who replaced Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord, the temporary leader of Heavenly Court, Fairy Zi Wei!

She retracted her attention from the information path Gu worm as her lips curled into a smile.

"Love Gu actually acknowledged Zhao Lian Yun? Interesting."

Fairy Zi Wei was not surprised.

She knew many historical secrets, love Gu had never been reliable in history. In the past, it could acknowledge the inkman Mo Yao, and now, was it really that strange that it acknowledged the otherworldly demon Zhao Lian Yun?

"Spirit Affinity House's supreme elders cannot decide on this matter, so they are pushing the decision to me? They have gotten smarter."

Fairy Zi Wei sighed to herself.

Spirit Affinity House was not having a good time recently.

During the battle of Yi Tian Mountain, Bo Qing, even though he was dead, had become an immortal zombie, playing a crucial role in that battle. Long ago, he had joined Spirit Affinity House as Sword Immortal Bo Qing. Bo Qing's sword lights rampaged over Central Continent, it caused great damage to Central Continent, the ten great ancient sects, and even Heavenly Court. After the battle of Yi Tian Mountain ended, Spirit Affinity House endured immense pressure because of it.

Whether they should make Zhao Lian Yun the current generation fairy of Spirit Affinity House, these Spirit Affinity House supreme elders could not decide. It was a hard decision regardless of whether they make her the fairy or not.

Pushing this difficult problem to Fairy Zi Wei, they could avoid the responsibility themselves.

Fairy Zi Wei did not feel angry about it.

Because she was from Spirit Affinity House in the past.

Fairy Zi Wei was once a Gu Immortal from Spirit Affinity House, because of her great talent, after she became rank eight, she was accepted into Heavenly Court.

Even though the ten great ancient sects were lower level sects of Heavenly Court, their relationship was not as simple as superiors and subordinates.

Because many Heavenly Court Gu Immortals did not forget their roots, the sect that they came from, when descendants from these sects enter Heavenly Court, they would become natural political allies of these Gu Immortals.

Thus, Fairy Zi Wei sided with Spirit Affinity House, and was willing to settle this problem for them.

In fact, she and Fairy Bai Qing had some bloodline relationship.

And Fairy Bai Qing was Feng Jin Huang's mother, and Feng Jin Huang was vying with Zhao Lian Yun for the position of fairy, neither would relent.

If Spirit Affinity House's supreme elders acknowledged Zhao Lian Yun, they would be denying Feng Jin Huang the position, thus, they gave this problem to Fairy Zi Wei and let her decide.

This problem was a small matter to Fairy Zi Wei.

She was about to use the information path Gu worm to reply when she suddenly felt a tremor.

This tremor was mild, Fairy Zi Wei almost thought that she was imagining things.

But soon, a tremor occurred again, at an even greater intensity than before.

Fairy Zi Wei stood up in shock.

She had to be shocked.

Because she was in Heavenly Court now, this was such an important place that was managed for countless years, the defense was extremely tight, how could tremors occur for no reason?

The tremors continued, this situation attracted the attention of many Gu Immortals.

Granny Sha stopped refining Gu, she had an expression of shock.

Wei Ling Yang walked out of his hall and looked around.

Fairy Zi Wei could not sit anymore, she left the hall and heard some dragon roars vaguely in the tremors.

The dragon roars were getting louder, Heavenly Court was shaking with even more intensity now.

Under Fairy Zi Wei's shocked gaze, a dragon shaped pillar of light soared to the sky from deep within Heavenly Court.

"That place, is that deep within the immortal graveyard?" Don't tell me, a senior has awakened?" Fairy Zi Wei frowned.

At this time, Granny Sha and Wei Ling Yang came to her.

"Such a scene inside the immortal graveyard, it must be a senior from Heavenly Court. But I wonder which one?" Granny Sha deduced.

Wei Ling Yang said: "The immortal graveyard is unfathomable and mysterious, even we do not know how many Gu Immortals are slumbering in it. But Heavenly Court has experienced such huge tremors, this person who woke up must be very extraordinary!"

Granny Sha nodded, she was also someone who had woken up from hibernation, but when she woke up, Heavenly Court was peaceful and quiet, without any commotion. It was a clear contrast to now.

Fairy Zi Wei breathed in deeply: "We'll know if we go and see."

The three immortals flew deep into the immortal graveyard, only to see a huge pit that had formed on the plain grassland.

Inside the pit, there was a withered and weak old man.

The old man saw the three Gu Immortals and quickly opened a slit of his eyes with much difficulty, saying weakly: "Water, water..."

Fairy Zi Wei quickly went ahead and used her healing methods.

Granny Sha and Wei Ling Yang looked at each other, the commotion was huge, but to think that this person was so weak when they saw him.

This was really surprising.

"My healing methods are not working." At this time, Fairy Zi Wei frowned as she spoke.

Wei Ling Yang quickly went ahead and used all his methods, but nothing was working on the old man.

Wei Ling Yang said solemnly: "Not good, this senior's body is very strange, my methods are not working. Senior's life force is dwindling, at this rate, he will die in less than a few minutes."

Fairy Zi Wei's eyes shined, she analyzed: "Earlier, senior said water, it must be a method to save him. Ordinary water would not work, then what water does he need?"

Granny Sha was a refinement path expert, she used her healing methods as she said: "There are three fires in this world, and also three waters. They are all rank nine immortal materials, Heavenly Court has stock of all of them, bring them here."

But the three types of water had no effect.

The old man could barely breathe, he was dying.

The three immortals were anxious, what should they do?"

Fairy Zi Wei suddenly pointed at the old man's head: "Senior's forehead had two protrusions, what are these rock-like things?"

Granny Sha was reminded as inspiration flashed in her mind: "I know what water it is!"

She took out the true dragon heavenly water, pouring this rank eight immortal material into the old man's mouth.

The old man obtained this water and his life force surged, his body started inflating, soon, his throat started moving, he had the strength to drink this water himself.

The result was immediate!

The three immortals were overjoyed.

After the old man drank five hundred grams of true dragon heavenly water, he pushed Granny Sha's hands away.

Granny Sha understood and stopped feeding him.

The old man stood up shakily.

He was different from before.

His dry skin had been puffed up, his entire facial shape had changed, he no longer looked like a skeleton.

He opened his aged eyes as he looked at the three immortals, sighing: "This is the last time I can awaken, true dragon heavenly water is not effective now, five hundred grams is enough, any more is a waste. I sensed that someone was using the humans alike dragons Gu refinement method, I can smell traces of fate, I had no choice but to wake up."

"You, you are Duke Long?!" Fairy Zi Wei stared with wide opened eyes, tongue-tied.

"That would be me."

Chapter 1229: Love Gu (1/2)

Zhao Lian Yun was brought into a small secret room in her daze.

"Where is this?" She opened her eyes, looking around.

This secret room was extremely quiet, a bone chilling silence was embedded into every brick in this room, and every inch of the wall.

The secret room was not bright, it was dim like only a candle was lit, sending out faint traces of light, Zhao Lian Yun could barely see anything.

"Come here." From the traces of light, an aged voice spoke.

Zhao Lian Yun followed the direction of the voice.

As she got closer, she saw an elderly person who was as aged as that voice.

She was the first supreme elder of Spirit Affinity House.

First supreme elder looked at Zhao Lian Yun with a deep glance, focusing her attention on love Gu, which was on Zhao Lian Yun's shoulder.

Her gaze moved slightly, she quickly calmed down.

"Kneel down." First supreme elder said.

Zhao Lian Yun felt that even though this old woman did not feel special, she had an immense authority, her calm words carried force that made people feel obliged to obey her.

Thus, Zhao Lian Yun lowered her head as she saw a cushion on the ground.

She knelt down on the cushion, her upper body was straight as she looked at the old woman.

The old woman said: "Look ahead."

Zhao Lian Yun looked ahead, she saw that the secret room was getting bright, Zhao Lian Yun gasped as she stared with wide opened eyes.

Because she saw that on the wall in front, there were countless jade-like small tablets.

"These are life tablet Gu, each of the names there is a certain fairy of Spirit Affinity House in the past. From the first generation until now..." First supreme elder said slowly.

Zhao Lian Yun's breathing intensified, her gaze swept past this wall, there were countless tablets, she was dazzled.

At the top left hand corner, there was a tablet, with the first generation fairy's name written, Shui Ni.

Second generation fairy, Xun Yu.

Third generation fairy, Hui Xin.

...

She also saw Mo Yao, Lian Xiang, and other familiar names.

Zhao Lian Yun looked at these names, her breathing became rough. She was like a child, staring at the night sky that was flickering with countless stars.

She knew that these people were all past stars in the Gu Immortal world. Every generation of Spirit Affinity House's fairies was a Gu Immortal that was famous in Central Continent! They were extraordinary and unrivaled. They were like pearls that were linked together, from the past to the present, they weaved Spirit Affinity House's future, leaving behind dazzling brilliance and glory throughout history.

Zhao Lian Yun was dazed, at this moment, first supreme elder spoke: "From now onwards, you are the current generation fairy of Spirit Affinity House. Your life tablet Gu is already at the lowest position."

At this moment, Zhao Lian Yun's heart froze.

She stared with wide opened eyes, looking at the old lady, she was overjoyed but had endless doubts: "How can this be? Am I dreaming? According to Spirit Affinity House's rules, I am not qualified yet, I..."

She said this until she thought of something, she turned her gaze away as she looked at love Gu on her shoulder: "Is it because of this Gu?"

First supreme elder nodded slightly: "This is love Gu, you have already received love Gu's acknowledgement."

After Zhao Lian Yun fainted, when she woke up, she was already inside this secret room.

She was unsure of what love Gu looked like, but she knew that love Gu was the signature Gu of Spirit Affinity House!

"Is this love Gu?!" Zhao Lian Yun's body shook, her voice was also off pitch.

First supreme elder nodded again.

Zhao Lian Yun breathed intensely, intense joy was in her heart, it slowly oozed out as she felt like fortune had hit her in her head.

But this bliss was too sudden, it was too great, she did not feel any joy, she felt some fear and uneasiness.

She was afraid that everything was fake, she was worried that this was just a dream after she fainted.

Thus, she stared with wide opened eyes, asking first supreme elder nervously: "Why?"

This why contained too many questions.

Why did love Gu choose her?

Why did she become Spirit Affinity House's fairy?

Why did all this happen?

First supreme elder did not answer her, she sighed deeply as she said slowly: "You must have read \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, among which, one chapter said this."

Ren Zu obtained love, courage, and betrayal, he was no longer unable to progress due to fear.

He continued to move forward.

On this day, he walked on his road, hearing a voice behind: "Oh Ren Zu, I finally found you. Slow down, wait for me."

Ren Zu stopped moving, turning around. He saw a snowman running up to him.

"What is it, snowman." Ren Zu asked curiously.

The snowman said: "Oh Ren Zu, I finally found you. I am the strongest snowman in my tribe, snowmen are said to be afraid of fire, I want to prove that it is untrue. I traveled the world, I have already conquered the bright light glorious ring fire in the sky, the azure divine stone furnace fire in the earth, and the raging wave rising dragon fire in the sea. But I heard that there is a fourth type of fire in this world, called the fire of love. Once it burns, it can turn all life forms in this world into cinders. I do not believe it, I heard that you have just obtained love Gu, thus I wanted to try it."

"Fire of love?" Ren Zu was surprised, he was hearing it for the first time.

Thus, he called out love Gu, asking: "Oh Gu, oh Gu, can you emit the fire of love?"

Love Gu replied: "I can, and I cannot."

Ren Zu and the snowman were curious, they asked: "What do you mean by can and cannot?"

Love Gu explained: "I can because I am necessary in order to emit the fire of love. But I cannot, because I alone am not sufficient, two hearts are needed."

"Two hearts?" The snowman was worried, she took out her heart from her chest.

This heart was huge and tough, it was emitting strong pressure.

The snowman said: "This is my heart of domination, it is a pity that I only have one heart."

Ren Zu said: "Don't worry, I have a heart too."

Ren Zu originally had one heart, but he gave it to hope Gu.

He next obtained a heart of loneliness, self Gu was residing within it.

He also had a heart of discontent.

Thus, right now, he took out the heart of discontent.

The heart of discontent was dry and shriveled, it was small and weak, because this heart had little blood left. Ren Zu had once used almost all of his heart blood in Ordinary Abyss, to grow the grass and trees of achievement.

Love Gu flew into the heart of discontent and flew out, it flew into the heart of domination and flew out again.

It flew into the sky and said: "Alright, you want the fire of love, let these two hearts clash."

The snowman and Ren Zu took out their respective hearts, putting them together.

Crackle, sparks were created.

The sparks grew rapidly, turning into a blazing flame.

Fire of love!

The fire of love burned on Ren Zu's heart of discontent, it instantly turned this heart into ashes.

Ren Zu was stunned.

Love Gu said: "Love has a price, it makes people willing to sacrifice."

The snowman laughed: "Oh Ren Zu, thankfully you have two hearts, otherwise, without a heart, you would die."

The snowman turned to look at the heart of domination in her hand.

The fire of love enveloped this heart, but this heart shone brighter and brighter.

The snowman was nonchalant: "Oh what, this fire of love only has an impressive appearance, it neither has the heat of bright light glorious ring fire, or the heaviness of azure divine stone furnace fire, or the chaos of raging wave rising dragon fire."

As she said, she placed the heart of domination into her chest.

Next, her body started bursting out in flames, she started melting like snowflakes under the sun.

She turned pale from shock, she quickly patted and attempted to put out the fire of love.

But the fire of love could not be extinguished.

Eventually, the snowman completely melted, only her heart was left, burning in raging flames.

Ren Zu was extremely shocked, he felt that this snowman was very strong, to think that she would vanish like this.

"The fire of love is so scary." Ren Zu was shocked.

Love Gu said: "The result of love varies from heart to heart. The heart of the snowman was domination, but you had the heart of discontent, and it was completely burned from the fire. Thus, this was the result. Actually, there are good results that can occur when the fire of love burns."

The results of love varied, each experience of love was a risk and gamble.

Ren Zu suddenly thought of something, becoming stirred up: "Oh love Gu, you said that love can make people willing to sacrifice. This is wonderful, I will fall in love with the feathermen and make them willing to fly for me, so that they can save my daughter from Ordinary Abyss."

Right at this moment, a voice could be heard: "Father, father."

From the burning flames of the heart of domination, a boy jumped out.

He was Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance.

Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance jumped into Ren Zu's arms as he said: "Father, father, so I have a sister as well. I support you, let's go save sister."

Ren Zu was extremely overjoyed, he rubbed Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance's head as he said: "My son, you are so smart and sensible!"

Ren Zu brought Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance and went on a journey again, not long after, they returned to the gathering spot of the feathermen.

Ren Zu took out his heart of loneliness, saying to the feathermen: "Do you all have hearts?"

The feathermen answered: "We all have the heart of freedom."

Ren Zu laughed: "Then let us fall in love, I have a heart too, as well as love Gu."

The feathermen shook their heads: "The heart of freedom will be completely burned in the fire of love."

The process of pursuing love was also the process of losing freedom.

Ren Zu was persistent: "The results of love vary from hearts to hearts. Don't just look at one heart, my heart of loneliness is part of the process too."

But no matter how Ren Zu urged, the feathermen would not agree.

Chapter 1230: Love Gu (2/2)

Ren Zu was helpless, he asked love Gu: "Oh Gu, oh Gu, they don't want to love me, you have to help me, and ignite the fire of love in our hearts."

Love Gu sighed: "This is beyond my abilities. I cannot force others to love, no matter what heart, it has to collide on its own free will."

Ren Zu shook his head: "No, this is a good chance to save my daughter, I cannot give up. Self Gu, I will rely on you."

Self Gu nodded, using its own strength.

It had once eaten a mouthful of strength Gu, right now, Ren Zu had his own strength.

Thus, these feathermen were all captured by Ren Zu, their hearts to dug out and used to collide with Ren Zu's heart.

But no matter how they collided, there were no hearts that created the spark of love.

Love Gu sighed: "Oh Ren Zu, forcing others to love is impossible, you will only create hatred."

As it said that, a Gu worm appeared before Ren Zu.

Ren Zu took a look, it was hatred Gu indeed.

Hatred Gu made all of the feathermen feel hatred.

They shouted: "Oh Ren Zu, you are too much, you are bullying us, we will make you pay the price!"

Thus, these feathermen flew up together, shining worms were flying out of their bodies, they were wild freedom Gu.

The freedom Gu fused together into a gigantic freedom Gu.

This freedom Gu easily took away Ren Zu's love Gu.

"Henceforth, love is free." This giant freedom Gu said.

Ren Zu's self Gu quickly flew out, it wanted to snatch love Gu, but it could not overpower freedom Gu, it only managed to take a bite of love Gu.

Self Gu said angrily: "Love, also belongs to oneself!"

...

After Zhao Lian Yun heard first supreme elder's words, she was still in a daze.

Stories in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> were widely spread, Zhao Lian Yun had seen them many times in her childhood, but she always thought of them as fictitious tales.

As a matter of fact, she did not expect that this strict granny would talk to her about \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> in such a heavy and serious atmosphere.

Spirit Affinity House's first supreme elder saw Zhao Lian Yun's expression and knew that she had never paid close attention to \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

Thus, first supreme elder said: "The love Gu on your shoulder is rank nine, but it has a major flaw."

"What flaw?" Zhao Lian Yun asked.

"It cannot be refined." First supreme elder said solemnly.

"What do you mean? Even... Gu Immortals cannot refine it?" Zhao Lian Yun asked.

First supreme elder smiled: "Not to mention Gu Immortals, even rank nine venerables cannot. In history, many venerables have tried. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had attempted to refine this Gu for three years in a row without pause, but he still failed miserably."

Zhao Lian Yun heard this secret and stared with wide opened eyes.

"So there are things in this world that Immortal Venerables or Demon Venerables cannot do!" She exclaimed.

"Venerables only have the strongest battle strength, invincible in this world. But they are not omnipotent, in the past, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had to ask Long Hair Ancestor for help in terms of Gu refinement, this is an obvious conclusion." First supreme elder spoke slowly.

"Thus, love Gu cannot be controlled, it is free and nobody can give it orders." First supreme elder concluded.

"But why did it..." Zhao Lian Yun did not know what to say, she looked at love Gu on her shoulder.

In her vision, love Gu was so dazzling and bright.

First supreme elder said: "This is the acknowledgement of love Gu, this situation is rare, but it has happened quite a number of times before. The last time was Fairy Mo Yao."

"Why did it acknowledge me?" Zhao Lian Yun was curious.

First supreme elder shook her head: "I am not sure. But our sect has concluded two points. Firstly, a person has to believe in love to gain its acknowledgement, this is the foundation. Secondly, someone's love has to reach an intense level, the greater your love, the higher the chances of gaining love Gu's acknowledgement."

"Is that so?" Zhao Lian Yun blinked as she listened.

She realized, it was because she loved Ma Hong Yun so deeply, even willing to give up her own life, that love Gu came and acknowledged her.

Why did this not happen for Feng Jin Huang?

Because she had no lover.

Love was not familial affection or friendship.

First supreme elder continued: "Precisely because love Gu cannot be controlled, to make use of it, one needs love Gu's acknowledgement. Thus, there is a rule in our sect since we were created. Anyone who gains love Gu's acknowledgement, be it female or male, would be our sect's current generation fairy."

Zhao Lian Yun blinked: "There are male fairies too?"

First supreme elder smiled: "Our sect has a large proportion of females, but we also have males. Why would we not have them? Look at that tablet in the center, named Sheng Yu Shan, at the bottom right corner, with Qian Yuan Liang, these are all people dedicated to love in our sect's history."

"Actually, love Gu has many special effects. For example, it has a different appearance as seen by different people. How does it appear to you now?"

Zhao Lian Yun replied honestly: "Dazzling with multi-colored rainbows."

First supreme elder nodded: "To my sight, it is grey and unattractive, like a rock by the roadside."

"How could this be?"

First supreme elder smiled lightly, deep wisdom hidden in her eyes: "I stopped believing in love long ago, thus, love Gu looks like that to me. In the generations of fairies, love Gu has always looked different, some see clear water, some see peach blossoms, there were countless forms that were observed."

"And also, love Gu has varying effects."

"Please enlighten me." Zhao Lian Yun said.

First supreme elder continued: "Normally speaking, a Gu worm, be it mortal or immortal, has only one effect. Like water arrow Gu, it can only shoot water arrows. But love Gu is different, it can be said to have unlimited effects. It can shoot fire, heal, or provide defense for instance."

Zhao Lian Yun became overjoyed as she listened: "So amazing!"

First supreme elder shook her head: "Love Gu is a rank nine Gu, it is naturally extraordinary. It has unlimited effects, but it cannot be controlled, if you want it to attack, it will bring you to fly away. If you want to defend, it will heal you. Often, when you want it to work, it does absolutely nothing. When you do not want it to activate, it will come out and unleash its might."

Zhao Lian Yun was a little disheartened, but she soon gathered her spirits: "Even so, it is a rank nine Immortal Gu, any of the effects used must be extraordinary."

First supreme elder said: "You are right, but you forgot something, strength cannot be gained from nothing, you have to pay a price. Every time love Gu is used, it will take something away from you."

Zhao Lian Yun was nervous: "What thing?"

"The most common thing is immortal essence. But you are not a Gu Immortal, it might take away your beauty, your eyesight, or your lifespan." First supreme elder said grimly.

Zhao Lian Yun's expression was pale, she looked at the love Gu on her shoulder again.

But now, her gaze was very different from before.

"This Immortal Gu might end up accelerating my death? If that is the case, I need to make good use of my time!" Zhao Lian Yun made a resolute decision.

She mustered her spirits, saying to first supreme elder: "Even if I have a pay a big price, I will save Ma Hong Yun. Elder, if I become Spirit Affinity House's current generation fairy, can I use the sect's power to return to Northern Plains?"

First supreme elder did not answer Zhao Lian Yun immediately.

She had a complex expression.

A while ago, Heavenly Court's Duke Long awakened, when news got out, the ten great ancient sects were stirred!

Duke Long was on par with Bo Qing in terms of strength. With just his own power, he created a brand new race, the dragonman.

In other words, he was the ancestor of dragonmen.

He had a legendary life, but his reputation was not high, buried deep in history. Even in the ten great ancient sects, barely anyone knew of him.

Duke Long had great seniority, he was unbelievably old, when he woke up, Fairy Zi Wei immediately gave up her position as leader, handing it to Duke Long.

The other Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were all in agreement.

Duke Long used information path methods and understood the situation, he immediately ordered for Zhao Lian Yun to be Spirit Affinity House's current generation fairy.

Not just that, Duke Long even gave Zhao Lian Yun a phantom aperture, turning her into a Gu Immortal. More absurdly, he even ordered the ten great ancient sects to cooperate with Zhao Lian Yun, to bring a team to Northern Plains and save Ma Hong Yun after some time.

The ten great ancient sects were in tumult, but they all obeyed him without objection.

Because of historical reasons, nobody dared to question Duke Long's arrangements regarding love Gu.

Such news were not for Zhao Lian Yun to know about.

First supreme elder also did not want her to know.

Zhao Lian Yun was kneeling before her now, but she had fainted for a few days already. She would not know that the ten great ancient sects were engaged in a contest regarding the huge storm surrounding her.

Zhao Lian Yun saw that first supreme elder did not answer her, she became very nervous. She was afraid that first supreme elder would say no.

But first supreme elder soon said: "Zhao Lian Yun, you are an otherworldly demon who obtained the Thieving Heaven true inheritance. Perhaps you might be one of the most unique fairies in Spirit Affinity House."

"And maybe because of your special traits..."

"Don't worry, Heavenly Court has been alerted by this, the ten great ancient sects will go ahead and form a team consisting of you as the core, to rescue your lover Ma Hong Yun in Northern Plains."

"What?!" Zhao Lian Yun stared with wide opened eyes, hearing this, she was extremely joyful and surprised!

Chapter 1231: Water Path Quasi-Grandmaster

Southern Border, super Gu formation.

Ba Quan Feng looked in Wu clan's direction, wondering discontentedly: "What is going on? This Wu Yi Hai is so patient, he is cultivating in seclusion and not going outside?"

He found it hard to believe.

Wu clan's members usually acted overbearingly, once in a while, they would find trouble with others.

Wu Yi Hai was Wu Yong's half-brother, he had very high status in Wu clan. But he actually chose to cultivate in seclusion and normally did not interact with Gu Immortals.

Ba De shook his head.

He said solemnly: "Now it seems, this Wu Yi Hai is not simple at all."

"Or rather, he is even harder to deal with than the rank seven Wu clan Gu Immortal earlier."

Ba Quan Feng laughed:" How can that be? He is merely a lone cultivator from Eastern Sea."

Old Treeman Ba De looked at Ba Quan Feng: "If he is only an ordinary lone cultivator, how can he manage this immortal opportunity business so outstandingly? Even if we place pressure on the business, we cannot do anything to Wu Yi Hai."

"These last days, we have prepared many ways, but this person completely ignored us, facing our taunts, he chose to stay silent and endure it. Such a person is far more dangerous than other Wu clan Gu Immortals."

Ba Quan Feng's expression changed, he breathed in deeply: "Lord Old Treeman, even you give him high praise, it seems this person is really outstanding. Why don't we go and ruin this immortal opportunity business, to force him to act?"

Ba De shook his head: "Impossible, he will definitely not do anything. If we expose this matter, the immortal opportunity business will certainly fall apart since it is not allowed in the first place. But we will not be able to harm Wu Yi Hai, and we will even offend the six other clans with them, all of their animosity will be drawn towards us. By then, Wu Yi Hai would benefit from it and unite them to form an even tighter political force."

Ba Quan Feng stared with wide opened eyes, bellowing: "Then what do we do?"

"Wait."

"Wait?"

"Wait for an opportunity." Old Treeman Ba De said: "The opportunity that we can create right now is small and insignificant. In that case, we wait for a better opportunity in the future."

Ba Quan Feng gritted his teeth: "Then wouldn't Wu clan be above us? How long would we need to wait, we might have to wait for a very long time."

Old Treeman Ba De's expression turned cold, he no longer spoke, only looking at Ba Quan Feng silently.

Ba Quan Feng felt an immense pressure from his gaze.

He took three steps back, lowering his head as sweat appeared on his forehead: "Lord, I... I..."

"You are too rash Little Feng, these last days, your mental state is not right." Ba De said slowly.

"Yes, yes lord, I was wrong." Ba Quan Feng obediently admitted his mistake in an earnest manner.

"Wu clan indeed lost a rank eight Gu Immortal, but they are still a huge force. The other clans are observing Wu clan, but nobody wants to strike first, because we have not uncovered Wu clan's true foundation yet. If Ba clan is the first to jump out and is met with Wu clan's iron fist, we would suffer a loss, while the other clans would benefit, do you understand?"

"Yes, I will remember lord's words."

"You will stay in seclusion, if Wu Yi Hai does not come out, you will also stay inside." Ba De said expressionlessly.

"Yes, lord." Ba Quan Feng had a bitter expression as he acknowledged this, before taking his leave.

Fang Yuan was still inside a dream realm.

The Gu Immortals outside all thought he was undergoing closed cultivation, most Gu Immortals thought that this was Wu Yi Hai's trait as an Eastern Sea lone cultivator, he had not adjusted his mindset. After all, lone immortals and secluded immortals loved to enter secluded cultivation.

A small portion, including Ba De, thought that Fang Yuan was purposely doing this to deal with their political methods.

But nobody thought that Fang Yuan was secretly exploring the dream realm!

Inside the dream realm, it was now a crucial moment.

Young Master Long had already gained a huge advantage in battle, he laughed at Fang Yuan: "You no longer stand a chance, you cannot win. If you surrender now, you can still save some face."

Fang Yuan was covered in injuries, he was breathing roughly as he gritted his teeth, not speaking.

This was the seventh scene of the dream realm.

Fang Yuan's cultivation level was also at rank five.

But Young Master Long was even stronger than him, at rank five peak stage.

Not only that, Young Master Long had many useful Gu worms, and with his dragonman constitution, be it the defense of his dragon scales, or the regenerative properties of his dragon blood, they were on par with rank five Gu worms.

His advantage was too huge!

Be it cultivation level, Gu worms, or his own human body, Fang Yuan was suppressed heavily by Young Master Long.

It was already a huge surprise to the spectators in the dream realm that the fight lasted this long.

In their opinion, even though Fang Yuan's spirit was commendable, this battle's result was already decided.

"Now, you have less than five percent of your primeval essence, let's see how you block my attack!" Young Master Long shouted as he pounced at Fang Yuan.

Even though Fang Yuan was in a bad state, his gaze was very clear, as he counted down in his head.

After several failed explorations, he had already learned that he did not need to defeat Young Master Long in this battle, he needed to stall for time, he needed sufficient time.

Once time was up, a chance would occur.

"Seven breaths of time left. This time, I should give it a try, immortal killer move — Unravel Dream!" Fang Yuan called out in his mind.

Ping.

Young Master Long, who was approaching imposingly and arrogantly as he took large steps towards Fang Yuan, suddenly fell face down on the ground, after tripping over a rock.

The entire arena turned silent.

All of the female Gu Masters who were cheering for Young Master Long since the start of the battle went quiet.

"How could I make such a mistake?!" Young Master Long had a jade-like appearance, but his face was flushing red as he turned angry from shame.

He quickly got up, shouting as he charged at Fang Yuan again.

Fang Yuan could only barely stand now, his injuries were too severe.

He was simply waiting for his defeat, the entire place started cheering for Young Master Long again.

"Go, Young Master Long! Defeat this overconfident challenger!"

"Ah, I will remember this scene in my heart. Young Master Long is so charming, if only I could stand beside him, that would be great."

"If he could talk to me, I would be satisfied in this life."

The male Gu Masters were roaring, the female Gu Masters were calling out while cupping their hands or holding their faces.

Immortal killer move — Unravel Dream!

Fang Yuan could only use this again, because he could no longer put up a fight in this battle.

Whoosh.

A soft sound echoed.

Young Master Long's movement paused.

He was taking large steps, and was ready to win the battle, but now, an unexpected accident occurred again.

Maybe because he took steps that were too large, or maybe his clothes were torn in the fight earlier, but now, his pants entirely ripped.

Wind blew, young master Long felt a chill in his crotch.

The entire place went silent.

Even Fang Yuan was surprised, thinking: "The effect of unravel dream currently is really quite peculiar."

"Ah—!" Suddenly, female Gu Masters screamed.

The place went into a clamor.

"What is happening?"

"Hahahaha!"

"Young Master Long's pants ripped."

"So Young Master Long does not wear underwear."

The male Gu Masters were watching with interest while the female Gu Masters were covering their faces, using the gaps between their fingers to continue watching secretly.

But the view was quite disappointing.

"So Young Master Long's.... is this small."

Young Master Long: "..."

His body was shaking intensely, his face was completely red, veins were popping on his forehead, his expression was extremely scary and malicious.

"Ahhhh! I will kill you!!" The shame in his heart was driving Young Master Long crazy, he pounced at Fang Yuan ferociously.

However, Fang Yuan smiled like a winner.

At the next moment, seven breaths of time had passed.

Plop.

With a soft sound, Young Master Long's entire body self-detonated.

His dragon blood splattered on Fang Yuan's face.

The entire place went into a commotion.

"Young, Young Master Long!"

"Why did this happen?!" Several female Gu Masters fainted on the spot.

"Did Young Master Long kill himself due to the shame and embarrassment?"

"It must be him." A Gu Master pointed at Fang Yuan: "He must have used some evil method to kill Young Master Long. He is a blood path demon!"

Boom boom boom.

At the next moment, the spectating dragonmen all self-detonated one after another.

At once, blood splattered all over the place, the surviving Gu Masters were in chaos.

Fang Yuan blinked, worried that these people would bring problems to him, but suddenly, the dream realm transformed as a new scene appeared.

"Puff, this seventh scene is finally over." Fang Yuan let out a breath.

He had been stuck at this seventh scene for three days. According to the special trait of the dream realm, he had to go through scene by scene, otherwise, he would need to repeat it endlessly.

A moment later, Fang Yuan left the dream realm after failing the eighth scene.

After regaining his senses, he treated his injuries.

The dream realm caused severe damage to the soul.

Thankfully, Fang Yuan's soul foundation was outstanding, and with guts Gu, these injuries were no problem.

More than ten breaths later, Fang Yuan's soul was as good as before.

Next, he inspected his gains.

"Hmm, not bad, my water path attainment level has already reached quasi-grandmaster."

Fang Yuan's water path attainment level was originally ordinary, it was not even master level. But the main character of this dream realm was a water path cultivator.

By the time Fang Yuan got to the seventh scene, his water path attainment level went from ordinary to master, after he passed the seventh scene, it became extremely close to grandmaster.

"It seems that the protagonist of this dream realm had very high achievements, they were definitely higher than rank six."

"Now that I have water path attainment level, I can annex most of those blessed lands inside City Well, in Eastern Sea. Wonderful, wonderful!"

Chapter 1232: Body Refinement

"However, the mortal Gu for unravel dream were expended greatly. Right now, I can use less than ten unravel dreams."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan frowned lightly.

This was a problem.

Unravel dream was very effective, but the expenditure of dream path mortal Gu was huge.

And because these dream path mortal Gu were all refined by Fang Yuan solely, he could not raise their production.

Give these dream path Gu recipes to Lang Ya Sect and get the hairy man Gu Immortals to refine Gu for him?

Fang Yuan did not even consider this.

At this time period, the value of these dream path mortal Gu was higher than Immortal Gu!

Of course, Fang Yuan believed that Lang Ya land spirit could afford to pay this, but there was no absolute secret in this world, if it was exposed, the impact would be too big.

Fang Yuan was at the peak of the five regions in terms of dream realm exploration, if these dream path mortal Gu recipes were known to others, his advantage would be gone.

This was what Fang Yuan did not want to see.

Thus, he would rather refine them himself, even though the production was lower, he had to keep it strictly to himself. As long as he did not expose it, who would know?

"I cannot get others to help, but I can make use of things like spring dream fruit trees to raise the efficiency of my dream path mortal Gu refinement." Fang Yuan thought of the spring dream fruit tree again.

Spring dream fruit trees were a very special type of plant.

It existed in dreams and did not have solid form. But it needed a real living tree as its foundation to survive.

Fang Yuan knew of one spring dream fruit tree, it was at the base of a nameless mountain in Central Continent.

This volcano erupted every several hundred years, the large amounts of volcanic ash created fertile soil in the surroundings. Thus, many people lived there.

Fang Yuan had once harvested the fruits of this spring dream fruit tree, they helped him greatly.

But Fang Yuan could not transplant this spring dream fruit tree.

The spring dream fruit tree at the base of the volcano was residing with a thousand year fire date tree. If Fang Yuan moved it, the spring dream fruit tree would be destroyed.

And Central Continent was a lions' den to Fang Yuan now, he could not go there.

Familiar face could allow him to disguise himself, but he could not avoid wisdom path Gu Immortals' deductions. Dark limit Immortal Gu could help him, but it was only rank six, that was not enough.

Fang Yuan could not solve this problem currently, it was out of his abilities.

And he also could not find a second spring dream fruit tree, he had no such methods, he could only give up.

After resting for a while, Fang Yuan did not rush into the dream realm.

He needed to deduce the eighth scene.

He was a wisdom path grandmaster, deducing things in advance could help him to explore the dream realm.

This was his advantage, he obviously made use of it.

In terms of wisdom path, he did not lack attainment level, but Immortal Gu instead. Unravel Mystery was his only wisdom path Immortal Gu, it was alone without any accompanying wisdom path killer moves, thus, Unravel Mystery had little use.

Right now, Fang Yuan was barely making use of it.

In terms of wisdom path, he was not focusing on developing it currently, so Fang Yuan was keeping things in this state.

Deductions were not just for dream realm, but also Fang Yuan's current environment and situation.

"If I guessed correctly, Ba clan is my biggest enemy. Earlier, they looked for many ways to find trouble with me but I solved it all, now it seems that they want to observe on the sidelines."

Ba clan's passive state was making Fang Yuan feel wary.

If they did not do anything, Fang Yuan would not know what they were thinking, preparing, or scheming. If they took action, Fang Yuan could sense their plan and deal with it, resolving whatever problems they sent to him.

"All in all, the situation is quite good, Wu Yi Hai's identity is really useful now."

"The weakness of the immortal opportunity business was no longer an issue after my arrangement, it became a scheme displayed right in front of me. Maybe I can trap some stupid Gu Immortals?"

After all, wisdom path Gu Immortals were few in numbers.

Even if there were wisdom path Gu Immortals, they might not be righteous, if they did not know the rules of the righteous path, it was impossible.

As for Wu An or Wu Liao, they were doing their work properly, Fang Yuan did not have to bother with them.

Wu Liao had come to report some matters to Fang Yuan earlier, but Fang Yuan was determined to leave the work to them, he said that he was not to be bothered unless there were major matters.

Wu Liao was extremely disappointed, thinking that Fang Yuan was the same as the previous rank seven, his attitude towards Fang Yuan turned cold.

Fang Yuan sensed this easily but ignored it.

This giant dream realm was expanding slowly at all times.

When Fang Yuan secretly explored it, the dream realm would shrink, but to the entire dream realm, it was just a small portion, it only would slow down the speed of the dream realm's expansion.

He could easily conceal it.

Those demonic path and lone immortals who explored the dream realm through the immortal opportunity business were Fang Yuan's greatest concealment.

These people usually met with difficulties in the dream realm, but there were one or two of them who could bring out dream path materials even though they failed the exploration.

These dream path materials could naturally refine dream path Gu worms.

These Gu Immortals treated them like treasure, even though only a small number had gains, the remaining Gu Immortals were extremely excited.

The righteous path clans were also secretly purchasing the Gu materials from these Gu Immortals.

Wu clan was no exception.

However, the Gu Immortals who gained dream path Gu materials rarely chose to sell them, they kept them as valuables.

Wu clan only purchased around ten Gu materials, Fang Yuan did not dare to touch these materials, Wu clan was keeping a close eye on them.

After resting for a while, Fang Yuan went into the dream realm.

It was not the giant dream realm, but his own dream.

To get dream path Gu materials, one's own dream realm was the best and safest option.

Unfortunately, these Gu Immortals did not know that.

Southern Border, Bai Xiang grotto-heaven.

At the center of a huge Gu formation, Bai Ning Bing sat down with difficulty.

Bai Xiang heavenly spirit was in the air, manipulating the Gu formation.

The Gu formation operated silently, multi-colored lights were flickering from time to time, gathering in a stream, or splitting up like flowers, flying around aimlessly.

Bai Ning Bing had a pale expression, but his aura was much more stable than before.

This was because the Gu formation was enduring a portion of the pressure for him. He used his body to contain the raging wave rising dragon fire, it was truly too reckless, his life was on the line.

"Next is the most important step, we will target the raging wave rising dragon fire in your body!" Bai Xiang heavenly spirit had a solemn expression: "Young master, you need to persevere and be completely focused, you need to coordinate with the Gu formation and suppress the raging wave rising dragon fire. The entire process will take forty-nine days. During that period, you will not get any rest, if I do not say stop, it would not have ended yet. Even at the final moment, if you lose concentration, you will die for sure."

Bai Ning Bing's eyes were seeing stars, he felt dizzy, almost unable to sit properly.

In this situation, not to mention forty-nine days, he would not even last half a day.

In this critical junction, his lips curled up, he was smiling.

"Hehehe, this is so fun."

"According to my current condition, this is an impossible task..."

"This can test the true limits of my body."

"Even if I die like this, it is very interesting!"

His body was tired, but he was very energetic in his mind.

Breathing in deeply, Bai Ning Bing called out to Bai Xiang heavenly spirit: "Why are you waiting, aren't you going to start?"

Bai Xiang heavenly spirit smiled as he thought: "I had waited so long for this young master to arrive, he seems to be quite capable, he has no fear towards death."

Thinking so, Bai Xiang heavenly spirit activated the Gu formation.

Boom!

At the next moment, brilliant lights burst out of the Gu formation, spreading over the entire place.

"Ah—!" Bai Ning Bing screamed as he raised his head.

A huge flame burst out of his eyes, nose, mouth, and ears.

Raging flames spread over his body, turning Bai Ning Bing into a human shaped fire pillar.

Pain, pain, pain!

Bai Ning Bing was someone who would not frown even if he was heavily injured, but now, he had no such composure, he screamed loudly in pain.

Simply because the pain was too intense, he had to do this to vent the anguish.

Bai Ning Bing was originally expecting the pain of a burning fire. But in fact, it was not like this.

While screaming, he realized something: This humans alike dragons Gu refinement method not only targeted the raging wave rising dragon fire but Bai Ning Bing himself. Be it his body or soul, or the dao marks in his body, they were all melted and separated under the humans alike dragons Gu refinement method.

This was the same as processing Bai Ning Bing as an immortal material, the pain was simply too immense to describe.

"Hang on, hang on!" Bai Xiang heavenly spirit screamed anxiously.

Bai Ning Bing's eyes already had turned over to show the whites, the intense pain sent him into despair, he was in a state of being close to unconsciousness.

If he fainted, at that very moment, he would be burnt to a crisp by the raging dragon fire!

Northern Plains, Snowy Mountain first peak.

Ma Hong Yun was also screaming.

"Ahhhh!" The veins on his neck were popping.

Intense lightning danced in his body, Ma Hong Yun's body was shaking intensely, he seemed to be spasming or dancing frantically.

After a moment, the lightning faded, as Ma Hong Yun breathed roughly with sweat pouring out of his pores, he did not have any strength left.

"Failed again?" Lady Wan Shou frowned, feeling slightly angry.

Ma Hong Yun had already been lightning refined countless times, even though he suffered each time, he did not lack any limbs, he was still intact. Furthermore, his cultivation level had risen to rank five peak stage.

This made Lady Wan Shou speechless.

Chapter 1233: Gathering of Central Continent Gu Immortals

Central Continent.

In a certain village.

Rumble!

Intense rumbling was occurring on the mountain.

An endless amount of rocks and soil were falling down the mountain grandly like an avalanche.

"Quickly escape for our lives!"

"I am going to die, I am going to die..."

"Father, where are you, don't leave me behind!"

Seeing the disaster unfold, the peaceful village exploded into complete chaos.

Countless people were scurrying around in a frenzy, some were lying on the ground in despair, children were crying as mothers held onto them, many had given up resisting.

In a situation without anyone noticing, a figure was floating in the sky.

It was a rank seven Gu Immortal.

He was dressed in a silky blue robe, his long hair extended to his shoulder, he was not brawny, but rather delicate looking.

At this moment, he was frowning, muttering as he looked at the mud flow: "This mud flow is very strange."

Normally speaking, before the mud flow there would be huge rain, but now, the weather was sunny.

The truth was, the environment of the surrounding tens of thousands of li had been secretly modified by the rank seven Gu Immortal, he could ensure a proper amount of rain and sun to gain plentiful harvests yearly.

Plop.

Mountain rocks suddenly burst apart, as a huge brass shell appeared from underneath.

The rank seven Gu Immortal with a blue robe floated in the sky, looking at this extremely eye-catching scene.

He frowned slightly, before it eased: "Oh. So it's a swamp crab."

The swamp crab was a desolate beast, its body was covered in a hard shell, its eyes had vanished due to evolution, it had no weaknesses left.

It was the king of the swamp among desolate beasts.

The ten pairs of claws were extraordinarily firm, the first pair of pincers was more fearsome than steel poles, a pair of pincers that could break mountain rocks or cut a flood dragon in half! Its remaining eighteen claws, although thinner than the first pair, they were still thicker than hundred year old trees.

The blue robed rank seven Gu Immortal saw this swamp crab and his eyes shone, feeling pleased.

He was a water path Gu Immortal, this swamp crab had both earth path and water path dao marks. Killing it would give this blue robed rank seven Gu Immortal a lot of usable immortal materials.

"But the swamp crab is only a desolate beast, if I nurture it well, it might grow into the ancient desolate beast muddy swamp crab, and above that, there is the mud coat swamp crab. The mud coat swamp crab is an immemorial desolate beast, I can stop dreaming about it. My immortal aperture blessed land cannot nurture an immemorial desolate beast, but I can try to get a muddy swamp crab."

Thinking of this, the blue robed rank seven Gu Immortal attacked.

He extended his hand out of his wide sleeves.

His skin was pale, and his fingers were slim.

His ten fingers moved around elegantly, they were covered in layers of multi-colored lights.

This was his special method to manipulate Gu worms!

Soon, countless Gu worm auras rose in his body, there were mortal Gu and also Immortal Gu, different auras weaved together, creating a complex aura that spread everywhere.

The swamp crab in the mountain had no eyes, but using its wild beast instinct, it acutely sensed the threat in the air.

The swamp crab started to go back inside the mountain.

Its huge brass shell had already half sunken into it.

But at this moment, the blue robed rank seven Gu Immortal finished his preparations, his immortal killer move was unleashed!

Rumble...

Blue waves resembling the tides of the sea appeared out of nowhere, crashing towards the swamp crab.

The swamp crab was huge, it could not dodge, it was swept by the waves.

But even with the ebb and flow, the swamp crab did not move, its body was too heavy.

The blue robed rank seven Gu Immortal's lips curled with a confident smile of victory, his ten fingers moved rapidly, only the afterimages of his fingers could be seen, it was a dazzling sight.

His immortal killer move was not ordinary.

As his red date immortal essence continued to be consumed, the light blue waves turned into dark blue waves, the waves got stronger and were three times as powerful as before.

A deep spiral was formed in the water under the blue robed rank seven Gu Immortal's skillful manipulation.

The swamp crab was in the middle of the spiral, it could not put up resistance, it was swept by the spiral.

Swish swish swish!

The swamp crab's heavy body started to move quickly in the spiral, like a piece of seaweed, it could not help itself.

The blue robed rank seven Gu Immortal made a grabbing motion with his hands, as countless shadows of fingers dissipated in the sky, the tides expanded and rose into a torrential tsunami.

Boom!

With a huge sound, a gigantic tide of water crashed onto the swamp crab's back.

The swamp crab's shell was very hard, but with the impact of the tsunami, a huge dent was formed on the smooth shell.

The swamp crab did not move, it had fainted on the spot.

The blue robed rank seven Gu Immortal laughed heartily, he spread out the fingers on his right hand, as he raised his index finger.

A gush of water shot up from the tides like a geyser, dragging the swamp crab's body towards the blue robed rank seven Gu Immortal.

The Gu Immortal opened his immortal aperture's entrance, storing this swamp crab.

"Immortal! It is an immortal!!"

"Thank you lord immortal, you saved our entire village."

"This immortal even defeated the crab monster in the mountain!"

Such a grand battle shocked the mortals in the village intensely.

Only after the battle was over, they reacted and shouted in joy, kowtowing to him.

The blue robed rank seven Gu Immortal closed his immortal aperture's entrance, he smiled lightly as he looked at the people below.

It turned out that while fighting the swamp crab, he had placed a part of his concentration in manipulating the waves to sweep away all of the falling rocks and mud.

"As expected indeed of the famous water path Gu Immortal in Central Continent, Mu Ling Lan." At this time, a voice came from the clouds.

The blue robed rank seven Gu Immortal moved all ten fingers as he stored away all of the water that was flooding the place.

Next, he flew into the clouds and met with another Gu Immortal.

This immortal wore a blue robe and had a square face, he had thick eyebrows and a tall nose bridge, he was emanating an aura of righteousness that could not be violated.

Mu Ling Lan smiled as he greeted: "So Senior Shi Ge has arrived."

Shi Ge returned the greeting: "I just arrived, to think that I would get to see your method of subduing the swamp crab."

Mu Ling Lan waved his hand, saying humbly: "My methods are just small tricks from your perspective. But, Senior Shi Ge, I hear you have also gotten orders from Heavenly Court to join this Northern Plains battle?"

Shi Ge nodded: "That's right, Mu Ling Lan, you are also in the list of names, why don't we travel together."

Mu Ling Lan had an appreciative expression: "It is my honor to travel with senior."

Thus, the two immortals traveled together.

The mortals were left behind, looking at the sky as they sighed in amazement.

Mu Ling Lan and Shi Ge spoke along the way, they were not silent.

Even though both were rank seven, Shi Ge was higher in seniority, having passed two grand tribulations, while Mu Ling Lan was still not at the first grand tribulation. Thus, Mu Ling Lan was seeking advice while Shi Ge taught him some things.

Along the way, Shi Ge suddenly descended as he floated in the air and waited.

Mu Ling Lan did not understand, this was not the gathering point.

Shi Ge smiled: "Pardon me, I have a son called Zheng Yi, he had recently passed his ascension tribulation and become a Gu Immortal. But he lacks experience and is still very childish. I intend to bring him along in this Northern Plains trip to train him."

"So that's it." Mu Ling Lan realized, looking towards the direction that Shi Ge was gazing at.

Under the cloud cover, there was a small city.

There were many buildings in the city, in one restaurant, a storyteller was talking about folklore regarding justice and heroism.

"Good, good kill!" Among the guests, one young lad with thick eyebrows was dressed like a farmer with innocent eyes. Hearing the story of the main character killing the rich and helping the poor, he clapped in happiness.

His screaming was loud and caused the curtains to shake slightly.

The storyteller was shocked as he paused.

The surrounding guests were all unhappily muttering: "Why are you screaming?"

"Screaming all of a sudden, you'll scare us to death."

"Why are you screaming, listen to the story quietly, or we will chase you away, little peasant."

The young lad was flushing red, he scratched his head and he looked around in embarrassment: "Sorry, sorry everyone."

The guests heard his polite apology and their clamoring became softer, they no longer bothered about it.

The young lad sat down slowly but suddenly his expression changed, he stood up as the table and chairs around him were pushed away, causing an even bigger commotion.

"What now, you lad!"

"Hey lad, are you asking for a beating!!"

The guests were furious, but suddenly, the young man's body shone with light as he shot out of the building like an arrow, tearing a hole in the window as he flew to the sky.

The restaurant went into chaos, countless people were shouting in panic.

The young lad came before Shi Ge and Mu Ling Lan as he cupped his fists, greeting politely.

He was Shi Ge's son — Shi Zheng Yi[1].

The three immortals continued on their journey, a few days later, they arrived at a mountain range.

An Immortal Gu House was stationed here.

It was a pavilion, exquisite and small, there were countless bird cages hanging on it, as birds chirped continuously.

This was an Immortal Gu House of Heavenly Lotus Sect, Canary Pavilion.

Shi Ge saw this and nodded slightly: "I have long since heard that Immortal Gu Houses would be sent out to attack Northern Plains. To think that this is Heavenly Lotus Sect's Canary Pavilion, this pavilion specializes in capturing flying beasts, it can move quickly, it is a good choice."

Mu Ling Lan added: "Heavenly Lotus Sect was created by Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable, it owns the highest number of Immortal Gu Houses, it makes sense that Heavenly Lotus Sect could send out an Immortal Gu House."

Shi Zheng Yi asked in confusion: "Heavenly Lotus Sect has Canary Pavilion, Yue Yang Palace, and Heavenly Pool, is there a fourth Immortal Gu House?"

Mu Ling Lan smiled: "Little Yi, you might not know, recently, Heavenly Lotus Sect created its fourth Immortal Gu House, but it was kept secret."

Shi Zheng Yi heard this and thought: "Senior Mu Ling Lan is from Spirit Butterfly Valley, this sect is most skilled in information path, it is not strange that he knows some secrets. But Heavenly Lotus Sect has four Immortal Gu Houses now, it is truly shocking."

[1] Zheng Yi = Justice Back

Chapter 1234: Rank Ten Immortal Gu!

Central Continent, Spirit Affinity House.

"Immortal killer move — Meteor Rain!" Zhao Lian Yun called out, a bright light bursting out of her body.

This light flew out of her body, in the blink of an eye, it entered the sky, vanishing.

At the next moment, the pale white space created by a Gu formation seemed to be covered in blue ink, turning deep blue.

Swish swish swish...

Countless meteors were falling from the sky, raining down like a storm of arrows, it was a majestic sight!

The meteors rained down on a hill-like desolate beast tortoise.

The tortoise's four limbs and head retracted into its shell.

Meteors landed on the desolate beast tortoise's back, fragments were created in large numbers, but the remaining meteor rain landed around the desolate beast tortoise, creating huge pits encircling the tortoise.

The meteor rain lasted twenty breaths of time until it stopped.

Zhao Lian Yun was covered in sweat, she was breathing roughly.

A voice came from within the Gu formation: "Not bad, Zhao Lian Yun, you are very proficient in meteor rain already. Next, go train your defensive killer move."

As this was said, the desolate beast tortoise broke apart and turned into black crows.

There were tens of thousands of crows.

They were like black arrows, flying around as they shot towards Zhao Lian Yun.

Zhao Lian Yun's eyes shone, she gritted her teeth as she used her defensive Immortal Gu before the crows hit her.

Suddenly, her body was covered in a layer of silver light.

The layer of thin silvery light successfully protected her from the impact and beaks of the countless crows.

Splat splat splat...

Zhao Lian Yun's tiny little body was soon covered entirely by the black crows.

Large numbers of crows were attacking the silver shield, loud crisp sound were resounding endlessly.

Zhao Lian Yun had a heavy expression.

She could feel her immortal essence expending rapidly.

"I have to think of a plan!" Zhao Lian Yun had an idea as she started using a defensive killer move.

At her first try, she successfully activated the defensive killer move.

Immortal killer move — Life Locking Silver Chain.

From the silver shield around her body, six silvery chains flew out.

The chains moved like dragons, they were extraordinary as they flew around in the crow group, stabbing and killing endlessly.

Many crows died, soon, in the ten li of space around Zhao Lian Yun, no crows were alive.

The silver chains also turned into a round cylinder, protecting Zhao Lian Yun, forming a tight defense. Any attacking crow would be ripped to shreds.

"This immortal killer move is amazing, it can attack and defend at once." It had incredible effect in this first battle, Zhao Lian Yun was extremely pleased.

The Gu Immortal controlling the Gu formation sighed internally: "This Zhao Lian Yun is an otherworldly demon indeed, her cultivation level was raised to rank five peak stage using relic Gu. After being given a phantom aperture, Immortal Gu, and immortal essence by Heavenly Court, she immediately showed her talent. Her battle talent is not weak at all, after so little practice with her immortal killer moves, she became proficient already."

Of course, these immortal killer moves were specially chosen for Zhao Lian Yun by Heavenly Court. They were very powerful and easy to control, they also used few Gu worms, the steps for activating them were simple.

"Alright, next, we will train your healing methods. you will get injured, but don't worry or panic, as long as you perform normally and use your immortal killer move, you will recover." The Gu Immortal controlling the Gu formation said.

Zhao Lian Yun nodded, seeing the crows vanish around her.

There was worry in her expression as she asked: "I have already trained for half a year in this Gu formation, when can I set off to Northern Plains for the rescue mission?"

The Gu Immortal controlling the Gu formation explained: "Don't worry, this is a time path Gu formation, a day outside is a year in here. Your time is very tight, battles between Gu Immortals are not just affected by training, there are also many situations that can occur in actual combat."

"Then give me some actual combat training!" Zhao Lian Yun shouted.

This time path super Gu formation was placed in Spirit Affinity House.

But everything inside was observed by Heavenly Court.

Heavenly Court.

Fairy Zi Wei watched Zhao Lian Yun start her combat training as worry appeared on her face: "Lord Duke Long, do you really think that such training will allow Zhao Lian Yun to adapt to the battlefield? This is too rushed, her battle strength cannot be relied on."

Even though he drank half a kilogram of true dragon heavenly water, it only managed to save Duke Long's life, barely.

He was still very old and weak.

Right now, he was sitting in front of Fairy Zi Wei, there was a chessboard between them.

This chessboard had a huge origin, it was an Immortal Gu House personally created by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable — Star Constellation Chessboard, it most excelled in wisdom path deductions, it was the number one wisdom path Immortal Gu House!

Fairy Zi Wei was not qualified enough, but after Duke Long woke up, he immediately took out this legendary Immortal Gu House from Heavenly Court's treasury and gave it to Fairy Zi Wei, allowing her deduction capability to reach a terrifying level.

Hearing Fairy Zi Wei's doubts, Duke Long smiled lightly: "We cannot depend on Zhao Lian Yun, but I am not depending on her anyway."

Fairy Zi Wei's gaze shined: "Lord Duke Long is counting on love Gu."

"That's right." Duke Long nodded: "Love Gu is very unique, even among rank nine Immortal Gu, it is extremely special. Most Immortal Gu have only one effect, one type of ability. But love Gu is the opposite, it can unleash all sorts of effects and expend a variety of resources beyond immortal essence. Most importantly, the power of love can resist fate and luck."

"Resist fate and luck?" Fairy Zi Wei muttered, slightly shocked.

"That's right, love can resist fate to an extent. If not for that, how could Red Lotus Demon Venerable damage fate Immortal Gu back then?" Duke Long exposed some shocking secrets, when he mentioned Red Lotus Demon Venerable, he had a solemn tone and complex expression.

Fairy Zi Wei was slightly shocked: "What? Back then, did Red, Red Lotus Demon Venerable obtain the acknowledgement of love Gu as well?"

"Precisely." Duke Long confirmed this: "Red Lotus was not an otherworldly demon, how could he have damaged Fate. It was because love Immortal Gu was with him, allowing him to damage fate Immortal Gu in the end."

"After the battle of Yi Tian Mountain, Zombie Alliance was wiped out, only a few Shadow Sect members are left, and Spectral Soul is trapped inside the giant dream realm. So many fate escapees have been destroyed, this allowed the repairing of fate Immortal Gu to be much easier than before."

Speaking until this point, Duke Long needed to catch his breath, after resting for a while, he continued: "However, even if fate Immortal Gu is repaired completely, our Heavenly Court cannot regain its former glory."

"This... is because of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable?" Fairy Zi Wei deduced and got an answer immediately.

Duke Long breathed in deeply: "Yes, because after Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, luck path appeared in the five regions. In the past, Fate was unchangeable, as long as we repaired fate, Heavenly Court would return to the apex again. But now, we have luck path. Fate is certain while luck is uncertain, good luck is a positive uncertainty for oneself while bad luck is a negative uncertainty for oneself."

"Even if we repair fate Immortal Gu completely, we can only control certainty, we cannot control the uncertainty. Only by controlling luck path as well, can we allow Heavenly Court to rule the five regions and two heavens completely."

"Thus, Lord Duke Long, you gave an order to gather elite Gu Immortals of all ten great ancient sects to go to Northern Plains, in order to snatch fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu. If we get Fortune Rivalling Heaven, will Heavenly Court be able to control luck?" Fairy Zi Wei asked.

Duke Long nodded before shaking his head: "Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's entire life of cultivation had three stages, self luck, all living being's luck, and heaven and earth luck. Fortune Rivalling Heaven is the apex of all living being's luck. Its true effect is to allow the possessor to continuously absorb the luck of all lifeforms around them."

"Like right now, looking at Ma Hong Yun, fortune rivalling heaven Gu's effect is related to the people near him. It continues to absorb their luck, collecting them on Ma Hong Yun, that is why Xue Hu and Lady Wan Shou continue to fail. Especially in refining a rank eight Immortal Gu, the chances are simply too low."

"Fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu might be rank eight, but it actually has quasi-rank nine power. With enough time, and if the affected individuals have enough luck, fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu would be able to absorb even more luck and gather it into one person. This is also why Giant Sun Immortal Venerable named it Fortune Rivalling Heaven. The meaning was: by absorbing the luck of all living beings, and gathering it into one person, supreme luck that rivals heaven and earth would be born!"

"So that's it." Hearing Duke Long's detailed explanation, Fairy Zi Wei had a realization.

Even though Duke Long was from the Olden Antiquity Era, over the process of his hibernation, he had woken up several times, he knew many precious lost secrets.

Duke Long continued: "If we can obtain Fortune Rivalling Heaven now, we would gain the accumulations in cultivation of half of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's life."

"In the future, if we have the chance, we can search for heaven and earth luck and self luck, to control all of these luck path Immortal Gu, including Fortune Rivalling Heaven."

"When fate Gu is repaired, Heavenly Court will reign supreme in the world."

"If we have a chance to go further and refine the luck path Immortal Gu with fate Immortal Gu, we might be able to create the legendary rank ten Immortal Gu — Destiny! By then, Heavenly Court will understand the complete profundity of heaven's will, we will act in the capacity of heaven, we will become the eternal rulers of the universe!!"

Duke Long spoke softly, but towards the end, his eyes were shining, he showed a fanatical and heated gaze.

"Rank ten Immortal Gu?" Even a Gu Immortal at Fairy Zi Wei's level was tongue-tied upon hearing such secrets.

"Above rank nine, there really is rank ten realm?" Fairy Zi Wei asked in complete shock and disbelief.

Chapter 1235: Blood Competition Ends

Duke Long sighed: "I cannot tell you if there is a rank ten Gu Immortal realm. But rank ten Immortal Gu likely can exist. Because this was confirmed by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable himself."

Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable was the rank nine venerable after Spectral Soul Demon Venerable. He was kind and merciful, he did not dispute with people and loved peace, but like Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, he did not truly enter Heavenly Court.

There were only three Immortal Venerables who truly entered Heavenly Court and fused their immortal apertures into Heavenly Court.

From the start of history, they were respectively, the first rank nine venerable, Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, the creator of wisdom path, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, as well as the creator of wood path and the owner of Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus, Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable.

Northern Plains.

The blood battle martial competition was having its final battle.

Chu Du walked onto the stage and said: "I am honored."

In front of him was a female immortal. She was clad in dazzling palace attire with the lower hems touching the ground, her black hair was tied up high with jade and gold ornaments. Her skin was snow white, her brows slender, her gaze sharp, and her chest was voluptuous and perky. She looked stately and beautiful, giving a feeling that she could not be offended.

It was Gong Wan Ting.

Prince Feng Xian's wife.

Gong Wan Ting had a solemn expression as she sighed lightly: "Domination Immortal, you live up to your reputation, you defeated Liu Zhuan Shen and Yao Yuan Ying consecutively. Regardless of the result of this battle, the reputation of Domination Immortal will spread in Northern Plains."

Liu Zhuan Shen and Yao Yuan Ying, who were mentioned, had pale expressions, there was no choice, Chu Du was stronger than them.

All in all, the blood battle martial competition was about to end with the Huang Jin tribes suppressing Chu Sect and Bai Zu tribe's alliance.

But towards the end, Chu Du took the stage, giving a slap to the righteous path allied forces.

The power of Domination Immortal struck wariness in these Huang Jin bloodline Gu Immortals.

This was the final battle, without any other options, Gong Wan Ting stepped forward.

This was a battle between the leaders of both sides!

"Please." Chu Du was very gentlemanly, even though he was injured, he did not panic.

Surprise flashed in Gong Wan Ting's eyes as she smiled: "Domination Immortal is truly brave and heroic."

Saying this, a purple light shot towards Chu Du like a blade or sword.

Chu Du shouted, moving ahead instead, charging towards Gong Wan Ting bravely.

An intense battle shook heaven and earth.

The two sides exchanged moves after moves, and after a hundred rounds, there was no victor.

They fought on both the ground and in the sky, the Blood Plain was almost completely destroyed.

The spectating immortals had to move back by thirty thousand li to avoid getting involved in Chu Du and Gong Wan Ting's battle.

Chu Du's might was unstoppable, he attacked more than he defended, while Gong Wan Ting did the opposite with much energy to spare.

This intense battle lasted for another hundred rounds, Chu Du was covered in injuries, blood spewed out of him, but Gong Wan Ting was also no longer as relaxed, her gaze was sweeping over Chu Du, preventing him from attacking her suddenly, she did not dare to be careless.

The Gu Immortal spectators were all moved, they quickly commented on this intense battle, it was the clash of two experts at the peak of rank seven. Without rank eight Gu Immortals interfering, these two would not be surpassed by Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world for several hundred years.

The sun set, the moon rose, from morning to night, the victor was still not decided.

Battling intensely without stop, it was truly heated.

By the dawn of the second day, both sides were much weakened, the battle was at its end, victory could be decided at the next moment.

The Gu Immortal spectators held their breaths as they watched the ending of this battle.

But right at this moment, a grand pillar of light descended and separated Chu Du and Gong Wan Ting, who were fighting fiercely.

"That is enough, this battle will end in a draw." Rank eight Gu Immortal Yao Huang showed himself in the air.

He looked away as he said: "Does Heavenly Lord agree with me?"

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu appeared from a cloud layer, nodding: "We will fight in the sky."

Saying this, both rank eight Gu Immortals flew up into white heaven under everyone's watchful gazes.

Soon, the immortals in Blood Plain could hear intense explosions coming from white heaven, it sounded like thunder and beast roars.

Domination Immortal Chu Du let out a breath of air, he was satisfied with this result.

Gong Wan Ting had a special status, she was Prince Feng Xian's wife, Chu Du thought of this and could not kill her. If he did, he would offend Prince Feng Xian.

When Chu Du was all alone, he might not be afraid, but with Chu Sect established, times were different.

And Chu Du himself had displayed incredible abilities in this blood battle martial competition, for the sake of Bai Zu tribe, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu would not let Chu Du die here.

Like what Yao Huang and Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had discussed before the martial competition, both sides managed to keep their losses to an acceptable level.

"Gasp... incredible, a crack appeared in white heaven."

"Hearing this, I can tell how intense the battle is."

"Unfortunately, we cannot penetrate the heavenly wind qi wall and observe the battle in white heaven."

The spectators did not leave, they were conversing.

The battle between Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and Yao Huang would decide everything.

During the entire process of the blood battle martial competition, no matter how many sacrifices or losses there were, or all the different battle results, none could compare to this one.

Be it either side, they had suffered great losses.

But Gu Immortals who actually died were not many. Several rank six Gu Immortals died, few rank seven Gu Immortals died, the biggest loss was actually Ye Lui Qun Xing who Fang Yuan killed.

Towards the later part of the competition, both sides came to a subtle agreement.

Of course, Gu Immortals getting injured was still a huge issue.

Because of dao marks, injuries were hard to heal, the cost of it would make Gu Immortals pay a huge price.

Inside white heaven.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and Yao Huang were sitting opposite each other, a chessboard was in front of them.

"Please try this, my newly made gold leaf tea." Yao Huang chuckled, recommending his tea.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu drank it as he nodded, taking out a big bag of snacks.

"This is my specialty, fried centipede."

The two rank eight great experts drank tea and ate fried centipedes as they played chess, it was an enjoyable time.

Yao Huang sighed: "This fried centipede is fresh and delicious, the flavor never gets tiring, this is truly a rare delicacy."

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu praised too: "Brother Yao Huang's gold leaf tea is superior to silver leaf tea. It seems that you are not far from refining resurrection from the dead Gu."

Every tea or wine could be treated as an incomplete food path Gu recipe.

Often, when Gu Immortals compete with their refinement path attainment, to avoid causing a commotion or to protect their reputation, they would offer wine or tea.

When Gu Immortals taste the tea or wine, they would understand the other person's Gu refinement attainment.

Of course, this method was very vague, it was only a shallow probe, it could not show both parties' true strength.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu could taste something different in Yao Huang's new tea. Because he had drank the silver leaf tea before, comparing the two, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu could see how Yao Huang's refinement path attainment had improved.

This improvement was naturally obtained from Yao Huang's attempts at refining resurrection from the dead Immortal Gu.

As for Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, the snack that he created was not simple either, it was a display of his own refinement path attainment.

But Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had been busy creating Bai Zu tribe recently, he also had to attack Hei Fan grotto-heaven, his refinement path aspects did not improve, thus, his fried centipede did not become different.

But Yao Huang's gaze was focused below them.

Not far away from them, two figures were fighting.

One resembled Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, while the other resembled Yao Huang.

Below white heaven, the clamor that these Gu Immortals in the Blood Plain heard was caused by these two figures.

Yao Huang praised: "Heavenly Lord, your cloning method is becoming more profound, you can actually mimic thirty percent of rank eight level strength."

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu shook his head as he smiled: "I don't deserve such praise. These last days, while attacking Hei Fan grotto-heaven, I created this immortal killer move after multiple failed attempts at invading it. I have once heard that Longevity Heaven possesses one of Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's immortal killer moves — Perfect Pair, it can allow a Gu Immortal to create a clone that has their full power. My method cannot compare to Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable."

Yao Huang smiled.

He understood clearly that Heavenly Lord Bai Zu mentioned Longevity Heaven for more complex underlying reasons.

Yao Huang explained: "Don't worry, Heavenly Lord, as long as Longevity Heaven's rank eight Gu Immortals do not show up, just the Longevity Edict cannot mobilize us."

"Furthermore, the situation in every region is dependent on the situation of the respective rank eight Gu Immortals, isn't it?"

"Right now in Northern Plains, among the rank eight Gu Immortals, Old Ancestor Xue Hu has the highest battle strength. If he succeeds in refining fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu, he would be unstoppable. But I can see that Snowy Mountain blessed land is heavily guarded now, even we will have trouble breaking into it."

"Our conflict is just an internal conflict of the righteous path. But if Old Ancestor Xue Hu refines fortune rivalling heaven Gu, the situation in Northern Plains would favor the demonic path."

Yao Huang said slowly as Heavenly Lord Bai Zu nodded, he agreed with the former's analysis.

Originally, when Eighty-Eight True Yang Building collapsed, Northern Plains' situation changed, the demonic path rose in power. If Old Ancestor Xue Hu manages to refine fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu, the situation would be even more uncontrollable.

Compared to the rise of new righteous path forces, Yao Huang was more unwilling to see the demonic path being rampant.

"Thankfully, in this martial competition, I invited many lone immortals and demonic path members, a portion of them died, while the rest would join either Chu Sect or Bai Zu tribe, this would weaken the demonic path and strengthen our righteous path." Heavenly Lord Bai Zu spoke with a smile.

Rank eight Gu Immortals had deep considerations.

The blood battle martial competition was helping Yao tribe weaken the other Huang Jin tribes, but Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and Chu Du were also weakening the lone and demonic cultivators, stabilizing the situation in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world!

But upon the mention of Chu Sect, Yao Huang frowned.

"This Chu Sect needs to change."

"Northern Plains will not allow the emergence of a sect."

"If Chu Du wants Chu Sect to exist, he has to change it to Chu tribe, otherwise, the righteous path will not allow it!"

Chapter 1236: Cultivation Itself Is Enjoyment

Yao Huang's attitude was very firm.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu laughed: "You don't have to worry about this, Chu Du understands this and has already talked to me, he can concede on this point."

"That's good." Yao Huang nodded.

Both of them talked for a while more, their chess game was half done, they had wasted enough time, both immortals flew down from white heaven.

Next, they announced that Yao Huang had won the battle by a slight margin, and this blood battle martial competition ended with the victory of the Huang Jin tribes.

Chu Sect and Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals had grim expressions, only Chu Du was calm, he had expected this.

In contrast, the Huang Jin tribe Gu Immortals were in a joyous mood.

The consequences that followed would not be detailed, but the blood battle martial competition that shook Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world came to an end.

Southern Border, giant dream realm.

Deep in the sea.

There was darkness, one could not see their own fingers.

Fang Yuan was inside, suffering huge injuries.

The pressure of the sea was intense, most importantly, around him, there were countless long dragon silhouettes, swimming around him vigilantly.

These were dragons living in the sea.

Each sea dragon had desolate beast level battle strength.

There were hundreds, or thousands of sea dragons moving in countless layers.

Fang Yuan was currently a rank six Gu Immortal, but facing this sea dragon group, there was nothing he could do.

"The most troublesome thing is that I need to kill all of the sea dragons to pass this ninth scene of the dream realm."

Fang Yuan smiled bitterly internally.

If this was reality, it was unclear what the chances would be for him to break out of the encirclement, and try to survive this dangerous situation.

But in this dream realm, there were specific rules, if Fang Yuan wanted to break out and survive, the dream realm exploration would fail.

Fang Yuan had no way out!

"To kill these sea dragons, with just my foundation and methods in this dream realm, it is impossible!"

Thus, if Fang Yuan wanted to pass this, he had only one option available, immortal killer move unravel dream.

"But there are so many sea dragons, unravel dream can be used less than ten times, it cannot resolve this huge problem."

"It seems that this scene is the final moment of the dream realm's main character."

Fang Yuan gained deep insight.

Dream realms had different categories, most were realistic dream realms, they replicated the lifeforms' experiences in their lives, but there were also few which were rare and peculiar, dream realms that were strange and weird.

Fang Yuan was exploring a realistic dream realm, but the severity of the content might be exaggerated compared to the actual event, even though there was some actual scenes that happened before.

"This Gu Immortal was once a Combat Immortal Sect Gu Master."

"He had decent aptitude but after becoming rank six, compared to other Gu Immortals, he was no longer so amazing."

"The ten great ancient sects of Central Continent allocate resources according to sect contribution. This Gu Immortal's aptitude was far from exemplary, he did not have great strength or powerful methods, it was hard to get sect contribution points, so he could not get much resources. That was why he went to explore Eastern Sea."

"In the end, when he passed the regional walls, his immortal aperture's foundation was damaged. Next, he heard some rumors about the Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace and came to this sea area, in the end, he died here from the attacks of the sea dragons."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan made up his mind, he chose to give up.

He left this dream realm.

Normally speaking, the deeper one gets into the dream realm, the greater their gains after getting past the scene.

But Fang Yuan wisely chose to retreat.

He withheld his remaining uses of unravel dream, he was not going to waste them here for no reason.

A moment later, Fang Yuan returned to reality.

Using guts Gu to heal himself, he inspected his own body again.

Water path quasi-grandmaster.

His attainment level did not change.

He was still a distance away from grandmaster level.

But it was already enough to many of the blessed lands in City Well, because most of them were rank six blessed lands.

"According to my current situation, it would be best if I could raise all of my attainment levels to at least master."

"That way, I would be able to annex any rank six blessed land."

"Even though rank six blessed lands have diminishing effect on raising my cultivation level, with enough quantity, the gains are still very prominent."

Fang Yuan thought.

Next, he entered his own dream realm and refined some dream path mortal Gu.

Of course, he used some time for deductions as well.

These last days, he had an inspiration, to fuse the killer moves myriad self and sword dragon transformation.

His deductions were progressing smoothly, Fang Yuan had enough strength path attainment, and his transformation path attainment level was also grandmaster, the only drawback was that his wisdom path deduction methods were slightly lacking.

But it was no problem.

Lady White Rabbit came to report to him about the situation of the immortal opportunity business, as well as some information.

Fang Yuan sat down on his cushion as he shut his eyes, telling her: "Go ahead and talk, I am listening."

Fang Yuan was deducing his own matters while listening to Lady White Rabbit.

He was multitasking.

A wisdom path grandmaster could do this with ease.

Lady White Rabbit talked as she looked at Fang Yuan's face, deep affection was in her gaze.

But to her disappointment, until she finished her report, Fang Yuan did not open his eyes to look at her once.

"Okay, you can go now." Fang Yuan said.

Lady White Rabbit could only leave slowly while feeling disappointed, as she looked at him with a longing gaze.

Outside the room, Wu An was waiting long ago.

"Lady, this way please." Wu An's attitude towards Lady White Rabbit was even more polite than before.

Lady White Rabbit was allowed to meet Fang Yuan, this showed that he still favored her, thus, Wu An placed a lot of importance on Lady White Rabbit. Because she represented the future of the immortal opportunity business!

Lady White Rabbit was a little worried, asking Wu An: "Wu An, does Lord Wu Yi Hai cultivate like this all the time?"

Wu An was stunned: "What do you mean?"

Lady White Rabbit sighed in a gloomy tone: "Lord Wu Yi Hai cultivates really hard, he does not even waste any second of his time. Even when listening to my report, he did not stop cultivating, has he always been like this?"

Wu An blinked: "Lady, I will speak the truth. Even though I have never watched Lord Wu Yi Hai cultivate, just a glimpse can tell many things. Lord Wu Yi Hai might be the most hardworking cultivator I have ever seen in my life. Disregarding anything else, just the fact that he is staying in his room and cultivating without leaving for so long, that would be impossible for me."

Lady White Rabbit became even more worried: "Precisely so, I am worried about Lord Wu Yi Hai. When he cultivates, he truly risks his life! There is a limit to cultivation speed, if he keeps at this, I am afraid he might not be able to endure it, and his mental state would be ruined. Wu An, if you have a chance, you must talk to Lord Wu Yi Hai, okay?"

Wu An thought: "You have met with him more than I have, what can I do?"

But he still nodded, acknowledging: "If I get a chance, I will talk to Lord Wu Yi Hai about this."

Fang Yuan analyzed Lady White Rabbit's information.

He had a clear grasp of Southern Border's situation all along thanks to this.

All in all, Southern Border was still quite peaceful.

Even though Wu Du Xiu died, and Wu clan only had one rank eight Gu Immortal, Wu Yong, left. But this person displayed great battle strength and political methods after taking over Wu clan.

Precisely so, even though Ba clan, Tie clan and others were watching closely, they had to contain their dark intentions.

The situation of the rank eight Gu Immortals was reflected on Southern Border in many aspects. The situation at the super Gu formation was still calm. The immortal opportunity business was ongoing, Gu Immortals benefited and profited secretly, they were very happy, there were also Gu Immortals who did not participate, simply looking on from afar.

"The Northern Plains blood battle martial competition has ended, Chu Sect became Chu tribe, Bai Zu tribe was preserved, while the Huang Jin tribes won and gained a lot of cultivation resources."

"This way, Northern Plains is also stabilizing."

"Eastern Sea, Western Desert, and Central Continent have little information available, most of them are obtained from treasure yellow heaven, I only have a vague idea. But they are also relatively peaceful now."

In truth, a peaceful state was most common in the five regions.

Who would go ahead and fight to the death if a peaceful life was available?

Northern Plains' chaos was thanks to Fang Yuan. He destroyed Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and in addition to Shadow Sect's schemes, a terrifying situation was created.

Only in the five regions chaotic war did the five regions go into chaos, all sorts of order was torn down, fighting to become Gu Immortal was the main trend.

The current situation was very calm.

This was best for Fang Yuan.

He entered his own dream realm, refining his dream path mortal Gu.

Amidst green and verdant mountains, the merchant caravan was temporarily resting at the base of a mountain.

Boom.

Moonlight curved in the air agilely, moving past a rock ahead and hitting the tree branch behind it accurately.

Immediately, wood shavings were sliced off, the thin branch was nearly cut down by the moonlight.

"After practising for so many days, I finally succeeded!" Fang Yuan was covered in sweat, he felt immense joy.

"Lad, not bad huh." Gu Master Big Beard walked towards Fang Yuan.

"Uncle Beard, thanks for teaching me this!" Fang Yuan gave a wide smile, he showed his white teeth as he smiled, he was a bright and joyful lad.

Gu Master Big Beard was almost blinded by his shining aura, he blinked as he asked in confusion: "Normal people would only be able to go through such intense training for a week or so. But you woke up early and slept late, you would cultivate so long as you had the time, after a month, your enthusiasm has not faded yet. Is this boring cultivation process really so interesting?"

Fang Yuan clenched his fists, his eyes were shining like the stars in the sky: "Of course, Uncle, don't you find it amazing and incredible? A person can unleash incredible attacks with a wave of their hand. Cultivation itself is a very enjoyable thing."

Chapter 1237: Dragon Lady

Gu Master Big Beard naturally did not understand Fang Yuan's emotions.

As a transmigrator from Earth, the special abilities of Gu Masters were simply superhuman. Turning from a normal person to a superhuman, of course Fang Yuan would be excited and enthusiastic.

"Furthermore, my aptitude is low, only at C grade. How can I not work harder?" The young Fang Yuan chuckled as he spoke.

"Uncle, go ahead with your business, I will continue cultivating." Fang Yuan said again.

Gu Master Big Beard laughed as he shook his head, tactfully leaving.

Standing afar, he looked at Fang Yuan who was cultivating earnestly, he had a complex gaze as he muttered: "Even if you work so hard, what for? C grade aptitude... cruel reality will assault you and extinguish that fire of enthusiasm, failure will get rid of your excitement. Such enthusiasm and hard work, how long can it last?"

At another corner of the dream realm, the real Fang Yuan was holding onto the branch that was nearly cut off by the moonlight.

"Hmm, not bad this dream path Gu material is quite good, if I am lucky, I can refine more than ten dream path mortal Gu."

He smiled lightly as his deep dark pupils flickered with light, resembling stars in the sky.

Bai Xiang grotto-heaven.

The humans alike dragons Gu refinement method was at its final crucial moment.

"Persevere, you cannot slack for even a moment, master, you can do it, you can definitely succeed." Bai Xiang heavenly spirit screamed.

The Gu formation was operating, the pillar of light was tall and mighty, like it was holding up heaven and earth.

The center of the pillar was so shiny that one could not look at the light directly, there was a human shaped figure of fire in it.

It was Bai Ning Bing!

His face and body had all melted, like candles that were exposed to intense heat.

His hair was all burned, his eyes were blind, even his hands and legs were all melted into one.

Bai Ning Bing was nothing like a human.

The intense pain had never stopped assaulting him for the last weeks!

Initially, he screamed in pain, roaring at the sky, nearly fainting.

But afterwards, he survived countless dangerous situations, forcibly preserving his life until now.

Gritting his teeth and enduring.

Next, his teeth and tongue were also melted by the raging wave rising dragon fire, fusing together.

He smiled.

A relentless smile.

Next, he could not even smile anymore, because his nose and face had all melted like wax.

Now, he was just a human pole, it was a horrific sight.

But Bai Xiang heavenly spirit could sense Bai Ning Bing's determination.

His determination was firm as steel, after the burning of the fire and the pain that tempered him, he was becoming more firm and unwavering.

Such determination made even Bai Xiang heavenly spirit lost for words!

Initially, even Bai Xiang heavenly spirit did not think Bai Ning Bing would succeed.

Because Bai Ning Bing's situation was too terrible, the humans alike dragons Gu refinement method was extremely dangerous. Every Gu refinement carried risks of failure. In history, any Gu Master or Gu Immortal who tried to turn into a dragonman would be extremely careful and make ample preparations, only taking this risk after they were sufficiently prepared!

Boom!

An intense sound resembled the striking of thunder.

The pillar of light dissipated, as a lump of fire flew upwards.

It was shaped like a fiery dragon, its red body was strong as ever, after flying one round in the sky, it flew down towards Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing was a lump of meat now, his bones, flesh, dao marks, blood, and skin were all fused into one.

The meat seemed like a bottomless hole, absorbing the whole of the fiery dragon that crashed towards it.

Next, the meat turned red, the temperature rose, intense flames were raging nearby, causing distortions in the air due to the high heat.

When the lump of meat became red to the extreme, it exploded, within a bright light, a brand new Bai Ning Bing was born.

"Success, we succeeded!!" Bai Xiang heavenly spirit stared with wide eyes and muttered.

Under the rays of the lingering light, Bai Ning Bing raised her head to the sky!

Only to hear her say: "Ten thousand li mountain and nine layers of the abyss, dragons coil at the bottom of the well. Today I rise up towards the clouds, my proud body soars towards true freedom."

Her voice sounded like the roar of a dragon, winds were rumbling as it echoed in the entire Bai Xiang grotto-heaven.

Bai Xiang heavenly spirit was in admiration, he knelt on the ground and said: "Congratulations to master's new life, you have regained your immortal status!"

Bai Ning Bing stopped her roaring, she descended.

She was expressionless, her skin was white as snow, her facial features were even more distinct now, her beauty had surpassed her former self!

Her pale blue dragon eyes were emitting a cold aura to the outside world.

But at the next moment, shock was expressed in her dragon eyes: "Hmm? What is going on? I already became an immortal, I have a real immortal aperture, why did I become a woman?"

"This..." Bai Xiang heavenly spirit thought about his words carefully before explaining: "The humans alike dragons Gu refinement method uses master as the immortal material. The result of the refinement depends on the proportion of immortal materials and how they mix together. Master had transformation path dao marks earlier, to think that these dao marks would affect your body and actually influence the final result of the Gu refinement, turning you into a dragon lady."

Bai Ning Bing: "..."

She realized that the information path dao marks and all her alliance agreements were gone, but the transformation path dao marks still affected the results of her refinement. Like what the heavenly spirit said, the humans alike dragons Gu refinement method could not be strictly controlled, the participating immortal material had a lot of influence on the result.

Bai Ning Bing furrowed her brows.

This was like a curse.

Her female body curse had started ever since she was in Qing Mao Mountain.

After pondering for a while, Bai Ning Bing asked: "How can I turn back to a man?"

Bai Xiang heavenly spirit replied: "This is easy, just cultivate transformation path in addition."

Bai Ning Bing was knowledgeable, she shook her head: "That does not solve the underlying problem, I have my Northern Dark Ice Soul Physique, I will cultivate ice and snow path in the future."

Bai Xiang heavenly spirit thought about it before saying: "Master, you have been reborn, the female body is your true gender. But if you want to change it, you will need to approach its root cause and find the other half of that rotation Gu from the past, and refine it into an Immortal Gu. Using that Immortal Gu, you will be able to become a man."

Bai Ning Bing: "..."

The image of a person appeared in her mind uncontrollably.

"Fang Yuan, to think that you would still be an obstacle to me now. Hmph!" Bai Ning Bing snorted internally, she knew that Fang Yuan had the rank eight battle strength upper extreme heavenly eagle.

She had to plan for a long time to get that crucial Gu worm from Fang Yuan.

Central Continent, Spirit Affinity House.

Above the clouds, Gu Immortals gathered.

Spirit Affinity House's first supreme elder said: "Bu Zhen Zi, you have to protect our sect's fairy in this Northern Plains journey, she is only a false immortal, and her ascension was only recently."

Bu Zhen Zi was a supreme elder of Spirit Affinity House, a rank seven phantom path Gu Immortal, he said: "Everyone, as long as I am alive, I will ensure her safety."

He spoke with great confidence.

First supreme elder nodded, looking at Zhao Lian Yun: "You must not charge ahead in this journey, always protect your own safety. Leave the rest to the others, the Gu Immortals going with you are all elite experts of the ten great ancient sects, with our advantage as the attacker, there is a high chance of success."

Zhao Lian Yun nodded, she understood now that this granny was actually the Gu Immortal with the highest authority in Spirit Affinity House.

She bowed deeply to the first supreme elder, Xu Hao, and Li Jun Ying: "I am going now."

"Set off." First supreme elder waved her hand.

Bu Zhen Zi cupped his fists, bringing Zhao Lian Yun with him, riding on a ruin bat and flying away.

"To think that Zhao Lian Yun would become our sect's fairy."

"Heaven is toying with us."

"I wonder if she will be able to save that Ma Hong Yun?"

"In my opinion, the chances are high, after all, all of the Gu Immortals going to Northern Plains are elites of our sects, this is a powerful force!"

The Gu Immortals conversed as they left.

"I will go talk to our daughter." Fairy Bai Qing had a look of worry as she spoke to Feng Jiu Ge.

Feng Jiu Ge nodded.

This time, he also wanted to go to Northern Plains, but Heavenly Court denied his suggestion.

Feng Jiu Ge was a legendary genius rarely seen in thousands of years, he was so talented none could match him, he possessed rank eight battle strength with just rank seven cultivation level.

According to common logic, he would be the best person to send to Northern Plains, but he was unable to become part of the rescue team.

At this point, Feng Jiu Ge did not know what Heavenly Court was thinking or planning.

When Fairy Bai Qing met with Feng Jin Huang, the latter was sitting by the lake, looking at the ripples on the surface as she went into a daze.

Fairy Bai Qing felt caring and affection in her heart.

She knew: Her daughter had always wanted to become Spirit Affinity House's fairy, she worked hard for it. But now, Zhao Lian Yun gained love Gu's acknowledgement, she was also supported by Heavenly Court, becoming Spirit Affinity House's fairy.

This way, Feng Jin Huang was eliminated from the competition.

Fairy Bai Qing walked towards Feng Jin Huang: "Why? Still thinking about the fairy position?"

"No, mother, I was thinking, why did I not obtain love Gu's acknowledgement?" Feng Jin Huang's eyes were red, she had secretly cried earlier.

"That is because you do not have love." Fairy Bai Qing sat beside Feng Jin Huang, stretching out her hand as she touched Feng Jin Huang's hair.

Feng Jin Huang asked: "Why do I not have love? What is love?"

Fairy Bai Qing's gaze flickered, she thought about it before saying: "Love is different from familial affection and friendship, it is a type of affinity, like when I met your father. Love came suddenly and nobody expected it. Love cannot be forced, it is all up to your affinity."

Feng Jin Huang shook her head: "I do not want to leave it to fate, this is not my style, I want to find love and be acknowledged by love Gu, and take back the position of fairy. Mother, do you think this is possible?"

Fairy Bai Qing smiled, this was basically impossible, but seeing her daughter's expectant gaze, as a mother, how could she say the truth?

Thus, she said: "There is a possibility, but you need to find a lover first. A lover is not your father or mother, or those female companions by your side."

Chapter 1238: Luck Path Master

"Mother, you mean to say, it has to be..." Feng Jin Huang frowned, in the process of her growth, there were few youngsters who could match her. Spirit Affinity House had more women than men, this made Feng Jin Huang look down on those males of her generation since a young age.

There was another important reason, that was, Feng Jin Huang's father was too talented, it elevated her expectations, she could not see anything good in those boys around her.

Fairy Bai Qing nodded, asking teasingly: "That's right Huang Er, among those youngsters you met, who are you interested in?"

Feng Jin Huang frowned, after thinking about it, she shook her head.

Fairy Bai Qing almost laughed out loud, her daughter's puzzled look was extremely cute, she asked again: "Then let me change my question, which youngster left the deepest impression on you?"

At this moment, Feng Jin Huang was stunned.

Fang Yuan's image uncontrollably appeared in her mind.

Fang Yuan was the one who dealt a pitiful defeat to her, Feng Jin Huang would never forget the scene on Dang Hun Mountain.

Furthermore, Fang Yuan had saved Feng Jiu Ge's life before!

All of these events made Feng Jin Huang have extremely complex feelings towards Fang Yuan.

It was not pure hatred.

It was also not pure gratitude.

Fairy Bai Qing looked at Feng Jin Huang, who was in a daze, and her expression turned dark, she became flustered as she blamed herself: "Oh no! Why did I forget about Fang Yuan's existence."

Fairy Bai Qing quickly said: "Huang Er, don't think about it!"

As a mother, Fairy Bai Qing was very worried. Even though Feng Jin Huang had grown a lot, she was still innocent regarding relationships, like a blank white sheet of paper.

"That Fang Yuan is an otherworldly demon, he used Spring Autumn Cicada to rebirth. His actual age is probably older than both myself and your father!" Fairy Bai Qing said in a solemn time.

"Most importantly, he is listed on the Demon Judgment Board, he is a vicious and evil demon, slaughtering countless and causing great harm to the world, he is very dangerous."

"But he saved father." Feng Jin Huang retorted.

Fairy Bai Qing said in a serious tone, looking deeply into Feng Jin Huang's eyes: "You must remember this, gratitude and enmity cannot be mixed together, you need to draw the line. His gratitude of saving your father's life was a coincidence, we will definitely repay him. But he is a demonic path member, he is vile and vicious, after repaying that debt, if we meet him again, we will exterminate him. Understood?"

Feng Jin Huang nodded: "Understood!"

Southern Border, Fang Yuan was inside the dream realm.

"Achoo! Achoo!" Fang Yuan sneezed twice.

He rubbed his nose as he said to the female Gu Master in front of him: "Again."

The female Gu Master was at the counter in front of him, she took out three rocks: "Please."

This was another dream realm.

The earlier water path dream realm was too hard at the end, Fang Yuan gave up. A few days later, the dream realm changed, and a suitable one appeared for Fang Yuan.

What made him happy was that successfully exploring this dream realm would raise his luck path attainment level!

Luck path Gu Immortals were very few in numbers.

Because even though Giant Sun Immortal Venerable created luck path, he did not spread it.

Thus, dream realms that contained luck path true meaning were rare. It was unlikely that Fang Yuan could encounter such a dream realm.

Fang Yuan looked at the three rocks, he knew that according to the rules, he would need to win three consecutive times, finding the most valuable item in these three rocks to get to the second scene.

Rock gambling.

"I succeeded twice already, if I fail now, my efforts would be in vain, I should use unravel dream."

Fang Yuan activated the immortal killer move unravel dream.

After waiting for a while, nothing happened.

"What is going on?" While he was confused, the female Gu Master who attended to him looked at him amorously and whispered: "Little brother, choose the middle one, don't worry, I won't harm you."

Saying this, she winked at Fang Yuan in a subtle manner, it had a teasing flavor.

Fang Yuan finally realized, this was unravel dream's effect. He did not hesitate, he grabbed the middle one.

The three rocks were opened, none had any Gu worms, but with the quality of the rocks themselves, the middle one had the highest value.

The first scene faded, as he quickly entered the second scene.

Northern Plains.

Longevity Heaven.

Rank eight Immortal Gu House, Calamity Luck Altar.

Three floors of round altars with multiple pillars holding it up, white jade railings and shining aurora.

Eight Gu Immortals in Longevity Heaven were standing at the center of the nine corners of Calamity Luck Altar, doing their best to concentrate in controlling the operations of Calamity Luck Altar.

At the center of Calamity Luck Altar, Five Elements Grandmaster had a solemn expression, he was surrounded by three layers of rings in the five elements, but Calamity Luck Altar's pressure was increasing, Five Elements Grandmaster had to use his true abilities to resist it.

Both parties were silent.

Because it was clear that both sides could not be moved with just words.

But at this moment, the entirety of Longevity Heaven resounded with bell chimes.

The Eight Extremities heard the bell chimes and shook, they were shocked and full of questions.

"This is the immortal killer move ringing alarm bell, why did it activate?"

"In the past, Ancestor Giant Sun set up this immortal killer move in Longevity Heaven, if we met with trouble, it would activate."

"But Five Elements Grandmaster has already been trapped."

The Eight Extremities were conversing, feeling lost.

The leader of the Eight Extremities, Heaven Extremity said: "No, even when Five Elements Grandmaster attacked, ringing alarm bell did not activate, right now, it is pointing to another danger."

The others were flustered.

"This means that the following calamity is going to be more severe than Five Elements Grandmaster's attack?"

"Right now, we have to use our full strength to suppress Five Elements Grandmaster using Calamity Luck Altar, we cannot divert our attention. How will we deal with it?"

"With Calamity Luck Altar here, heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities cannot do anything to us, it has to be a terrifying human calamity instead."

The second-in-charge, Earth Extremity, looked at Heaven Extremity and said: "In this situation, we can only awaken the Four Desolation Immortals."

Heaven Extremity had a solemn expression as he nodded.

Five Elements Grandmaster spoke with a smile: "Longevity Heaven can barely fend for itself, I am curious, what kind of disaster can make this ringing alarm bell activate."

Heaven Extremity was about to speak when a voice could be heard near him: "These so called disasters are accompanied by fortune and good luck. They are luck path in essence, a type of uncertainty, as Gu Immortals, we have to turn these negative uncertainties into positive uncertainties. The concept of Calamity Luck Altar was derived from this."

Heaven Extremity heard this voice and felt great joy and surprise.

Five Elements Grandmaster looked at this mysterious Gu Immortal who appeared, asking: "Which of the Four Desolation Immortals are you?"

"Greetings to Lord South Desolation." The Eight Extremities respectfully greeted at once, giving the answer to Five Elements Grandmaster.

Longevity Heaven had twelve positions, separated into Eight Extremities and Four Desolations.

The Four Desolation Immortals were East Desolation, South Desolation, West Desolation, and North Desolation, four rank eight immortals respectively.

The Eight Extremities were: Heaven Extremity, Earth Extremity, Black Extremity, Yellow Extremity, Space Extremity, Time Extremity, Flood Extremity, Desolate Extremity, a total of eight rank seven Gu Immortals.

Of course, Longevity Heaven was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's grotto-heaven, it had a huge space and abundant resources, other than these twelve, there were other Gu Immortals. But these twelve had the core authority of Longevity Heaven, they were elites among Gu Immortals.

South Desolation Immortal wore an azure-gold suit of armor, his beard extended to his chest, he was a muscular man with an old appearance, he said: "When the bell rang, I woke up. This sound has three long notes and two short notes, it is neither fast or slow, it means that love Gu has entered Northern Plains. Love Gu has the power to defy fate, in the past, even Ancestor was wary of it. To obtain love Gu, Ancestor made a bet with Heavenly Court, but he failed to refine it even after three years. He could only set up some supreme luck path methods in it, that would activate one day. Love Gu would come to Northern Plains due to luck, and this would be the best opportunity for us to snatch love Gu!"

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's immortal killer move was very amazing. His descendants could gain some information just by hearing the bells.

Even though the Eight Extremities knew of ringing alarm bell, they did not know its specific details, after hearing South Desolation Immortal's words, they were excited.

It turned out that long ago, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had made his preparations.

Heaven Extremity said: "Us Eight Extremities will follow Lord South Desolation's lead, we are willing to die for Longevity Heaven, and obtain love Immortal Gu!"

Southern Border.

"This is Bai Xiang grotto-heaven!" Hei Lou Lan stepped through the immortal aperture's entrance, officially getting into Bai Xiang grotto-heaven.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng, Ying Wu Xie and Shi Nu followed behind.

"Hmm? Something's not right." Ying Wu Xie's expression changed.

At the next moment, the surroundings changed, the Gu formation was activated, trapping the four immortals in a special space.

Bai Ning Bing's figure slowly appeared.

Shi Nu was shocked and furious, he growled: "You are Bai Ning Bing? You dare to betray us!"

"Hmph, remnants of Shadow Sect, today will be the day you die!" Bai Ning Bing smiled coldly, a cruel light was shining in her pale blue dragon eyes.

Ying Wu Xie was greatly surprised, Bai Ning Bing had broken free of his control, this was out of his expectations.

He had a flash of inspiration: "So that's it, you used the humans alike dragons Gu refinement method? This method had been lost long ago, Bai Xiang grotto-heaven actually had it?!"

"Honestly speaking, I need to thank you, now accept this present of gratitude from me." Bai Ning Bing snickered, the image of the four immortals faded in front of her, before they vanished completely.

"Wait, we can still negotiate..." Ying Wu Xie had not finished his words when the Gu formation activated, large amounts of snow rained as countless ice spears shot up from the ground, the four immortals quickly defended themselves.

Remains of Yi Tian Mountain, inside the super Gu formation.

Fang Yuan opened his eyes, returning to reality.

His soul was extremely weak, but it was not a problem, he had enough guts Gu to use.

"Luck path master!" Fang Yuan inspected himself, his luck path attainment had risen to master level.

The luck path dream realm earlier was fully explored.

He had no remaining uses of unravel dream, but his gains were huge, his luck path attainment had jumped from ordinary to master attainment level.

He immediately felt a difference.

This feeling was mystical, it could not be described with words.

"If my luck path attainment is at grandmaster level, I might want to get the self luck true inheritance from Lang Ya land spirit, if I can use it well, my strength would rise greatly."

"In my current case, I feel like I can already use unravel mystery Immortal Gu and dog shit luck Immortal Gu together, to greatly boost the effect of my immortal killer move qi luck sensation!"

Chapter 1239: Filled With Killing Intent

Qi luck sensation.

This immortal killer move came from Hei Fan grotto-heaven, the inheritance of Gu Immortal Feng Jun.

It used qi luck Immortal Gu as the core, with supplementary mortal Gu, to allow a Gu Immortal to sense people who were closely related to them in terms of luck.

Furthermore, the closer they were to each other, the clearer the connection would feel.

Fang Yuan used this move to sense the locations of Ying Wu Xie and the rest, even though they were separated by regional walls.

This was because Ying Wu Xie and the rest had their luck connected to Fang Yuan.

After using Connect Luck, both parties would have their luck closely connected, they would share both fortune and disaster together.

However, with Ying Wu Xie's methods, he was able to negate a portion of the effect of qi luck sensation, he even could hide inside an immortal aperture to cut himself off from Fang Yuan's detection.

Fang Yuan was very wary of Ying Wu Xie and gang, even though Shadow Sect was a fraction of its former size, a broken ship was still better than a plank, a dying camel was larger than a horse, by just gathering Shadow Sect's remaining resources, Ying Wu Xie and the rest would grow much more rapidly than Fang Yuan and at a steadier rate.

"This time, after elevating qi luck sensation, I should be able to detect the locations of Ying Wu Xie and the rest. I will eliminate them in advance and get rid of this huge threat!"

Fang Yuan decided to add Unravel Mystery into qi luck sensation, causing this killer move to have two cores instead of one.

"Unravel mystery Immortal Gu is wisdom path, hmm... I should add some wisdom path Gu in."

"After that, I will use some group think Gu and some mortal connect luck Gu, hmm, and some pair Gu and sequence Gu."

...

Fang Yuan did not make any deductions, he was making decisions based on his instincts.

A large number of mortal Gu were added in.

Among these Gu worm, a portion were owned by Fang Yuan, but he had to buy more of them through treasure yellow heaven.

Without any hurdles, soon, he obtained these Gu worms.

But next, he did not activate the immortal killer move immediately, he went to do further testing.

After adding so many Gu worms, qi luck sensation had changed greatly, if he activated it blindly, he might just fail immediately, Fang Yuan might get injured, or worse, his Gu worms might be destroyed. Destroying mortal Gu was fine, but if his Immortal Gu were destroyed, what would he do?

When Gu Immortals create a new immortal killer move, the experimentation process was also very risky.

Fang Yuan first separated the new qi luck sensation into several portions and did experiments on them one by one.

The results of the experiments were very good.

Not a single one failed.

Fang Yuan next used wisdom path methods to deduce, modify and improve on the newly created qi luck sensation.

Half a day later, Fang Yuan finally finished his deductions, he activated the newly modified qi luck sensation for the first time.

Halfway through activating it, a small problem that was beyond Fang Yuan's estimations occurred.

It was not a big problem, but the result of success might possibly be affected.

Fang Yuan was vigilant, he forcibly stopped the activation.

Many mortal Gu were destroyed.

Fang Yuan did not even blink at the result, as long as qi luck Immortal Gu and unravel mystery Immortal Gu were fine, it was no problem. He was very rich now, expending some mortal Gu was simply a negligible loss to Fang Yuan.

As for the supplementary mortal Gu, they did not need to be purchased.

Fang Yuan had considered this situation long ago, thus he purchased more than what he needed for one activation.

He continued to deduce and found out the reasons that resulted in this unexpected change.

This time, Fang Yuan spent half a day again modifying the immortal killer move. After fixing it, he experimented again.

This time, towards the later half of the immortal killer move, a mishap occurred again.

The immortal killer move used too many Gu worms, Fang Yuan could not completely deduce the entire process.

Even though these small unexpected sparks appeared minimally, Fang Yuan still thought of inspecting them, he forcibly stopped the killer move once again.

Be it unravel mystery Immortal Gu or qi luck Immortal Gu, they had to be used at the final juncture, thus, although he lost many mortal Gu, they were inconsequential.

After repeated trial and error, he continued to deduce and modify it.

Several days later, Fang Yuan finally obtained a relatively perfect version of qi luck sensation.

This immortal killer move used three times the number of Gu worms as before, with two Immortal Gu as the core, unravel mystery Immortal Gu and qi luck Immortal Gu, they were like two shining suns in the sky.

Activating the new qi luck sensation!

A mystical feeling appeared inside Fang Yuan.

First, he detected Ye Fan, Hong Yi, and Han Li, they were in Southern Border, Central Continent, and Western Desert respectively, the exact details were clearer than before, especially Ye Fan, Fang Yuan could tell that he was currently on Shang Liang Mountain.

The rest were more vague.

Ying Wu Xie and Hei Lou Lan appeared in Fang Yuan's detection again.

It was vague, countless times less clear compared to Ye Fan, he also did not know their exact location, but Fang Yuan could tell the general area they were in.

"Strange, other than Ying Wu Xie and Hei Lou Lan, there is a third person, but they are just as unclear as them. Don't tell me Ying Wu Xie used connect luck Immortal Gu to connect his luck with an unknown Gu Immortal?"

Fang Yuan guessed the truth immediately.

He frowned.

Connect luck Immortal Gu was in Ying Wu Xie's hands, this was no secret.

This was Fang Yuan's weakness.

Currently, Fang Yuan no longer used Spring Autumn Cicada, he sealed it. In regards to luck, with dog shit luck Immortal Gu's protection, it had turned from a weakness to his strength.

But Ying Wu Xie and the rest were taking a portion of Fang Yuan's advantage.

When Giant Sun Immortal Venerable developed in his early days, a lot of his success was attributed to this dog shit luck Immortal Gu. But Fang Yuan was not enjoying it alone, his dog shit luck Immortal Gu's effect was split among other people.

If it was split equally with Ye Fan, Han Li, Hei Lou Lan, and Hong Yi, so be it. After all, these were four lucky people. But Ying Wu Xie and that new Gu Immortal were huge burdens, they were weakening the effects of Dog Shit Luck.

"This direction... hehehe, to think that they are in Southern Border!"

"Ying Wu Xie and the rest need to be eliminated, after killing them, I will be truly safe, nobody would come after the sovereign immortal body again."

"At the same time, after I kill them and remove the threat, my luck will rise greatly, the true power of Dog Shit Luck would be unleashed."

At this moment, Fang Yuan was filled with killing intent, he wanted to move immediately and get rid of Ying Wu Xie and the rest once and for all!

Central Continent.

"It is time, we can go now!" Rank eight Gu Immortal Wei Ling Yang shouted.

His voice was hoarse, he had a middle aged appearance with dark bags under his eyes and looked listless, giving others a feeling of extreme fatigue.

But he was the strongest among the three rank eight Gu Immortals on this journey, he was tasked as the leader of this rescue mission.

Along with him, there were Bi Chen Tian and Myriad Tidal Dragon.

These two were rank eight Gu Immortals as well.

Bi Chen Tian joined the battle of Yi Tian Mountain and survived in the end.

Myriad Tidal Dragon had higher seniority than Bi Chen Tian, recently, he was given pointers by Duke Long, his strength rose again.

Duke Long was old and it was difficult for him to fight once again, but he controlled the situation and immediately changed the way that Heavenly Court functioned.

They sent out three rank eight Gu Immortals, all from Heavenly Court, they had phantom apertures but their battle strength greatly surpassed the rank eight Gu Immortals of the ten great ancient sects.

The immortals acknowledged his words and split into three groups, entering three Immortal Gu Houses respectively.

These three Immortal Gu Houses were: Wind Cloud Manor's Wind Sweeping Building, it had seven floors and had fluttering curtains; Heavenly Lotus Sect's Canary Pavilion, small and exquisite, filled with liveliness; Combat Immortal Sect's Edge Link Camp, it was a military stronghold with waving battle flags.

Each Immortal Gu House was guarded by a rank eight Gu Immortal.

Zhao Lian Yun was in the middle one, Wind Cloud Manor's Wind Sweeping Building.

She was at the top floor, the safest place inside this Immortal Gu House.

"Right now, our group is too powerful, we have three rank eight Gu Immortals as well as three Immortal Gu Houses! Victory is basically assured." Bu Zhen Zi followed behind Zhao Lian Yun, saying this.

Zhao Lian Yun nodded, she was expressionless but her heart was jumping: "Hong Yun, I am coming! You must persevere."

The three Immortal Gu Houses were like shooting stars, flying towards the sky.

Edge Link Camp was at the front, opening a path for the rest. Wind Sweeping Building was in the middle, in charge of reinforcements. Canary Pavilion was at the back, looking out for unexpected situations.

The heavenly wind qi wall was right before them.

Boom!

Edge Link Camp unleashed its might, giant sharp horns were formed, resembling solid figures, as they stabbed into the heavenly wind qi wall fiercely. Without any resistance, they forcefully created a tunnel.

Wind Sweeping Building and Canary Pavilion followed after it quickly.

Swoosh, swoosh, swoosh.

Wind Sweeping Building continued to shake, Zhao Lian Yun was also shaking at the top floor, almost falling down.

Bu Zhen Zi was tongue-tied: "It is said that the heavenly wind qi wall is thicker than the five regional walls, it seems to be true after seeing it myself. Our Wind Sweeping Building is just in the center, moving along the created tunnel, yet the heavenly winds are already causing us to be so unstable. It is hard to imagine what it is like inside Edge Link Camp!"

The heavenly wind qi wall was created by heavenly wind qi, even after creating a tunnel, the wind would rush in and fill the gap very quickly.

Thus, the three Immortal Gu Houses were very close together, almost touching the edges of each other, they continued to charge forward.

Halfway through their journey, Edge Link Camp lost many Gu worms, its charging power fell and it went to the back.

Wind Sweeping Building replaced Edge Link Camp's spot, taking charge of creating a path ahead. After a quarter of the journey, Canary Pavilion went to the front.

This way, some days later, the three Immortal Gu Houses finally broke through the heavenly wind qi wall and reached black heaven.

Right now, in the Gu Master world, there were only black heaven and white heaven left of the immemorial nine heavens.

It was clear why they did not choose white heaven.

It was to prevent exposing themselves.

Black heaven had natural concealment, it could help to hide the traces of the three Immortal Gu Houses to an extent.

This way, the Central Continent Gu Immortals would ensure that they had the advantage in launching a sneak attack on this journey.

Chapter 1240: Usefulness of Attainment Level

Southern Border.

Inside the super Gu formation.

Fang Yuan recalled the power of qi luck sensation, realizing the usefulness of attainment level.

"The process of elevating qi luck sensation just now was quite tedious, but it was actually very easy."

"Everything flowed naturally like water running down a drain."

Ordinary Gu Immortals would face difficulty in trying to improve or complete an immortal killer move. For example, Vicious Lightning Fiend from Myriad Dragon Dock of the ten great ancient sects took years before creating the immortal killer move lightning deity.

"Vicious Lightning Fiend's lightning deity was deduced using the remnant recipe of Blood Deity. It involved both lightning path and blood path. Vicious Lightning Fiend had enough lightning path attainment level, but his blood path attainment was just ordinary. Thus, he had to spend years, using resources from Myriad Dragon Dock, to succeed with difficulty."

"This is the lack of attainment level, one can only deduce forcefully, maybe high wisdom path attainment level can provide a lot of help, otherwise, inspiration or time would be needed. Hei Fan was a time path great expert, but even he had many immortal killer moves that were not completed after his death, right?"

"However, once the attainment level is sufficient, deducing killer moves will no longer be deductions, it would be an instinct, it is extremely easy."

Fang Yuan thought about it.

Just now, he elevated the immortal killer move qi luck sensation, he only spent a few days.

But the results were shocking!

When creating the framework of the immortal killer move, Fang Yuan did not think much, he only had a vague concept in his mind.

Next, when he chose Gu worms, as long as they were luck path or wisdom path mortal Gu, he had a strong instinct about the selection.

Instinct?

This was hard to imagine.

It really was, but once the attainment level was sufficient, one's understanding towards Gu worms and the concepts of immortal killer moves of the specific paths would turn into an instinct of the Gu Immortal.

This instinct was like a natural skill, as if one had it since birth, it was simple and effortless.

Like how someone could breathe through their nose, it was a natural thing.

"Attainment level is one's understanding of the Great Dao."

"My luck path attainment is master level, this allows me to have acute sensations towards all contents of luck path, it is hard to describe with words. When elevating qi luck sensation, I did not need to test anything, I already knew what Gu worms would be suitable as the supplementary Gu."

"Similarly, for wisdom path, I have wisdom path grandmaster attainment level. My understanding of wisdom path surpasses luck path, thus, I could perfectly fuse unravel mystery Immortal Gu into qi luck sensation successfully."

Fang Yuan concluded and realized that the benefit of attainment level surpassed his former expectations.

Being able to annex more immortal apertures was just a physical benefit.

It had great effects on other aspects as well.

"If I raise all of my attainment levels to grandmaster or even great grandmaster in the future, will I be able to create a terrifying killer move that uses all of the paths?"

Fang Yuan's thoughts started to wander.

"In fact, Spectral Soul had already reached this level. Perhaps this was why he could create sovereign immortal fetus Gu?"

Conceptualizing immortal killer moves was the same in essence as creating Immortal Gu recipes.

Thinking of Spectral Soul, Fang Yuan subconsciously looked towards a certain direction in Southern Border.

Not long ago, he had confirmed with qi luck sensation that Ying Wu Xie and gang were over in that direction in Southern Border.

Fang Yuan had already known the rough range of their whereabouts.

Even though Fang Yuan had deep killing intent towards Ying Wu Xie and the others, he thought about it and decided to make some preparations before starting his assault.

Even though Fang Yuan hatched the upper extreme heavenly eagle, it only had rank six battle strength.

Ying Wu Xie and the rest had wrong information, thinking that Fang Yuan had rank eight battle strength, but he could not possibly use this non-existent power to kill them, right?

In the previous battle in Eastern Sea, Fang Yuan saw the strength of Ying Wu Xie and the others.

This time, after a long while, Fang Yuan could not estimate whether Ying Wu Xie and the rest had inherited Shadow Sect's resources and gained a huge boost in strength.

To play it safe, Fang Yuan made a lot of preparations, just in case.

He wanted to use this chance to get rid of this huge threat!

Qi luck sensation was a great example, Fang Yuan had also already started to fuse myriad self and sword dragon transformation.

Other than that, he even borrowed Immortal Gu from Wu clan.

This was the benefit of joining Wu clan.

It was different from Lang Ya Sect, that was a sect and required sect contribution points. But Wu clan was a clan, Fang Yuan's identity was Wu Yi Hai, the younger brother of Wu Yong, he had the closest bloodline relationship in the entire clan.

Thus, when Fang Yuan asked to borrow some Immortal Gu from Wu clan's treasury, Wu Yong did not stop him, he agreed.

In fact, Wu Yong was quite satisfied with Fang Yuan's recent performance.

After Fang Yuan went to the super Gu formation, he held his side of the agreement and did not interfere in Wu clan's politics, this allowed Wu Yong to easily gain control of Wu clan.

Secondly, Fang Yuan, who acted as Wu Yi Hai, perfectly handled the immortal opportunity business. He displayed great political abilities and prevented Ba clan from interfering, he helped Wu clan control the situation and defend their territory inside the giant dream realm.

This was a contribution to Wu clan, Wu Yong remembered Fang Yuan's contribution, thus he not only agreed to lend some Immortal Gu from the treasury, he even lowered the cost of doing so.

Fang Yuan paid a lot of Eastern Sea resources to borrow multiple Immortal Gu, among them were strength path dragon strength Immortal Gu and transformation path dragon scales Immortal Gu, they were all available. These Immortal Gu were added to fuse myriad self and sword dragon transformation, providing great help to Fang Yuan.

Bai Xiang grotto-heaven.

Inside the super Gu formation, Hei Lou Lan, Shi Nu, Tai Bai Yun Sheng, and Ying Wu Xie were at four spots, defending against Bai Ning Bing.

Howl howl howl...

The super Gu formation was activated, intense winds blew, ice blades shot out, encircling the four Gu Immortals.

With Ying Wu Xie leading and the three immortals helping, they resisted the super Gu formation's pressure. Even though they were in a difficult state, the formation was still quite stable.

Suddenly, a figure appeared in front of Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

It was Bai Ning Bing, but only her upper body was present, her lower half was like smoke.

'Bai Ning Bing' appeared and charged towards Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was the weakest among the four immortals, Bai Ning Bing chose to attack him, it was the right choice.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng quickly retreated!

In the battle earlier, he had already seen how powerful Bai Ning Bing's attacks were, he suffered a lot due to it, if not for the other immortals' help, he would have died already.

"Change! Shi Nu, go." Seeing Tai Bai Yun Sheng's predicament, Ying Wu Xie quickly commanded.

A white light appeared on all four of them, before a deep eerie sigh was heard in the sky.

Shi Nu and Tai Bai Yun Sheng had changed locations, swapping as Shi Nu faced 'Bai Ning Bing''s attack.

Shi Nu grunted, defending against it.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was behind Shi Nu, seeing this, he quickly used his cloud path Immortal Gu to heal him.

"Bai Ning Bing is getting stronger, she is familiarizing herself with Bai Xiang's methods, she is in control of many ice and snow path Immortal Gu that Bai Xiang had. The longer this drags on, the worse it will be for us!"

"Damn it!"

"Bai Xiang heavenly spirit actually had the humans alike dragons Gu refinement method! Wasn't this method completely eliminated by Duke Long? How could he have missed this."

"Also... during the battle earlier, I sensed something in my luck. Fang Yuan actually raised his detection method to this extent, even if I hide inside an immortal aperture now, he would still discover me."

Ying Wu Xie was facing huge pressure!

Bai Ning Bing betrayed them and was getting stronger every minute, Ying Wu Xie and the rest were desperately trying to defend against her, they could not leave.

On the other hand, Fang Yuan knew where they were.

But Ying Wu Xie had the information that Fang Yuan possessed rank eight battle strength! If he got here, Bai Xiang grotto-heaven could not block the immemorial desolate beast upper extreme heavenly eagle.

This meant that Fang Yuan could appear at any moment. Ying Wu Xie would not even be surprised if Fang Yuan showed up suddenly at the next moment.

"Bai Ning Bing, stop it! Fighting would harm us both, only working together will bring benefits."

"Since you are now a dragonman, you are qualified to inherit the Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace. In the past, the dragonmen were extremely powerful with a large number of Gu Immortals, they managed to create Dragon Palace. After the dragonmen went extinct, Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace has been secretly hidden in a certain area of Eastern Sea. My Shadow Sect knows roughly where it is, but only someone who has used the humans alike dragons Gu refinement method to become a dragonman Gu Immortal can inherit it."

"If you work with us, Dragon Palace will be yours!"

Ying Wu Xie shouted.

Bai Ning Bing had no reaction, the super Gu formation was continuing to attack unceasingly.

Ying Wu Xie was stifled, he called out: "Bai Ning Bing, it will be too late if you don't stop! A great enemy whom we both know of is coming, he has a rank eight level upper extreme heavenly eagle, and has already used luck path methods to find out our location."

"I am not lying to you, our luck vibrated earlier, you must have sensed it too, right?"

Bai Ning Bing snorted, transmitting: "I would like him to come here. I want to cooperate with him, even if I have to give up this Bai Xiang grotto-heaven, so be it."

Ying Wu Xie was anxious, he yelled: "Aren't we clear what kind of person he is? You are playing with fire, you will get burned to a crisp in the end. Wait, why do you want to cooperate with him?"

Bai Ning Bing sneered: "This is our business, it has nothing to do with you. The four of you should just die here!"

Ying Wu Xie had a flash of inspiration: "I know, you want that rotation Gu in his hands? That's right, you used the humans alike dragons Gu refinement method but turned into a dragon lady. You want to become a man, you need to solve the origin of the issue. I have the Gu worm that you need! It is with me."

"What?" Bai Ning Bing was surprised.

For the first time since the super Gu formation attacking Ying Wu Xie had activated, it showed signs of slowing down.

Chapter 1241: Journey in Black Heaven

Zhao Lian Yun stood at the top of the Immortal Gu House, Wind Sweeping Building, looking outside.

Only to see that black heaven was covered in darkness, a dark veil was shrouding the surroundings.

But there was light.

Small specks of blurry lights appeared in Zhao Lian Yun's vision, they seemed far away.

Black heaven was huge, or rather, the immemorial nine heavens were all huge, every layer of the heavens would have the collective size of the five regions.

But because of Ren Zu and his ten children, only black heaven and white heaven were left now.

"We finally got past the heavenly wind qi wall and entered black heaven."

"This is black heaven? It seems peaceful."

The surrounding Gu Immortals started conversing.

There were more people on this floor than Zhao Lian Yun and Bu Zhen Zi.

"We entered black heaven." Wei Ling Yang transmitted to the other two rank eight Gu Immortals.

Right now, the three Immortal Gu Houses changed their positions again.

Edge Link Camp was at the lead, flying in front, while Canary Pavilion and Wind Sweeping Building were at its sides respectively, slightly towards the back.

The other rank six and seven Gu Immortals have never entered black heaven before, they did not know the dangers. Wei Ling Yang, Myriad Tidal Dragon and Bi Chen Tian were very clear about them.

The immemorial nine heavens were usually places only rank eight Gu Immortals could enter and explore for resources.

There were special rank seven Gu Immortals like Feng Jiu Ge and Chu Du, they could enter but at a high risk.

Regardless of anything else, after entering black heaven, the three Immortal Gu Houses became much slower.

Furthermore, the Immortal Gu Houses no longer shined brightly, they were grey and dusty, like three lifeless rocks.

The surrounding Gu Immortals' discussions came to a stop.

The entirety of this floor in Wind Sweeping Building went into silence.

It was completely silent.

The first impression that black heaven gave to Zhao Lian Yun was that it was really huge.

"It seems that we were quite lucky." Bi Chen Tian said.

"We should remain careful, the journey has just started." Myriad Tidal Dragon kept up his vigilance.

Wei Ling Yang suddenly said: "Careful, there is a beast group ahead."

The three Immortal Gu Houses went even slower now, even with such a strong lineup, the three rank eight Gu Immortals were careful and moved with vigilance.

Loud sounds soon entered Zhao Lian Yun's ears.

"What are those things?"

"It seems like a group of boars."

Many Gu Immortals leaned on the windows, looking outside.

Soon, the immortals gasped in succession.

With the power of the Immortal Gu Houses, the Gu Immortals could see past the dark veil, noting that a large group of boars were below them.

Pigs were flying in the sky, was it quite funny?

No, the Gu Immortals had different feelings.

They were all shocked!

"These are astral wind flying heavenly boars, my goodness, there are so many."

"It is hard to imagine that each astral wind flying heavenly boar is an ancient desolate beast that has rank seven Gu Immortal battle strength. It is rare to see one in the five regions, but here there are hundreds."

"Thankfully, desolate beasts have low intelligence, they do not have the intelligence of humans."

The Gu Immortals felt gladness amidst their shock.

These astral wind flying heavenly boars were snorting loudly as they flew in the sky. Under the immortals' gazes, the leading boar king who had the largest body suddenly charged and stomped its feet into the heavenly wind qi wall.

Immediately, the astral wind flying heavenly boars behind the boar king did the same.

They were agile like flying fish, they had agility incomparable with their boar bodies, they charged into the heavenly wind qi wall.

Soon, the large group of astral wind flying heavenly boars vanished from sight.

Bu Zhen Zi stood beside Zhao Lian Yun, sighing: "Nature is wondrous and incredible. Us Gu Immortals have such difficulty passing the heavenly wind qi wall. But for these astral wind flying heavenly boars, it is incredibly easy. The heavenly wind qi wall is like water for fish in the sea."

At this time, a voice said: "Actually, long ago, Gu Immortals of the past had realized this. They eliminated the astral wind flying heavenly boars and used the immortal materials gathered from their bodies to refine qi path Immortal Gu. These qi path Immortal Gu were useful in helping the Gu Immortals pass the heavenly wind qi wall."

Bu Zhen Zi and Zhao Lian Yun turned around, only to see a young male Gu Immortal as beautiful as a female, he stood before them quietly, smiling.

Bu Zhen Zi's eyes shined, he recognized this person.

The young male Gu Immortal cupped his fists and greeted: "I am Yu Yi Ye Zi from Ancient Soul Sect, greets to senior Bu Zhen Zi, and Spirit Affinity House's Current Generation Fairy Zhao."

"Yu Yi Ye Zi, you may have rank six cultivation level, but you are extremely talented, often, rank seven Gu Immortals would approach you to refine Immortal Gu, or research Immortal Gu recipes, you are one of the top rank six Gu Immortals." Bu Zhen Zi replied with a praising tone, but most importantly, he was explaining this to Zhao Lian Yun.

Zhao Lian Yun obtained a phantom aperture and placed love Gu inside, after intense training, she finally joined the circle of Gu Immortals.

She was not very familiar with Central Continent's Gu Immortals.

"Hello, Yu Yi Ye Zi." Zhao Lian Yun nodded at the young Gu Immortal, before asking: "Since you said that, why did we not use those Immortal Gu when we passed the heavenly wind qi wall?"

Yu Yi Ye Zi laughed: "That is because the era where qi path was strong is over. Right now, countless qi path Gu recipes are lost, and Gu materials used to refine them have gone extinct. Think about it, how many people can enter the immemorial nine heavens? Almost all Gu Immortals can only explore this place after reaching rank eight. Thus, having such an Immortal Gu has little effect on them to begin with."

Zhao Lian Yun nodded, expressing her understanding.

At this time, clamors could be heard from the immortals by the windows.

Zhao Lian Yun turned around and looked, only to see that a huge patch of black clouds narrowly moved past Wind Sweeping Building.

"Black clouds are very common in black heaven. The ones we are seeing are among the smallest in black heaven. The real giant black clouds are like floating continents in the sky. Deep within the black clouds, there are terrifying fierce beasts or plants." Yu Yi Ye Zi explained.

Even these smallest black clouds took several minutes for the three Immortal Gu Houses to fly past.

Yu Yi Ye Zi was really knowledgeable, he knew many things that even the rank seven Gu Immortal Bu Zhen Zi was unsure of, and could explain them clearly.

He answered almost all of Zhao Lian Yun's questions.

The two conversed more as time passed, and the atmosphere was very relaxed.

In the following journey, the three Immortal Gu Houses encountered several black clouds along the way. These black clouds were not very evident in black heaven, without a strong investigative killer move, one would unknowingly fly into them.

The black clouds were like lone islands in the sea, the surface of the black clouds and even the interior were not empty, there were living beings residing there.

The three rank eight Gu Immortals were very careful, they did not move their Immortal Gu Houses into the black clouds.

They would rather take a detour and spend more time to avoid the clouds.

But sometimes, even when you avoid trouble, trouble still comes to you.

Hissing could be heard as a large group of dark venomous snakes flew out of the black clouds, attacking the three Immortal Gu Houses.

These dark venomous snakes were all desolate beast level, while the king snake was an ancient desolate beast.

"How can this be? At this distance, we should not be in the territory of the dark venomous snake group." Wei Ling Yang was surprised.

"Fight or retreat?" Bi Chen Tian asked.

Wei Ling Yang thought about it: "Retreat, we should avoid fighting to preserve our battle strength, the journey ahead is very long."

"But retreating won't be easy, these are dark venomous snakes." Inside another Immortal Gu House, Myriad Tidal Dragon transmitted.

The dark venomous snakes held grudges, once they lock onto prey, they would not give up.

The three Immortal Gu Houses flew rapidly, but even after a distance, the dark venomous snake group still trailed behind them.

Not only this, more and more dark venomous snakes were emerging from the black clouds.

"So many snakes!"

"That black cloud is like a snake den."

"I wonder how our three rank eight lords will deal with this?"

"In my opinion, we should fight, we have three Immortal Gu Houses after all!"

"That's right, these dark venomous snakes have poison path dao marks, and their snake guts are the best immortal material to refine healing Immortal Gu."

The Gu Immortals inside the Immortal Gu Houses talked to each other, expressing their views.

But the three rank eight Gu Immortals continued to escape, they did not follow their wishes to fight.

They continued flying like this.

The three rank eight Gu Immortals tried to avoid as they retreated, in their following journey, they encountered another group of dark venomous snakes, the size was even larger than before. Other than that, they even encountered bear mosquitoes.

These mosquitoes were huge like bears, they had terrifying mouths. But most importantly, their numbers were huge, far greater than the dark venomous snakes.

The bear mosquito group was very large, on one occasion, the three Immortal Gu Houses were surrounded by a group of bear mosquitoes, they had to fight.

Each bear mosquito had desolate beast battle strength.

Tens of thousands of bear mosquitoes attacked at once, what did that mean?

It was terrifying!

After that battle, the Gu Immortals who wanted to fight all shut up, they realized how dangerous black heaven was.

Thankfully, they had three Immortal Gu Houses and the protection of rank eight Gu Immortals, otherwise, they would all die under the attacks of the bear mosquitoes.

After flying for a while more, they started seeing starlight ahead.

Above a black cloud, there was star fragment grass growing with countless insect groups living on top of the grassland.

The three Immortal Gu Houses stopped for the first time, several Gu Immortals were sent out to harvest the star fragment grass and other resources.

"Did you all feel it?" Wei Ling Yang transmitted.

"That's right, this journey in black heaven is especially smooth, I have never encountered this when exploring black heaven." Bi Chen Tian sighed.

Myriad Tidal Dragon continued: "Perhaps the most crucial thing currently in saving Ma Hong Yun is Zhao Lian Yun's existence, it affects our luck. These clouds in the immemorial nine heavens normally float randomly, they have no fixed pattern, even heaven's will cannot interfere with their movement. Whatever we encounter is up to luck."

Wei Ling Yang nodded: "I think so too."

Chapter 1242: Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace

Above the vast sea of clouds, a person was standing still, looking at the clouds move as he remained silent.

This person wore an azure-gold suit of armor, his beard extended to his chest, he was a muscular man with an old appearance, it was South Desolation Immortal.

"I, Yao Huang, pay respects to Lord South Desolation!" A figure emerged, it was Yao tribe's first supreme elder, rank eight Gu Immortal Yao Huang.

South Desolation Immortal turned around and said while smiling: "We are both rank eights, just treat me as a friend, no need to be so polite."

Yao Huang bowed reverently: "In terms of cultivation level, Lord South Desolation, you are far beyond me. In terms of seniority, I am a descendant of countless generations below you, how can I be so rude?"

South Desolation Immortal nodded, sighing: "You are good, but it is a pity that our Huang Jin bloodline is dwindling. In this huge Northern Plains, outside of Longevity Heaven, you are the sole rank eight Gu Immortal that belongs to a Huang Jin tribe!"

Prince Feng Xian was a member of Gong tribe, but from South Desolation Immortal's perspective, he was an outsider in terms of bloodline.

"Back in my generation, there were four rank eights in the Huang Jin tribes, one of them was known as the Tiger God, he had incredible might, he was thought highly of by the people and was a potential seed to ascend to rank nine. Unfortunately, he died in black heaven. Time is merciless, the Huang Jin bloodline is declining every generation."

South Desolation Immortal showed deep disappointment in his eyes.

Yao Huang could not speak.

Yao Huang was not qualified to speak such criticism of the Huang Jin bloodline, only South Desolation Immortal had the right to comment on it.

And he was expressing a fact as well.

Yao Huang had nothing to retort.

It was like this, Northern Plains' Huang Jin tribes were degrading, they were lacking talents, in contrast, lone and demonic cultivators were rising up with large numbers of geniuses, like Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, Chu Du, and that Liu Guan Yi as well.

"However, Ancestor Giant Sun had anticipated this situation." South Desolation Immortal suddenly said, causing Yao Huang to feel great shock.

"Oh? Ancestor Giant Sun lived in the Medieval Antiquity Era, he could predict this future situation?"

"Even though our ancestor cultivated luck path, his wisdom path capabilities were not low at all. Furthermore, 'luck' is uncertainty in essence, ancestor created luck path, he naturally learned the true meaning of change in this world. After he created Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, he proclaimed that this building was bound to fall one day, when it did, a great era would begin, it was a sign of changing times." South Desolation Immortal added.

Yao Huang was shocked: "Is that so?"

What was a great era?

It was a great era if an Immortal Venerable or Demon Venerable could come into existence.

South Desolation Immortal sighed deeply: "Ancestor Giant Sun spent a lot of effort and set up many arrangements to help his descendants and preserve strength. He wanted to ensure that they would be part of the wave in this great era's storms and tides. In the worst case, he wanted to ensure that his bloodline would be passed down intact."

Yao Huang hesitated: "No matter how weak our Huang Jin bloodline becomes, we must be able to defend ourselves, at least? Northern Plains is still under our control, and even if we are useless, there is still Longevity Heaven."

South Desolation Immortal shook his head: "Longevity Heaven might be strong, but it is just the immortal aperture of our ancestor. Meanwhile, Heavenly Court has the immortal apertures of three Immortal Venerables, and all of the members of Heavenly Court have contributed their own grotto-heavens throughout history. How can Longevity Heaven's foundation compare to Heavenly Court? Like right now, Central Continent came to invade us, they sent three rank eight Gu Immortals and three Immortal Gu Houses. Does our Huang Jin bloodline possess such strength?"

Yao Huang was tongue-tied: "What? Central Continent invaded?!"

South Desolation Immortal did not explain, he said: "Follow me."

Saying this, he flew to the sky.

Yao Huang quickly followed after him.

The two immortals flew through the heavenly wind qi wall, getting into black heaven.

Under South Desolation Immortal's lead, Yao Huang headed towards the southeast direction.

After flying for a while, Yao Huang was shaken: "Black heaven is such a dangerous place, even though I explore it often for rank eight immortal materials, I have never had such a smooth journey without any obstacles before. Don't tell me Lord South Desolation has a map of black heaven?"

But the truth was, maps did not work in the immemorial nine heavens.

The clouds that were in the nine heavens were constantly changing. Some were in specific locations, but those were rare and few.

The Central Continent group had a relatively smooth trip, but they still encountered trouble like the astral wind flying heavenly boar group, the dark venomous snake group and other problems. South Desolation Immortal and Yao Huang met with absolutely no issues, they were safe and sound, as if they were strolling in their own garden.

"Alright, this is the place." South Desolation Immortal stopped flying.

Yao Huang also slowed down, stopping beside him.

He felt a little strange, this place was empty, without a trace of wind, why was South Desolation Immortal stopping here?

At the next moment, South Desolation Immortal answered him with an action.

His body shined with golden light, like a fragment of the sun, Yao Huang had to close his eyes in response.

Yao Huang's heart jumped.

Black heaven was dark and eerie, this action of creating strong light would attract the attack of countless fierce beasts.

Even though he became alert, no beast groups came attacking.

"Is this really black heaven?" Yao Huang wondered.

A moment later, South Desolation Immortal's immortal killer move was completed, a grand dark gold palace appeared out of nowhere, revealing its majestic appearance.

Yao Huang had never expected an Immortal Gu House to be hidden here.

But he quickly realized what this palace was, he became extremely agitated as he called out: "This is Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace?"

Calamity Luck Altar, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace, these were the three Immortal Gu Houses that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable owned during his life.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was placed in Imperial Court blessed land by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, Calamity Luck Altar was kept in Longevity Heaven, while this Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace was placed in black heaven, hidden for countless years!

"Ancestor Giant Sun placed Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace here, there clearly are deep intentions. But what was he planning?"

Yao Huang continued to guess as South Desolation Immortal turned around to look at him: "Follow me."

Yao Huang followed South Desolation Immortal, entering Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace.

"Both of you have arrived." Inside the hall, there was one person.

He sat on a cushion, he was not formed from will, he opened his eyes as lightning flashed in his eyes, golden radiance shone brightly.

Yao Huang saw this and shuddered, huge waves were churning in his heart: "Ancestor, Ancestor Giant Sun?!"

...

Howl!

The wolf group called out, chasing after the three Immortal Gu Houses.

These wolves had long and slim bodies, they had black eyes, claws, and fangs, they were emitting cold glints of light. Most amazingly, they had no fur on their bodies, they had black and shiny leather armor that were very tough.

This was a night heavenly wolf group. The size was huge, there were over ten thousand night heavenly wolves.

Each night heavenly wolf was a desolate beast, wolf kings were ancient desolate beasts, there was even a wolf emperor, it had rank eight battle strength!

"We can't escape, we are surrounded."

"To think that the wolf emperor has a wild rank eight Immortal Gu that can conceal traces!"

"A wolf group of this scale is not seen often in black heaven, we actually met one."

The three rank eight Gu Immortals conversed rapidly.

Wei Ling Yang shouted: "Charge towards the northwest!"

Edge Link Camp opened a path in front, its aura rose as immortal essence was expended rapidly, forming a huge charging horn.

Wherever the giant horn went, it pierced into the wolf formation, creating a huge hole as several hundred desolate beast night heavenly wolves died.

The Immortal Gu House charged into the wolf group, as Canary Pavilion and Wind Sweeping Building followed close after it.

The huge battle was dangerous and terrifying.

The wolf emperor attacked during the battle, its huge hill-like claws sent the Immortal Gu Houses flying.

Thankfully, each of the Immortal Gu Houses had a rank eight Gu Immortal inside, the three Immortal Gu Houses could display their might and kill countless wolves.

The wolf group's encirclement tactic was at an incredibly profound level, even though the three Immortal Gu Houses charged ahead, they could not break out.

Eventually, the wolf emperor howled and retreated with the other wolves, causing this bloodbath to end.

The wolf group had sustained losses that were too huge, the wolf emperor did not want to weaken it any further, thus it left.

The three Immortal Gu Houses were extremely damaged, a great number of Gu worms were destroyed, including three Immortal Gu. The three rank eight Gu Immortals also worked up a sweat, they were in difficult conditions.

Their immortal essence expenditure was immense.

"Why is it that the closer we get to Northern Plains, the harder it becomes?"

"We have already encountered five night heavenly wolf groups, we also met dragon crocodiles, ghost spirit foxes... it seems like countless beast groups are trying to kill us."

"Forget about these beast groups, the most important thing is that we cannot encounter any black-white overturning clouds anymore. That time, this Wind Sweeping Building almost failed to come back."

"Let's rest first and fix the Immortal Gu Houses." Wei Ling Yang said.

The three Immortal Gu Houses had just stopped, when countless lights illuminated an enormous surrounding range.

It resembled the blooming of countless flowers, the sparks were light red and looked like countless overlapping petals of flowers, but inside the flames, there were dark spots.

"Oh no, this is a special phenomenon of black heaven — black lanterns, blind fire nurtures inside them, do not look at them!" Bi Chen Tian shouted as he shut his eyes.

But it was too late, many Gu Immortals only took one look before they lost their sight.

Inside the three Immortal Gu Houses, screaming and shouting could be heard, it was chaotic.

Zhao Lian Yun was quite lucky, she was facing the interior of the Gu House as she spoke to Yu Yi Ye Zi.

Yu Yi Ye Zi looked at the blind fire from the black lanterns, feeling his vision weakening rapidly as it turned blurry, he quickly shut his eyes.

He was very knowledgeable, but many Gu Immortals were not.

Some were leaning on the windows as they looked around, they saw at least ten thousand blind fires, their vision turned completely dark, losing the ability to see anything.

The three Immortal Gu Houses quickly escaped hurriedly.

Black lanterns did not cause any physical damage, unlike wind or rain, the Immortal Gu Houses charged through them as they quickly left the black lanterns behind.

The three rank eight Gu Immortals counted, at least three people permanently lost their sight without any ways to recover. Seven had severely weakened vision, it greatly affected their battle strength, but it could be salvaged at a high price, some healing Immortal Gu were needed to be sent through treasure yellow heaven.

"We just left the wolf group and wanted to rest, when we encountered black lanterns, while at the center of them! This is too unlucky."

"Wait, what is that?"

A swarm of ants were approaching.

Each ant was a Gu worm.

Nether ant Gu!

"Nether ants open a path, there has to be a soul beast army of hundreds of thousands or even millions. Run, quickly run!"

The three Immortal Gu Houses had just stopped when they were forced to flee again.

Chapter 1243: A Favor

Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable actually appeared in front of Yao Huang.

Yao Huang was overwhelmed with shock, he could not believe it.

"I, South Desolation, pay respects to Immortal Venerable." At this time, South Desolation Immortal greeted respectfully.

"This unfilial descendant greets ancestor!" Yao Huang was shaking from excitement, he quickly knelt down on the ground, tears flowing over his face.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable smiled lightly: "Stand up, my main body has already died, I am merely a corpse sitting before you now."

Yao Huang raised his head in shock, after inspection, he finally saw that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable in front of him was not alive, he was an immortal zombie.

Ever since Red Lotus Demon Venerable damaged fate Gu, all souls in this world could remain in the realm of the living, since then, zombies appeared.

Gradually, when Gu Immortals realized they had insufficient lifespan, they would become immortal zombies, it was their best alternative.

Even though Heavenly Court was against it and tried to stop it, they could not resist the desires of humans, more and more immortal zombies showed up in the five regions.

Ordinary Gu Immortals could become immortal zombies, there was no reason why Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could not do the same, right?

Thinking of this, Yao Huang's doubts vanished.

Giant Sun immortal zombie continued to explain: "Right now, other than my body, I only have some remnant will left inside this body."

But Yao Huang was still very excited: "Undeniably, you are the source of our Huang Jin bloodline, our common ancestor. As long as you show yourself, all of the Huang Jin tribes would end their conflicts and be united as one. The entirety of Northern Plains would belong to us Huang Jin tribes again!"

But Giant Sun immortal zombie shook his head: "My main body died long ago, I only left a corpse behind. I did not manage to surpass rank nine and attain eternal life, what is the point of showing myself? I will just be a laughing stock."

"Furthermore, my body only has one attack left, if I move even slightly, it will fizzle out."

"Just one attack?" Yao Huang was shocked, the admiration and excitement in his eyes did not fade at all: "Even if ancestor can only attack once, it will definitely shake heaven and earth, and make the sun and moon pale in comparison."

Giant Sun immortal zombie laughed: "That is naturally the case. But don't count on it. I set Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace here to defend Northern Plains. But I left this body behind for another reason, I need to return a favor."

"A favor?" Yao Huang was shocked.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable became an immortal zombie and stayed in Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace for three hundred thousand years just to return a favor.

Who was it, who could make a great Immortal Venerable owe a favor?

And this favor was so huge that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had to do this?

Yao Huang was very confused, but Giant Sun immortal zombie did not explain it, he said: "Right now, Central Continent invaded but I cannot fight them off. Don't count on me, it all depends on you two."

Yao Huang slowly stood up with a solemn expression: "Central Continent's Gu Immortals might have a strong lineup, but we have Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace, myself and Lord South Desolation. Don't worry ancestor, I will defend against these people at all costs, even if I have to give up my life, I will do so without hesitation."

Giant Sun immortal zombie looked at Yao Huang before shutting his eyes, returning to an inactive state.

At this moment, he seemed to have become a statue, he no longer spoke.

Yao Huang did not know why, but South Desolation Immortal patted his shoulder: "Come with me."

The two immortals left the main hall, going to the hall behind it.

Yao Huang was still excited from earlier: "Please give me orders, Lord South Desolation, I will do whatever it takes!"

South Desolation Immortal shook his head: "Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace is a rank eight Immortal Gu House, it was created by Ancestor Giant Sun personally using the heaven and earth luck true inheritance. Ancestor Giant Sun had great foresight, he placed Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace here for three hundred thousand years, suppressing this area until now. Do you know what heaven and earth luck is?"

Yao Huang was dazed, muttering: "Heaven and earth luck..."

South Desolation Immortal did not wait for a response, he smiled: "A person has their own luck, a beast has its luck, a blade of grass also has its own luck. Any life form has luck. Other than that, rocks, rivers, they all have luck. And for the entirety of this heaven and earth, there is also heaven luck and earth luck."

"The heaven and earth luck true inheritance deciphers the profundities of heaven and earth, researching them, using them, and changing them."

"Forget the fact that there are three rank eight Gu Immortals who brought three Immortal Gu Houses with them, even if they doubled in numbers, once they came here, they were goners."

"I did not call you here for you to risk your life. You are the only rank eight Huang Jin bloodline descendant outside of Longevity Heaven."

"Huh?" Yao Huang was shocked.

South Desolation Immortal continued: "I have little lifespan left, after surviving for so long, lifespan Gu stopped working on me. Next, I want you to see how I manipulate this Immortal Gu House, and eliminate these Central Continent Gu Immortals. After I die, you will inherit my position as South Desolation."

Yao Huang stared with wide opened eyes, shouting: "Lord South Desolation!"

...

Wind Sweeping Building was silent inside.

The black lanterns were like wind, rain, and lightning, they were a unique type of phenomenon in black heaven.

They were not unprotected, but the black lanterns appeared too suddenly. And most importantly, when they appeared, Canary Pavilion, Wind Sweeping Building, and Edge Link Camp were right at the center of countless black lanterns.

Normally speaking, when rank eight Gu Immortals explored black heaven, if they saw any black lanterns, they would avoid them from afar.

This time, the Central Continent Gu Immortals had just escaped the night heavenly wolf group, they relaxed and did not expect the black lanterns to appear, thus, many Gu Immortals were heavily injured as a result.

At the top of Wind Sweeping Building.

"Father! Your eyes?!" Rank six Gu Immortal Shi Zheng Yi had tears in his eyes as he sobbed.

His father was a famous rank seven Gu Immortal expert, to think that he was one of the three who went blind.

When the black lanterns appeared, he was using an investigative killer move to observe the wolf group, his investigative killer move was very useful, but that resulted in him losing his vision instead.

It was confirmed that from now on, Shi Ge would no longer be able to see, he would be a blind man that could never use his eyes again.

But Shi Ge was calm, he stretched out his arm, patting Shi Zheng Yi's head, saying: "So what if I lose my sight? I have many methods and countless investigative killer moves, even if I lose my vision, I can still cultivate and fight. What is the matter?"

"But..." Shi Zheng Yi lowered his head and gritted his teeth, almost at the point of crying.

"My son, don't cry easily. Gu Immortal cultivation is full of dangers. As long as we are still alive, we should continue charging ahead. Don't cry like a weakling. Don't you like listening to stories? Think about those protagonists, how did they live?" Shi Ge said softly.

Shi Zheng Yi nodded: "Father, I understand!"

Even the rank seven Gu Immortal expert Shi Ge lost his sight from this.

Zhao Lian Yun looked at this as her heart shook, she felt that this Immortal Gu House, Wind Sweeping Building, was not so safe after all.

But she soon thought of Ma Hong Yun.

"Hong Yun, wait for me. No matter how dangerous and hard this is, I will find you and rescue you!"

Zhao Lian Yun cheered herself on as determination shone in her eyes.

"Yu Yi Ye Zi, how are you?" Zhao Lian Yun asked the young Gu Immortal beside her.

This refinement path Gu Immortal had been sitting on the ground with his eyes shut after seeing the black lanterns outside the window, he had been using an immortal killer move to heal himself.

Hearing Zhao Lian Yun's question, Yu Yi Ye Zi did not stop his immortal killer move, he spoke without opening his eyes: "Thankfully, I realized early on and shut my eyes, if I was a bit slower, I would not be able to heal myself."

Yu Yi Ye Zi did not speak anymore.

He stopped talking.

Cold sweat was still remaining on his forehead, as he experienced lingering fear.

Gradually, the Gu Immortals became silent, inside the three Immortal Gu Houses, they were enveloped with a solemn mood.

Outside the Immortal Gu House, there were soul howls, it was disturbing to the ears, even if the Immortal Gu House was dampening the effect.

Bu Zhen Zi looked outside worriedly: "Oh no, we are encircled by a soul beast army."

Zhao Lian Yun heard this and looked outside, only to see countless nether ant Gu surrounding the three Immortal Gu Houses, like waves of black river currents.

Chapter 1244: Star Cloud Storm

Outside, there were countless nether ant Gu, with the figures of soul beasts among them, they were truly a massive army. The shocking thing was that their auras were joined together like a group of mountains, they would be incredibly powerful once they moved, like a tsunami that crashed down with endless might.

Not just the size of the soul beast army, but also the fact that there were many ancient and immemorial soul beasts among them. The Gu Immortals could also sense the auras of many wild Immortal Gu.

"Five immemorial soul beasts!"

"We have just left the black lanterns, and now a soul beast army is here."

The three rank eight Gu Immortals conversed secretly.

They were having a bad feeling regarding how the situation was developing, their luck was too bad, it was very suspicious.

Wei Ling Yang said grimly: "It seems that we need to consider the worst case scenarios in our trip from now on."

"Damn it!" Bi Chen Tian clenched his fists: "Ever since Red Lotus Demon Venerable damaged fate Gu, the door of life and death became much weaker in absorbing souls. Many strong souls are able to stay in this world. After Spectral Soul Demon Venerable ascended, the world changed in that great era, and soul beasts appeared, many souls even directly turned into soul beasts. Right now in immemorial black heaven, soul beasts are rampant in great numbers, when can we eradicate them and return to world to its rightful form?"

"Soon!" Myriad Tidal Dragon added: "After the battle of Yi Tian Mountain, most of the immortal zombies in the world were destroyed. These were fate escapees that were meant to die, now that they are dead, the difficulty of refining fate Immortal Gu lowered drastically. With Granny Sha repairing it now, even without success dao marks from Infallible blessed land, we are still making huge progress."

Wei Ling Yang shook his head: "Take note, the soul beast army is coming. The matter at hand is to try and escape from the soul beast army!"

Myriad Tidal Dragon sighed: "The best way is to use Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's defensive method, the killer move that pairs with divine concealment — Ghostly Concealment. Rumors has it that the Gu Immortal who possesses this immortal killer move would not be detected by soul beasts at all. But now, let's use my dragon flow escape."

"But in this case, I need to bring myself and three Immortal Gu Houses with me, along with many Gu Immortals. Once I use this move, I will not be able to fight for the next three days."

The three immortals discussed and decided to use Myriad Tidal Dragon's method.

Dragons roared!

Countless flying dragon phantoms appeared in the air, encircling the three Immortal Gu Houses.

The white dragon phantoms were like a long river, an uncountable number of dragons made of light, grand and unstoppable, charging forward with the three Immortal Gu Houses.

The soul beast army howled, blocking them with multiple layers.

But dragon flow escape was incredible, by charging relentlessly, an opening was forcibly created as the three Immortal Gu Houses escaped from the dangerous soul beast army.

The soul beasts moved quickly, the army did not give up, it followed closely behind.

Myriad Tidal Dragon did not dare to deactivate 'dragon flow escape', he had to grit his teeth and continue fuelling it.

Both sides chased for six hours, until the soul beast army gave up, its attention was drawn to a group of dark venomous snakes.

"I'm spent! I need to rest for seven days before I can do anything again. It will depend on the rest of you now." Myriad Tidal Dragon had a pale expression, his face turned white, his originally vigorous eyes were filled with traces of blood, like he was completely exhausted beyond his limits.

After stopping the killer move dragon flow escape, Myriad Tidal Dragon fell backwards as he sank into deep sleep.

His eyes were shut as he snored.

His snore was special, it sounded like the roaring of dragons.

As he slept, a thick fog appeared around his body.

The thick fog started to form into a cocoon, two hours later, the cocoon thickened and turned into a pale white dragon egg.

"We are free from those soul beasts."

"It was really dangerous!"

"The killer move earlier seemed to be from one of the three rank eight great experts, Lord Myriad Tidal Dragon's method, it was truly grand and majestic, I was completely in awe."

Inside the three Immortal Gu Houses, the Gu Immortals were cheering and praising.

But Bi Chen Tian and Wei Ling Yang had grim expressions.

Myriad Tidal Dragon had fallen into deep sleep, they had lost one of their three rank eights, but the journey was still around half done.

The three Immortal Gu Houses slowed down as the Gu Immortals inside tried to repair the Immortal Gu Houses.

In the next two hours, the Central Continent Gu Immortals encountered several ghost spirit fox groups and bear mosquito groups. They either retreated or fought, using the might of the Immortal Gu Houses to move forward.

Bi Chen Tian's heart suddenly shook, his lips curled into a smile as he said: "Lord Wei Ling Yang, I found a huge field of heaven attached fungi three thousand li away from here."

"Is that so? Wei Ling Yang let out a breath of air: "Then we will rest there."

The three Immortal Gu Houses turned around and flew away, in a while, all three Immortal Gu Houses landed on the surface of the heaven attached fungi.

"Where is this? Are we safe?" Zhao Lian Yun looked outside in shock. Especially when she saw her Gu Immortal companions leaving the Immortal Gu House to move freely on the heaven attached fungi.

Yu Yi Ye Zi smiled as he explained: "The immemorial nine heavens have their own special points. Like the black lantern phenomenon, it is unique to black heaven. But in the nine heavens, there are some common aspects, like the astral wind flying heavenly boar, or this heaven attached fungi."

"This fungi only grows in the immemorial nine heavens. Heaven attached fungi is a rank six immortal material, most importantly, it has to grow on its own without any foreign dao marks, other life forms and even rocks cannot exist here. Thus, once we see a field of heaven attached fungi, we know it is a safe place to rest at. Alright, I have to go out now and collect some heaven attached fungi, this is a rare opportunity."

Yu Yi Ye Zi quickly left Wind Sweeping Building.

Zhao Lian Yun had no interest in the heaven attached fungi, she had just become a Gu Immortal, it had been too little time, she did not know the importance of cultivation resources, she was only thinking of how to save her lover Ma Hong Yun.

A moment later, there were no Gu Immortals left in Wind Sweeping Building.

"Are you not going to collect some heaven attached fungi?" Zhao Lian Yun looked at Bu Zhen Zi, asking this.

Bu Zhen Zi smiled: "The sect ordered me to protect you, I will not leave you for even a second."

Zhao Lian Yun was understanding towards this: "Then I will go down as well."

Bu Zhen Zi shook his head: "Thank you for the thought, but even if we are standing on the heaven attached fungi, I will not pick them. That would only distract me, if anything happens, it will be too late to regret it."

Zhao Lian Yun heard this and felt warmth in her heart, she said softly: "Thank you."

Bu Zhen Zi shook his head: "No need to be so polite, you are the current generation fairy of Spirit Affinity House, my duty is to protect you."

Zhao Lian Yun sighed, leaning on the window as she said gloomily: "To think that black heaven is so dangerous, but there is such a safe place here. It shows that heaven always leaves a way out, we will definitely succeed in this trip. Right?"

Bu Zhen Zi did not hesitate, he answered: "Of... course."

But he suddenly dragged out his words in a strange tone.

At the same time, Zhao Lian Yun saw that there were some starlight shining far away.

This was not the blind fire from black lanterns, of course, the color was different. This blue starlight resembled countless diamonds embedded on black silk, it was distant and unforgettable.

Zhao Lian Yun squinted as she sighed: "So beautiful."

"Very dangerous! According to the records, this size..." Bu Zhen Zi turned pale, he said in a trembling tone.

Zhao Lian Yun became alert: "What?"

She had just asked when the warning and orders of rank eight Gu Immortal Bi Chen Tian came.

Outside the Immortal Gu House, Gu Immortals were rushing back in a panic.

Wei Ling Yang's gaze was like an eagle, he looked at the approaching starlight with a grim expression: "What a huge star cloud storm!"

Millions upon millions of stars were flying now.

Some shooting stars had long trails left in the night sky. Among which were huge stars, some were island-sized, while some were as large as a piece of land.

Between stars, there were countless starlight specks, like the weaving of a web of lightning.

The star cloud storm was a phenomenon unique to immemorial blue heaven, but due to historical reasons, immemorial blue heaven shattered and large numbers of stars fell into immemorial black heaven.

Thus, there were star cloud storms in black heaven as well.

"This is the first time I am seeing a star cloud storm of this scale!" Bi Chen Tian had an ugly expression: "Now it seems, this heaven attached fungi field was a trap to lure us to rest here!"

Chapter 1245: Watching A Meteor Shower With You

The star cloud storm's range was too huge, it was fast and powerful.

The three Immortal Gu Houses from Central Continent could not escape from it.

The stars flew over endlessly, lightning clouds were rumbling as starlight shot out continuously, it was a magnificent sight, but one could only feel weak and helpless, expressing nothing but shock at this.

"I will charge ahead with Edge Link Camp, the rest of you follow me." At the crucial moment, Wei Ling Yang decided this.

The three Immortal Gu Houses flew towards the star cloud storm.

The huge Immortal Gu Houses were like tiny ants in front of the star cloud storm.

Heaven and earth was growling loudly.

The star cloud storm was like a prehistoric whale, swallowing the three Central Continent Immortal Gu Houses easily.

The three Immortal Gu Houses were unable to satisfy the appetite of this star cloud storm.

Rumble...

Wind Sweeping Building was shaking intensely.

Zhao Lian Yun could not stand stably, she fell to the ground. Outside the window, countless glaring starlight specks were shining in, turning the entirety of Wind Sweeping Building blue.

Zhao Lian Yun felt like she was on a plank in a stormy sea, she was enduring the might of the tides and strikes of lightning.

Her mouth was dry, she was scared, even with Gu Immortal battle strength, she could not resolve this problem.

She could only rely on the Immortal Gu Houses, on the three rank eight great experts.

Zhao Lian Yun did not know that among the three rank eight Gu Immortals, Myriad Tidal Dragon was sleeping now. Thankfully, Wind Sweeping Building was under Bi Chen Tian's control, the situation was better than Canary Pavilion.

But even so, Bi Chen Tian was covered in sweat, he was concentrating and did not dare to relax his mind.

He moved Wind Sweeping Building and traveled in the star cloud storm, continuously avoiding the huge stars.

These stars moved quickly, if Wind Sweeping Building crashed into them, it would suffer huge damage. Even though Wind Sweeping Building was an Immortal Gu House, and would not break apart from just a few stars, in this situation, once Wind Sweeping Building loses control of its movement, it would slow down and be hit by endless number of stars. If that happened, it would be destroyed inside this star cloud storm, everyone would die.

"Gu Immortals are powerful, and Immortal Gu Houses are useful, but against the might of heaven and earth, we are still minuscule and insignificant." Bi Chen Tian gritted his teeth: "Oh no!"

He could not react in time, Wind Sweeping Building finally got hit, a hill-like star crashed into Wind Sweeping Building with the ferocity of a storm.

Wind Sweeping Building's entire size was less than ten percent of the star.

But it was an Immortal Gu House, it was sturdy.

It was the star which shattered instead of Wind Sweeping Building.

But the impact of the star's collision sent Wind Sweeping Building flying far away through brute force.

The three Immortal Gu Houses were working together and flying alongside each other earlier, but now, the other two Immortal Gu Houses dodged the star while Wind Sweeping Building was pushed away from the group.

"Bi Chen.... quick....." Wei Ling Yang's voice could be heard.

But in this star cloud storm, fragments were everywhere, the uncountable number of star path dao marks were disrupting the information path communication method of Wei Ling Yang and Bi Chen Tian.

Bi Chen Tian could only hear a short and incomplete message.

But he knew what Wei Ling Yang wanted to say.

Wei Ling Yang wanted him to try and catch up with them!

In the star cloud storm, Wei Ling Yang could not stay behind or even have any strength to reinforce Bi Chen Tian. Because around him, Canary Pavilion also needed to be taken care of.

Bi Chen Tian had to rely on himself.

"Let's do it." Bi Chen Tian shouted, his eyes shone with endless brilliance, his rank eight aura surged like a tornado.

Wind Sweeping Building shone with a jade green light, which quickly turned into fierce winds rapidly.

The winds moved and howled shrilly.

These deep green colored winds joined together, forming into a strong and sturdy tornado pillar.

Immortal Gu House Wind Sweeping Building stabilized, the surrounding stars were all pushed away by the wind pillar.

"This is Wind Sweeping Building's strongest method!" Yu Yi Ye Zi was roused, his eyes shone with light as he said excitedly.

Wind Sweeping Building was at the center of the wind pillar, it was completely peaceful here, as if they had left the terrible tsunami and landed on a shore.

The Gu Immortals inside Wind Sweeping Building erupted into cheers.

Zhao Lian Yun had just crawled up from the floor when a huge star crashed into the tornado wind pillar, before breaking in and assaulting Wind Sweeping Building.

At the crucial moment, Bi Chen Tian had a timely response, he controlled Wind Sweeping Building and lowered their altitude.

This huge star grazed past Wind Sweeping Building.

Some Gu Immortals by the window could see that at the moment near collision, the star had countless holes on the surface, they could be seen due to the close proximity.

The Gu Immortals who were normally graceful and elegant screamed again, they were like mortals who were experiencing natural disasters.

Wind Sweeping Building moved with difficulty inside the star cloud storm.

Even though this Immortal Gu House used its strongest method, against the star cloud storm, it was not enough.

Some huge stars approached forcefully, directly crashing into the tornado wind pillar.

And between the stars, there was a chaotic magnetic field, these fields repelled, attracted, and crushed Wind Sweeping Building.

Wind Sweeping Building had to dodge those stars while under the might of these magnetic fields, thankfully it was the rank eight Gu Immortal Bi Chen Tian holding the fort, any rank seven Gu Immortal would falter for sure.

However, even Bi Chen Tian was covered in sweat, his rank eight immortal essence was rapidly expended, his expenditure far surpassed any battle he had ever had.

"This will not do, this star cloud storm is too huge, I do not know when I can escape!" Bi Chen Tian had a thought as he ordered for the Gu Immortals to send their immortal essence into Wind Sweeping Building.

The Gu Immortals quickly contributed their efforts, including Zhao Lian Yun.

She had a phantom aperture, but she had refined immortal essence stones before and accumulated some immortal essence.

Boom! Boom! Boom!

From time to time, huge stars would crash into the wind pillar, most would be dodged by Wind Sweeping Building, but some still hit.

The magnetic fields were everywhere, like a cruel giant toying around with Wind Sweeping Building.

Inside the Immortal Gu House, the Gu Immortals did not speak, they were infusing their immortal essence into Wind Sweeping Building wholeheartedly.

The atmosphere was tense.

Every time a giant star crashed, many Gu Immortals' bodies shook.

Zhao Lian Yun's heart was in trepidation. She had never been faced with such danger, she would not be surprised if she died at the next moment.

"Hong Yun, Hong Yun..." She thought of Ma Hong Yun's name, each time she mentally muttered it, her heart returned to peace slightly.

After countless times, Zhao Lian Yun's mental state became completely peaceful.

"Hong Yun, you had once risked your life for me, do you know? I am doing the same now."

"Even if I die here, I have no regrets. I am coming to save you!"

"When I meet you, I will tell you that the starlight here is very fierce and dangerous beyond your imagination, it is not romantic at all."

In a daze, Zhao Lian Yun recalled the past.

At that time, Zhao Lian Yun's father had died in the battlefield, she was all alone, forced to marry someone else, she had to rely on Ma Hong Yun.

On a small mound.

It was night time, Ma Hong Yun was lying on the grassland with her.

"Lady Xiao Yun, quickly look, it's a meteor shower!" Ma Hong Yun pointed at the sky as he shouted.

"Boring, you brought me here to see this?" Zhao Lian Yun rolled her eyes: "What is so nice about this?"

"Guh." Ma Hong Yun scratched his head: "I don't find it nice either, but they said that to make a girl happy, I need to watch a meteor shower with her. At this time, in Northern Plains, we can often see meteor showers at night."

Zhao Lian Yun mentally sighed, thinking: "I am so old already, I am afraid only young girls would like this. Hmm? Wait a minute, my body is still young, I am still a young girl."

At this time, Ma Hong Yun asked: "Lady Xiao Yun, after looking at this meteor shower, has your mood improved?"

Zhao Lian Yun mentally sighed once again, she said in a coaxing tone: "I am much better now, I am so happy, look, this meteor shower is so beautiful, huh."

Ma Hong Yun's body shook, he quickly waved his hand: "Lady Xiao Yun, don't say that, I am getting goosebumps."

Zhao Lian Yun stood up in an instant, stomping at Ma Hong Yun: "Learning how to woo women out of all things, and you want to flirt with me, you are actually flirting with me."

Ma Hong Yun was screaming out in pain from getting kicked, shouting: "Lady Xiao Yun, stop, stop it! What is flirting? I have done no such thing. If I did something wrong, I will change it, okay? Stop kicking, stop kicking me!"

Zhao Lian Yun ignored him as Ma Hong Yun rolled around from getting kicked. Eventually, Zhao Lian Yun worked up a sweat, she placed her arms at her waist as she looked at the scurrying Ma Hong Yun, laughing smugly.

Ma Hong Yun heard her laughter and thought: "Lady Xiao Yun is finally laughing, at expected, the meteor shower made her mood better. Gasp... but it is so painful for me."

Her memories flashed right before Zhao Lian Yun's eyes.

Unknowingly, Zhao Lian Yun had started smiling.

"Hong Yun, after I save you, I will kick you countless times to celebrate it." Zhao Lian Yun thought. Right at this time, love Gu inside her phantom aperture actually emitted a profound aura on its own.

The aura was colorless and formless, it spread rapidly.

Ordinary Gu Immortals could not sense it, but Bi Chen Tian's body shook, his eyes shone with brilliance, he subconsciously thought: "Is this the power of love Gu?"

Chapter 1246: Spaceless Tunnel

Every moment in the star cloud storm was hard to endure.

After a long time.

A certain Gu Immortal in Wind Sweeping Building realized something, saying: "Everyone... for some time already, there have been no stars crashing at us?"

As he said that, the tornado pillar surrounding Wind Sweeping Building vanished instantly.

The immortals saw that in the calm dark night, far away, the star cloud storm was moving away with imposing might.

Wind Sweeping Building was silent for a moment before exploding with cheers.

"We made it!"

"So close, even with an Immortal Gu House defending us, being in immemorial black heaven still poses a danger of dying."

"Thanks to Lord Bi Chen Tian, otherwise, we would have died in this star cloud storm."

The Gu Immortals talked with great joy.

Bi Chen Tian had a hazy gaze, he thought: "We were able to escape the star cloud storm all thanks to Zhao Lian Yun's love Immortal Gu."

At the crucial moment, love Gu emitted an aura that led Bi Chen Tian towards the correct direction.

Bi Chen Tian controlled Wind Sweeping Building, he followed this direction and quickly escaped from the star cloud storm.

And within the star cloud storm, star path dao marks were filling the area, with conflicting dao marks, Bi Chen Tian's methods were very ineffective.

Bi Chen Tian's expression was still gloomy.

"We have already escaped danger, but Wei Ling Yang does not have love Gu, I wonder if they are still struggling inside the star cloud storm."

After losing contact with the other two Immortal Gu Houses, Bi Chen Tian did not continue on his journey, he moved around the area, searching for them.

Thankfully, half a day later, he successfully contacted Wei Ling Yang.

Wei Ling Yang led Canary Pavilion and charged through the star cloud storm with difficulty. They had left the star cloud storm after Bi Chen Tian, but unfortunately, they were ambushed by a sky chief beast group.

After being informed of this, Bi Chen Tian manipulated Wind Sweeping Building, bringing the Gu Immortals with him to rescue them.

After getting to the ambush site, the Gu Immortals saw Canary Pavilion and Edge Link Camp, they gasped loudly.

These two Immortal Gu Houses were surrounded by sky chief beasts.

Sky chief beasts lived in basically all of the immemorial nine heavens. Each sky chief beast was at least a mutated beast king, they were on par with ordinary beast emperors. And the kings of each sky chief beast group were desolate beast level. Beast emperors among them were at least ancient desolate beasts.

Within this sky chief beast group, there were a hundred ancient sky chiefs, and over a thousand desolate beast sky chiefs, the remaining sky chief beasts were overwhelming in number, they were uncountable.

Edge Link Camp and Canary Pavilion were at the center, surrounded by countless sky chiefs. Even though they defended themselves, they were heavily damaged and were in great danger.

Bi Chen Tian could not waste any more time, he charged ahead with Wind Sweeping Building.

At this time, both sides could communicate again, Wei Ling Yang immediately moved Edge Link Camp towards Canary Pavilion and Wei Ling Yang, cooperating with them to break out of the encirclement.

The sky chief beast group roared loudly, the sound waves were like a tsunami, it was shocking.

Both sides engaged in fierce combat, countless immortal killer moves were sent out like fireworks, displayed among the sky chief beast group.

The sky chief beast group died in batches after batches, but they were quickly replaced with even more beasts.

The sky chief beast group was too huge, it did not mind such losses.

And those desolate beast sky chiefs and ancient sky chiefs could last much longer in battle.

During this time, Edge Link Camp suddenly burst with strength, silhouettes of sharp horns were formed, shooting out in all directions.

This was an incredibly strong attack in which even desolate beast sky chiefs would be unable to withstand. Even ancient sky chiefs did not dare to take the attacks head on.

Wind Sweeping Building created a jade wind pillar again, as Canary Pavilion emitted the cries of a thousand birds.

The three Immortal Gu Houses worked together, opening a path within the sky chief beast group and meeting at the convergent point.

Next, the three Immortal Gu Houses turned around and fled, in a few minutes, they were free from the pursuit of the sky chief beast group.

"The situation is horrible!" Bi Chen Tian and Wei Ling Yang communicated in a grim tone: "The three Immortal Gu Houses are heavily damaged, half of Canary Pavilion is completely unstable now. We need to rest and recover, Myriad Tidal Dragon is unconscious, and my immortal essence has already been depleted by more than half."

Immortal essence affected the Gu Immortal's battle strength to a great extent.

Bi Chen Tian used more than half of his immortal essence, so did Wei Ling Yang.

Even though Immortal Gu Houses were powerful, they consumed a lot of immortal essence.

This was why Fang Yuan had never planned to construct any Immortal Gu Houses.

Even though he knew most of Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage's composition (of course, he forgot a portion), and also the entirety of Sacred Feather City's structure. But he did not have Giant Sun's immortal essence anymore, with his own immortal essence, he could not sustain the use of an Immortal Gu House.

Immortal Gu Houses used too much immortal essence, only rank eight Gu Immortals could sustain the consumption alone. Rank six and seven Gu Immortals had to work together to display their might fully.

Most importantly, the Central Continent Gu Immortals still had half the journey left.

"It seems we can only use spaceless tunnel now." Wei Ling Yang said grimly.

Bi Chen Tian was stunned before nodding, agreeing: "That is the only way to cross half of the distance and reach our destination!"

The two rank eight Gu Immortals were determined figures, the greater the setbacks, the greater their fighting spirit, they had never thought of retreating.

And their encounters might not have been expected, but Heavenly Court's wisdom path Gu Immortal Fairy Zi Wei had already prepared other plans for them in advance.

Spaceless tunnel was one of them!

Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace.

Through this rank eight Immortal Gu House, the experiences of Central Continent's three Immortal Gu Houses could be seen by Yao Huang.

"Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace affects the luck of heaven and earth. All that happens within immemorial black heaven, the direction where the lightning storms go, cannot be affected by even heaven's will. But Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace can interfere with it. This is an invincible defense, with this palace, who can invade Northern Plains?!" Yao Huang was extremely excited, his tone was heated and he had great admiration towards Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Yao Huang looked at South Desolation Immortal, saying: "Lord, I finally understand why you are so calm now. With Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace here, nobody can think of invading Northern Plains!"

South Desolation Immortal laughed: "Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace has been stationed here for three hundred thousand years. What does that mean? It has already deeply affected immemorial black heaven, even immemorial white heaven has been influenced. This is the supreme power of heaven and earth luck!"

Yao Huang thought of Ma Hong Yun, saying: "Heaven and earth luck is so incredible, then all living being's luck cannot be lacking in comparison. But now, fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu's user is in Old Ancestor Xue Hu's hands."

Yao Huang had no other options against Old Ancestor Xue Hu, but South Desolation Immortal was different.

Especially when Yao Huang saw the power of Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace and the sorry states of these three Central Continent Immortal Gu Houses, thus he was moved and wanted to incite South Desolation Immortal to deal with Old Ancestor Xue Hu.

But South Desolation Immortal shook his head and smiled: "Ma Hong Yun has our Huang Jin bloodline, and is a descendant of Ancestor Giant Sun, there is no problem with him getting fortune rivalling heaven Gu. It will not be easy for Old Ancestor Xue Hu to snatch it away."

Yao Huang was worried: "That Old Ancestor Xue Hu has already been refining it for so long, with just fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu's power, can it really make the refinement fail?"

South Desolation Immortal shook his head: "Of course not, even though fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu has quasi-rank nine power, it cannot resist the rank eight Gu Immortal Old Ancestor Xue Hu. Furthermore, he has the aid of Lady Wan Shou, one of the four great refinement path experts in Northern Plains. Do you think my Longevity Heaven has done nothing? We will not let Fortune Rivalling Heaven end up in the hands of others, we made our arrangements long ago. If Old Ancestor Xue Hu cannot find them, he will not succeed in this refinement."

Yao Huang realized that Longevity Heaven had taken action long ago, but its method was too impressive, everyone was deceived, even Xue Hu and Wan Shou could not notice.

"Amazing, truly amazing! Compared to Longevity Heaven, even Old Ancestor Xue Hu was toyed in our palms." Yao Huang was truly impressed in his heart.

His gaze towards South Desolation Immortal changed again, he felt that South Desolation Immortal was unfathomable, he truly had the demeanor of a senior.

But at the next moment, South Desolation Immortal's expression changed suddenly.

South Desolation Immortal was confused, he called out: "What happened? These Central Continent Gu Immortals vanished all of a sudden?!"

Chapter 1247: Water Path Grandmaster

"This... where are we?" Zhao Lian Yun looked outside, expressing shock on her face.

But this time, even the knowledgeable Yu Yi Ye Zi could not answer her.

Bu Zhen Zi, who was in charge of Zhao Lian Yun's safety, said in an uncertain tone: "This unique phenomenon, is it spaceless tunnel?!"

The three Immortal Gu Houses from Central Continent, Canary Pavilion, Edge Link Camp, and Wind Sweeping Building, were moving inside a huge tunnel.

This tunnel was blue in color, with rainbow colored threads that extended forward in the path. These rainbow colored threads were lined around the blue tunnel walls, they were dazzling and beautiful.

"What is spaceless tunnel?" Yu Yi Ye Zi asked.

Bu Zhen Zi looked at Zhao Lian Yun with a complex gaze: "You should be familiar with it?"

"Me?" Zhao Lian Yun was confused, she did not know why Bu Zhen Zi would say this.

Bu Zhen Zi sighed, saying: "Because spaceless tunnel is a unique immortal killer move created by Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable!"

Southern Border, super Gu formation.

Inside the dream.

"This disciple greets master!" Fang Yuan knelt on the ground, paying respects to the female Gu Immortal in front of him.

The female immortal gave a murmur of acknowledgement before saying: "I am Jing Miao Zi, I cultivate water path. Even though you are my descendant, whether you can cultivate my water path will depend on your understanding and aptitude. Pass this test and you will become my true disciple."

"Please tell me, master." Fang Yuan said respectfully.

The female immortal waved her sleeve and the dream realm changed, Fang Yuan was standing in front of a jade pool.

This jade pool was extremely green and calm, like a huge piece of jade.

"A rumbling river is water. The sea is water. The calm jade pool is also water. Water path is deep and profound, I personally cultivate the path of calm water. Step into the pool and the moment you can stand on top of it without using any Gu worms, I will accept you as my disciple."

Fang Yuan stared with wide opened eyes, he was hearing this for the first time, he said: "Master, if I do not use Gu worms, I will be like a mortal. How can a mortal body stand on top of the water surface?"

"That is your problem." The female immortal waved her sleeve, vanishing in front of Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan frowned, he walked around the jade pool, after several rounds, he stepped into it.

Plop.

With a soft sound, he fell into the water directly.

He quickly climbed up the edge of the pool, he was completely soaked, it was a sorry sight.

Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, he hesitated before using the immortal killer move unravel dream.

But this time, the all-powerful unravel dream did nothing, there were no changes.

Fang Yuan sighed internally: "It was useless indeed... sigh, this is problematic."

Not long ago, Fang Yuan's luck path attainment level had risen, he could easily raise qi luck sensation to a new level. Therefore, the location of Ying Wu Xie and gang was exposed, they were in Southern Border.

Fang Yuan realized this and started to make preparations, raising his strength and borrowing Immortal Gu from Wu clan.

However, he met with a problem when he wanted to leave.

If Fang Yuan left, Wu clan would have no rank seven Gu Immortals holding the fort at the super Gu formation. With Wu clan initiating the immortal opportunity business, the situation was quite severe, without any experts around, the other clans could easily find trouble with them.

Wu Yong agreed readily to lend Fang Yuan Wu clan's Immortal Gu, but he did not agree to the matter of leaving.

Wu clan had many Gu Immortals and had a huge force, but their territory was too big, they needed a lot of manpower. They had few Gu Immortals, causing them to be short on people. Some jobs could not be transferred easily, like Fang Yuan's role of defending the super Gu formation, not many people in Wu clan could do it. Even if they had strength, their political abilities were a concern as well.

Fang Yuan gave the request of leaving his assigned position, Wu Yong felt a deep headache.

But Fang Yuan was insistent on it, Wu Yong had to relent and change the roles of the other Gu Immortals.

But this matter had huge implications on the others, Wu Yong said that a lot of time was needed, Fang Yuan had to wait.

But in the process of waiting, Fang Yuan encountered a superb dream realm.

There were all sorts of dream realms that were constantly changing. There were realistic dream realms and also strange ones.

Fang Yuan would normally choose realistic dream realms to explore. The strange dream realms were hard to decipher, Fang Yuan did not want to take unnecessary risks.

"According to historical records, Jing Miao Zi was a disciple of Shui Ni. This dream realm's owner is the disciple of Jing Miao Zi, her true disciple. That can only be one person, the water path great expert famous in history, Sea Calming Lord!"

"In Central Continent's history, there was an immemorial desolate beast that caused Falling Heavenly River to change directions, resulting in a tsunami that swept the lands. Central Continent's central area was flooded and the tsunami to the east was overwhelming. Back then, Heavenly Court Gu Immortal Sea Calming Lord stood up and used several immortal killer moves to return Falling Heavenly River to its rightful direction, the sea level returned to normal, he had incredible methods."

"My killer move unravel dream is usually effective, but it had no effect here. No wonder, no wonder."

This was not the first time Fang Yuan was using unravel dream.

But this time, even after using it several times, the dream realm was unmoved.

Fang Yuan thought about it, most likely, this dream realm was too powerful, killer move unravel dream only used a rank six core Immortal Gu, it could not unravel this dream!

The strength of a dream realm was not closely related to the crucial person in the dream realm.

For example, Fang Yuan had once explored Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream realm, he used unravel dream there and achieved great success.

But now, Fang Yuan's unravel dream could not unravel Sea Calming Lord's dream realm.

Sea Calming Lord was only rank eight, he could not match Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

But the strength of the dream realm was not closely related to their cultivation level or strength during their lifetime.

As for what relationship there was, Fang Yuan had no idea.

Don't forget, in the five hundred years of his previous life, Fang Yuan was not adept at exploring dream realms either, his main focus was on his blood path cultivation.

Fang Yuan did not study dream realms deeply, but he knew something, the stronger the dream realm, the greater the benefits after exploring it.

Remembering this, Fang Yuan's interest in this dream realm rose again.

"Wu clan has not redistributed the roles yet, I want to borrow Immortal Gu, but Wu Yong would not let me have them until he finishes the new role distribution."

"In that case, for this period of time, I should research in this dream realm."

In the following days, Fang Yuan calmed down and went to explore the dream realm again.

Allowing him to stand on the surface of the water without using any Gu worms.

On the surface, this seemed impossible.

Because without using any Gu worms, the Gu Master was no different from a mortal. Of course, this was different from Fortune Rivalling Heaven, or black boar Gu which carved dao marks onto the Gu Master's body.

"There are water path Gu worms like water walking Gu, they can allow the Gu Master to carve water path dao marks on their feet and allow them to run freely on the water surface. But this has nothing to do with the dream realm's task."

This dream realm did not allow the use of water walking Gu. Even if it could be used, Fang Yuan would not use it.

Because he knew that this problem was not about the task at hand, but himself instead.

As for solutions like freezing the surface of the water and standing on it, they were ideas that dodged the question, they did not target the true essence of this problem.

"Like what Jing Miao Zi had said, she is testing my aptitude. This is a realistic dream realm, Sea Calming Lord must have passed it, there is no reason that I cannot. After all, my water path attainment level is at quasi-grandmaster."

Fang Yuan continued to try, he had fallen into the pool many times.

If ordinary mortals ended up in this dream realm and fell into the water once, their souls would dissipate on the spot.

For Gu Immortals, falling inside several times would weaken their souls to a great extent.

Fang Yuan's soul foundation was deep, every time he entered the dream realm, he could fall into the water seventeen to eighteen times before his soul reached its limit.

At this time, Fang Yuan would use guts Gu to heal himself.

Guts Gu was a mortal Gu, but it originated from a secluded domain of heaven and earth, Dang Hun Mountain, it was very effective.

Fang Yuan had such a strong aid, he continued to work hard and started to have a feeling.

This feeling could not be expressed with words, it was mystical.

Fang Yuan tried again.

When he stepped onto the water surface again, plop, he fell into the water again without doubt.

When he climbed ashore, he saw his master Jing Miao Zi standing by the pool, looking at him.

Jing Miao Zi spoke furiously: "What aptitude is this? Such a simple test but you still can't pass it until now. You are not fit to be my disciple."

Fang Yuan smiled lightly: "No master, I did it. Like what you said, I have to stand on the water surface without sinking, I have already done it."

Jing Miao Zi smiled from extreme anger, she pointed at the water on Fang Yuan's body: "Then what is this?"

Fang Yuan shook his head: "This is nothing. The pool of water in my heart is calm and unmoving, I am already standing on it. Looking down, I can see my own reflection on the clear water surface."

Jing Miao Zi's anger and smile vanished gradually.

She looked at Fang Yuan deeply, nodding as she said plainly: "Not bad, from today onwards, you are my official true disciple."

At the next moment, the entire dream realm vanished, Fang Yuan returned to reality.

"This dream realm only has one scene?" Fang Yuan was shocked.

But soon, his shock turned into extreme joy.

"Wonderful, my water path attainment finally reached grandmaster level!"

Earlier, Fang Yuan's water path attainment level was at quasi-grandmaster level, he seemed close to grandmaster, but he was actually still very far from reaching grandmaster.

But now, this distance was passed as Fang Yuan became a true water path grandmaster!

Succeeding transformation path, strength path, blood path, wisdom path, and star path, Fang Yuan had finally become a grandmaster of a sixth path.

Chapter 1248: Ying Wu Xie's Objective

Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace.

"Not here."

"Not here either!"

"So strange, why did these Central Continent Gu Immortals vanish without a trace?"

South Desolation Immortal was no longer as composed, his calm smile vanished, sweat was covering his forehead.

He continued to manipulate Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace, inspecting everywhere, but he could not deduce the location of the Central Continent Gu Immortals.

Yao Huang was also dazed, he asked quickly: "Lord South Desolation, do I need to do anything?"

At this time, Giant Sun immortal zombie's voice resounded: "This is spaceless tunnel."

South Desolation Immortal was even more shocked now: "Central Continent's Gu Immortals possess this immortal killer move of Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable?"

But Giant Sun immortal zombie denied it: "No, they are just using the spaceless tunnel left behind by Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable."

Spaceless tunnel.

A space path immortal killer move.

In the past, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had roamed the entire world to look for a way to return home.

Undeniably, he was the venerable who had traveled the most in this world compared to the others. Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had covered almost every area in the five regions and two heavens.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable felt that a person was too small, and the Gu Master world was too big, thus he created spaceless tunnel.

This immortal killer move could shorten his traveling distance greatly, and hasten his exploration speed.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had gone missing long ago without a trace, but portions of his spaceless tunnel killer move left behind in the five regions and two heavens were still in existence even now, they seemed to be able to last forever.

The ten great ancient sects of Central Continent had never stopped researching Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable.

Because Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable was different from the other venerables, he was an otherworldly demon. From this point, Heavenly Court would not ignore him.

Spirit Affinity House possessed a Thieving Heaven true inheritance, they let Zhao Lian Yun inherit it. This was a fruit of Heavenly Court's research regarding Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable.

When Central Continent's Gu Immortals found this spaceless tunnel, they could use a corresponding method and shorten their travel distance.

"Then where does this spaceless tunnel lead to?" South Desolation Immortal reacted, realizing the key to this problem.

Giant Sun immortal zombie answered: "I cannot find out either, this is the work of Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable after all."

When Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was still alive, he had suffered a loss in a Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable inheritance. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was the creator of luck path, but against Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable, he did not have any strong methods to deal with his arrangements.

South Desolation Immortal was silent.

Yao Huang was stunned.

What could they do?

Giant Sun immortal zombie answered: "Since they used the spaceless tunnel, we only need to wait for them to reappear."

Yao Huang asked: "This means that Central Continent's Gu Immortals can appear at any place? If they appear in Northern Plains directly, what should we do?"

Central Continent's Gu Immortals were in a distressed state and lost a lot of their battle strength, but they were still very powerful!

Three Immortal Gu Houses and three rank eight Gu Immortals, along with many rank six and seven Gu Immortals, as well as the rank nine love Gu!

If this lineup appeared in the base of any super force Huang Jin tribe, the ones to lose would definitely be the Huang Jin tribe!

"If these Central Continent Gu Immortals appeared in my Yao tribe..." Thinking of this, Yao Huang felt uneasy.

"Please guide us, ancestor." South Desolation Immortal sought help.

Giant Sun immortal zombie chuckled: "My descendants have their own fortune, fortune and disaster coexist, they can be interchanged. This is Northern Plains' calamity, but it can be turned into Northern Plains' blessing. My main body died long ago, this is not my era. Go and work hard for the future, regardless of failure or success. Turning the calamity into a blessing, that will depend on your actions."

Giant Sun immortal zombie said that before returning to silence again.

South Desolation Immortal and Yao Huang looked at each other helplessly.

Southern Border, super Gu formation.

Fang Yuan was holding an ordinary Gu material.

He casually threw this Gu material into the stove.

The flame in the stove was burning, but it was emitting coldness instead.

The fire inside the stove was very special, it was not orange, it was pale white and blue, this was a cold flame.

Soon after, the cold flame extinguished all of a sudden, leaving no traces behind.

From the stove, a Gu worm flew out.

This Gu worm looked like a mosquito larva, it was thin and brown with a little green inside, it was wide and big. When it floated towards Fang Yuan, its body retracted and expanded, it was quite special.

This was a strength path Gu worm, obviously a mortal Gu.

But its name was Pulling Water, this made it a little special.

Fang Yuan already had Pulling Water, it was a rank six strength path Immortal Gu. But this one was a strength path mortal Gu.

Pulling water Gu could emit a mysterious power to allow the Gu Master to manipulate water currents like rivers and streams. This pulling water mortal Gu's effect was naturally far below the rank six pulling water Immortal Gu.

But Fang Yuan was overjoyed.

Why?

Firstly, Immortal Gu were unique. If Fang Yuan used two immortal killer moves that needed pulling water Immortal Gu at the same time, what would happen? With mortal pulling water Gu, Fang Yuan could use a great number of mortal Gu to temporarily replace pulling water Immortal Gu in the killer move. Thus, even though a Gu Immortal may have the Immortal Gu version of a certain Gu, that did not mean they did not need the mortal version as well.

Secondly, Fang Yuan's attempt succeeded because his water path attainment had reached grandmaster level.

Pulling water Gu might be a strength path Gu worm, but it was also related to water path. All along, even though Fang Yuan was a strength path grandmaster, he could not deduce the recipe of pulling water mortal Gu.

Now that his water path attainment level reached grandmaster, he did not even need to deduce it, he could instinctively detail the mortal Gu recipe.

Everything happened naturally.

"Water path grandmaster." Fang Yuan started to feel the benefits from many aspects.

Not just Gu recipes, there were also killer moves, Fang Yuan had a lot of water path accumulations in his five hundred years of life, he had water path killer moves and water path Gu recipes.

Now that he recalled these details, he had a brand new sensation and deeper understanding.

This was an incredible feeling that could not be described with words.

Formerly, he was standing below the tower, observing the bricks of the tower. But now, he was at the top of the tower, the sights were completely different.

"Even though my attainment level rose drastically and it cannot be evaluated easily in material terms, my strength has grown immensely."

"Especially when I already had five grandmaster attainment levels, the paths of these grandmaster attainment levels can work together and influence each other, forming an even greater benefit for me."

"No wonder everyone went after dream realms so desperately in my previous life."

Fang Yuan recalled, back then, his focus was placed on his blood path cultivation.

Of course, he had reasons for that.

Firstly, Fang Yuan's circumstances were not good at that time, he constantly faced strong enemies, he needed great battle strength.

Secondly, Fang Yuan knew nothing about dream realms, he did not have exploration methods like unravel dream, exploring dream realms was a huge risk that he did not need to take.

Thirdly, as Fang Yuan recalled his memories now, heaven's will quite likely was interfering in the circumstances.

When Fang Yuan was about to further explore his water path grandmaster attainment level, and see what benefits he had obtained, Wu clan finally sent a rank seven Gu Immortal over.

This Gu Immortal brought Wu clan's instructions, as well as the Immortal Gu that Fang Yuan borrowed from Wu clan.

Fang Yuan quickly completed the trade, leaving the super Gu formation.

He flew north-east without stopping.

Just now, the excuse he gave to Wu Yong was that he had personal reasons to return to Eastern Sea alone.

Everyone had their own secrets, if it were an ordinary Wu clan Gu Immortal, Wu Yong would investigate further. But this was Wu Yi Hai, even if Wu Yong asked, he would likely not get an answer. Thus, he wisely chose not to pursue it.

Fang Yuan went through the regional wall and arrived in Eastern Sea, he found a nameless sea area and placed his immortal aperture, resting temporarily.

During this period, he stayed inside the sovereign immortal aperture and practised his killer moves, getting familiar with his new Immortal Gu.

The closer he got to the crucial time, the more steady Fang Yuan was. He decided to use this chance to kill Ying Wu Xie, and eliminate this threat, he wanted to prepare amply.

When Fang Yuan saw that the time was ripe, he stored his immortal aperture and prepared to move, executing his plan that had been set for a long time.

Qi luck sensation!

Fang Yuan had just activated this killer move, when, out of his expectations, he found that Ying Wu Xie and the rest had left Southern Border, returning to Eastern Sea.

"Good, it will be easier for me to strike in Eastern Sea." Fang Yuan had no hesitations, he flew to the sky, towards his targets.

Ying Wu Xie and the rest were flying above the sea.

Bai Ning Bing was flying with them.

Their relationship had changed, she was an equal ally now.

A few days ago, Ying Wu Xie took out yang Gu, curbing Bai Ning Bing's killing intent.

Ying Wu Xie used this chance to seek cooperation with Bai Ning Bing.

But Bai Ning Bing was not the same as before, she expressed that she would rather give up yang Gu to kill Ying Wu Xie and gang.

Ying Wu Xie spoke with a glib tongue, by listing the problems involved, he managed to convince Bai Ning Bing to establish a new alliance agreement with him.

Bai Ning Bing got back yang Gu, she knew that Fang Yuan had the upper extreme heavenly eagle and was a big threat.

At this time, it was not wise to stay in Bai Xiang grotto-heaven.

Because of the upper extreme heavenly eagle, Fang Yuan could easily enter the grotto-heaven. If Bai Ning Bing and the rest stayed in Bai Xiang grotto-heaven, they instead would give Fang Yuan clues to find it.

At this time, Bai Ning Bing looked at the blue sea as she frowned, transmitting secretly: "Ying Wu Xie, you said that you have a way to deal with Fang Yuan, but we are all the way in Eastern Sea now, and are still traveling. What method is it, say it directly."

Ying Wu Xie laughed: "To deal with a rank eight, we need another rank eight existence. Eastern Sea is not our destination, we are going to Northern Plains."

"You mean Shadow Sect's remnant force in Northern Plains still has a rank eight existence? Hmph, bullshit." Bai Ning Bing snorted in disdain.

If they had rank eight battle strength, why did they not use it in Yi Tian Mountain?

Ying Wu Xie smiled bitterly: "The timing was not right."

"And the timing is right now?"

"It is a great opportunity now, Northern Plains and Central Continent are engaging in battle over Fortune Rivalling Heaven, by going to Northern Plains now, we are heading towards the center of the commotion — Snowy Mountain blessed land! Taking Fortune Rivalling Heaven, using the rank eight battle strength to kill Fang Yuan, and take back the sovereign immortal body!" Ying Wu Xie laughed as he said this, turning around to look behind him.

"Heh, he is coming."

Chapter 1249: Reappearance of Ghost Face

While speaking, Ying Wu Xie felt the luck on top of his head shaking intensely.

Earlier, Fang Yuan elevated qi luck sensation greatly, even if Ying Wu Xie hid inside an immortal aperture, he could not evade detection.

But Ying Wu Xie was not someone who passively waited for death, he thought about it and decided to make use of this.

Previously, he had tried to conceal himself and his aura. Now that this was not possible, Ying Wu Xie decided to strengthen the luck sensation instead.

Everyone had their luck connected, Fang Yuan could use this to activate qi luck sensation and find them. Then Ying Wu Xie could also do the reverse.

Thus, Ying Wu Xie had researched a brand new Gu worm combination recently to use his own luck's vibration to deduce his distance from Fang Yuan.

Ying Wu Xie named this immortal killer move luck vibration distance.

This way, Fang Yuan's familiar face could not be used, it could not deal with Ying Wu Xie's methods.

Ying Wu Xie was a split soul of Spectral Soul, even though he lost his memories, after getting replenishment inside the River of Time, he did not lack attainment level.

Attainment level was the most important thing.

Precisely because of thing, Ying Wu Xie could think of new Gu worm combinations at any time, to deal with all sorts of situations.

Of course he had to have enough attainment level, and the creation needed to be given time for experimentation and practice.

"Get into formation! We will use the tactic we discussed to repel Fang Yuan." Sensing that Fang Yuan was getting close, Ying Wu Xie ordered this, the five Gu Immortals stopped moving, assembling their formation.

After successfully convincing Bai Ning Bing to join the alliance, Bai Ning Bing's inheritance in Bai Xiang grotto-heaven also caused Ying Wu Xie's group to rise greatly in strength.

This immortal level Gu formation was the powerful method used to trap Ying Wu Xie and gang earlier, now, Fang Yuan was going to be the one facing it.

"He's here." Bai Ning Bing suddenly said.

She was the owner of Bai Xiang grotto-heaven, her wealth rose drastically, she had very useful Immortal Gu and her investigative methods were far superior than before, she surpassed Ying Wu Xie, Hei Lou Lan, and the others, becoming the first person to notice Fang Yuan's traces.

The other four immortals looked at where she directed.

Only to see that waves were forming at the southern sea area.

A sword dragon was moving its body, flying past the clouds nimbly.

Its sharp dragon horn was piercing towards the sky, its scales were shining with silver light, its dragon claws were sinister and sharp, its dragon teeth were glowing with an eerie cold light.

Ying Wu Xie and the rest were ready to face this strong foe.

Bai Ning Bing took a step forward: "Do you dare to enter our formation?"

Fang Yuan saw Bai Ning Bing, even though she was a dragon lady now and was even more beautiful than before, her overall appearance was still similar, Fang Yuan was slightly stunned.

He did not think that he would meet Bai Ning Bing under such circumstances.

In fact, Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing had not met for a long time. Even during the battle of Yi Tian Mountain, Bai Ning Bing was not involved too deeply, they did not meet.

After Three Kings blessed land, Bai Ning Bing betrayed him and Fang Yuan separated from her, until now when they met again.

But everything had changed already.

The two surviving young Gu Masters from Qing Mao Mountain were now Gu Immortals.

Bai Ning Bing, who was known as a genius with a bleak future, possessing one of the ten extreme physiques, Northern Dark Ice Soul Physique, had become a rank six dragonman Gu Immortal, and owned Bai Xiang grotto-heaven.

Meanwhile, Fang Yuan's experiences were even more bountiful, he had first become the owner of Hu Immortal blessed land, and after causing havoc in Northern Plains and destroying Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and Imperial Court blessed land, he went to Eastern Sea, Central Continent, and Western Desert. Eventually, he appeared during the battle of Yi Tian Mountain and took away the fruit of Shadow Sect's hundred thousand years of preparation — sovereign immortal fetus Gu.

Using this Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan's cultivation level rose like a rocket, he grew at an unthinkable speed, being a rank seven Gu Immortal already. Using dream realms, he even became a grandmaster in six paths.

The two were known as the Black and White Demons during their time in Southern Border as Gu Masters, they had worked closely together, but this time, their reunion was as enemies.

"Good, I will kill you as well." Fang Yuan was filled with killing intent, he roared as he shot out his dragon breath.

The white dragon breath was extremely sharp, as a bright light, it traveled rapidly and reached Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing did not dodge, she smiled lightly.

At the next moment, the sword light dragon breath landed on an invisible wall of light, dealing no damage to her.

The Gu formation able to trap Ying Wu Xie and the others was naturally not simple.

"Gu formation?" Fang Yuan thought.

At this point, he did not have many ideas.

Formation path.

Fang Yuan had little knowledge about formation path, even during the five hundred years of his previous life, it was like this.

To break the Gu formation, he either needed to have formation path attainment or use wisdom path deductions.

Fang Yuan was a wisdom path grandmaster, but he lacked a useful wisdom path Immortal Gu that could deduce the flaw in this Gu formation, it would not be easy.

The sword dragon flew in the sky, observing without advancing.

Ying Wu Xie and the rest were inside the Gu formation, awaiting Fang Yuan's attack.

At once, Fang Yuan was filled with thoughts on how to deal with this situation.

"The other party set up a Gu formation, this means that they cannot conceal their traces, but are already able to find out my location."

"In the probing earlier, it can be seen that this Gu formation is not simple at all."

"Since they set up this formation, they must have confidence in dealing with me."

"A broken ship is still better than a plank, after such a short time, Ying Wu Xie already possesses such a method."

Fang Yuan did not attack rashly.

He could not decipher this Gu formation, he would have to be an idiot to charge in recklessly. But there was a possibility that Bai Ning Bing and gang were putting up a front, this Gu formation might be weak on the inside and only strong against a direct attack.

Thus, Fang Yuan had to continue probing.

While Fang Yuan and Ying Wu Xie's group were fighting, inside black heaven.

Inside the spaceless tunnel.

Three Immortal Gu Houses were traveling slowly.

Myriad Tidal Dragon had already woken up, he looked at the scene inside the spaceless tunnel as he sighed: "Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's method is truly unthinkable. He has already vanished for so long, but this immortal killer move created three hundred thousand years ago can still be used effectively. If I was not experiencing this myself, I would not believe it."

Wei Ling Yang smiled: "Alright, since you are awake, we will not stay any longer, let's go!"

It turned out that the Central Continent Gu Immortals could have left the spaceless tunnel long ago, but they purposely stayed inside to wait for Myriad Tidal Dragon to wake up.

Myriad Tidal Dragon had used an immortal killer move to escape and fell into slumber.

After he woke up, Central Continent's Gu Immortals regained their full strength with three rank eight Gu Immortals!

The three Immortal Gu Houses moved quickly.

This was the final bit of distance in the spaceless tunnel.

Central Continent's Gu Immortals were enthusiastic, they were focused and awaiting the future battles.

"Hong Yun, hang on, I am coming!" Zhao Lian Yun's eyes shone with determination as she prepared herself mentally.

But right at the final part of the tunnel, a change occurred.

A giant ghost face suddenly appeared, obstructing the three Immortal Gu Houses, completely blocking the entire spaceless tunnel.

"What is going on?"

"This is Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's..."

The three rank eight Gu Immortals were still shocked when the ghost face opened its mouth, roaring without emitting a sound.

As it roared, the entire spaceless tunnel started to collapse, countless dao mark fragments of the spaceless tunnel flew everywhere, a terrifying space crack spread out like a spider web.

Crack!

With a loud sound, the Central Continent Gu Immortals found that the tunnel that they were in broke into countless pieces, like a shattered mirror.

"Defend!" Myriad Tidal Dragon shouted.

"Hang on." Bi Chen Tian and Wei Ling Yang activated their Immortal Gu Houses to their limits.

However, even the three Immortal Gu Houses were weak and fragile, as if they were planks facing a tsunami, there was nothing they could do.

At once, the three Immortal Gu Houses which had been together were separated and scattered by the space path chaotic currents.

A giant hole suddenly formed, it was like a huge beast's mouth, devouring everything around it.

Myriad Tidal Dragon controlled Canary Pavilion, he did not even last several breaths of time before this hole devoured it, vanishing without a trace.

Wind Sweeping Building and Edge Link Camp were hanging on desperately, Edge Link Camp was like a bun getting shaved layer after layer by the space path dao mark fragments, Wind Sweeping Building was also breaking apart, the powerful Immortal Gu Houses looked so fragile here.

Spaceless tunnel was Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's immortal killer move, together with Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's methods, there was the power of two Demon Venerables here.

The Central Continent Gu Immortals did not expect that the spaceless tunnel shortcut they were using was a fatal trap!

Three hundred thousand years ago, when the Medieval Antiquity Era's Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable traveled in black heaven, he left behind spaceless tunnel.

Next, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable failed to refine love Gu and left behind many methods.

Then in Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's era, he seemed to have noticed the former's plan, or because of some other reason, he left behind an immortal killer move here as well.

Duke Long did not understand these venerables' secrets, even Fairy Zi Wei could not deduce such a thing.

Right now, the Central Continent Gu Immortals were facing the threat of getting wiped out!

"Am I going to die? Will I die here? No, no! I need to save Hong Yun, how can I die here? Help me, please help me, love Gu!"

Zhao Lian Yun cried out in her heart.

As if sensing her unwavering love and determination, love Immortal Gu started to shine with an immensely bright light in her phantom aperture.

This light spread out with Zhao Lian Yun at the center.

Boom.

Wind Sweeping Building had completely broken apart, the Gu Immortals were screaming loudly, activating their defenses.

But many people did not last for even a few breaths of time before they were cut into pieces by the space path chaotic storm. Only Zhao Lian Yun was covered in a thin layer of light, completely protected.

Not just that, this layer of light was expanding to the four people around her.

A hole formed before Zhao Lian Yun's eyes.

At the next moment, love Gu emitted a strong force and entered the hole with Zhao Lian Yun and the other four Gu Immortals.

Their vision changed.

"Where is this?" Zhao Lian Yun realized that she was standing on firm ground.

"This is naturally Snowy Mountain blessed land." A voice said.

Chapter 1250: Inside and Outside the Formation

"Snowy Mountain blessed land?!" Zhao Lian Yun cried out in surprise.

She raised her head and saw a female Gu Immortal in front of her.

This person was lying on a cloud bed. She wore a silk dress, she had an ordinary appearance but her blue hair was extremely eye-catching, it was like a river that flowed from her head down to the cloud bed and covered the surface.

The female immortal saw that Zhao Lian Yun's emotions were not a facade, and asked, finding it somewhat strange: "It seems you five did not intentionally barge into Snowy Mountain blessed land?"

"Five?" Zhao Lian Yun looked around her, and only then did she find she was in a large hall and she was not alone, there were four of her Gu Immortal companions from earlier.

The four also woke up around the same time.

Zhao Lian Yun had just recently become a Gu Immortal, but she essentially recognized these four Gu Immortal companions.

The most familiar one was Bu Zhen Zi, he was a supreme elder of Spirit Affinity House, a rank seven Gu Immortal who was tasked to protect Zhao Lian Yun.

Yu Yi Ye Zi, this young handsome Gu Immortal came from Ancient Soul Sect, although his cultivation was only rank six, he had a high refinement path attainment and was widely acknowledged for it.

Shi Zheng Yi was similarly a young man, with thick eyebrows and large eyes. He had been at the top floor of Wind Sweeping Building with Zhao Lian Yun just earlier, and although Zhao Lian Yun had not talked with Shi Zheng Yi, she had seen his father who had become blind from the blind fire, this gave her a deep impression.

The final one was someone Zhao Lian Yun did not know and it was the first time she had seen him.

However, Shi Zheng Yi clearly knew this person, he immediately ran to this person's side and greeted: "Senior Mu Ling Lan, how did we appear here?"

This person was Mu Ling Lan, a water path Gu Immortal coming from Spirit Butterfly Valley and having rank seven cultivation.

"I am also baffled. Space suddenly shattered and threw you five out." The female immortal spoke lightly, "Entering Snowy Mountain blessed land without permission, I am still waiting for you people to clear my doubts."

"Snowy Mountain blessed land... this place is Snowy Mountain blessed land?" Shi Zheng Yi called out, he looked outside the window and saw the snowy white world outside, and in the distance were more than ten snowy peaks standing loftily.

At the same time, Shi Zheng Yi discovered he was currently in a hall on one of the snowy peaks.

Central Continent's Gu Immortals quickly reacted.

Bu Zhen Zi ran to Zhao Lian Yun's side, tensely looking at the female immortal before them: "If I am not wrong, you are Snowy Mountain blessed land's ninth peak lord, Hair Mistress!"

"Snowy Mountain blessed land... Hong Yun is here!" Zhao Lian Yun's eyes let out bright light.

The female immortal straightened her upper body, revealing a solemn and nervous expression: "So you really came for Ma Hong Yun!"

"That's right, hand over Ma Hong Yun!" Zhao Lian Yun shouted.

Hair Mistress took a deep glance at Zhao Lian Yun: "Ma Hong Yun is not at my place, if you want to find him, you probably need to charge to the first peak. But that peak has Lady Wan Shou and Old Ancestor Xue Hu staying guard, you five probably won't even be able to make a ripple."

"Where there is a will, there is a way!" Shi Zheng Yi telled with clenched fists.

"Even if I die here, I am going to save Hong Yun!" Zhao Lian Yun was resolute.

Mu Ling Lan took a few steps forward: "Us five are only the first to reach here, there are still rank eight Gu Immortals behind us. Although your Snowy Mountain blessed land has the territorial advantage, you only have one rank eight Gu Immortal in the end."

Mu Ling Lan was bluffing.

In truth, the outcome of the Gu Immortals who remained in the spaceless tunnel bode ill rather than well.

It might be that the only people who were saved were their group of five.

Relying on love Gu's power and under Zhao Lian Yun's obsession, the five Gu Immortals directly arrived at Snowy Mountain blessed land.

Hair Mistress's expression slightly changed, she was only a rank six Gu Immortal, while the group before her had the numerical advantage and there were also two rank sevens present.

Snowy Mountain blessed land had a total of fifteen snowy peaks.

Hair Mistress was at the ninth peak, she had never expected her peace would abruptly be broken, and five Gu Immortals would appear in front of her without any warning.

"I will be the main attacker, the rest of you retreat to the back." Mu Ling Lan secretly transmitted his voice, he shouldered responsibility and stepped forward.

Hair Mistress saw things going awry, quickly stretching her arm: "Wait, we are friends, not enemies."

"What do you mean?" Bu Zhen Zi stopped the eager Mu Ling Lan.

Hair Mistress: "You think I will willingly lay down my life for Old Ancestor Xue Hu? For his own private interests, Old Ancestor Xue Hu forcibly commanded us to gather immortal materials, we have suffered a lot but are helpless in front of Old Ancestor Xue Hu's might."

"As a matter of fact, I had already wanted to surrender and was thinking of when Northern Plains' righteous path Gu Immortals would attack, but I had never expected the ones to come would be all of you from Central Continent."

"I don't want to fight with you, you want to find trouble with Old Ancestor Xue Hu, I welcome you to do so."

"Eh? It was like that..." Bu Zhen Zi and Mu Ling Lan glanced at each other with some doubts.

Hair Mistress continued: "Since you are attacking Snowy Mountain, you must have gathered relevant information. I won't hide from you, there is already discord within the members of Snowy Mountain, Old Ancestor Xue Hu has become crazy in his desire to refine fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu and completely disregarded the feelings of us, the snowy peak lords. Regretfully, we are under his control and cannot rebel, we can only wait for external forces to help us."

Central Continent's five Gu Immortals did not speak, they had not expected such a development.

Mu Ling Lan spoke: "Since you want to surrender, just this information won't be enough. Join our ranks and then we can be sure of your sincerity."

Hair Mistress smiled bitterly: "If I could attack, I would have already rebelled. You do not have to probe, would you believe me even if I joined you? There is not only one way to help you, I am willing to tell you of the defense arrangements of Snowy Mountain."

"Oh? Speak." Mu Ling Lan nodded.

Hair Mistress gazed at the five immortals in front of her, before speaking slowly: "Old Ancestor Xue Hu has recklessly modified Snowy Mountain blessed land to refine fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu, not long ago, he invited Sun Ming Lu to arrange a super Gu formation here."

"This super Gu formation is extremely powerful. With the snowy peak lords as the formation cores, it links to Reverse Flow River. The invaders have to charge through each peak. And the peak lords guarding each snowy peak would receive the Gu formation's amplification; rank six cultivation can display rank seven strength. On the other hand, the charging Gu Immortal would be greatly suppressed. With this contrast of strengthening and weakening, every snowy peak is a difficult hurdle. Even if rank eight Gu Immortals come, unless they can destroy this Gu formation, they will have to spend some time in here."

"How do we know if your information is true or false?" Mu Ling Lan asked.

Hair Mistress smiled bitterly again: "All my words are true, if you don't believe, you can test me."

"Good!" Mu Ling Lan flicked his sleeve, and a wave of water appeared in the air and rushed towards Hair Mistress.

Hair Mistress did not panic, she slightly willed and a strand of hair suddenly sprang up, turning into a dam that blocked the wave.

Mu Ling Lan frowned, he saw through the issue with one attack, and did not make another move.

The other four Central Continent immortals looked at each other.

Just like Hair Mistress said, she could display rank seven battle strength here, while Mu Ling Lan himself was a rank seven Gu Immortal, but his attack was weakened greatly. His powerful offensive method was actually blocked easily by Hair Mistress.

"This Gu formation is too powerful." Shi Zheng Yi exclaimed in shock.

Bu Zhen Zi directly questioned: "Then where is the flaw of this Gu formation?"

Hair Mistress shook her head: "I am not familiar with this Gu formation, but over these days of feeling around, I have some experiences that I can tell all of you."

"First of all, the Gu formation isolates what is inside from outside, you cannot even connect to treasure yellow heaven. Currently, only Old Ancestor Xue Hu can contact us snowy peak lords, while the snowy peak lords cannot communicate with each other."

"Secondly, each snowy peak lord is a formation core of the Gu formation, we can seemingly only defend from our main halls at the peak and are unable to leave our peak. This point is my guess, but it should be pretty accurate."

"Finally... it is time for you guys to die!"

Hair Mistress's expression suddenly changed, her blue hair suddenly rose up to entangle the five Gu Immortals.

Mu Ling Lan was vigilant the whole time, instantly flying out of the hall.

With Bu Zhen Zi's help, Zhao Lian Yun was also able to escape.

Inside the hall, the dense blue hair quickly wrapped around Shi Zheng Yi and Yu Yi Ye Zi, forming two thick blue cocoons.

"Treacherous witch! Attack!!" Mu Ling Lan was alarmed and furious.

Before he spoke, Bu Zhen Zi and Zhao Lian Yun had already attacked.

Rumble...

The ninth snowy peak emitted thunderous noises.

The battle had instantly started.

Eastern Sea.

Dragon breaths that resembled white sword lights shot at the Gu formation, shaking the whole Gu formation.

"Fang Yuan is too careful, he is not entering the Gu formation, what do we do now?" Bai Ning Bing asked Ying Wu Xie.

Ying Wu Xie sighed, transmitting his voice: "I had planned to use this super Gu formation to match against Fang Yuan's upper extreme heavenly eagle, and probe his exact strength. Who could have expected him to only attack from afar, not giving us any opportunity at all."

A concealed sword was the most terrifying.

Fang Yuan naturally could rely on the upper extreme heavenly eagle to move through space and get inside the Gu formation. But if he did so, he would be revealing the fact that his upper extreme heavenly eagle only had rank six power.

How could Fang Yuan reveal his own weakness?

"Although we have the Gu formation's protection and are secure, Fang Yuan has the initiative. He is using a transformation path killer move, while we are using the super Gu formation, our immortal essence is expending at an extremely fast rate." Bai Ning Bing spoke.

Shi Nu requested to battle: "Why don't I go out to battle and lure him in?"

Bai Ning Bing disdainfully sneered: "Fang Yuan is a crafty old scoundrel, how could he be provoked by you and rashly enter the Gu formation?"

Shi Nu furiously glared at Bai Ning Bing: "Then what do you think we should do?"

"Forget it." Ying Wu Xie spoke: "Wait for me to make some arrangements and leave behind a cover to confuse him. We will then quietly use the ancient battle formation Omni-directional Travel to leave this place. As long as we make haste, we will reach Northern Plains and meet with the rank eight Gu Immortal, that would be the time to turn around and deal with Fang Yuan."

Bai Ning Bing's expression was heavy: "You asked me to arrange this Gu formation only to give it up? Forget about the mortal Gu, but you want me to give up the Immortal Gu used in it as well?!"

Chapter 1251: Hair Mistress Battle

"These are just a few Immortal Gu, so what?" Ying Wu Xie spoke in a profound voice, "As long as our plan succeeds, all your losses can be compensated. Being able to let go is the mark of a wise person. Moreover, we are not just abandoning them senselessly, instead we are leaving them behind to confuse the enemy and get some precious time for ourselves."

Bai Ning Bing snorted: "Why do I feel like you are intentionally weakening my strength?"

"You are thinking too much. The enemy is outside, you can also choose to stay behind and personally control this Gu formation to help us delay the enemy." Ying Wu Xie glanced at Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing's eyes flickered with sharp light, before finally nodding: "I shall go with your plan then!"

It was not that she did not want to fight by herself, but facing such a powerful Fang Yuan, she did not have any confidence in winning.

Northern Plains, Snowy Mountain blessed land.

Ninth peak.

Central Continent's group of five immortals were plotted against by Hair Mistress, they were all wrapped around like cocoons by her blue hair.

"What killer move is this?!"

"My immortal essence is rapidly being consumed!"

"Ah!" Yu Yi Ye Zi suddenly shouted, his whole body suddenly burned with bright flames.

But the fire was actually not able to burn the blue hair, instead, large amounts of water vapor emerged from the hair, drenching Yu Yi Ye Zi.

"My fire is earth furnace fire, even melting rank seven Gu material only is a matter of minutes, but it actually cannot burn even a single strand of this hair!" Yu Yi Ye Zi was extremely shocked.

"Hahaha, it is useless. My move is blue hair constriction, the longer the time taken to activate it, the stronger it becomes. Ever since Old Ancestor Xue Hu began refining fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu, I have been activating this immortal killer move without stopping. Just think of it and you will know how long a time it has been."

Hair Mistress lay down on her bed again, laughing heartily.

"Moreover, I did not completely lie to you. Snowy Mountain blessed land is indeed already covered in a super Gu formation, my battle strength has reached rank seven in here, while all of you have been weakened. Surrender obediently and allow yourself to be captured, maybe you will still have a chance for survival."

"Hmph, you are too simpleminded." Right at this time, an illusory shadow flew out of a blue cocoon.

The hair cocoon was not damaged at all, but this phantom figure had strangely passed through the cocoon.

The figure shortly turned from phantom to solid, it was none other than Spirit Affinity House's rank seven Gu Immortal —

Bu Zhen Zi!

Hair Mistress's expression sank: "So there was a phantom path Gu Immortal, no wonder you can escape my blue hair constriction!"

While she spoke, a huge amount of blue hair shot out from the ground, hard as needles, supple as snakes, and shot towards Bu Zhen Zi.

Bu Zhen Zi smiled brightly: "You are still too inexperienced to be able to hurt me."

He again turned into phantom form, this time entering another blue cocoon.

The Gu Immortal inside this cocoon was Zhao Lian Yun.

Right now, she was activating her immortal killer move to guard against the cutting and strangling of the blue hair.

Bu Zhen Zi came to her side suddenly, giving Zhao Lian Yun a fright at first.

"I will count to three, deactivate your defenses and follow me." Bu Zhen Zi put his hand on her shoulder, as he instructed this.

Zhao Lian Yun thought: "If I stop my defensive killer move, would I not be shred into pieces by the blue hair?"

However, she thought again, Bu Zhen Zi would absolutely not deceive her, and decided to believe in him.

At the next moment, she let go of her defense and stopped activating her defensive method, the blue hair immediately moved towards her, but Zhao Lian Yun had already turned into phantom form.

Then, both phantoms rushed out of the blue hair cocoon.

Hair Mistress finally paled with fright.

Bu Zhen Zi cultivated phantom path, it was normal for him to be able to turn into phantom. But it was unusual to be able to turn others into phantom as well, and even being able to affect those he had turned into phantom.

Phantom path Gu Immortals were very few in number, Bu Zhen Zi was no doubt an exceptional talent among them.

It was because of these methods that Spirit Affinity House was confident in him being able to ensure Zhao Lian Yun's safety.

After Bu Zhen Zi rescued Zhao Lian Yun, he repeated the same thing, rescuing the other three.

The five Central Continent Gu Immortals then started to surround and attack Hair Mistress.

However, even with one against five, Hair Mistress was not at a disadvantage.

Blue hair coiled around her whole body, dancing around like snakes and at times, standing up like a wall, as it dissolved all the offenses of the five Gu Immortals.

"She clearly has only rank six cultivation, but actually has rank seven battle strength!"

"I have also found there are indeed traces of a super Gu formation in Snowy Mountain blessed land."

"Get out of my way, let me attack!" Mu Ling Lan moved away from the four immortals, and activated his immortal killer move.

Howl!

Wolf howls resounded, three giant light blue water wolves appeared from thin air and charged towards Hair Mistress while brandishing their teeth and claws.

Hair Mistress's hair wall was broken again and again, and was unable to stop the water wolves' offense. She quickly rose up and broke out of the ceiling into the air.

The five Central Continent Gu Immortals immediately flew up to give chase.

Hair Mistress soon fell into a passive state.

Although her battle strength was rather strong, Zhao Lian Yun's side had the numerical advantage.

Hair Mistress's offense lowered as she started to defend more, most of her blue hair was destroyed, the remainder had curled up into a ball that firmly protected her.

"This immortal killer move is truly terrifying, it can absorb and release energy."

"A portion of our immortal killer moves are absorbed by it and released back against us."

"Even my snake wave stab cannot pierce through this hair ball." Mu Ling Lan was solemn.

Bu Zhen Zi suddenly transmitted his voice to Mu Ling Lan.

Mu Ling Lan's expression shook: "Let's try again then."

He accumulated energy for a while before suddenly pointing out his right index finger towards the continuously revolving blue hair ball.

At the next moment, a water snake half a foot long flew out from his fingernail.

The small snake was lifelike, completely formed from water and was deep blue in color.

The water snake was extremely fast, but right now, under Mu Ling Lan's control, it intentionally flew slowly.

At this moment, Bu Zhen Zi suddenly used his immortal killer move, turning the water snake into phantom, the water snake was easily able to pass through the hair ball and appeared in front of Hair Mistress.

Hair Mistress turned pale from the shock, quickly activating her second defensive killer move.

But the water snake turned into solid, breaking open Hair Mistress's defense and piercing straight into her heart.

Hair Mistress gave a sharp screech as her soul escaped out of her body.

The hair ball detonated, a huge number of short hairs shot out everywhere like sharp arrows.

Central Continent's five immortals could only concentrate on defending themselves, and let Hair Mistress' soul escape.

"We won! Hair Mistress is dead, only her soul is left now." Shi Zheng Yi was extremely excited.

"Good teamwork." Bu Zhen Zi and Mu Ling Lan looked at each other and smiled.

These two rank seven Gu Immortals had made the biggest contributions in defeating Hair Mistress. First, Bu Zhen Zi rescued them from the cocoons, then Mu Ling Lan was the main attacker. Yu Yi Ye Zi, Zhao Lian Yun and Shi Zheng Yi were only supporting figures.

The battle ended, the ninth peak turned silent.

What should they do next?

The five immortals discussed and soon came to a consensus.

They would first retreat and wait for the other forces from Central Continent to arrive!

With just the five of them, how could they go against the whole of Snowy Mountain? Forget about other Gu Immortals, just Old Ancestor Xue Hu alone was an opponent they could not beat.

However, the five immortals found they were unable to leave this place.

Snowy Mountain blessed land was a public blessed land, the whole blessed land was pieced together, its defense could not compare to a normal blessed land. But there was a super Gu formation arranged here, even Bu Zhen Zi's phantom transformation method was of no use.

"Damn it, we don't have a formation path Gu Immortal among us. If we had a formation path great expert, maybe we could decipher the profundities of this Gu formation." Mu Ling Lan wrung his hands in disappointment.

There had been multiple formation path Gu Immortals specially mixed in among the Central Continent Gu Immortals sent. Unfortunately, because of the unexpected collapse of the spaceless tunnel, not even one formation path Gu Immortal was among this group of five.

The five Central Continent immortals helplessly found that even though they defeated Hair Mistress, her soul escaped, while they were trapped in the ninth snowy peak, unable to escape from this super Gu formation.

"What should we do?" They looked at each other, feeling great pressure.

How could they not feel pressure?

This was the enemy's base.

The rank eight Gu Immortal Old Ancestor Xue Hu could crush them with just his fingers.

"Did you all find something strange? We have already been here in Snowy Mountain blessed land for a while now, but no one has actually come." Yu Yi Ye Zi suddenly spoke.

The other four immortals had the same feeling.

"It is indeed strange. We have invaded Snowy Mountain blessed land and battled Hair Mistress, the commotion was huge, but besides Hair Mistress, no one else has appeared."

"Our fight with Hair Mistress was not a short one, but no other Gu Immortals came to reinforce her."

"Old Ancestor Xue Hu did not appear, it could be because of a rank eight's pride. But the other Gu Immortals should have allied and besieged us, there is no way they are holding back now!"

Mu Ling Lan, Bu Zhen Zi and Yu Yi Ye Zi pondered over this, and felt it was odd.

Right at this time, inside Zhao Lian Yun's immortal aperture, love Gu suddenly activated, a powerful Immortal Gu aura rose from Zhao Lian Yun's body.

Such a majestic aura caused the other four immortals' expression to change.

"What a powerful aura! Is it a rank nine Immortal Gu?"

"I remember this aura appeared in the spaceless tunnel as well."

"So it was you who protected us!"

Mu Ling Lan, Yu Yi Ye Zi and Shi Zheng Yi stared at Zhao Lian Yun, dumbfounded.

Zhao Lian Yun, however, did not have control over her body, her eyes had rolled back, showing her whites, her legs were a foot above the ground, her head was slightly raised, and she was emitting chuckling sounds.

"Don't disturb her, this is love Gu's power." Bu Zhen Zi quickly spoke.

"Love Gu?!"

"Spirit Affinity House's signature Immortal Gu was actually brought here by Zhao Lian Yun?!"

The other three immortals were extremely shocked.

Bu Zhen Zi smiled bitterly, as he explained to them.

After a while, Zhao Lian Yun woke up: "I know all the secrets of this Gu formation now!"

The four immortals were joyous.

"This was because of love Gu?" Mu Ling Lan's eyes were wide open.

Zhao Lian Yun nodded.

"Quickly explain it to us." Bu Zhen Zi urged.

Chapter 1252: Fate Reversing Sacrificial Refinement Formation

"This formation is called fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation. It was set up by Sun Ming Lu, using over ten Immortal Gu, the crucial point is it irrigates the water of Reverse Flow River, thus it has extremely astonishing power!"

Zhao Lian Yun explained in a heavy voice.

Love Immortal Gu had activated of its own accord, using up large amounts of immortal essence in Zhao Lian Yun's immortal aperture, it had all sorts of effects, and this time, it had let Zhao Lian Yun directly obtain the origins and history of the fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation.

"Reverse Flow River? That legendary Reverse Flow River?" Yu Yi Ye Zi's eyes opened wide.

"Right, it is the Reverse Flow River recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>." Zhao Lian Yun nodded.

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> stated, Dang Hun Mountain, Luo Po Valley and Reverse Flow River were the three obstacles inside the door of life and death. Back then, to save his eldest son, Verdant Great Sun, Ren Zu had traveled to Obsession Death Domain but had failed. Ren Zu could only pass through the three obstacles, to revive once again.

In the end, Ren Zu had passed Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley, but had failed in Reverse Flow River.

"Reverse Flow River is a secluded domain of heaven and earth, who could have thought it was in Old Ancestor Xue Hu's hands." Bu Zhen Zi sighed.

Mu Ling Lan spoke: "Supposedly, in the past, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had relied on ghostly concealment to enter the door of life and death, and moved Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley out, but was unable to take Reverse Flow River. I never expected Reverse Flow River to be taken by someone as well."

Mu Ling Lan was a supreme elder of Spirit Butterfly Valley, this ancient sect was most skilled in information gathering, so Mu Ling Lan knew many secrets.

This group of immortals soon accepted this fact.

Since Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley could be taken away, it was not that strange for Reverse Flow River to appear as well.

"The main thing now is how to break this fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation." Bu Zhen Zi emphasized.

But Zhao Lian Yun shook her head: "It is almost impossible to break this formation. Even a rank eight Gu Immortal will be trapped and not be able to extricate themselves. Although there are no rank eight Immortal Gu used in this super Gu formation, this super Gu formation perfectly utilizes Reverse Flow River, which allows it to display endless might."

Zhao Lian Yun explained slowly while the other four immortals listened speechlessly, no longer having the intention to break the formation.

This super Gu formation has completely remodeled Snowy Mountain blessed land, using the fifteen snowy peaks as the formation cores to form a solid defense.

If a Gu Immortal charges into the formation, they would be forcibly sent to different snowy peaks depending on their cultivation.

If it was a rank seven Gu Immortal, they would be sent to the snowy peaks with rank seven Gu Immortals to fight.

If it was a rank eight Gu Immortal, they would be sent to Old Ancestor Xue Hu.

Hair Mistress' words had some truth and some lies, and were not completely nonsense.

The fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation could indeed amplify the strength of the Gu Immortal in the formation cores. It could let rank six Gu Immortals have rank seven might, and while it could not let rank seven Gu Immortals have rank eight strength, there would still be a tremendous boost.

Moreover, this fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation also imitated Regret Pool, having some mysterious abilities of time path.

The truly wicked thing was any Gu Immortals that died within the formation would be considered as sacrificing their life to this formation, helping Lady Wan Shou, who was in the center of the formation, refine Ma Hong Yun.

"No wonder when we killed Hair Mistress, her body and immortal aperture turned into ashes and disappeared."

"Although her soul escaped, her soul must have already dispersed completely due to this formation."

"Who could have thought Sun Ming Lu could actually construct such a level of super Gu formation? Such a powerful formation, even the ten great ancient sects might not be able to match it."

"Sun Ming Lu is Northern Plains' publicly recognized number one formation path grandmaster. According to rumors, he has an unyielding nature and highly values ties of friendship. He did not associate himself with the demonic path. Earlier, Old Ancestor Xue Hu had put down his pride and invited him repeatedly, but Sun Ming Lu did not yield to such an expert. In the end, he was touched by Old Ancestor Xue Hu's love for Lady Wan Shou, and helped Lady Wan Shou construct a refinement path Gu formation. But from the looks of it now, creating such a wicked refinement path Gu formation, this Sun Ming Lu is not a good person."

The Central Continent Gu Immortals discussed.

"That means, if we go out of this snowy peak, we will be forcefully separated and have to fend for ourselves?" Bu Zhen Zi asked.

Zhao Lian Yun nodded: "It should be the case. We appeared here because of love Immortal Gu's strength."

Love Gu was a rank nine Immortal Gu, its might surpassed the whole super Gu formation, so it could make the five Gu Immortals appear at the ninth snowy peak together.

However, right now, love Gu did not activate, this group of five would be separated by the Gu formation once they stepped out of the range of this snowy peak.

Bu Zhen Zi frowned deeply. This was extremely bad news.

He was given the task to escort Zhao Lian Yun, to protect Zhao Lian Yun as well as love Gu. But now, this super Gu formation would separate them, and there was nothing he could do.

"How about this, Fairy Lian Yun, enter my immortal aperture. I don't believe this super Gu formation can influence my immortal aperture?" Bu Zhen Zi hesitated before making up his mind.

The immortal aperture of a Gu Immortal was their greatest secret, and normally they would not let others enter.

However, Bu Zhen Zi knew the significance of this matter and decided to make a sacrifice, letting Zhao Lian Yun in.

They could only do this.

Because Zhao Lian Yun did not have a true immortal aperture, hers was a phantom aperture. Heavenly Court's phantom aperture had advantages as well as disadvantages. A disadvantage was that it could only store immortal essence, Gu worms and will, but could not be managed and developed like normal immortal apertures. It also had to be replenished at set intervals of time and could not last forever. An advantage was that it could store Immortal Gu of any rank, just like Zhao Lian Yun currently could store love Gu, and not have to worry about this rank nine Immortal Gu bursting the immortal aperture.

However, after attempting it, Central Continent's Gu Immortals found that they could not even open the entrance to their immortal apertures.

Clearly, Sun Ming Lu had considered this issue when he constructed this super Gu formation. This flaw was not in the Gu formation.

The Gu Immortals fell into an awkward situation.

They had gotten rid of Hair Mistress, but they themselves were trapped here.

But there was good news, they did not need to worry about any reinforcements or the rank eight Old Ancestor Xue Hu making a move against them.

Because in this super Gu formation, each snowy peak lord guarded one peak, and could not leave it. Any rank eight Gu Immortals whom invaded Snowy Mountain blessed land could not fight rank six or rank seven snowy peak lords, and could only fight Old Ancestor Xue Hu.

This rule restricted Old Ancestor Xue Hu as well.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu could not make things difficult for rank six and rank seven invaders.

The reason for this rule came from Reverse Flow River.

Humans aspired to move up the social ladder, while water flowed downwards due to gravity.

These were rules of the world.

With rank eight as the high point, and rank seven and rank six as the low, the higher ranked Gu Immortals could only look for those of similar level or fight with stronger Gu Immortals.

In the whole Gu formation, the first snowy peak was the highest point, the invaders must move on to other peaks and could not leave.

This was the might of Reverse Flow River.

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> recorded that even Ren Zu was not able to successfully emerge from the river.

But this Reverse Flow River was, after all, only a secluded domain of heaven and earth. Sun Ming Lu used the plentiful dao marks in this secluded domain to create the fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation.

And as the main parts of the formation, Old Ancestor Xue Hu and the snowy peak lords were also unable to go against this rule.

If it was not Reverse Flow River, and was one or more other Immortal Gu, the Gu Immortals could control the formation by themselves and create an environment favorable to themselves, instead of being in such a rigid situation like now.

But regardless, even though there was this flaw, Snowy Mountain blessed land was a solid fortress, easy to defend but hard to attack. With this Gu formation helping him, it was no wonder that Old Ancestor Xue Hu felt extremely confident and did not hide the commotion of refining fortune rivaling heaven Gu.

Even if he wanted to hide it, he might not necessarily be able to. The crucial thing was that he was not afraid of Gu Immortals attacking. Instead, he was even waiting for them, because the Gu Immortals who died in the Gu formation, whether it be enemies or his own side, they would turn into fuel which would help him refine fortune rivalling heaven Gu!

"Since that is the case, we might as well stay here and wait for the response from our reinforcements." Bu Zhen Zi suggested.

This suggestion was approved by the other Central Continent Gu Immortals.

They were now familiar with the details of this Gu formation, but it was not of much use.

Zhao Lian Yun frowned, but she did not argue. After all, Ma Hong Yun was at the first peak, that was the center of the Gu formation, used to refine Gu. Even if Zhao Lian Yun and the group charged through the many snowy peaks and reached the first peak, they would have to face the rank eight Gu Immortal Old Ancestor Xue Hu.

Black heaven, Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace.

"We have discovered a small group." South Desolation Immortal breathed out deeply.

"Ah? Where?" Yao Huang asked.

"They actually ran right inside Snowy Mountain blessed land. Strange..." South Desolation Immortal was uncertain.

Although he knew Central Continent Gu Immortals had entered the spaceless tunnel, he was not aware that an unexpected mishap had occurred in the spaceless tunnel.

He had thought he could find the majority of Central Continent's forces, but he only discovered a small group.

However, this discovery included Zhao Lian Yun, an important person.

Love Immortal Gu.

The reason South Desolation Immortal woke up was due to this.

"Snowy Mountain blessed land." Yao Huang frowned, "Not all the Central Continent Gu Immortals have appeared?"

South Desolation Immortal shook his head: "Maybe this is their plan of luring enemies, but whether it be rank eight Gu Immortals or Immortal Gu Houses, there are none of them."

Yao Huang's frown became deeper.

Just like when Fang Yuan confronted Ying Wu Xie, he did not take out the upper extreme heavenly eagle, but it had instead caused Ying Wu Xie to be even more apprehensive.

The situation of Yao Huang and South Desolation Immortal was largely similar.

If the Central Continent Gu Immortals had all appeared, they would be able to use all their strength to deal with them.

However, only five people appeared, which instead caused South Desolation Immortal and Yao Huang to not understand what the Central Continent Gu Immortals were planning.

Was this some kind of sinister plot? Are they brewing some special plan?

South Desolation Immortal thought about it before deciding: "Let this group of Central Continent Gu Immortals fight with Snowy Mountain blessed land first. The important thing is still the larger portion of the Central Continent group. Until this larger portion appears, we will just watch the events from the side."

"Okay." Yao Huang nodded, but was guessing inwardly: "Lord South Desolation is aware about the situation inside Snowy Mountain blessed land. This is not Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace's ability, does our side have an insider in Snowy Mountain blessed land?"

Chapter 1253: Courting Death

Eastern Sea.

The sword dragon kept on breathing out sword light.

Rays of white dragon breath struck the Gu formation, causing the Gu formation to truly sway.

"Something is not right. Ying Wu Xie and the others are not fools, their immortal essence expenditure while activating the super Gu formation is far greater than mine. But they are actually maintaining the stalemate without retreating and letting me attack, do they have some other plan?"

Fang Yuan was attacking furiously, although he was not able to break the formation, he firmly held the initiative. Thoughts were surging in his mind and had not stopped even for a second.

"They should know I have the upper extreme heavenly eagle. Are they not afraid of me using the upper extreme heavenly eagle to penetrate space and enter the formation? Or is this Gu formation a trap to deal with my upper extreme heavenly eagle?"

"Or could it be that Sixth Hair has already learned from Lang Ya land spirit that my upper extreme heavenly eagle is only an egg, thus they are not afraid?"

"Wait."

Fang Yuan suddenly stopped attacking, and dived inside the sea.

While under the sea, he waited for a reaction from Ying Wu Xie's group while activating an immortal killer move.

Qi luck sensation.

"They are indeed all inside the Gu formation." Fang Yuan relaxed: "It seems I was thinking too much."

Fang Yuan continued to attack the Gu formation, but he gradually discovered the Gu formation was only passively defending and there were no signs of Ying Wu Xie, Bai Ning Bing or the rest.

Fang Yuan suddenly had a thought and stopped attacking again.

Right now, he was holding the initiative, and he could choose freely whether to attack or not. On the other hand, the enemy was defending and in a very passive situation, not knowing when Fang Yuan would attack, and they had to maintain the Gu formation all the time, which consumed their immortal essence.

Fang Yuan stopped his offenses and besides maintaining the sword dragon transformation, he did not need to use up any immortal essence, thus his expenditure was even lesser.

The silent confrontation lasted for an hour, Fang Yuan gradually realized the fishy situation.

The Gu formation was like a deep pool, and no commotion was visible inside. The enemy was actually firmly deciding on maintaining this stalemate with Fang Yuan.

"Ying Wu Xie seems to have some other motive that requires the safe environment created by the Gu formation. No matter what, I cannot let him continue smoothly, I should quickly take action and destroy the formation. It seems I can't continue to hide this trump card, I need to use it early!"

Ying Wu Xie's plan had come into effect and Fang Yuan's qi luck sensation was misled.

But Fang Yuan still had sharp judgment regarding the situation, he firmly acted without hiding any trump cards.

If it was earlier, dragon breath would be his strongest weapon, but it was different now.

At the next moment, a dragon roar resounded over an enormous surrounding distance!

Ancient battle formation — Omni-directional Travel.

Ying Wu Xie's vision suddenly changed, and when his vision was stable, he was already at the regional wall.

This was Eastern Sea's blue water regional wall, it was deep blue, and was like a giant screen that connected heaven and earth, expansive and boundless. The four Gu Immortals (Tai Bai Yun Sheng had entered Hei Lou Lan's immortal aperture) standing in front of the vast and mighty regional wall were as small as ants.

Once they entered, the ancient battle formation could not be used and they could only move by themselves.

Because using Gu worms or immortal killer moves in the regional wall would shake their immortal apertures, the ancient battle formation would cause this even more and the backlash would be extremely big.

Just as they were looking at the regional wall, Ying Wu Xie's expression changed, Bai Ning Bing also subconsciously looked back, her eyes letting out sharp light as she stared at the direction they came from.

"The Gu formation has been broken." Bai Ning Bing spoke in a heavy voice.

"So quickly?!" Hei Lou Lan was also moved.

She thought of when she was trapped, and compared it to how quickly Fang Yuan had broken the formation. Even if she was inside and he was outside, it clearly showed his terrifying battle strength.

"Did he use the upper extreme heavenly eagle?" Hei Lou Lan quickly thought of a possibility.

"No." Bai Ning Bing shook her head.

Fang Yuan had broken the Gu formation, but did not discover anybody and was not able to obtain any Gu worms. Once the Gu formation was broken, the Gu worms would all self-detonate, how could Bai Ning Bing leave behind resources for the enemy?

Although the losses were huge, the scene when Fang Yuan attacked had been shown to them.

In a battle between Gu Immortals, information was a crucial and very important factor.

Bai Ning Bing, Ying Wu Xie and the group naturally would not let go of such a good opportunity to gather information.

"Fang Yuan used a completely new killer move, it is probably a recent creation of his." Ying Wu Xie spoke.

"This killer move is terrifyingly powerful." Bai Ning Bing's expression was heavy: "Unless we have a method which targets it, we won't be able to last a few breaths of time even if we combine our strengths."

"What?!" Hei Lou Lan took a sharp breath, even the silent and expressionless Shi Nu was visibly terrified.

Ying Wu Xie knew the situation was far from good, he had arranged the formation and planned to delay for time.

Although his plan succeeded, he had not expected it to delay him for just such a short period of time.

They would have to spend some time in passing the regional wall.

The crucial thing was that the nature of the sovereign immortal body made it so that the sovereign immortal body could travel through regional walls freely without any restriction. Ying Wu Xie naturally already knew about this.

"The super Gu formation was forcefully broken, Fang Yuan has discovered we are not there. He will definitely use qi luck sensation again and search for us. If we enter the regional wall, even if I consider the best case scenario, according to Fang Yuan's previous speed, he will certainly be able to catch up to us. We would then have to fight with him inside the regional wall. So, should I not enter this regional wall?"

Ying Wu Xie began to let out cold sweat, his heart felt like it was pressed under an enormous weight.

Ying Wu Xie judged the situation, he clearly knew his side was already on the brink of life and death, even though they were not under attack right now, if they did not handle the following situation properly, they would be in danger of dying!

And whether they could get out of this danger or not would depend on his plan.

The heavy pressure weighed down on Ying Wu Xie's shoulders. This did not concern only his survival, it also concerned the Gu Immortals beside him.

Alright, Ying Wu Xie did not care about the safety of the Gu Immortals beside him, he did not even fear his own death. But if he died, who would save the Demon Venerable's main body? Shadow Sect was in ruins currently, he was the only hope left!

"How could this be? How could Fang Yuan's battle strength rise to such a level in such a short time?"

"He cannot even use wisdom Gu, how did he make deductions? Could it be that he gained some powerful wisdom path methods?"

Deducing immortal killer moves could not be done in a matter of days. Fang Yuan's trump card was too abrupt, catching Ying Wu Xie off-guard.

"I have already used up the method to confuse the enemy, if we enter the regional wall, we will definitely have to fight Fang Yuan. Our side is at a great disadvantage!" Ying Wu Xie was very clear on this, using immortal killer moves in the regional wall would cause backlash, but Fang Yuan did not have such a restriction.

The five regional walls were the perfect places for him to fight! Even rank eight Gu Immortals might be in a bad situation. Because when rank eights entered the regional walls, they would face much more restriction than rank sixes or rank sevens.

Naturally, rank eight Gu Immortals moved through black heaven or white heaven, and would not stupidly travel to and fro through the regional walls.

If Ying Wu Xie persisted on entering the regional wall, undoubtedly, he would be taking a huge risk. Fang Yuan had shown his trump card, even without counting the upper extreme heavenly eagle, just this trump card alone made Ying Wu Xie feel he could not go against Fang Yuan..

"No, there is still Bai Ning Bing." Ying Wu Xie suddenly had a thought, secretly glancing at Bai Ning Bing.

He immediately felt the alliance was an extremely good decision. At the same time, he also felt some emotions, who could have thought he would actually have to rely on Bai Ning Bing's strength at this moment.

This was truly, what goes around comes around, the trajectory of fate had countless changes, he, the grand Ying Wu Xie, would actually have to rely on Bai Ning Bing, who had been arranged as a pawn before!

"But how much strength does Bai Ning Bing have? It has not been long since she inherited Bai Xiang grotto-heaven." Ying Wu Xie did not have much confidence as he thought on it.

He then thought: "But if don't enter the regional wall now, we can only wander around in Eastern Sea, Omni-directional Travel is also not a method that can be used repeatedly and requires some time before it can be used again. If so, we will sooner or later be found by Fang Yuan."

"More importantly, this is Eastern Sea. All the Gu Immortals on my side are of other regions!'

Ying Wu Xie's physical body was a Western Desert immortal zombie, Bai Ning Bing was a Southern Border Gu Immortal, Tai Bai Yun Sheng and Hei Lou Lan were from Northern Plains, and Shi Nu was from Central Continent. There was not one Eastern Sea Gu Immortal.

Foreign region Gu Immortals would be marginalized in other regions and even be hunted. Although this was not too common in Eastern Sea, one should not forget that Fang Yuan was an Eastern Sea Gu Immortal.

Sovereign immortal body!

It could completely blend into any region and become a Gu Immortal of that region.

When the time comes in which both sides battle, and Eastern Sea Gu Immortals appear, and Fang Yuan had the upper hand, it goes without saying that the Eastern Sea Gu Immortals would help Fang Yuan.

Few people would provide help when one desperately needed it, but there were many who would add fuel to the fire.

"So if we stay in Eastern Sea, we might not only be facing Fang Yuan, but other Eastern Sea Gu Immortals as well." Ying Wu Xie smiled bitterly.

After experiencing many setbacks, he had matured immeasurably. Thinking through all elements comprehensively, it was incomparable to the past.

"Moreover, Fang Yuan still has the upper extreme heavenly eagle."

"We must go to Northern Plains! Snowy Mountain blessed land is our only hope. We can use the rank eight Gu Immortal to kill him."

After considering everything, Ying Wu Xie finally made a firm resolution and flew straight into the regional wall.

Several hours later, a sword dragon flew over from far away.

"Trying to enter Northern Plains?" This sword dragon was Fang Yuan's transformation.

Everything was like Ying Wu Xie expected, after he broke the Gu formation, he did not discover any trace of Ying Wu Xie and the rest.

How would Fang Yuan not understand that the other side had made a ploy to escape, fortunately, he had not hesitated to expose his trump card and forcibly destroyed the Gu formation, otherwise, he would still be in the dark.

"It seems that although qi luck sensation can detect the target, it can also be misled."

"Then this target I am sensing, will it also be false?"

If it was false, Fang Yuan could do nothing about it, after all, this was his only clue.

But if it was real...

Hehe.

"I can get rid of you all in the regional wall. All of you are actually traveling in the regional wall in front of me, you are courting death!"

Chapter 1254: Love Becomes The Problem

Waiting was often long and difficult to endure.

Shi Zheng Yi was unable to sit still, pacing back and forth in the large hall.

Yu Yi Ye Zi was sitting cross-legged on the ground with his eyes closed, he spoke with dissatisfaction: "Can't you rest properly, don't move back and forth."

Shi Zheng Yi yelled: "I have already rested enough, sigh, how long do we have to wait?"

"Until the other group arrives." Bu Zhen Zi spoke.

"If they don't come, do we continue waiting forever?" Zhao Lian Yun frowned, she was also somewhat impatient.

When fighting with Hair Mistress, the five immortals were all wholeheartedly focused and did not feel anything. Now that they were cooped up in here, every second became unbearable.

Zhao Lian Yun was feeling even worse, like a fire was burning her heart.

Bu Zhen Zi frowned and was about to speak.

But at this moment, Zhao Lian Yun spoke again: "You must have some thoughts. All of you have seen and even personally gone through the final moment in the spaceless tunnel. Do you think that perhaps the other Gu Immortals have died there?"

"Impossible!" Shi Zheng Yi was the first to refute it, as he glared at Zhao Lian Yun with anger.

His father, Shi Ge, was among those Gu Immortals. Zhao Lian Yun's words were like predicting his father's death.

Zhao Lian Yun ignored Shi Zheng Yi's attitude, continuing: "You are all aware that we came here because of love Gu's power. But the other Gu Immortals did not get such help. Even the Immortal Gu Houses were on the verge of destruction at that time, let alone Gu Immortals. If there are no reinforcements, how long do we wait for?"

The other Gu Immortals had slight changes in their expressions. They actually had such worries, but it was just that they did not take the initiative to speak up.

Now, Zhao Lian Yun had brought up this topic, Bu Zhen Zi thought and spoke in a deep voice: "Your speculation is not impossible. But even if there are no reinforcements, Central Continent's ten great ancient sects will send a second group of Gu Immortals."

Zhao Lian Yun continued: "The can the second group of reinforcements reach here? You have all experienced the difficulties and dangers we faced on our way. Can spaceless tunnel still be used a second time? Even if it can be used, can we be at ease using it again?"

Bu Zhen Zi firmly stared at Zhao Lian Yun's eyes, and spoke solemnly: "You need to believe in our sect, Zhao Lian Yun, you are Spirit Affinity House's fairy, the sect is your biggest backer. If you don't believe in even the sect, who can you trust?"

Zhao Lian Yun sharply sensed Bu Zhen Zi's displeasure.

But she disregarded it, and continued: "Even if the sect sends reinforcements and they reach here, what about the time? When will they arrive here? What price will they have to pay? Will there be mishaps again? This is Northern Plains, not Central Continent."

Bu Zhen Zi was silent.

He was unable to retort to Zhao Lian Yun's words.

Zhao Lian Yun let out a breath of air: "In short, I don't want to wait any longer."

"You have to wait even if you don't want to." Bu Zhen Zi frowned in anger.

He stared at Zhao Lian Yun, both did not retreat and were fixated on their own stance.

Zhao Lian Yun's eyes were soon filled with mist, she moved her sight and looked the other way: "If, during this time, Hong Yun is killed, what would we do? Can you make a guarantee?"

In truth, Zhao Lian Yun was feeling more and more afraid as she waited.

What she was afraid of was not her own safety.

Instead, under the situation where the reinforcements were far away, waiting could not solve the problem.

If during this time, Ma Hong Yun was harmed by Old Ancestor Xue Hu and successfully used as a Gu material to refine fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu, this would be Zhao Lian Yun's lifetime regret.

In the future, when she recalled it, she would be filled with extreme regret!

Regret that she had once been so close to Ma Hong Yun, charging into Snowy Mountain blessed land, and fate gave her a perfect opportunity but she did not take it.

The blurry view of the first peak could be seen from the ninth peak. It was such a short distance, but she just kept on waiting here, losing the final chance.

Zhao Lian Yun did not want to see such a thing happening, that result would make her feel sadness and pain that was worse than death!

The other three immortals did not find it convenient to meddle in the quarrel between Zhao Lian Yun and Bu Zhen Zi, after all, it was Spirit Affinity House's internal matter.

Bu Zhen Zi retorted: "Even if you don't want to wait, can you save Ma Hong Yun? Even if you are able to defeat other snowy peak lords, don't forget that you will have to face Old Ancestor Xue Hu in the end because Ma Hong Yun is kept at the first peak!"

"I know." Zhao Lian Yun clenched her fists, her voice becoming sharper, "But you said as well that before Old Ancestor Xue Hu, we will have to deal with the other ten or so snowy peak lords. We can get rid of them first, in any case, rank eight Gu Immortals cannot act against us in this Gu formation! With this, once our reinforcements arrive, we can directly attack the first peak, saving time and energy."

Bu Zhen Zi was furious, his expression turning dark: "Then I will speak frankly, this super Gu formation amplifies the enemy's power while weakening us. If we leave this place, we will be forcefully separated by the formation and transported to other snowy peaks. Will each of you be able to fight them alone? In the previous battle, Mu Ling Lan and I led the main attack, what help can you three rank sixes bring?"

Bu Zhen Zi spoke bluntly, but the three rank six Gu Immortals were not able to retort because what he said was a fact.

Zhao Lian Yun lowered her head in silence for a while, before she raised her head and said: "Then I am going to use love Gu again!"

Bu Zhen Zi scoffed: "Who do you think you are? Will Love Gu listen to you and allow you to control it? Back then, even Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was not able to refine love Gu."

"That is because he did not receive the acknowledgement of love Gu." Zhao Lian Yun retorted.

"So what you are saying is that all the other fairies of Spirit Affinity House were useless? Not even one of them was able to control love Gu?" Bu Zhen Zi sneered.

"How would I know without trying?" Zhao Lian Yun was persistent.

Bu Zhen Zi laughed, and was just about to speak when Zhao Lian Yun had already taken action, she called out in her heart: "Love Gu, oh love Gu, please display your might, take the five of us to another snowy peak!"

Love Gu did not even budge, as if it was dead.

Zhao Lian Yun was unwilling to give up, she continued to pray and beg in her heart.

Bu Zhen Zi noticed Zhao Lian Yun's stillness, and was about to speak, but right at this moment, love Gu's aura rose from Zhao Lian Yun's body and, at the same time, bright radiance covered Zhao Lian Yun.

The other four immortals were extremely shocked, all of their eyes were wide open as they stared fixedly at this sight.

Mu Ling Lan could not help but say: "This... it seems like the time when we left spaceless tunnel and appeared at Snowy Mountain blessed land, it was this aura and also the light."

"Continue, don't stop." Shi Zheng Yi urged.

At the next moment, the light moving around Zhao Lian Yun seemed to act on its own, as it spread towards the other four Gu Immortals.

"Like this, we can charge our way towards the other snowy peaks. Ah! Maybe it can directly take us out of Snowy Mountain blessed land." Shi Zheng Yi was hopeful.

Bu Zhen Zi's mouth was wide open, unable to say a word at this moment.

The shock he felt was much more intense than the others.

"Love Gu cannot be controlled, this is absolutely true from history! Even Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was left without options. But why? Why!"

"Why is love Gu so obedient in Zhao Lian Yun's hands?"

"Could it be that Zhao Lian Yun is the strongest fairy in the whole history of Spirit Affinity House?!"

"No, it is more likely because of her status. She is an otherworldly demon, could it be that otherworldly demons and love Gu complement each other? Others cannot control love Gu, but an otherworldly demon is an exception?"

Countless thoughts welled up in Bu Zhen Zi's mind, like surging waves in the sea.

While he was thinking, the space behind him suddenly ruptured and turned into a fist sized black hole. The black hole let out an unimaginable suction force, forcibly dragging in Bu Zhen Zi!

A person as strong as Bu Zhen Zi, a rank seven Gu Immortal, was unable to do anything and was directly dragged in, disappearing from the spot.

At the same time, the same thing happened to other Gu Immortals. In the blink of an eye, this large hall was empty and silent.

"We have left the ninth snowy peak!" Bu Zhen Zi held feelings of shock, as he sized up his surroundings the moment his feet landed on solid ground.

This was similarly inside a large hall. But this hall was different from the previous one, the previous hall was decorated and beautiful, and seemingly emitted feminine aura, while this hall was majestic and grand, with a masculine air emanating from it.

"Which snowy peak is this?" Bu Zhen Zi had this thought.

But shortly afterwards, his expression suddenly changed, as he shouted: "Damn it!"

He found that he was the only one in the whole hall. The other four Gu Immortals were nowhere to be seen.

He sobered himself up: Looks like I was overthinking it. Zhao Lian Yun might be an otherworldly demon, but how can she control love Gu? Love Gu is still unreliable and has countless abilities, who knows when it will act up.

"I was sent here, what about the others? Where are they? It would be best if they were together, Zhao Lian Yun would be slightly more safe then. But if Zhao Lian Yun is alone..."

Bu Zhen Zi did not dare to continue thinking.

Right at this time, an inky black shadow crept near him from the ground and silently attacked him.

Bu Zhen Zi's instincts set off warning signs, he quickly jumped back and dodged.

But the shadow was like a viper, extremely fast, and within a breath of time, it had pounced towards Bu Zhen Zi's feet.

Turn phantom!

At the crucial moment, Bu Zhen Zi used his specialty as a phantom path Gu Immortal, turning into phantom form.

The shadow helplessly passed through him, reaching behind Bu Zhen Zi.

Chapter 1255: Zhao Lian Yun's Death?

Clap clap clap.

A series of claps could be heard.

"It is indeed phantom path." A Gu Immortal showed himself.

This person was tall and well-built, with residues of a beard on his face, his eyes had no white color, being completely black. The most eye-catching thing was he had a skin-like black cloak draping behind him.

Bu Zhen Zi's pupils shrunk slightly as he recognized this person. Since the Central Continent Gu Immortals had come to save Ma Hong Yun, how could they not have information on Snowy Mountain blessed land?

"So it is Shadow King." Bu Zhen Zi lightly spoke, pointing out the other Gu Immortal's identity.

At the same time, he also realized he was now at the seventh peak of Snowy Mountain blessed land.

Previously, this seventh peak's owner had been Xue Song Zi.

However, after Xue Song Zi died, a demonic path Gu Immortal joined of his own accord, and it was this person.

In fact, Snowy Mountain blessed land was a place which Northern Plains' demonic path Gu Immortals were attracted towards, especially those demons who were wanted by Huang Jin tribes, needing to find a reliable backer like Old Ancestor Xue Hu. Perhaps there were also some Gu Immortals, wanting to prolong their lives, who joined Snowy Mountain blessed land because of Lady Wan Shou.

Naturally, because Old Ancestor Xue Hu was refining fortune rivalling heaven Gu, it caused the morale of the members of Snowy Mountain blessed land to drop.

Shadow King looked at Bu Zhen Zi, and laughed: "You guys from Central Continent truly came running into death."

"It isn't certain who dies yet." Bu Zhen Zi sneered.

"Is that so?!" Shadow King suddenly turned into a pitch-black shadow, pouncing towards Bu Zhen Zi.

Rumble, at the next instance, muffled explosions resounded from the seventh snowy peak.

The large hall shook, large amounts of snow that had accumulated on the mountain rolled down, forming a small avalanche.

Different from what Bu Zhen Zi had expected, Zhao Lian Yun was not alone but also was not with all the other immortals.

Twelfth peak.

Both sides had already started fighting.

"Oh? Two little ants, hmph, see how I step on you and send you to death." The twelfth snowy peak lord called out, and stepped fiercely with his right leg.

The twelfth snowy peak lord had transformed into a giant with the head of a bull and body of a human, his two legs had also turned into thick and firm bull legs.

Bam.

The bull leg stomped, creating a deep pit.

The peak lord had powerful might, the two Central Continent Gu Immortals quickly retreated.

One was Zhao Lian Yun, and the other was Shi Zheng Yi.

Zhao Lian Yun was slightly pale, the enemy was a giant while she had limited battle experience, this no doubt created strong mental pressure on her.

Shi Zheng Yi had rolled away on the ground, barely dodging the bull leg, he was clenching his teeth: "Damn it!"

He turned around and stood up from the ground: "Take this!"

"Lelelelelele!"

Shi Zheng Yi opened his mouth, flicking his tongue like a fast mechanical spring. With every flick, a crimson sword light shot out from the tip of his tongue at an extremely fast rate.

Zhao Lian Yun was speechless for a moment.

Normal people could only curl up their tongue, some might not even be able to do that. It was the first time Zhao Lian Yun had seen someone's tongue actually contracting and darting forward like a mechanical spring.

The crimson sword light was extremely sharp, the twelfth snowy peak lord had transformed into a giant which had thick skin and a sturdy physique, but the crimson sword light opened up holes all over his body.

"So painful!" The twelfth peak lord cried out in pain, and raised his arms to protect his head. For a moment, he could only defend and could not attack, all his momentum from before was suppressed.

"So powerful." Zhao Lian Yun praised.

"Naturally, this is my vital Immortal Gu — sword tongue Gu." Shi Zheng Yi flicked his tongue, sending out crimson sword light while also replying to Zhao Lian Yun. The strange thing was that his voice was clear even then.

"Are you a sword path Gu Immortal?" Zhao Lian Yun asked.

"Ah, no... I cultivate information path." Shi Zheng Yi replied.

"Speaking while still fighting, so you are so strong!" Zhao Lian Yun had a new level of respect towards Shi Zheng Yi, this person who had thick eyebrows, large eyes, and was somewhat lacking in brains.

"Hehe, I have sworn to defeat all the evils and demons in the world!" Shi Zheng Yi looked quite pleased and smug.

"Don't be so happy!" The twelfth peak lord roared.

Boom!

An overwhelming aura suddenly erupted from his giant body.

The majestic aura shot everywhere, creating a huge air wave.

"Not good, it is an immortal killer move!"

"Defend!!"

Shi Zheng Yi and Zhao Lian Yun defended with all their might, but it was of no use. The air wave was extremely powerful, the two were like a pair of small toys, easily sent flying.

With the twelfth peak lord at the center, the floor tiles of the hall started flying all around, turning the whole scene into chaos.

Thump thump, Zhao Lian Yun and Shi Zheng Yi crashed into the walls, throwing out mouthfuls of blood. Their whole bodies were suffering from intense pain, their internal organs were bleeding and their bones were fractured.

With one attack, the twelfth peak lord had completely turned around the slight disadvantage, and now had the upper hand.

"This is a qi path killer move!"

"How could it be so powerful?"

Zhao Lian Yun and Shi Zheng Yi endured the pain and struggled to stand up. The two were sent flying and were quite far from each other right now.

"How was it? Did you like my, Zhao Da Niu's, immortal killer move, rising heaven bull qi?"

"You are young and also powerful. Unfortunately, my battle strength is amplified in this formation, and it has risen to rank seven level, how can you possibly compete with me?"

"Hahaha." Zhao Da Niu laughed loudly, his laughter filled the hall like a huge wave.

"Watch as I stomp you to death!" Suddenly, Zhao Da Niu stopped laughing, gazing malevolently at Shi Zheng Yi.

He bent his waist and knees and suddenly jumped towards Shi Zheng Yi like a small hill.

Rumble!

A loud crashing sound echoed as Zhao Da Niu pressed Shi Zheng Yi to the ground.

"Shi Zheng Yi!" Zhao Lian Yun cried out in shock. This was a horrifying sight, being crushed by the heavy Zhao Da Niu, would Shi Zheng Yi not be turned into meat paste?

But the next moment, Zhao Da Niu's back protruded up. Shi Zheng Yi stood up from below, lifting Zhao Da Niu up with his hands, and with a yell, he actually pushed Zhao Da Niu away.

This was like a small rabbit pushing away a lion. This unimaginable scene caused Zhao Lian Yun to open her eyes wide.

"What? My transformation has the weight of a desolate beast bull, you actually pushed me away?" Even Zhao Da Niu found it unbelievable.

Shi Zheng Yi was coughing up blood, after pushing away Zhao Da Niu, he knelt down on the ground, extremely tired.

"This, this is the power of justice!" Shi Zheng Yi spoke with difficulty.

"Don't speak, you are coughing up too much blood." Zhao Lian Yun called out.

"Bullshit justice!" Zhao Da Niu pulled himself together, and charged towards Shi Zheng Yi again.

He was extremely huge, but right now, his speed was like the wind, not fitting with his body size at all.

In the blink of an eye, Zhao Da Niu was right in front of Shi Zheng Yi.

"Ahhh, look at the power of my justice!" Shi Zheng Yi shouted, and actually collided head on.

Bam, a muffled sound echoed.

Zhao Lian Yun felt pain in her body just from hearing the sound.

Shi Zheng Yi was like a small ball that was thrown far away, coughing up large amounts of blood.

Then, like a broken sack, he fell to the ground, his blood dying the path red.

"I will kill you! Eh?" Zhao Da Niu was just about to rush forward and give a fatal blow to Shi Zheng Yi, but he had just stepped forward when he found his whole body was tied by a bright silver chain.

At the other end of the chain was Zhao Lian Yun.

She had already been preparing to activate her immortal killer move.

Unfortunately, real battle was different from practice, especially this intense atmosphere which caused Zhao Lian Yun to fail twice in activating her killer move.

But it was fortunate that Shi Zheng Yi had stalled for time, and Zhao Lian Yun finally succeeded on her third attempt.

Immortal killer move — Life Locking Silver Chain!

"Cough cough, thank you, this killer move is really beautiful." Obtaining precious time for a breather, Shi Zheng Yi crawled up from the ground, coughing up blood in between his words.

"Don't speak, you are still coughing blood!" Zhao Lian Yun was worried for him.

"Hehe, you don't understand, I cultivate information path; by continuing to speak, I can heal my injuries. The louder I shout, the more powerful my attack becomes." Shi Zheng Yi spoke of the reason.

"Little girl, you are annoying!" Zhao Da Niu roared and exerted strength from both of his arms, trying to break the chains on him. But no matter how much strength he used, he was unable to break these chains.

"Since it's like this." Zhao Da Niu gave a malevolent smile, activating the killer move rising heaven bull qi.

Boom!

An intense explosion shook the hall.

The surging air wave erupted once again, and this time, it sent the ceiling of the hall flying.

Clang clang!

Crisp sounds echoed as the silver chain broke into countless pieces. Before these chain fragments touched the ground, they turned into specks of silver light and disappeared completely.

Zhao Da Niu used his main killer move to destroy the life locking silver chain, and was free now.

On the contrary, Zhao Lian Yun and Shi Zheng Yi were struck by the air wave again, both coughed out blood as they fell to the ground, unable to stand up.

"Damn, damn it!" Shi Zheng Yi wanted to climb up, but his whole body was on the verge of breaking apart.

As for Zhao Lian Yun, she had already fallen into a stupor.

Her injuries were worse than Shi Zheng Yi's.

Because life locking silver chain was forcefully broken, Zhao Lian Yun had suffered backlash, adding on Zhao Da Niu's immortal killer move, her injuries had worsened.

She had rank nine love Immortal Gu, but from the start of the battle, she had not seen love Immortal Gu being activated.

Love Immortal Gu could not be controlled, even if it showed its strength, it might not necessarily be the correct solution to the problem.

Darkness.

The stupefied Zhao Lian Yun felt she was floating amidst boundless darkness.

"This is the feeling of death?"

"So this is death?"

"I must be the biggest failure of a transmigrator in history. I actually died at the hands of an irrelevant side character."

"Let me just go down like this, after I die, I won't have to feel so exhausted and anguished anymore."

Chapter 1256: For The Sake of Love and Justice!

As she was thinking of this, Zhao Lian Yun suddenly heard a sound coming from the darkness.

This sound was calling out her name: "Zhao Lian Yun... Zhao Lian Yun..."

"Who?"

"Who is calling for me? I hear my name."

"Why do I feel that this voice is so familiar?"

"Ah, I remember, isn't this my voice before I lost it?"

Zhao Lian Yun suddenly recalled a scene of the past.

It was during the time of the Imperial Court contest, Zhao Lian Yun's father had died and she was treated as a political chip for an arranged marriage. However, she went against this fate by relying on Ma Hong Yun. In just a short while, she had turned from a wealthy young miss to an orphan.

One day, Ma Hong Yun brought her to a valley.

"Look, I found a good place for you!" Ma Hong Yun looked pleased.

Zhao Lian Yun gazed around, but when she discovered this was just a common small valley, her mouth uncontrollably twitched: "What is special about this? Isn't it just a normal valley? There is not even nice scenery."

"What are you saying?" Ma Hong Yun's eyes opened wide, "Valleys are very rare in Northern Plains. Here, let me teach you, shout at the valley with your name and the valley will reply to you. Like this!"

Ma Hong Yun took a deep breath, then yelled to the valley: "Zhao——Lian——Yun!"

An echo soon came from the valley: "Zhao——Lian——Yun!"

Zhao Lian Yun helplessly rolled her eyes: "Foolish people are the happiest, what is strange about echoes, I truly haven't seen anyone as dense as you!"

"Hahaha." Ma Hong Yun rubbed his hair: "Others have said I am an idiot, I am truly an idiot, how could I be as smart as Lady Xiao Yun."

"But, when I felt sad in my childhood, when I was teased by others and no one played with me, I used to run to the valley near my home, and shout at the valley."

"I call my name once, and the valley will reply back to me once, when I call again, the valley will reply again. It played with me, never abandoning or ignoring me. Unless my voice was not loud and clear enough."

"I saw you were not feeling happy recently, there is probably no one to play with you, right? I have to be beside the young clan leader and cannot accompany you all the time, so when you are unhappy, come to this valley and play with it."

Zhao Lian Yun did not speak, she looked at Ma Hong Yun who had an earnest expression, a feeling of pity rose in her heart.

"This Ma Hong Yun is so silly, but he is not bad at heart."

"He must have lived a very sad life since a young age. Even now, when he works under young clan leader, he is scolded frequently. But I have never seen him cry in sorrow, he is always smiling the whole day."

"Forget it, let me play with you then."

Thinking of this, Zhao Lian Yun took a deep breath and called at the valley with her name.

Ma Hong Yun was so happy he almost danced when he saw Zhao Lian Yun following his words: "That's wrong, you should shout louder, be louder."

Zhao Lian Yun shouted once again.

Ma Hong Yun shook his head: "You are still not loud enough, the valley can hear you only if you are loud. It is not responding to you now, because it is not able to listen to you."

Zhao Lian Yun took in a deep breath, and shouted with her loudest voice.

Zhao Lian Yun!

The valley replied — Zhao Lian Yun.

Ma Hong Yun laughed heartily.

Zhao Lian Yun also felt very refreshed, all her sadness seemed to have decreased and her mood also brightened.

"Zhao Lian Yun."

"Zhao Lian Yun."

"Zhao Lian Yun!"

In the darkness, the voice shouted constantly.

Zhao Lian Yun, what are you doing? Don't be lost.

Zhao Lian Yun, you are not alone. Heaven and earth is with you, as long as you shout loudly, heaven and earth will hear you.

Zhao Lian Yun, wake up. There is someone who is still waiting for you to rescue him.

That person once stood beside you, accompanied you to watch the stars, accompanied you to call out to the valley...

Go help him.

Go help him!

He must be feeling lonely now, or maybe even afraid.

Shout loudly, send out your voice, let him know you are coming! Let him know he has to persevere, let him know he has hope!

"Yes!"

"I will save him!"

"How can I fall here?"

Zhao Lian Yun suddenly opened her eyes!

She had woken up from her stupor.

The moment she woke up, she found her whole body was burning with a pale blue light.

This blue light was let out by love Immortal Gu!

Zhao Lian Yun's injuries rapidly recovered, and her condition was soaring.

The blue light also shone towards the surroundings.

Zhao Da Niu retreated step by step, his face filled with horror: "Ah, what is this light? It is heavier than a mountain! This aura, what Immortal Gu is this?!"

Shi Zheng Yi was similarly bathed in the light.

He suddenly stood up, feeling inexhaustible energy within him, his injuries had already disappeared, and his condition had reached an unprecedented peak.

"Thank you, Zhao Lian Yun, leave this to me now!"

"All you evildoers, I will strike you down. Take my..."

"Fist—Of—Justice!"

Shi Zheng Yi shouted loudly, the louder he shouted, the more powerful his immortal killer move became.

A giant fist of light rose up from his body and struck towards Zhao Da Niu.

Boom!

Like the roar of thunder, Zhao Da Niu's defensive methods were broken, a bloody hole appeared in his wide chest from which one could see the wall behind him.

"I... I..." Zhao Da Niu's eyes gradually lost their luster, before he fell down.

Bam.

His body collapsed on the ground, no longer moving.

Several breaths of time later, his body, soul and immortal aperture turned into pure energy that was absorbed by the fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation.

"Haha, justice prevailed!" Shi Zheng Yi raised his fist and yelled.

Zhao Lian Yun smiled from the side.

Northern Plains, licorice regional wall.

Dragon roars resounded throughout the surroundings: "Ying Wu Xie! Where do you think you are going?"

It was Fang Yuan in sword dragon form, who had finally caught up to Ying Wu Xie and the group, under qi luck sensation's guidance.

Ying Wu Xie and the group immediately turned around and faced Fang Yuan, their expressions extremely solemn.

Ying Wu Xie had said Fang Yuan would catch up to them, so the five immortals were already mentally prepared for it and not panicked.

Right now, they were waiting for the start of this vicious battle!

The sword dragon roared, opening its mouth wide, revealing fangs that were sharp like spears and very ferocious. Its eyes were ruthless and cold, emitting bone-chilling killing intent!

Without saying any nonsense, Fang Yuan directly charged forward!

To kill!

"If you want to go against my lord, you must go through me first." The loyal Shi Nu took a step forward, standing in front of the group, and raised his right hand.

A tall and thick rock wall immediately rose up and formed an obstacle!

Boom boom boom.

At the next moment, the rock wall was pierced through repeatedly.

Fang Yuan had used his dragon breath, the extremely sharp rays of dragon breath shot forward and gathered into a rain of sword light that pierced through the rock wall, moving towards the five immortals.

Hei Lou Lan gave a cry, breathing out small fire birds from her mouth.

These small birds could act on their own, they moved towards Fang Yuan's dragon breath. The fire birds collided into the dragon breath, turning into balls of flames that dissipated in the air.

"Angry bird?" Fang Yuan was slightly surprised.

This was clearly a fire path method, he had not expected Hei Lou Lan to use it.

The external appearance of these fire birds made Fang Yuan think of Blazing Heaven Demoness.

Back then during the battle in Eastern Sea, Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng, along with Shark Demon, Su Bai Man as well as the one finger flow shark, were unable to beat Blazing Heaven Demoness.

Blazing Heaven Demoness' immortal killer move, angry bird, had left an extremely deep impression on Fang Yuan.

But the fire birds Hei Lou Lan used were different from the true angry bird.

After Hei Lou Lan's strength path Immortal Gu were sent to Fang Yuan, she suffered from a lack of strength path Immortal Gu to support her battle strength, in Eastern Sea, she then chose to cultivate fire path, which was not complemented by the strength path dao marks in her body.

She possessed a fire path inheritance.

When Blazing Heaven Demoness met Hei Lou Lan, she secretly handed her fire path inheritance to Hei Lou Lan.

Blazing Heaven Demoness felt extreme guilt towards Hei Lou Lan, and thought of every way to compensate her.

Hei Lou Lan received the fire path inheritance and had not cared about it originally, feeling she would not use it in her whole life. But who could expect the way events unfolded, under strange coincidences, she chose to focus on fire path.

Naturally, she did not have even a trace of fire path dao marks in her.

But she possessed all the Immortal Gu of Blazing Heaven Demoness.

This matter would have to be traced back to before the battle of Yi Tian Mountain.

To refine sovereign immortal fetus Gu, Spectral Soul had no choice but to sacrifice the whole of Zombie Alliance, using the countless immortal zombies as immortal materials to further the progress of refinement.

Zombie Alliance was underneath Shadow Sect from its establishment, and was controlled by Shadow Sect. It was just that many immortal zombies did not know of this fact despite joining Zombie Alliance.

Zombie Alliance had gone all-out in establishing super Gu formations to protect immortal zombie corpses. But in truth, this was a perfect excuse and a way to keep them in captivity.

Using this chance, Shadow Sect assassinated all the immortal zombies, it did not matter if the dead apertures of the immortal zombies existed or not, but the Immortal Gu in them were all safely stored.

Northern Plains Zombie Alliance's Immortal Gu were all still hidden in Dark Flow Giant City.

Ying Wu Xie and Hei Lou Lan were far away in Eastern Sea, but there was still Sixth Hair in Northern Plains.

Dark Flow Giant City was hidden in the depths of Earth Trench, Sixth Hair quietly sneaked in and used his methods to take away all the Immortal Gu of Blazing Heaven Demoness, sending them to Ying Wu Xie.

After Ying Wu Xie refined them, he gave them to Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan already had Blazing Heaven Demoness' true inheritance, and with the Immortal Gu as well, she could almost replicate all the methods of Blazing Heaven Demoness.

Fang Yuan did not know of this before, but now that he saw these fire birds, he immediately had a pensive look.

The sword light dragon breath continued to be breathed out, Tai Bai Yun Sheng quickly acted and added the protection of cloud rings around the other Gu Immortals.

Chapter 1257: Ruthless Sword Dragon

Tai Bai Yun Sheng mainly cultivated time path, but Man as Before and Landscape as Before were traded to Fang Yuan, so he chose to cultivate cloud path. He already had a foundation in cloud path, and with Shadow Sect not lacking on cloud path true inheritances, the defensive method he used right now was quite good.

However, after Tai Bai Yun Sheng placed a cloud ring around his allies, his expression turned pale.

When Gu Immortals use their immortal killer moves inside the regional walls, their immortal killer moves would tremor.

Using the immortal killer move five times caused Tai Bai Yun Sheng's immortal aperture to tremor five times, inflicting huge losses.

"Interesting." Fang Yuan smiled sinisterly, his dragon body moved in a zigzag fashion, and lightly flew to the sky.

Ying Wu Xie and the rest looked sombre.

In this regional wall, every movement of theirs was performed with difficulty, having to constantly resist the formless repulsion and attraction forces.

On the contrary, Fang Yuan could move easily and freely.

Fang Yuan flew high above, immediately gaining control of the situation. He looked down from above and moved around, breathing out dragon breath constantly, sword light fell down towards the heads of the five immortals like rain.

"Defend, don't split up, we can't fight him alone!" Ying Wu Xie shouted loudly, reminding everyone.

Seeing the sword light falling towards them, Ying Wu Xie suddenly roared, letting out an incomparably sharp screech.

Immortal killer move — Soul Howl!

Soul Howl's power completely covered the sky, but did not affect the surrounding Gu Immortals in the slightest, showing Ying Wu Xie's outstanding control.

Fang Yuan's offenses were immediately suppressed. The sword light dragon breath clearly stopped for a moment, before quickly recovering.

"Since I am going against Shadow Sect, how could I not have prepared against soul path attacks?" Fang Yuan sneered inwardly.

He was already mentally prepared.

However, he did not have a method to protect his soul against soul path Immortal Gu, so he was hit by the attack and affected.

But his soul's foundation was extremely robust. He was completely able to endure the attack of soul howl. It would not matter even if his soul was injured because he had guts Gu!

"Damn it." Ying Wu Xie cursed while blocking the sword light dragon breath.

He knew Fang Yuan had guts Gu.

Guts Gu was only a mortal Gu, but it came from Dang Hun Mountain, and was beyond ordinary.

A secluded domain of heaven and earth like Dang Hun Mountain had an enormous amount of dao marks, the total surpassed even rank nine Immortal Gu. However, secluded domains of heaven and earth had scattered dao marks, though they could be of the same type and closely linked together. While rank nine Immortal Gu were fragments of the Great Dao, they could be controlled by a Gu Immortal to bring out mysterious powers.

Rank nine Immortal Gu and secluded domains of heaven and earth could not truly be compared and evaluated.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh.

Sword light fell down like rain, the five immortals were stifled.

There were traces of sword cuts everywhere on the ground.

The five immortals naturally did not like being suppressed like this.

The best way to deal with such a focused attack was to separate and dodge. But if they did that, Fang Yuan would have the chance to attack them separately!

But the five immortals would not take being beaten down passively, Shi Nu had finally finished his preparations as he activated an immortal killer move.

Rumble!

Muffled sounds echoed continuously, earth shook, a large hand made completely from soil and rocks rose up from the ground.

The large hand spread open and slowly hovered above the five immortals' heads, protecting Ying Wu Xie and the others under its palm. The thick back of the hand took on the sharp dragon breath.

Despite the large earth path hand being badly mauled and showing signs of being destroyed, Hei Lou Lan had finished preparing her killer move using this chance.

She stretched out her right arm, her five fingers together with no gaps between them, as she thrusted at the sky.

Boom!

A burning crimson ray of light erupted from between her fingers, and with breakneck speed, it pierced through the whole large hand and rushed towards Fang Yuan.

This immortal killer move was astonishingly fast, and it was concealed by the large earth path hand, if Fang Yuan was even the slightest bit inattentive, he would definitely be struck.

However, this ray of fire did not hit Fang Yuan and was easily avoided by him lightly moving his dragon body.

"It actually did not hit!" Hei Lou Lan's heart sank.

Three breaths future vision.

Hei Lou Lan did not know that Fang Yuan had such a time path investigative killer move.

"Strange, Hei Lou Lan is a strength path Gu Immortal and is using fire path methods, but she is actually not impeded by the conflict of dao marks. It should be from Shadow Sect's methods. After all, sovereign immortal fetus Gu was designed by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable." Hei Lou Lan's efforts were in vain, and instead gave away some of her details.

Soon, the large earth path hand collapsed, and the sword light dragon breath continued to rain down.

However, the five immortals were no longer as hurried before, each used their immortal killer moves to defend against the sword light rain.

"Then how about this move? Let me see how you deal with it." Fang Yuan firmly held the initiative, easily using another immortal killer move.

Time path — Year Beast Summoning.

Roar!

A tiger shaped year beast answered the summoning and appeared in the regional wall, helping Fang Yuan battle.

Fang Yuan threw large amounts of mortal year Gu, raising the morale of the tiger year beast as it charged towards Ying Wu Xie and the group.

Shi Nu felt bitter, the sword light dragon breath was already difficult to cope with, now there was an ancient year beast worsening the situation.

This year beast could similarly move freely in the regional wall.

The reason was similar to the cloud beasts, the cloud beasts were life forms of white heaven and were not native to the five regions, thus they were not restricted by the regional walls.

While the year beasts which lived in the River of Time were similar.

"Allow me." Ying Wu Xie stepped forward, and used an extremely similar method.

Soul path — Soul Beast Summoning!

In the past, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had created soul path, thus Shadow Sect was most proficient in soul path. Hei Fan could think of summoning year beasts, how could Shadow Sect not have similar methods?

Ying Wu Xie's method was extraordinary, summoning three ancient soul beasts at once.

"My soul beasts are not influenced by the regional wall, because they come from the door of life and death!"

Ying Wu Xie's complacency did not last long because he saw that Fang Yuan had already rushed forward.

The sword dragon snaked around, flying extremely fast.

It grabbed forward with its dragon claws, directly destroying a soul beast's head.

Its tail whipped, severing the thigh of another soul beast.

It breathed out, dragon breath pierced through the third ancient soul beast.

Fang Yuan's sword dragon transformation had outstanding battle strength, the main thing was that Fang Yuan also had Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's immortal killer move on him — Ghostly Concealment.

This made any soul beast unable to sense his existence.

Thus, with Fang Yuan's battle strength surpassing the ancient soul beasts, and the soul beasts unable to sense him, Fang Yuan had huge superiority when fighting the soul beasts!

These soul beasts could not even react before they were severely injured by Fang Yuan.

Fortunately, soul beasts did not have a clear weak point on them, otherwise they would have been completely destroyed by Fang Yuan.

But even so, the soul beasts had clearly thinned, becoming increasingly transparent.

Ying Wu Xie's expression was unsightly, but he simply watched as Fang Yuan destroyed the three ancient soul beasts without making a move.

Ying Wu Xie inwardly thought: "It doesn't matter, even if you kill these three ancient soul beasts, so what? I can use the killer move again and summon another three ancient soul beasts. What is found everywhere in the door of life and death? Souls and soul beasts!"

But at this time, Fang Yuan suddenly gave up on attacking the ancient soul beasts and activated Sword Escape.

Sword escape Immortal Gu!

Fang Yuan's speed suddenly erupted, leaving behind an afterimage in his original spot.

Fast! Fast! Fast!

Tai Bai Yun Sheng could not react at all and was struck by Fang Yuan's claws.

The cloud ring protecting him directly collapsed, his stomach was torn open and his large intestine spilled out.

"He did not die?" Fang Yuan was surprised.

He had wanted to use dragon breath, after all, the dragon breath was the most powerful weapon of his sword dragon transformation, but at the crucial moment, a layer of ice had sealed his mouth out of nowhere.

Fang Yuan could not open his mouth, thus he chose to use his claws.

But his speed was too fast and rushed, Fang Yuan could not use his full strength, as a result, most of the strength of his claws was offset by Tai Bai Yun Sheng's cloud ring, and Tai Bai Yun Sheng thus was barely able to survive.

"It is Bai Ning Bing!" Fang Yuan exerted strength, forcibly opening his dragon mouth, breaking the ice on it.

Fang Yuan looked back, his speed was too fast and right now, he was already a few li away from the five immortals.

Bai Ning Bing was guarding in front of the four immortals, her icy-blue eyes emitted cold light as she stared at Fang Yuan with no fear.

"Quick, quick!" Hei Lou Lan grabbed Tai Bai Yun Sheng's leg and dragged him to the rear.

Then, she sat down and used healing methods, but unfortunately, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's injuries were severe, and for the moment showed no signs of healing.

Once a Gu Immortal was injured, it was difficult to heal.

Because of the conflict between dao marks!

Once Fang Yuan's ancient sword dragon transformation injured someone, it would leave behind large amounts of sword path dao marks. This was very hard to endure for Tai Bai Yun Sheng's fragile human body.

"Oh, if I had Man as Before, it would not be so troublesome." Saying this, Tai Bai Yun Sheng fainted, his life hanging by a thread.

This was after Hei Lou Lan used all her healing methods.

"Damned Fang Yuan, his true target was Tai Bai Yun Sheng!" Ying Wu Xie's expression was ashen.

He could see Fang Yuan's thought process.

Fang Yuan was entangled against the soul beasts on the surface, but ever since the battle began, he had been searching for an opportunity. He had probably marked Tai Bai Yun Sheng as his target since the beginning.

After all, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was the weakest among the five immortals.

Always pick out the weakest enemy first!

"Tai Bai Yun Sheng cannot be counted on now!" Ying Wu Xie's expression was heavy. How long had it been since they battled? There was already a casualty on his side, how should they deal with such a strong Fang Yuan?

"Huh?"

At this moment, Fang Yuan was surprised, feeling something wrong.

He stretched out his dragon body, but astonishingly discovered that his dragon scales were covered by a layer of thin ice, who knows when it formed.

"Bai Ning Bing's gaze is strange!" Fang Yuan immediately reacted.

"If we want to force back Fang Yuan, we need to first restrict his speed." Bai Ning Bing's eyes flickered with cold light. She had clear judgment of the whole situation!

Chapter 1258: Fang Yuan versus Five (1/2)

Despite becoming an immortal just recently, Bai Ning Bing had some advantages over normal Gu Immortals.

First of all, she possessed one of the ten extreme physiques, Northern Dark Ice Soul Physique, which was the best for cultivating ice and snow path. Similarly to Hei Lou Lan's Great Strength True Martial Physique, her dao marks surpassed most rank six Gu Immortals in the same condition.

Secondly, she had become the owner of Bai Xiang grotto-heaven. She obtained Bai Xiang's true inheritance, and had all the Gu worms left behind by Bai Xiang, among which were rank seven Immortal Gu as well!

However, there were no rank eight Immortal Gu.

Bai Xiang's status in history was slightly inferior to Hei Fan. But the joint forces of the five Xiangs surpassed Hei Fan by a lot.

Bai Ning Bing's flaw was that she was not familiar with the Immortal Gu and the immortal killer moves, she often failed when activating them, which caused danger of backlash.

Nurture, use, and refinement, using Gu was one of the three important aspects of Gu Master cultivation.

To get familiar with her gains, Bai Ning Bing had to spend a long period of time in practising them.

As such, she was a long way away from being able to use them freely in real battle.

But...

At this time, Bai Ning Bing's flaw was effectively concealed.

Because she had Ying Wu Xie, Hei Lou Lan, Tai Bai Yun Sheng and Shi Nu beside her.

Because of their protection, Bai Ning Bing had the time to use her immortal killer move unhurriedly.

Fang Yuan's information regarding Bai Ning Bing was lacking.

On one hand, he thought Bai Ning Bing was like Tai Bai Yun Sheng and Hei Lou Lan, whose battle strength rose after receiving benefits from Shadow Sect.

On the other hand, Fang Yuan had used qi luck sensation many times before and had sensed Bai Ning Bing, but he could not know matters concerned with Bai Xiang grotto-heaven and so on.

Fang Yuan had thus greatly underestimated Bai Ning Bing's true battle strength.

If he knew of the truth, he might not have chosen Tai Bai Yun Sheng as the first target, and marked Bai Ning Bing instead.

But Fang Yuan had always lacked information path methods, so how could he know about Bai Xiang grotto-heaven?

Fang Yuan had been reborn, but he was not all-knowing.

Bai Ning Bing's gaze could actually freeze any targets in her sight, slowing down their mobility. This was Bai Xiang's method.

After Fang Yuan realized the strangeness, he immediately took measures, flying back and concealing his traces.

Visibility was very poor in the licorice regional wall, after Fang Yuan flew back, he immediately disappeared from Bai Ning Bing's sight.

Bai Ning Bing clenched her teeth, Fang Yuan was an old fox, seeing through the limits of her move in just a short while.

"Even with such a trump card, he doesn't force himself to take risks. Unfortunately, we have especially formulated a battle tactic for this." Bai Ning Bing felt regret.

The move Fang Yuan used to break the super Gu formation in Eastern Sea was so powerful that it gave chills to Ying Wu Xie, Bai Ning Bing and the rest.

On the way, they had discussed about defensive measures against this method of Fang Yuan.

However, Fang Yuan did not use that move the whole time, making the prior preparations of Ying Wu Xie and the rest useless.

"Unfortunately, I have only just obtained Bai Xiang's true inheritance, this killer move has its limits, but other killer moves can be used together with it to make up for this limit."

Bai Ning Bing had barely been able to activate this killer move. If she tried to activate another immortal killer move on top of this, she was almost certain to fail.

Bai Ning Bing was not Fang Yuan, Fang Yuan could do many tasks at once and use multiple immortal killer moves at the same time, but Bai Ning Bing had very low attainment in this aspect.

Fang Yuan had retreated and hidden himself, but he still held the initiative and upper hand.

Under this situation, Bai Ning Bing could not take the risk.

Once she failed, their arrangement would be in disorder, creating a weakness which Fang Yuan could exploit.

Bai Ning Bing understood Fang Yuan very well, he absolutely would not give up such an exposed weakness. Even Bai Ning Bing was in deep admiration of Fang Yuan's ability to grasp opportunities in a fight.

"Fang Yuan's scales have been frozen by my gaze, once he recovers, with his speed, it will be difficult for me to lock onto him with my sight!" Bai Ning Bing pondered.

Fang Yuan's burst of speed in ancient sword dragon form was astonishing by itself, adding on Sword Escape and his sword path dao marks, even the rank seven expert Ye Lui Qun Xing had died at his hands.

Bai Ning Bing knew she had been able to use her freezing sight earlier because Fang Yuan was unprepared.

Now that Fang Yuan was on guard, when he used that astonishing speed again, this immortal killer move's effectiveness would decrease drastically.

"It seems I can only change my tactics!" Bai Ning Bing immediately decided.

She had no choice but to change.

Previously, when Fang Yuan showed his speed, he had almost killed Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

If Bai Ning Bing did not change her tactics and continued to use freezing sight, the one to die might be her!

The situation was perilous, Bai Ning Bing retreated behind Shi Nu while saying to Ying Wu Xie: "Protect me, I am going to use that move!"

Bai Ning Bing and Ying Wu Xie had formed a new alliance, and with a formidable enemy in front of them, both sides had informed each other of some of their trump cards.

Thus, Ying Wu Xie understood without needing Bai Ning Bing to explain.

He nodded solemnly: "Okay, use that move, let us take care of your safety!"

He immediately commanded Shi Nu: "Even if you have to sacrifice yourself, you need to protect Bai Ning Bing."

Shi Nu was loyal to Ying Wu Xie, he immediately nodded at this command with no hesitation.

"Relax, he has been hit by my freezing sight, according to the flaw you mentioned of the sovereign immortal body, if he does not have a specific method to counter it, he will need about a dozen breaths of time to recover completely." Bai Ning Bing spoke with confidence.

Ying Wu Xie nodded: "That's good, then."

He did not doubt Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Xiang's methods had their own originality. It was not easy to specifically target an immortal killer move. Often, one had to fight numerous times, getting familiar with the immortal killer move, and go through a long period of deduction to create a method that countered the immortal killer move. There was a low probability of Fang Yuan having a method to counter it.

But right at this time, in the sights of the five immortals, a white ray of light flashed by.

"Careful!"

"It is the dragon breath!!"

"Defend, protect Bai Ning Bing and Tai Bai Yun Sheng!"

Rays of sword light dragon breath attacked, recreating the previous sword light rain, for a moment, Ying Wu Xie and the group had their hands tied dealing with them.

Bai Ning Bing was using all her concentration in activating her immortal killer move, while Tai Bai Yun Sheng was unconscious from the severe injuries.

As such, for the remaining three other immortals, the pressure on them had amplified suddenly, and they did not even have enough strength to strike back.

Fang Yuan circled around Ying Wu Xie and the rest from afar, breathing out dragon breath, rays of sword light dragon breath shot from all directions towards Ying Wu Xie and the others.

His sword dragon body was still covered in thin ice.

Bai Ning Bing's freezing sight was quite effective. Naturally, the main reason was Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal body.

Despite transforming into an ancient sword dragon, his dao marks still did not have repulsion to different dao marks.

This created a disadvantage.

Like when Bai Ning Bing's freezing sight affected Fang Yuan, it would not be weakened by Fang Yuan's dao marks, and could strike with all its might.

Fortunately, the ancient sword dragon had a tough body and strong vitality, otherwise a human body might have been directly frozen to death.

Fang Yuan was breathing dragon breath, suppressing Ying Wu Xie and the rest, while quickly recovering.

He was influenced by the freezing sight, but healing was also rather easy.

Because his dao marks did not have repulsion, even using mortal methods repeatedly could display effect.

It was not like Tai Bai Yun Sheng, whom, after being injured, could not be healed easily.

Fang Yuan continuously breathed out dragon breath, probing and suppressing Ying Wu Xie and the others.

He quickly discovered: Bai Ning Bing was being heavily protected by Ying Wu Xie and the others. Unless he made his way in through brute force, he had no other routes to get to Bai Ning Bing.

"Activating an immortal killer move, huh..." Fang Yuan thought heavily. Since she was being so greatly protected by Ying Wu Xie and the others, Bai Ning Bing was definitely preparing an extraordinary immortal killer move.

Thus, as soon as he recovered, he directly dived in.

He was not restricted in the licorice regional wall and could move freely, when he burst with his speed, even Fang Yuan himself was not able to have complete control!

It was simply like a white ray of light!

Ying Wu Xie and the rest did not even have time to call out when Fang Yuan penetrated through their defensive lineup and charged in.

Bai Ning Bing broke out in cold sweat, almost failing her killer move's activation.

Hei Lou Lan was heavily injured!

Her left arm was completely gone and even her left torso was injured, the injuries were so frightening that one could see her ribs.

Blood spurted out like a fountain and soon accumulated into a pool below Hei Lou Lan!

The injury was covered with dao marks, causing the blood to flow unceasingly!

If this continued, Hei Lou Lan would be the first person to die.

Under this critical situation, Hei Lou Lan immediately chose to transform into an immortal zombie.

Immortal zombies could bear this level of injury. The warm and bright red blood immediately turned into cold and gloomy green blood, blood was still flowing outside, but the speed had reduced by countless times.

"Hehehe..." Hei Lou Lan knelt on one leg, taking huge gasps of breath, but her lips were curled up.

She was actually laughing!

On the other hand, Fang Yuan got a peculiar feeling: "Hmm? I was actually hit! Not bad from Hei Lou Lan!"

The dragon claw he used to rip apart Hei Lou Lan's left arm still had traces of flesh and blood.

Right now, this flesh and blood slowly turned into a blood colored fire, which followed Fang Yuan's dragon claw to his scales.

Immortal killer move — Flesh Blood Fire!

This fire used flesh and blood as the fuel. As long as there was flesh and blood, the fire wouldn't stop. Without any methods to counter it, it simply would not be extinguished.

Moreover, the stronger the flesh and blood were, the brighter and more powerful the fire would become!

Fang Yuan's ancient sword dragon transformation had instead become the perfect target for flesh blood fire.

However, Fang Yuan reacted extremely quickly.

He immediately dispelled his transformation killer move, and returned to his human form.

The, he activated a time path healing Immortal Gu —

Man as Before!

Chapter 1259: Fang Yuan versus Five (2/2)

Over twenty beads of red date immortal essence were expended.

The next moment, the blood colored fire completely disappeared and Fang Yuan went back to his previous state.

"Sigh!"

"Man as Before is effective only on human bodies, when I transform to other living beings, I cannot directly use Man as Before. This is quite inconvenient."

"Moreover, Man as Before has quite a big restriction in terms of time, fortunately I have my investigative killer move, three breaths future vision!"

Fang Yuan inwardly sighed, as he activated another immortal killer move.

Convergence of enslavement and strength path — Myriad Self!

Whoosh whoosh whoosh.

Tens of thousands of Fang Yuans converged to create a vast human tide that charged towards Ying Wu Xie and the rest.

"How can this be? He actually recovered so quickly? He has already gotten rid of blood flesh fire?" Hei Lou Lan was extremely surprised.

Fang Yuan's counterattack was too quick, and it still carried strong momentum, making Hei Lou Lan's heart sink to rock bottom.

Hei Lou Lan knew Fang Yuan had Man as Before.

But Man as Before had rather stringent requirements regarding time. Even Fang Yuan would only survive by a hair's breadth. After he was struck, he would have to first discover his state, then dispel his transformation killer move, during this time, he might hesitate before he finally used Man as Before. Activating this Immortal Gu, furthermore, required some time.

Under such a situation, Hei Lou Lan thought if it was herself instead of Fang Yuan, it would also be very difficult to get rid of this blood flesh fire.

Fang Yuan was not clear of Hei Lou Lan and Bai Ning Bing's methods, likewise, Hei Lou Lan similarly did not know that Fang Yuan had three breaths future vision.

This investigative killer move could let Fang Yuan see anything wrong that would happen to him three breaths earlier. Because of this, Fang Yuan had much more time to react and take action accordingly.

In short, Hei Lou Lan was heavily injured but only managed to slightly affect Fang Yuan.

Red date immortal essence was consumed, but Fang Yuan was rich and his financial condition was rather good, thus, he did not care about this small expenditure.

Immortal killer move — Soul Howl!

Ying Wu Xie howled, countless phantoms of Fang Yuan around him burst at once.

Immortal killer move — Spike Forest.

Shi Nu stamped his right leg, countless spikes rose up from the ground, piercing through thousands of Fang Yuan's phantoms.

Then, Shi Nu called out, the earth spikes shot to the air, instantly clearing large amounts of phantoms in the air.

This move hid a second stage within, and was extremely effective, almost completely destroying all of Fang Yuan's phantoms.

Earth path rank seven Gu Immortal Shi Nu, he was the cornerstone in this battle, without his protection and contribution, how could Ying Wu Xie and the rest last until this moment?

"Your turn next." Fang Yuan transformed back into a sword dragon, laughing sinisterly inwardly.

Roar!

At this moment, the tiger year beast beside him roared and suddenly retreated.

This ancient year beast had been summoned by Fang Yuan, although it had been fighting all along, Ying Wu Xie and the rest were on guard against it, thus it was not able to assist a lot and instead suffered many injuries.

The tiger year beast was not loyal to Fang Yuan, this could not compare to Ying Wu Xie's soul beast summoning.

Once the year beast suffered severe injuries, it immediately retreated, penetrating space and returning to the River of Time.

But it did not matter.

Immortal killer move — Year Beast Summoning!

Fang Yuan activated this killer move again, this time he summoned a sheep shaped ancient year beast.

Although year beast summoning could only summon one year beast each time, there were many year beasts in the River of Time, if one left, he just had to summon another.

The sheep ancient year beast stampeded towards Ying Wu Xie and the others, Shi Nu gave a deep roar, his body suddenly bulged, turning into a giant that was as big as the year beast; he stood stably and countered it, using his profound fighting techniques to throw the year beast to the ground.

Boom.

The sheep ancient year beast fell to the ground, causing the ground to tremor for a while.

The year beast quickly stood up, and furiously charged towards Shi Nu with its horns.

Shi Nu sidestepped smoothly while grabbing the curved sheep horns at the same time.

The two giant beings tangled together, at a deadlock for the time being.

On Fang Yuan's end, the amount of dragon breath he used was reducing.

He was starting to feel a burning pain in his throat, as if his throat was about to emit smoke!

Dragon breath was the ancient sword dragon's strongest weapon. Even a true ancient sword dragon would not be able to continue using dragon breath more than twenty to thirty times.

However, Fang Yuan had already used his dragon breath over a hundred times, reaching the limits of his physical body.

If he continued breathing out, his throat would be damaged, and the sword light dragon breath's power would reduce by a huge extent.

The battle had lasted up until now, the tiger year beast had retreated from severe injuries, and now Fang Yuan was showing some signs of fatigue.

Although he had become a rank seven Gu Immortal, with red date immortal essence, his battle strength rising sharply and reaching the upper level among rank sevens, the enemies he faced were also not minor characters.

Hei Lou Lan was a formidable person with the Great Strength True Martial Physique, she had annexed a strength path blessed land in Jade Pot Mountain, her dao marks increasing by a lot. At the same time, she also had Blazing Heaven Demoness' true inheritance along with her Immortal Gu.

Bai Ning Bing had the Northern Dark Ice Soul Physique, and had changed into the mysterious dragonman, grasping Bai Xiang grotto-heaven and obtaining Bai Xiang's true inheritance.

There was no need to say anything about Ying Wu Xie, he was one of the main split souls of Spectral Soul. He once had the eleventh extreme physique, he was the final hope of Shadow Sect, with astonishing attainment in soul path, and although his attainment in other paths was unclear, they should not be low. At least, it was the case for luck path.

Shi Nu was a rockman, this race innately had rich earth path dao marks, and with Shi Nu cultivating earth path mainly, it could be they complemented one another well.

The most useless was Tai Bai Yun Sheng, but even so, this old guy was becoming sharper as he grew older, he mainly cultivated time path, but perfectly dual-cultivated cloud path as well, and with the Immortal Gu on him, his cloud ring's defensive ability was quite remarkable.

Although the majority of these five was rank six, they were similar to Fang Yuan when he was rank six, with battle strength that reached rank seven level.

And right now, these elites with outstanding disposition had allied and were working together, adding on the constant support of Shadow Sect's remaining resources and methods emerging one after another, they were stronger than a lone Ye Lui Qun Xing and were even more difficult to handle.

When Gu Immortals battled, they could not rush things.

Because there were many types of Immortal Gu, immortal killer moves were endless in number, some were extremely mystical, some were powerful and unconstrained, some were tyrannical, and some were sinister and strange.

Fang Yuan was fighting alone against five, and was firmly holding an advantage, while Ying Wu Xie and the others were exhausted by just dealing with his attacks, and were unable to turn the situation around.

"Damn it, he has not used that move even now!" Ying Wu Xie thought as green immortal zombie blood flowed down from his nose.

Ying Wu Xie wiped the blood using the back of his hand, but the green blood flowed down again.

"Damn it!"

"I have been using immortal killer moves repeatedly, and have been bearing so much backlash that even this immortal zombie body is showing signs of reaching its limits."

"Even I am like this, the others must be in even worse circumstances."

Ying Wu Xie gazed at his allies, and saw they were all pale and their states were worsening.

Fang Yuan was unrestricted here, but they were not. They not only had to steady themselves constantly, resisting the repulsion and attraction force in the regional wall, they also had to fight Fang Yuan at the same time, using many immortal killer moves which caused heavy losses to their immortal apertures!

"My side has Shadow Sect's remaining resources, it is normal for our battle strength to rise rapidly."

"But, Fang Yuan's battle strength also rose so quickly!"

"This speed is too astonishing. Even us five allied together are not his match."

The more Ying Wu Xie thought, the more apprehensive he felt towards Fang Yuan. And in the depths of this apprehension was a trace of fear!

Right, it was fear.

Ying Wu Xie was beginning to feel afraid.

He could not help but admit Fang Yuan was strong, he was even more afraid of Fang Yuan's growth speed!

"Bai Xiang, activate."

Bai Ning Bing who had been preparing the killer move all along, suddenly gave a cry, a soaring aura rose up from her body.

Ying Wu Xie was immediately filled with joy as he looked at Bai Ning Bing: "You finally succeeded!"

Bai Ning Bing's appearance had a great change right now.

In the blink of an eye, she had transformed into a five meter giant.

She had three heads, six arms and bare feet, her body was covered in ice armor and frost aura flowed around her, like a long ribbon was revolving around her. She stood on two frost clouds that emitted light hints of blue.

Immortal killer move — Bai Xiang!

"Fang Yuan, come fight me!" Bai Ning Bing gave a shout, and suddenly sped up like a white light passing through the air. She had changed her defensive stance, taking the initiative to attack.

"Let our old and new enmity be resolved today." Fang Yuan's dragon eyes narrowed, and without dodging, he charged head-on.

A silver light and a white light passed by each other.

The inertia from their speed was too powerful, whether it be Bai Ning Bing or Fang Yuan, they each flew far away.

"A light injury." Fang Yuan slightly looked down and saw a long but shallow sword mark on his body, the dragon scales along the sword mark were all cut, some even broke through the dragon skin, letting out some blood.

By contrast, Bai Ning Bing was much more miserable.

There was a hole in her chest, three of her arms were destroyed, and almost half of her body was gone.

But she did not bleed, cold air flowed on massively, restoring her back to normal in a blink of an eye.

"Bai Xiang. This immortal killer move is rumored to be undying. Even if there is only a nail sized fragment remaining, the user can immediately revive and recover back to normal. Because after the Bai Xiang transformation, the body is no longer a flesh and blood body, instead it becomes a certain mystical life form!" Ying Wu Xie was inwardly excited.

Sure enough, as the battle went on, Bai Ning Bing's performance was like Ying Wu Xie estimated.

She was not Fang Yuan's match. But relying on the Bai Xiang transformation's special characteristics, she could immediately recover back to normal.

Most of Fang Yuan's attention was absorbed in fighting with Bai Ning Bing.

As the battle continued, even Fang Yuan felt exhausted, after all, his was a flesh and blood body, while Bai Ning Bing was still energetic and lively.

Just as Fang Yuan intended to give up on Bai Ning Bing and target Ying Wu Xie and the rest...

"It is time!" Ying Wu Xie suddenly cried out, auras of countless Gu worms rose from his body...

He looked at Fang Yuan and spoke—

Lead soul into dream!

Chapter 1260: Lead Soul Into Dream

Fang Yuan got a shock when he heard Ying Wu Xie say "lead soul into dream".

Lead soul into dream was a rare and powerful dream path immortal killer move. In the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain, Ying Wu Xie's lead soul into dream had made even Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord fall asleep, trapped within a dream realm.

Fang Yuan was also struck by this move in the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain, if not for heaven's will working secretly, he would have surely died.

In this current time period, dream path Immortal Gu were extremely rare, let alone dream path killer moves.

One skill to dominate all, facing lead soul into dream, Gu Immortals were basically defenseless.

Fang Yuan was not an exception.

He had unravel dream, but he also had the sovereign immortal body. Facing lead soul into dream, even if he spent only an instant in the dream realm, it was very likely there could be various changes during that instant, and he might even die.

Fang Yuan immediately soared up, retreating without hesitation.

While retreating, he had doubts in his mind.

Back then, Ying Wu Xie's lead soul into dream was very powerful because of many Immortal Gu as well as the amplification from the eleventh extreme physique.

Right now, could Ying Wu Xie have those Immortal Gu to form lead soul into dream?

Fang Yuan did not know the exact details, but he was aware that Ying Wu Xie's strength path immortal zombie body absolutely lowered the power of this move by several levels.

Fang Yuan quickly got a long distance away from Ying Wu Xie and the rest, but still did not see himself falling into a dream realm.

"Was Ying Wu Xie only trying to trick me?"

Fang Yuan just had this thought, when the scenery in front of him changed.

Southern Border, in his first life.

Qing Mao Mountain was already destroyed from Bai Ning Bing's self-detonation. Fang Yuan threw himself in with a merchant caravan, earning primeval stones while continuing his cultivation.

The merchant caravan had reached a certain valley, when suddenly, two groups of bandits rushed from in front and behind.

"Kill!"

"Protect the goods!!"

The caravan was in a great uproar. In an instant, yells resounded throughout the valley, one side was the demonic path bandits, while the other was the caravan escorting the goods.

The young Fang Yuan was mixed in the merchant caravan, clenching his teeth, panicking at the sudden ambush.

...

"This is a dream realm. I am trapped in a dream realm!"

The confusion from just entering the dream realm disappeared quickly, and Fang Yuan immediately prepared to activate unravel dream.

However, right at this time, he inexplicably exited the dream realm and returned to reality, his ancient dragon body still in the regional wall.

"What's going on?" Fang Yuan just had this question, when his vision changed once again.

He found he had once again entered a dream realm.

This dream was a continuation of the previous dream.

In the valley, the righteous and demonic sides were fighting a bitter battle.

"Strange, there should not be any bandit hideouts here." The young master of the merchant caravan was looking down from his carriage in the center, puzzled.

The steward beside him was maintaining defense while replying: "Right, this trade route is an old route, who knows where these mountain bandits came from."

The young master snorted: "The strongest demonic path Gu Masters among them are only rank two, our defense is rock solid, we don't need to fear them."

"Young master is right. We will make sure these bandits remain here forever." The steward gave a malicious smile.

Right at this time, a rumbling noise came from above them.

The young master, the steward and others quickly looked above.

The sight immediately caused a great fright.

Countless boulders were rolling down from above the valley. The caravan was right at the base of a cliff, and these giant boulders were falling down right towards them, the power was not inferior to a rank two Gu Master's attack.

Countless figures could be seen above the cliff. They were all mortals, but with meticulous planning and correct battle tactics, these mortals showcased the battle strength of rank two Gu Masters!

"Quick, retreat!" The young master's face was pale.

"It is too late..." The steward called out miserably.

The boulders smashed onto the caravan's Gu Masters, in an instant, the merchant caravan suffered many casualties, and the demonic path side's morale was greatly raised.

...

"Damn it!" Fang Yuan shook his head fiercely, escaping from the dream realm again.

"This is indeed lead soul into dream, but it is incomplete, it can send me into a dream realm now and again, but it can't keep me trapped in there. However, this is enough to pose a huge threat to me." Fang Yuan's heart sank.

Ying Wu Xie and the rest were vigilantly looking at their surroundings, but even after guarding for a while, they did not see Fang Yuan, there were also no attacks coming towards them.

"He retreated?" Hei Lou Lan spoke, somewhat disbelievingly.

Bai Ning Bing gazed at Ying Wu Xie.

Ying Wu Xie heaved a long sigh: "Sigh... such a pity."

After the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain, Ying Wu Xie had secretly reconstructed lead soul into dream. During the time in Eastern Sea, Ying Wu Xie gave Immortal Gu to Hei Lou Lan and others, he naturally had even more gains.

But even until now, he was only barely able to assemble lead soul into dream.

Ying Wu Xie had intended to use lead soul into dream when Fang Yuan activated that trump card.

However, Fang Yuan did not use that trump card at all.

Fang Yuan would need a long time to activate that trump card, which would give Ying Wu Xie a very good opportunity to make a move. If Fang Yuan was struck by lead soul into dream at that time, he would be trapped in a dream realm. Even if it was only for an instant, it would still lead to failure in activating the immortal killer move.

The stronger an immortal killer move was, the greater the injury the Gu Immortal would have to bear after they fail in activating it.

There was no doubt that if Fang Yuan was trapped in the dream realm when he activated that killer move, he would fail and suffer a severe backlash.

Ying Wu Xie explained it in detail, Bai Ning Bing, Hei Lou Lan and the rest also felt regret.

However, in the situation earlier, Ying Wu Xie had no choice but to use lead soul into dream prematurely.

If he still did not use it, Fang Yuan's successful attack would result in a qualitative change, causing the battle situation to shift greatly, which would finally result in their deaths.

Ying Wu Xie had a very sharp and accurate judgment of the situation.

"Looks like Fang Yuan won't be able to attack for the moment. We should leave quickly. Lead soul into dream is not complete, its effect will continue to decrease with time."

Ying Wu Xie gave the command, the five immortals set off immediately.

However, they had not walked far when Fang Yuan once again recovered and attacked.

The dream realm's interference was becoming smaller and smaller, Fang Yuan was not willing to let Ying Wu Xie and the others slip away from right under his nose, so he immediately began his chase.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was still unconscious, the four immortals were harried by Fang Yuan, it was already difficult to move in the regional wall, but with Fang Yuan's interference, it became even more difficult for them to move forward.

...

"Careful!" Suddenly, a familiar voice came from behind Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan could not react in time and only heard a muffled sound as stone debris hit him on the head.

"Uncle Big Beard, you saved me, thank you!" Fang Yuan saw Uncle Big Beard nearby, and immediately reacted. Just now, he was almost hit by a falling boulder, but Uncle Big Beard had acted in time, destroying the giant boulder before it could reach Fang Yuan.

"Kid, don't be so hungry for battle, protect yourself properly." Uncle Big Beard said with a concerned tone.

Right at this moment, from the center of the caravan came the caravan steward's sharp scream — "Men, come quickly and protect young master!"

Out of nowhere, two rank three demonic path Gu Masters had already charged into the center and were surrounding the owner of the merchant caravan, that young master who had once humiliated Fang Yuan.

The young master was in a dangerous situation, even the righteous path Gu Masters were afraid.

"Wait here, I will go help!" Uncle Big Beard spoke this before quickly rushing to the center.

...

The dream realm appeared again and again, Fang Yuan was having a tough time.

The dream realm greatly influenced him, and he was only able to display twenty to thirty percent of his battle strength.

But looking at the battle situation, it was much more unfavorable to Ying Wu Xie and the rest.

They were clearly able to sense that the dream realm's influence to Fang Yuan was becoming smaller.

And they were still unable to leave the regional wall.

"All of you go ahead, I will hold him back!" At the crucial moment, Shi Nu stood up.

Immortal killer move — Land Boundary!

His whole body emitted frightening cracking sounds, as cracks started appearing everywhere on his body.

At the same time, with him at the center, an enormous surrounding area of space underwent a mysterious change, being cut off from the space further out.

Fang Yuan wanted to retreat, but at the critical moment, the dream realm started, making him miss the chance to escape the range of the killer move.

Fang Yuan sent out dragon breath, but the sword light dragon breath disappeared like smoke before even flying five to six steps of distance.

Fang Yuan charged with his dragon body, but was actually unable to leave.

Chapter 1261: Blood Path Demonic Immortal

"You are looking for death!" His dragon eyes stared at Shi Nu.

Shi Nu raised his head to look at Fang Yuan, shouting: "Master, leave quickly! Leave!"

"Shi Nu, I will remember your loyalty." Ying Wu Xie took a deep glance at Shi Nu, before leaving.

He took the other two immortals and quickly retreated.

Because Shi Nu risked his life to hold back Fang Yuan, Ying Wu Xie and the others were able to smoothly leave the licorice regional wall and enter Northern Plains.

The moment they stepped on the grass of Northern Plains, Ying Wu Xie took out Tai Bai Yun Sheng from his immortal aperture.

The latter had already woken up, but his injuries were extremely severe, his life was still in danger.

Combining the four immortals' power, they immediately activated the ancient battle formation Omni-directional Travel and disappeared from the spot.

...

Inside the dream realm.

The battle had already concluded.

The attacking demonic path bandits were all dead.

The merchant caravan did not have it easy as well, as they suffered many casualties and injuries.

Corpses were littered everywhere in the valley and blood filled the area.

"Uncle Big Beard, pull yourself together! Wake up!" The young Fang Yuan was beside Gu Master Big Beard, looking at the terrifying injury with shock and panic.

"Someone, someone save him!" Fang Yuan shouted, his voice somewhat hoarse.

But nobody came.

Fang Yuan quickly ran to the young master: "Lord, Uncle Big Beard was injured while saving you, he is going to die, please save him!"

"He cannot be saved, the injury itself is not a big problem, the main thing is that he has been struck by a poison Gu, we have no way of saving him." The young master shook his head and gave a rueful smile.

"No, you have a way. Weren't you also hit by the same poison Gu?" Fang Yuan persisted.

The young master's expression sank: "You want me to use a precious Gu worm for a mere outsider? Do you know this kind of healing Gu worm can only be used for a limited number of times?"

"But, Uncle Big Beard was injured to save you." Fang Yuan argued.

"Even if he did not save me, I have father's secret guards who would have ensured my safety." The young master sneered, waving his hand at Fang Yuan, "Get lost now, how could my healing Gu worm be used on ants like you guys?"

Fang Yuan gritted his teeth and stared at the young master with clenched fists, not moving from his spot.

"Are you looking to die?" The young master was getting furious.

"Fang Yuan..." At this time, Gu Master Big Beard woke up and softly called out.

Fang Yuan shook, quickly turning around and running to Big Beard's side: "Uncle Big Beard, you are awake!"

Fang Yuan was surprised and happy.

"Don't oppose young master, you will be the one to suffer. Don't keep on begging, how could such a precious healing Gu be used on people like us?" Big Beard smiled mockingly.

"But uncle, your injuries..." Fang Yuan was very upset, choking as he sobbed.

...

Plop.

Shi Nu powerlessly dropped to the ground.

"Hehehe." He looked at the sword dragon hovering in front of him and laughed: "I succeeded! Master was able to escape, haha... Shadow Sect won't be defeated, long live Spectral Soul — ugh!"

Fang Yuan grabbed him with his claws and forcefully crushed him to pieces.

Loosening his dragon claws, rock fragments and debris were scattered over the ground with no signs of Shi Nu's original appearance.

"You're merely dying, what was the point of yelling." Fang Yuan sneered, picking up the most crucial piece from among the rock fragments.

He then flew out of the licorice regional wall and returned once again to Northern Plains.

He threw the crucial piece of rock to the ground, immediately, the immortal aperture inside began to absorb Northern Plains' heaven and earth qi and formed a blessed land outside.

Fang Yuan did not wait, instead activating qi luck sensation to check the locations of Ying Wu Xie and the others.

Fang Yuan immediately discovered that Ying Wu Xie and the rest were already extremely far away from him.

"Hmph! They used that ancient battle formation? But so what? You will all die at my hands, sooner or later."

"But this location, it seems to be in that Earth Trench under Zombie Alliance."

Fang Yuan returned to his human form, slightly frowning.

Of course, he was familiar with the location of Zombie Alliance's Earth Trench. Dark Flow Giant City was still hidden there, unfortunately, no one had found it yet. It was not strange for Ying Wu Xie and the rest to enter it.

"Southern Border Zombie Alliance has already been destroyed, Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance's headquarters were besieged, but Northern Plains Zombie Alliance is still hidden in the Earth Trench. Looks like Ying Wu Xie and the rest will once again go through a period of growth."

This was an expected situation.

Dark Flow Giant City's cultivation resources included all sorts of Immortal Gu from Northern Plains' immortal zombies.

However, Shi Nu was already dead, and they were injured, if they fought again, even if it was in Northern Plains and not the regional wall, Fang Yuan would still have the upper hand.

Shi Nu's blessed land had formed, Fang Yuan entered it but was unable to subdue the land spirit. His attainment in earth path was only at master level and not grandmaster, thus he could not annex this rank seven blessed land and could only leave it for the moment.

Inside the dream...

There was a kind of medicinal herb said to be able to relieve Gu Master Big Beard's poison, the young Fang Yuan chose to sneak out of the caravan and climbed the cliff to pick the medicinal herbs growing there.

The cold mountain wind blew at him, causing his body to shiver greatly.

The cliff was steep, and a careless step could lead to a brutal death.

"I will definitely get the medicinal herb and treat Uncle Big Beard!"

"He saved my life, how could I not repay this debt of kindness?"

"Persevere, Fang Yuan, don't be afraid, huff huff..."

Fang Yuan was breathing roughly as he stretched out his arm and after several attempts, he finally picked out a medicinal herb.

At daybreak, with a basket full of herbs and ragged clothes, he returned to the camp.

...

"Alright, this dream realm is finally over." Fang Yuan woke up from the dream realm.

He finally got rid of the dream realm's interference.

This dream realm was not completely without benefits, the dream path materials inside surpassed Fang Yuan's imagination. In the final scene, the basket of herbs Fang Yuan carried were actually all dream path Gu materials.

"If I dreamed by myself, there is no way I would have had such huge harvests. Could it be that Ying Wu Xie's lead soul into dream is not only an offensive ability, but is actually a killer move to get dream path Gu materials?"

Fang Yuan pondered over this as he flew.

Without the dream realm's interference, he once again began to chase after Ying Wu Xie.

Even if Ying Wu Xie ran to the ends of the world, Fang Yuan would give chase to nip this great problem in the bud!

Snowy Mountain blessed land.

"Fairy Lian Yun, don't use love Immortal Gu again. You have already paid the price and are now unable to speak. If you continue using it repeatedly like this, I really don't know what kind of price you will have to pay next!" Shi Zheng Yi tried to persuade.

Zhao Lian Yun shook her head, her gaze firm and determined.

In the dangerous battle with Zhao Da Niu, love Immortal Gu had displayed its might. But that time, love Immortal Gu did not take immortal essence as the price, instead it seized away a certain thing from Zhao Lian Yun.

This thing was Zhao Lian Yun's voice.

After the battle, Zhao Lian Yun was unable to let out any sounds. She was not even able to make crude grunts and noises that mute people could make.

"Hong Yun is still waiting for me! I cannot just wait here and watch from the sidelines. So what if I can't speak? I can still converse with all of you through Gu worms. It is not a big problem." Zhao Lian Yun transmitted her voice to Shi Zheng Yi.

Shi Zheng Yi sighed, unable to say anything, and could only let Zhao Lian Yun act on her will.

This time, however, no matter how Zhao Lian Yun called out, love Immortal Gu showed no signs of budging.

Helpless, Zhao Lian Yun could only walk out of the twelfth snowy peak's range, along with Shi Zheng Yi.

Once they walked out of this range, Zhao Lian Yun was sent to another snowy peak, separated from Shi Zheng Yi.

Different from before, there were sounds of an intense battle on this snowy peak.

"Who is fighting here? It should be either Yu Yi Ye Zi, Bu Zhen Zi or Mu Ling Lan, right?" Zhao Lian Yun was surprised and happy, as she quickly rushed towards the peak.

She soon reached the hall at the peak.

The stench of blood assaulted her nose, inside the crimson hall, a gorgeous young Gu Immortal was fighting a bitter battle with a Snowy Mountain Gu Immortal.

It was refinement path Gu Immortal Yu Yi Ye Zi!

"Yu Yi Ye Zi, hold on, I am coming to support you." Zhao Lian Yun transmitted her voice.

Yu Yi Ye Zi was both surprised and happy, quickly replying: "Be careful, this is a genuine blood path demonic immortal!"

"What? Blood path!" Zhao Lian Yun got a huge fright. She looked at the enemy with dread and wariness.

Chapter 1262: Golden Sun Spear

Blood path Gu Immortal!

Because of Blood Sea Ancestor and other historical reasons, as well as blood path's characteristics, any person who cultivated blood path would be judged as a demonic path member in the five regions.

In the battle between the alliance of Chu Sect and Bai Zu tribe against the allied Huang Jin tribes, Chu Du's side could have brought in a strong reinforcement. Unfortunately, this person cultivated blood path, Chu Du had immediately refused with not the slightest bit of hesitation.

It was because Chu Du wanted to establish a righteous path force, if he collaborated with a blood path member, his side would be judged as demonic path, and all his painstaking effort would go down the drain.

However, Snowy Mountain blessed land did not have such concerns.

Because Snowy Mountain blessed land was a gathering point of Northern Plains' demonic path Gu Immortals. It was not a tribe or a sect. Whether it be a tribe or a sect, both had the characteristics of nurturing its members, and both had mortal members as well. However, Snowy Mountain blessed land was an entity formed and linked purely through benefits.

Zhao Lian Yun arrived at the tenth snowy peak after leaving the twelfth snowy peak.

The demonic path Gu Immortal guarding this place was called Zhao Pu. He was wearing hemp clothes and cloth shoes, he was bald, had an ordinary appearance and was of a middling stature.

He was standing at the center of the hall, while Yu Yi Ye Zi was retreating back again and again, until he reached the edge of the hall.

His whole body was bathed in blood, his injuries were frightening.

When Zhao Lian Yun saw this companion, she was almost unable to recognize him. Yu Yi Ye Zi was a pretty and delicate looking man, but right now, it was like he had fallen in a boundless sea of blood and was pulled out by someone.

"His other abilities are normal, but he has one blood path immortal killer move that is extremely powerful! When activating it, all of his blood splashes out before turning into a stream of blood. Once the stream of blood touches your skin, you will start bleeding and as time passes, the bleeding will continue to worsen! You need to be careful." Yu When Yu Yi Ye Zi saw Zhao Lian Yun in the middle of the fight, he quickly warned her.

"I understand! Take a rest first, I will deal with him." Zhao Lian Yun stepped forward.

"Good, another person is here looking for death." Zhao Pu stood at the same spot without moving, his hands folded across his chest. He let out a sinister smile, revealing his dense and sharp teeth, a demonic and bloodthirsty aura pounced forward.

Immortal killer move — Life Locking Silver Chain.

Zhao Lian Yun had been preparing this move since earlier, under the consumption of immortal essence, auras of large numbers of Gu worms rose from her body, and a silver light covered her.

Clang clang...

A series of chains clashing against each other could be heard coming from within the silver light.

Shortly afterwards, six long chains shot out from the silver light. The six chains were bright silver and extremely nimble, as they moved around Zhao Lian Yun, forming a strong defense.

Zhao Lian Yun had gone through intensive training and after the life and death battle with Zhao Da Niu, she seemed to have been reborn, her every move was decisive and did not have an inexperienced air like before.

The tenth snowy peak lord, Zhao Pu, noticed Zhao Lian Yun activating her killer move, but actually did not stop her and simply watched her.

Zhao Lian Yun saw this, and immediately activated another immortal killer move.

Meteor rain!

Immortal essence was expended once again, as a patch of deep blue formed above Zhao Lian Yun, above the dome of the hall.

Swish swish swish...

Countless meteors were falling from the sky, raining down like an army of arrows, it was a majestic sight!

These meteors were extremely thin and small, like countless hidden weapons, but their power was majestic as they fell down like a storm that could not be avoided.

If Zhao Pu kept on staying still, he would be turned into meat paste by these tiny meteors.

He indeed did not dare to be so prideful, suddenly a large bloody cloud floated above his head, it was like a huge umbrella that firmly protected Zhao Pu. The falling meteors were blocked by the bloody cloud, but the bloody cloud's volume was shrinking at a visible speed.

Zhao Pu gritted his teeth and stamped his foot, as his body shot towards Zhao Lian Yun like a red ray of light.

Zhao Lian Yun's mind shook, subconsciously taking a step back.

The silver chains moving around her reacted faster than her, one of the chains shot out towards Zhao Pu like a charging dragon.

Zhao Pu quickly dodged and chose another direction to attack.

But at almost the same time, another silver chain shot towards him.

Zhao Pu had no choice but to retreat and choose another direction again.

This repeated a few times, Zhao Pu shockingly realized these silver chains could attack on their own, these chains could be said to have both attack and defensive properties. Not to mention how agile these silver chains were, they could even coordinate with each other.

"Little girl, your defensive killer move is pretty good!" Zhao Pu could not see any results, he did not continue trying and retreated some distance, using his methods to replenish the thinning bloody cloud.

This was natural.

Zhao Lian Yun had many immortal killer moves, these methods were chosen specifically for Zhao Lian Yun by Spirit Affinity House and Heavenly Court.

They were especially suitable for a beginner like Zhao Lian Yun. Not only were the killer moves easy to control, the injuries from backlash in the case of failure were also not severe, the main thing was that these killer moves were extremely refined.

The meteors continued to fall down in torrents.

Zhao Pu was constantly replenishing the bloody cloud above him.

Yu Yi Ye Zi was in a corner, healing himself.

Zhao Lian Yun did not answer, she silently continued to prepare for a third immortal killer move.

It was just that these two killer moves, meteor rain and life locking silver chain, were the ones she had practised the most, this third move was slightly more complex than these two moves.

During the normal training, Zhao Lian Yun only had to spend some effort to activate it.

But in a real battle, she found she had to use a lot more effort.

Although, right now, with the protection of life locking silver chain, the environment was similar to the training field, her mental state was not the same, her few attempts had already ended up in failure.

"Another immortal killer move? Don't you know immortal killer moves cannot be used easily? The more you use them, the more chances where you will expose a weakness. Let me teach you how to fight!" Zhao Pu smiled sinisterly and pounced forward.

But this time, when he had reached halfway, he opened his mouth wide.

Boom!

An enormous explosion occurred, Zhao Lian Yun felt the blood throughout her body shaking violently. A little less than half of the Gu worms that had soared up in Zhao Lian Yun's phantom aperture fell down again because of the disturbance.

Among them, many mortal Gu were destroyed.

Zhao Pu was a blood path demonic immortal, but also had sound path methods which caught Zhao Lian Yun unprepared, even Yu Yi Ye Zi, who had been healing himself, was affected.

Like this, Zhao Pu continued to attack Zhao Lian Yun from all sides while life locking silver chain ensured her safety.

Zhao Lian Yun did not succeed in activating her third immortal killer move due to all sorts of interference from Zhao Pu.

She was filled with a sense of powerlessness, thinking: "This guy is indeed like what Yu Yi Ye Zi described him as, he has a number of methods which are all ordinary and cannot break my life locking silver chain. But he is extremely troublesome, he has all kinds of methods emerging one after another, causing me to repeatedly fail in activating the killer move. This won't do, I need to continue to persevere!"

Zhao Lian Yun firmed her resolution and continued to attempt activating her immortal killer move.

Maybe due to being obstructed too many times and failing many times, it instead tempered her will and strengthened her conviction.

Finally, her eyes suddenly let out a piercing sharp light.

Zhao Lian Yun then stretched out her right arm, and spat at her right palm, spitting out a chain of fire.

The fire stopped at her palm, at first it was only a fireball hovering over her right palm.

But with Zhao Lian Yun continuing to spit out fire, the fire in her hand began to inflate.

It was quite strange, this fire was not inflating as a whole, but it was its left and right side that were enlarging.

Soon, a staff of fire formed in Zhao Lian Yun's hand.

The staff grew until it was the side of an adult's arm. The burning flames on the staff began to shrink.

Several breaths later, the raging fire was completely gone, as it condensed into a staff that seemed to be cast from crimson bronze.

Zhao Lian Yun closed her mouth before suddenly opening it, letting out a shrill scream: "Strike!"

Following her voice, a golden ray of light immediately shot out from her mouth and struck the fire staff.

Chapter 1263: Blood Drain

The fire staff completely absorbed this golden light. The golden light quickly moved around in the fire staff before finally stopping at the head of the staff, gradually turning into a sharp spear.

Right now, the fire staff had changed into a short crimson-golden spear!

Immortal killer move golden sun spear had finally activated successfully!

"It is time for you to die." Zhao Lian Yun let out a breath of air, she was filled with confidence. Her right hand slowly raised the golden sun spear and pointed at Zhao Pu, her willpower soaring high.

Zhao Pu was solemn as he fixed his gaze at the golden sun spear in Zhao Lian Yun's hand, praising it: "Impressive spear, both its temperature and radiance are well restrained, once it bursts out, it will definitely be terrifyingly powerful. But..."

He suddenly changed the subject, revealing a smile as if his scheme had succeeded.

He said to Zhao Lian Yun: "Don't you feel anything strange right now?"

"What?" Only then did Zhao Lian Yun sense something warm was flowing down the sides of her lips.

She lightly wiped with her left hand, it was blood!

Who knew when she had started to bleed.

"This is?!" Zhao Lian Yun's pupils immediately shrunk to pin size and her body started shaking.

"This is my killer move — Blood Drain. Hehehe." Zhao Pu laughed loudly.

"This can't be... you clearly..." Zhao Lian Yun had only spoken a few words, when blood started to flow out of her mouth, dying her white teeth red.

"Hahaha, you want to say that I did not show any signs of activating an immortal killer move? Actually, I had already activated it, I only changed the method." Zhao Pu laughed.

"Could it be the rumored technique — split move?" Yu Yi Ye Zi cried out in shock, his eyes wide open.

Zhao Pu glanced at him: "Kid, you are quite knowledgeable."

Gu Masters nurtured, used, and refined Gu, no matter which aspect, they were all very profound and deep.

Refining Gu involved all sorts of refinement methods. Using Gu naturally was also the same.

Among immortal killer moves, there were many extraordinary methods and techniques. For instance, the consecutive moves of Blazing Heaven Demoness. She could use two or more fire path immortal killer moves one after the other, achieving a stronger effect in the end.

Another example was Fang Yuan's variant moves. Myriad self, formed from the convergence of enslavement and strength path, could produce large numbers of strength path phantoms to battle. But Fang Yuan was able to create a variant move, myriad self first style, strength path giant hand. This variant move used myriad self as the foundation, but was able to produce an offensive effect that myriad self could not achieve by itself.

And the method Zhao Pu was using right now was a split move. If he directly activated blood drain, it would definitely be sensed by the highly vigilant Zhao Lian Yun, and she would either disturb him or evade. However, Zhao Pu split this immortal killer move into multiple parts, and used them as he fought. After he unleashed all of these split moves, he achieved the effect of blood drain.

The advantage of this method was clear. There was no indication of the move being used, which made it impossible to guard against!

"Damn it! So he had been hiding and pretending, he attacked multiple times but did not break my life locking silver chain's defense, it was actually because he was secretly plotting!"

Right now, Zhao Lian Yun found that she was not only bleeding from her mouth, blood was starting to flow continuously from her nose and ears as well. Her eyes were also filled with some traces of blood, causing her vision to become blurry.

Zhao Lian Yun's heart thumped loudly as she recalled Yu Yi Ye Zi's appearance.

"I was still hit by that move!"

"If it continues like this, would not I end up the same way as Yu Yi Ye Zi?"

"He is truly crafty!!"

In her agitation, Zhao Lian Yun threw the golden sun spear towards Zhao Pu.

But Zhao Pu was already prepared, he was extremely vigilant against Zhao Lian Yun's fire spear, Zhao Lian Yun's shoulder had just started to move, when he had already begun to move.

The golden sun spear did not have the ability to lock onto the target, but it was extremely fast, brushing past Zhao Pu.

Zhao Pu got a great fright, the golden sun spear pierced through the hall, shooting towards outside the hall before it exploded. A boundless heat wave swept over all directions. The dazzling golden light and the flames instantly formed a small sun-like sphere. But soon, this small sun disappeared completely.

"Such power, if it truly struck me..." Zhao Pu's body was soaked in cold sweat: "Fortunately, they have already been struck by my move."

"Oh." Yu Yi Ye Zi inwardly sighed, and walked towards Zhao Lian Yun, prepared to fight alongside her.

Zhao Lian Yun was downcast, her morale falling sharply. She had very little real battle experience, her state of mind was easily influenced. This immortal killer move, golden sun spear, was a valuable advantage, but now it was wasted by her.

"Your injuries..." Zhao Lian Yun worriedly looked at Yu Yi Ye Zi.

Yu Yi Ye Zi's injuries showed no signs of getting better.

Zhao Pu laughed: "Did you think I was intentionally letting you off when I let you rest and heal? Hehehe, as long as you are hit by my move, unless I personally cancel the effect, normal methods won't be of any use. You have already tried, do you see any effects?"

"But I am quite benevolent. I will allow you both to surrender, as long as you kneel and beg for mercy, giving me your Immortal Gu, I will take you as my slaves and spare your lives."

"Stop dreaming!" Zhao Lian Yun gritted her teeth, refusing Zhao Pu's invitation.

Zhao Pu ignored her and laughed: "The battle is decided, are you still unaware of your situation? A wise person submits to circumstances, you are still young, it is over if you die, but you will still have hope as long as you live."

Yu Yi Ye Zi sneered: "I am indeed unable to heal my injuries and can only let the blood continue to flow. But I have made some gains. I have already deduced that as long as we kill you, the injuries on our body will heal by themselves."

"Huh?" Zhao Pu's expression slightly changed, he sized up Yu Yi Ye Zi once again: "Kid, I have changed my opinion about you."

Yu Yi Ye Zi was a genius refinement path Gu Immortal, having extremely deep attainment level in refinement path. Even rank seven Gu Immortals often discussed Gu refinement matters with him, and even asked him for guidance.

Yu Yi Ye Zi was not only proficient in Gu refinement, he also was skilled in deducing Gu recipes.

Refinement path and wisdom path were close to each other and could coordinate with each other.

Yu Yi Ye Zi was able to deduce the truth from his injuries along with Zhao Pu's various behaviors.

"We must kill him before all our blood is drained. If he doesn't die, we will die!" Yu Yi Ye Zi transmitted his voice to Zhao Lian Yun.

They were already forced into a dead end. They had no options other than to fearlessly charge ahead and kill the enemy to have the right to survive.

"Charge!" Zhao Lian Yun called out, and charged forward without hesitation.

"Conceited brats, I will let you taste my true strength!" Zhao Pu laughed loudly, and valiantly charged forward, fighting as one against two.

Both sides went at each other, neither yielding a step.

Life locking silver chains shuttled back and forth, Zhao Pu had a bloody cloud above him and one below his feet, he avoided three chains and immediately spat blood towards the three chains coming from behind.

The blood dyed the silver chains, immediately turning them into a pool of blood.

"Eight refinement gates, third gate -hand gate - open!" Yu Yi Ye Zi took the chance to palm-strike towards Zhao Pu's back from afar.

Immediately, two exquisite palm silhouettes struck Zhao Pu's back with incredible speed.

Zhao Pu gave a muffled groan, blood suddenly splashed out from his back and covered his injuries.

A slightly surprised expression flashed past his face, as he thought: "Strange, why is this kid's attack much stronger now?"

Yu Yi Ye Zi might be a refinement path Gu Immortal, but his battle strength was also extraordinary.

As long as he was given some time, he could target his opponent's weaknesses properly. Especially his immortal killer move — Eight Refinement Gates, it could change according to the situation and unleash some properties that were specially effective against the enemy.

Yu Yi Ye Zi and Zhao Lian Yun knew they had no way to retreat, and instantly burst out with remarkable battle strength.

Chapter 1264: Crying, Screaming

If humans staked their all, their danger would naturally increase explosively.

In contrast, the blood path demonic immortal Zhao Pu was not willing to fight to the death, he just needed to delay some time and he could obtain victory.

As such, for a moment, Zhao Pu was instead suppressed by Zhao Lian Yun and Yu Yi Ye Zi.

However, Zhao Pu's battle experience was much greater than these two immortals of Central Continent.

He was extremely slippery, moving around all the time, Zhao Lian Yun and Yu Yi Ye Zi did everything they could but could not catch him at all.

As time passed, the situation inclined towards Zhao Pu.

Yu Yi Ye Zi was the first to weaken in his attacks.

He had been struck much earlier than Zhao Lian Yun and had suffered much greater injuries, now because of the high blood loss, he fell unconscious.

"Your friend might have died from blood loss, you are next. You also don't have much time, why aren't you attacking more frequently?" Zhao Pu laughed.

Zhao Lian Yun was in low spirits. She knew Zhao Pu was intentionally provoking her to disturb her mind, but she was unable to calm her mind and became more and more agitated.

Blood had started flowing out of her eyes, her sight was completely blurry and red.

More terrifyingly, blood was not only pouring out of her seven orifices, but also from the countless pores on her body.

"Damn it... damn it...." An intense dizziness constantly attacked Zhao Lian Yun, her whole body was starting to shake and waver.

Finally, Zhao Pu sent a long ranged attack which sent Zhao Lian Yun flying. She fell to the ground and rolled three times before stopping.

"Damn it!" Zhao Lian Yun pushed the ground with her hands and tried to stand up, but she had lost too much blood and had no strength left in her.

She could not even prop her body up anymore.

"It's over." Zhao Pu folded his arms across his chest, as he walked slowly towards Zhao Lian Yun and looked down at her.

Blood.

It was flowing out continuously from Zhao Lian Yun's body.

Soon, a pool of blood had formed around her.

Zhao Lian Yun had become a blood soaked person in this pool, blood was flowing down from her eyes along with her tears.

"Is it over..."

"This is where I fall."

"Blood... I am not in the least bit afraid this time, Hong Yun."

Zhao Lian Yun recalled a scene of the past.

That was during the fighting for Imperial Court.

Zhao Lian Yun had lost the protection of her father, and was unwillingly turned into a political chip to be married to Wei tribe's young master, and had no choice but to rely on Ma Hong Yun.

During one battle, Zhao Lian Yun was unfortunately shot in the thigh by a falling arrow.

Blood flowed.

"I am going to die, ahhh, so painful! I am going to die!" Zhao Lian Yun was lying inside a carriage, screaming and crying.

"Don't make a fuss, Lady Xiao Yun, you are not going to die. This is only a little injury." Ma Hong Yun proficiently dressed her injury while consoling her.

"Blood, so much blood! Don't you know I get dizzy at the sight of blood?! I have never suffered such a heavy injury." Zhao Lian Yun groaned.

"You, how could you be so squeamish? Injuries are normal for people of Northern Plains. Many times, the scars are a source of glory and symbol of our feats!"

Zhao Lian Yun rolled her eyes: "Do you know how to comfort people? Sigh, how could I be so unlucky..."

"Hahaha." Ma Hong Yun laughed loudly, carelessly using a bit more strength.

Zhao Lian Yun cried out in pain: "Aaahh! Be softer! Also, what are you laughing at. I have suffered such a serious injury and you seem to be very happy."

Ma Hong Yun quickly waved his hand, but was still laughing: "I'm not gloating, it is just that I feel Lady Xiao Yun is truly cute. You normally act like an elder, and fill people with awe. But only now do I truly feel you are a little sister younger than me."

"You are getting truly arrogant..." Zhao Lian Yun was just about to erupt, when suddenly, Ma Hong Yun touched her forehead.

Zhao Lian Yun was dazed. For some reason, she got a feeling of warmth.

Ma Hong Yun ignored her: "There is no fever, this is good. Lady Xiao Yun, you cannot be so squeamish. Suffering some injuries and letting out some blood is nothing. If you scream so loudly again, people will ridicule you."

Her recollection ended here.

"Ridicule?"

"You should not be able to ridicule me now, right?"

"You brat..."

"I really used up all my blood to save you."

"It is truly strange, I actually willingly sent myself to death for someone."

"So, even if I die, I am willing to do this!"

Such thoughts emerged in Zhao Lian Yun's mind.

"Die!" Zhao Pu gave a loud shout and pierced forward with his hand like a sharp knife.

A fatal blow!

If this battle struck true, it would pierce through Zhao Lian Yun's head like tofu.

But right at this time.

An intense radiance burst out from Zhao Lian Yun's body.

The radiance was so glaring that Zhao Pu had no choice but to close his eyes and step back.

"This is..."

"Why is there such a strong light?"

"Impossible! This aura... so powerful!"

"Ahhhhhhh——!"

Zhao Pu let out a miserable cry.

His whole body did not budge in the light. Soon, he was like the melting snow under a hot sun, completely destroyed.

At the crucial moment, love Immortal Gu showed its might once again, directly killing Zhao Pu!

Northern Plains, in the depths of Earth Trench.

"Ying Wu Xie, where will you hide now?!" Fang Yuan's sword dragon form roared in the Earth Trench, his voice, filled with killing intent, resounded everywhere.

Relying on qi luck sensation, Fang Yuan had moved at extreme speed and finally reached here.

From within the darkness, a giant city slowly rose up.

Ying Wu Xie was standing on top of the giant city.

"I have been waiting for quite some time." Ying Wu Xie spoke, his gaze tranquil and his tone indifferent.

"Hmph! Shi Nu is dead, you want to fight me with just you four and this mortal Gu house?" Fang Yuan sneered.

Dark Flow Giant City was huge and looked majestic, but it was only a mortal Gu house, not an Immortal Gu House.

It was not easy to form an Immortal Gu House. Shadow Sect possessed many Immortal Gu, but they also could not casually upgrade Dark Flow Giant City to an Immortal Gu House.

If they had an Immortal Gu House, Fang Yuan would feel a lot of apprehension.

Because the power of an Immortal Gu House increased with the amount of immortal essence expended. Fang Yuan had once used Giant Sun's immortal essence to control Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage and shined in the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain.

But Dark Flow Giant City was only a mortal Gu house, and it was absolutely not enough to put fear in Fang Yuan.

"Then what if you add me?" A second figure appeared on top of Dark Flow Giant City.

This person was only a rank six Gu Immortal, but he was an 'old acquaintance' of Fang Yuan.

It was the spy Shadow Sect had inserted in Lang Ya Sect, refinement path Gu Immortal Sixth Hair!

Fang Yuan's gaze became slightly dark.

Fang Yuan did not think much of Sixth Hair's strength. But Sixth Hair and Fang Yuan were members of Lang Ya Sect, both of them had an information path alliance agreement.

This made it extremely inconvenient for Fang Yuan to go against Sixth Hair, with just slight carelessness, he would suffer the backlash of the information path alliance agreement and be injured.

However, Fang Yuan had mentally prepared for Sixth Hair's appearance.

"Die!" Fang Yuan swung his dragon tail, directly charging forward.

Dark Flow Giant City quickly moved back, and at the same time, a battlefield killer move rose up and large numbers of yaksha octopuses closed in.

"Your status has already made Fang Yuan hesitate. We just need to delay some time and we can use Omni-directional Travel again." Ying Wu Xie patted Sixth Hair's shoulder.

"Lord, you should go take a rest, let me handle this." Sixth Hair said to Ying Wu Xie.

Ying Wu Xie nodded and entered Dark Flow Giant City.

It was a slaughterhouse.

Despite there being large numbers of yaksha octopuses, they were not a match for Fang Yuan.

The ancient sword dragon raised a bloody storm, rampaging around the battlefield.

Dark Flow Giant City was within his sight, but Fang Yuan did not dare to carelessly use dragon breath, it would be bad if he killed Sixth Hair by mistake.

It would be himself who would suffer instead.

He might even be counterattacked by Ying Wu Xie and the rest due to that and lose his life here.

Ying Wu Xie and the others were in a bad situation, but Fang Yuan was not blindly optimistic. He knew he had the upper hand, but was not yet able to turn it into crushing dominance.

Especially when there was Bai Ning Bing, who could turn into the Bai Xiang state, and Ying Wu Xie, who had lead soul into dream. Even though the former only had rank six cultivation and the latter's lead soul into dream was incomplete.

"Information path... when can I be free from its restrictions?"

Fang Yuan was vexed.

Information path was a pain that had repeatedly troubled him.

Fang Yuan had also tried hard, but lacking fortuitous encounters, he had not been able to solve this issue.

Sixth Hair presided over the battle, his strategy was not to win, but to not make any mistakes.

Chapter 1265: Nightmare Demonic Colts

After Fang Yuan killed the wave of yaksha octopuses, wall climbing demon apes started to appear. These apes similarly were beasts of Earth Trench, not inferior to yaksha octopus.

After this wave of wall climbing demon apes was eliminated, Fang Yuan was attacked by a large group of red flame snakes.

"These beast groups were probably all controlled by Northern Plains' Zombie Alliance division. For example, yaksha octopuses probably belonged to the rank seven immortal zombie Dragon Commander Ye Cha."

"The Zombie Alliance divisions in other regions were all besieged, only on Northern Plains Zombie Alliance's end did they rely on Earth Trench to remain until now."

"Not only these desolate beasts, looking at Hei Lou Lan's performance earlier, there probably are Immortal Gu as well!"

"If so, I will have to re-evaluate the battle strength of Ying Wu Xie and the others. However, it is not possible to grasp immortal killer moves in a short period of time, with just Immortal Gu, when there is conflict between dao marks..."

Fang Yuan analyzed the situation while fighting.

At this time, a large group of horse desolate beasts galloped towards Fang Yuan.

These horses were extremely strange, they had a pair of sheep horns on their heads, their whole bodies looked like they were burnt charcoal, they were letting out dense smoke from their noses and their tails and limbs were burning with a dull red fire.

"Huh?"

"Dream path desolate beast nightmare demonic colt!"

Fang Yuan was stunned, before recognizing it shortly afterwards.

"So it seems, nightmare demonic colts had already appeared during this time period..."

"Moreover, in such high numbers!"

Fang Yuan was greatly joyous.

Nightmare demonic colts were a dream path desolate beast, this desolate beast was extremely common during his first life of five hundred years. But now at this time, it was extremely rare, Fang Yuan thought this horse had yet to appear.

Times changed, humans were changing and the world was also changing.

Many Gu materials were extinct, leading to the decline of strength path, qi path and other paths. Similarly, many new Gu materials were constantly formed.

Dream path.

This path had just begun to flourish near the end of Fang Yuan's first life. At present, the Gu Immortals were all researching it, although they made some gains, they were extremely small and almost could not be considered anything.

Only after a few hundred years would many dream path Gu materials start to appear, nightmare demonic colts were one of them.

Fang Yuan had thus believed nightmare demonic colts did not exist at this time. But this group of nightmare demonic colts made him realize his estimation was completely wrong!

"Good thing I was wrong! I must get these nightmare demonic colts!" Fang Yuan was extremely happy.

What did dream path desolate beasts signify?

Large amounts of dream path Gu materials!

Why was Fang Yuan painstakingly going deep into his own dreams?

It was to gather dream path materials!

If he had these nightmare demonic colts, Fang Yuan could cut the meat of these desolate horses and refine large numbers of dream path mortal Gu, and even dream path Immortal Gu!

When he was exploring the giant dream realm in Southern Border, why could he not use unravel dream as much as he liked? Why did he have to plan carefully every time he used it?

Simply put, wasn't it because he did not have enough dream path mortal Gu?

The efficiency of refining dream path mortal Gu alone was truly too low.

"These nightmare demonic colts are all mine!"

Fang Yuan started to capture these nightmare demonic colts.

His ancient sword dragon form was extremely fast, maneuvering around these nightmare demonic colts with no obstruction.

Fang Yuan was trying to knock these nightmare demonic colt unconscious, and then raise them in the sovereign immortal aperture.

However, Shadow Sect had clearly prepared for it and had made some arrangements on these nightmare demonic colts.

Fang Yuan tried hard, but finally discovered he could not capture these nightmare demonic colt alive, at most, he could kill them and obtain their corpses.

But even so, Fang Yuan had a huge harvest.

After killing these nightmare demonic colts, Fang Yuan then slaughtered the next few waves of desolate beast groups, among which were ancient desolate beasts as well.

Fang Yuan's battle strength was already at the upper layers of rank seven, whether it be the desolate beast groups or the battlefield killer move, they were not a threat to Fang Yuan.

Dark Flow Giant City did not have an endless supply of desolate beast groups.

After a while, Fang Yuan had killed all the beast groups, and he spent some time in breaking the battlefield killer move, wrecking Dark Flow Giant City.

However, a lot of his time had still been wasted, Ying Wu Xie and the others had already left.

Sixth Hair had remained behind, like Shi Nu, to hold back Fang Yuan.

Sixth Hair's cultivation could not compare to Shi Nu's, but he had a huge advantage.

He looked at Fang Yuan with no fear: "Do you dare to kill me?"

"What use is there in killing you? Wait till I kill Ying Wu Xie and let you fall into despair and suffering." Fang Yuan gave a sinister smile, as his dragon body ascended and flew out of Earth Trench.

The ashen faced Sixth Hair was left behind, along with the ruined Dark Flow city.

Northern Plains was extremely huge, even though they had Omni-directional Travel, Snowy Mountain blessed land was at the extreme north-west.

Omni-directional Travel could not be used continuously, while Ying Wu Xie was hurrying towards Snowy Mountain blessed land, Fang Yuan caught up to them once again.

"Let's see who will help you this time?" The ancient sword dragon rushed over.

Lead soul into dream!

Ying Wu Xie activated his immortal killer move.

Fang Yuan was hit again.

However, this dream realm was unexpectedly deep, he had to use unravel dream to break the dream realm and return to reality.

"What is going on?" Fang Yuan immediately sensed something fishy.

This was somewhat beyond what he had expected, causing him to suffer a minor loss.

Ying Wu Xie laughed: "I sacrificed all those nightmare demonic colts earlier. Do you think these dream path immortal materials can be taken so easily? I will give you advice, don't chase us, if you continue chasing, even if you have the upper extreme heavenly eagle, you will lose your life."

"Hmph, crafty guy!" Fang Yuan snorted.

Regardless of what intention Ying Wu Xie had, whether it was provocation or probing, Fang Yuan decided to give up chasing for now.

The dream realm was constantly pestering him, he had to get through the entirety of the dream realm, only then could he be completely free of worries.

Undoubtedly, lead soul into dream was truly troublesome. Even though Fang Yuan had unravel dream, he could not resolve it in one attempt, and had to pass through all the stages of the dream realm.

Inside the dream.

Southern Border, dawn.

The wet dew and the dense cloud-like mountain fog produced a depressing feeling.

The merchant caravan did not continue moving, moving in this dense fog on the mountain was very likely to create problems.

The young Fang Yuan was sitting beside a simple bed.

Gu Master Big Beard was lying on the bed, and was already on the verge of dying.

"Fang Yuan, thank you for the medicinal herbs." Gu Master Big Beard spoke with an extremely weak voice.

Fang Yuan was feeling extremely stifled, as he sobbed: "Uncle Big Beard, you will get better."

Gu Master Big Beard shook his head: "How could I not be clear of my injuries? Don't cry, child, crying is of no use to us."

"I was once young like you, and had big dreams."

"Unfortunately, my aptitude was too bad, and I finally sank into this current state."

"Hehe."

"This world is too big, while we are too small."

"When I was a child, I wanted to be a grand hero, like those legendary figures of the righteous path. When I was a youngster, I wanted to be a clan leader. When I was an adult, I was satisfied with becoming a clan elder. When I was a middle aged man, I was exiled from the clan, I felt that I could live by myself just as well, I was satisfied with just raising my Gu worms and myself."

"Do you know what I want now?"

Fang Yuan wept softly: "What?"

"I just want to quietly lie down inside a quiet room and slowly recall the past, until death comes to take me." Gu Master Big Beard had a self-mocking expression.

"Then, then should I leave?" Fang Yuan did not know what to do.

"Leave. Let me be here alone, I don't want others to see my dying appearance." Gu Master Big Beard said.

Fang Yuan slowly stood up and hesitantly walked to the door.

At this time, Gu Master Big Beard spoke once again: "You must have read \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>. There is a chapter which tells the story of the miniman walking out of Ordinary Abyss."

"We are all minimen, and we all want to walk out of Ordinary Abyss."

"Oh..."

"You must continue on, Fang Yuan."

"Continue living, continue persevering."

"It is a pity that all my Gu were destroyed in the battle. This is my advice to you, my only gift. To us minor characters, crying is of no use, no one will hear us even if we shout, we can only persevere by ourselves."

"Persevere until you accomplish great feats, become extraordinary. Either that, or embrace death."

Chapter 1266: I love him!

"Did we win?" Zhao Lian Yun had to use quite some effort to climb out of the blood pool.

Her injuries were severe, and she was blacking out.

Fortunately, Zhao Pu was already dead, and the blood drain immortal killer move on Zhao Lian Yun and Yu Yi Ye Zi also dissipated.

If it did not dissipate, Zhao Lian Yun and Yu Yi Ye Zi would undoubtedly follow Zhao Pu to death.

Huff, huff...

On the other side, Yu Yi Ye Zi was breathing roughly, standing up while leaning on the wall.

When he saw Zhao Lian Yun, this young Gu Immortal was dazed and turned pale: "Lian... Fairy Lian Yun... your face... no... your body..."

Yu Yi Ye Zi's eyes were wide open, and he stuttered, not knowing how to express himself.

Zhao Lian Yun felt strange, transmitting her voice: "What's wrong with me?"

She lowered her head to look at herself, the first thing she saw were her hands.

A pair of old and skinny hands.

Zhao Lian Yun's heart gave a jolt as she found she had unknowingly become an elderly woman!

Her back was bent, wrinkles covered her body, her sight was blurry and her hair had turned white.

"What's happening?" Zhao Lian Yun was shocked.

She grabbed her hair, easily pulling out strands of white hair. Her strong hair roots had degraded and become loose.

Yu Yi Ye Zi spoke with a heavy voice: "It is probably love Gu. Love Gu consumed your lifespan to burst out with the terrifying power that could directly kill Zhao Pu!"

"Is that so?" Zhao Lian Yun was dazed and at a loss.

Anyone who turned from the prime of their youth to an old and frail person the next moment, would definitely receive a huge shock in their mind.

"Yes." Yu Yi Ye Zi nodded, and consoled, "But you don't have to worry, you can restore your youth by using lifespan Gu. Normal Gu Immortals might not be able to gather lifespan Gu, but you are different, you are the current generation fairy of Spirit Affinity House, the sect will definitely provide you lifespan Gu."

Zhao Lian Yun did not reply.

She was feeling complicated emotions. Shock, disappointment, disbelief, dazedness.

She was an otherworldly demon, but even before transmigrating, she had not experienced becoming this old.

After a while of silence, Zhao Lian Yun finally recovered from the shock.

"I will continue going forward!"

"Old age doesn't matter, Hong Yun is still waiting for me."

Zhao Lian Yun gazed at the distant first snowy peak through the window, her gaze becoming resolute once more.

"You cannot continue!!" Yu Yi Ye Zi was shocked, quickly walking over to Zhao Lian Yun and holding her arm.

"Love Immortal Gu is powerful but it is not stable. Maybe it will take your lifespan the next time as well. If so, you will definitely die!" Yu Yi Ye Zi persuaded.

"So what if I die?" The old Zhao Lian Yun looked at the young Yu Yi Ye Zi with a slight smile.

Her smile was not even a little beautiful, but Yu Yi Ye Zi was dazed.

Then, Zhao Lian Yun softly drew back her arm.

She clearly did not use much strength, but Yu Yi Ye Zi felt a formless strength attacking his heart, letting him voluntarily release his hand.

He then quietly stood on the spot, looking at Zhao Lian Yun's hunched back, looking at her walking towards the outside of the hall with heavy and aged steps.

This scene was ordinary and nothing strange, but Yu Yi Ye Zi felt an intense tremor in his heart.

He even subconsciously held his breath, as Zhao Lian Yun's weak receding figure imprinted deeply in him at this moment.

"What kind of spirit is this!"

"For her love, she is willing to make sacrifices, unafraid of death and destruction."

"Zhao Lian Yun, I would have definitely died in Zhao Pu's hands without you."

"Alright, let me follow you, at worst, this life will be paid to you!"

Yu Yi Ye Zi was not old, he was still hot-blooded, and after firming up his mind, he quickly followed Zhao Lian Yun.

There was not much immortal essence left in her phantom aperture, Zhao Lian Yun was also worried that recklessly summoning love Immortal Gu would spend what little remained of her lifespan. As such, she chose to walk down the peak.

Under the effect of the fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation, Zhao Lian Yun and Yu Yi Ye Zi separated, and she alone went to another snowy peak.

There was still a large hall at the peak, and the atmosphere was quiet.

"There was a battle here!" Zhao Lian Yun slowly walked to the hall, finding the inside of the hall in ruins, signs of an intense battle were everywhere.

"Fairy Lian Yun?" A voice suddenly transmitted to Zhao Lian Yun's ears.

Zhao Lian Yun was slightly dazed, before shortly recognizing the voice as that water path Gu Immortal, Mu Ling Lan's voice.

"This is the eighth peak of Snowy Mountain blessed land, I fought with the owner of this peak, Xiao Fei Fei, and now, we are both wounded."

"We are both hiding right now, healing our injuries as quickly as possible."

"You need to be careful, don't be hit by her ability. She has an immortal killer move which can cause the target to continuously lose their memories."

Just as he finished speaking, a ray of strange light flew and struck Zhao Lian Yun's forehead.

"No!" Mu Ling Lan quickly called out, "Every time you lose your memory, the related memory will float in your mind. Use Immortal Gu to defend yourself, don't use any immortal killer moves, that would be even more dangerous. If you forget an immortal killer move by any chance, you will suffer the backlash from the immortal killer move. Persevere, wait until I heal my injuries and recover some strength to fight!"

Zhao Lian Yun quickly agreed.

She hid in a corner and used Immortal Gu to protect herself, then waited for the killer move to activate.

"Damn it!" Zhao Lian Yun gradually felt unease. She knew her situation, she had just recently become a Gu Immortal, most of her battles came from during her training time. It would be an extremely huge blow to her if the memories of this period were erased.

Memories began to surface in her mind...

Northern Plains.

Ma tribe was defeated, and surrendered to Hei tribe.

"I didn't think we could still live, Lady Xiao Yun!" Ma Hong Yun held Zhao Lian Yun's hands and spun round and round on the spot, "Hahaha."

"Let me down, you big fool!" Zhao Lian Yun shouted.

...

Imperial Court blessed land.

"You, kid, are truly lucky, you actually became Chang tribe's son-in-law, hahaha." Zhao Lian Yun patted Ma Hong Yun's shoulder.

Ma Hong Yun chuckled while scratching his hair: "Lady Xiao Yun, don't worry, you have helped me so much, I will treat you well."

Zhao Lian Yun gave a sound of acknowledgement and nodded: "Then I will rely on you."

Inside, however, she felt strange: Why do I have some feelings of loss and bitterness?

...

Inside Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

"To think that you are an otherworldly demon! You are actually lurking by Ma Hong Yun's side! Hehehe, you have such guts, you are really daring. Unfortunately... you met me." Giant Sun's will exuded strong killing intent.

Zhao Lian Yun felt like she had fallen in an ice cave, shouting in her mind: "Damn it, there is still such an obstacle? Transmigrators are otherworldly demons? This world is too big of a trap! Oh no, my death is certain this time!! I am actually going to die here?"

But the next moment, Ma Hong Yun stood in front of Zhao Lian Yun.

He spread open his arms, protecting Zhao Lian Yun behind him.

"Boy, you want to protect an otherworldly demon?" Giant Sun's will sharpened his tone, his expression becoming ice-cold.

"What otherworldly demon! I don't know any otherworldly demon, I only know she is Lady Xiao Yun, without her help, I would likely have been killed already." Ma Hong Yun tried his best to defend Zhao Lian Yun.

Zhao Lian Yun's pupils shrunk as she looked at Ma Hong Yun in a daze.

"Even against Giant Sun's will, this fellow will still stand up for me?"

"Why?"

"I am clearly an otherworldly demon, and not a person of this world!"

"You idiot, you are going to die. By protecting me, you are offending Giant Sun's will, that is your ancestor, you idiot!"

Hei Lou Lan's gaze towards Zhao Lian Yun started showing killing intent.

"No, Lady Xiao Yun is innocent, you must not harm her!" Ma Hong Yun was extremely determined, he wholeheartedly wanted to protect Zhao Lian Yun.

However, Giant Sun's special will did not care about Ma Hong Yun, directly making a move against Zhao Lian Yun.

"No——!" Ma Hong Yun saw the situation going south, he called out in a moment of desperation, extending both his arms and hugging Zhao Lian Yun within his bosom.

During this moment.

Time seemed to have become endlessly slow.

Zhao Lian Yun was curled up in Ma Hong Yun's chest, her heart beginning to beat wildly.

An unprecedented feeling of safety and warmth filled her heart.

Following that came a kind of panic.

This panic was not towards her life hanging by a thread, instead it was a strange feeling that came from the depths of her heart.

Zhao Lian Yun found at this moment that she had hopelessly fallen in love with the stupid Ma Hong Yun.

In this world, there could be guys who would watch the stars with her, accompany her to shout at the valley, heal her and give her flowers. But who would sacrifice their life for her?!

In this world, otherworldly demons were despised by even Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, who would be so stupid to protect her?

Ma Hong Yun.

Ma Hong Yun!

...

The memories surfaced one by one in Zhao Lian Yun's mind.

Then, they started to disappear one by one.

"No, stop it!" Tears filled Zhao Lian Yun's face as she called out with incomparable sorrow.

Xiao Fei Fei's voice transmitted: "Hehehe, when you are struck by my immortal killer move, you will lose your most precious memories. Do you feel pain? It doesn't matter, the more you forget, the more relaxed you will be, maybe you will even smile. Hehehe...."

The memories disappeared, a smile suddenly appeared on Zhao Lian Yun's face.

"Don't smile. This is Xiao Fei Fei's famous sinister killer move, it will kill people while they smile. The longer you smile, the more easily you will lose your life." Mu Ling Lan quickly transmitted his voice to warn her.

However, Zhao Lian Yun seemed to have turned silly, as her smile became increasingly wider.

"Damn it!" Mu Ling Lan knew he had to take action.

He unleashed his killer move after a long period of preparation, creating an incredible effect!

"Ahh! You actually..." Xiao Fei Fei had exposed her location while attacking Zhao Lian Yun, and was struck by the fatal move while unprepared, losing her life miserably.

"Fairy Lian Yun, you need to persevere!" Mu Ling Lan quickly rushed over and helped Zhao Lian Yun.

Zhao Lian Yun still had a smile on her face, but she was no longer in a daze.

Two streams of translucent tears dripped down her face from her eyes.

Her eyes were blurry from age and her hair had turned white, she could only use Gu worms to transmit her voice.

"What should I do?"

"I have forgotten almost everything about him, even his appearance."

"I only remember his name."

"I only remember...."

"That I love him."

Chapter 1267: Central Continent's Reinforcements

Northern Plains, Snowy Mountain blessed land, first snowy peak.

"Once more." Lady Wan Shou approached Ma Hong Yun step by step, holding a ball of lightning in her hand.

"Go ahead." Ma Hong Yun nonchalantly rolled his eyes.

Lady Wan Shou snorted, throwing the ball to Ma Hong Yun's chest.

Crackle crackle crackle!

Lightning sparkled all over Ma Hong Yun's body, Ma Hong Yun was clenching his teeth, actually maintaining his consciousness amidst the lightning assault.

When the lightning assault ended, Ma Hong Yun did not faint, but was sweating all over, with a flushed face.

"I failed again!" Lady Wan Shou could not believe it: "What is going on? Something is not right!"

She had already failed who knows how many times in trying to lightning refine Ma Hong Yun.

Even though the success rate of rank eight Immortal Gu was extremely low, there was no reason for being stuck at this one juncture from the start.

Lady Wan Shou felt like vomiting blood.

Especially when she saw that Ma Hong Yun had already advanced to rank five peak stage, moreover, because of the repeated lightning refinement failures, many lightning path dao marks were engraved on his body.

If Ma Hong Yun cultivated lightning path, these dao marks would no doubt give him tremendous help.

"Aren't you tired of always doing this? How about changing to another method, even I am bored." Ma Hong Yun knew his death was certain, so he no longer cared at this point, making fun of Lady Wan Shou.

Lady Wan Shou's eyes shot out cold light that shone on Ma Hong Yun, an incomparable pain immediately attacked his body and mind.

He no longer had the content expression, as he raised his head and cried out miserably, his whole body twitching non-stop.

Lady Wan Shou silently listened to Ma Hong Yun's screams, but the cold light from her eyes did not stop flickering.

Ma Hong Yun yelled himself hoarse, finally, his eyes rolled back and he fainted.

Lady Wan Shou gave a cold snort, the cold light from her eyes gradually dissipated and revealed her thoughtful expression.

....

"Zhao Lian Yun is already close to dying."

"The number of times love Immortal Gu can show its might has become limited."

"It seems Lady Wan Shou has also noticed something."

Far away in Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace, South Desolation Immortal was well aware of the situation in Snowy Mountain blessed land.

Right now, he was also somewhat impatient.

Central Continent's Gu Immortals had still not appeared, what on earth were they planning?

"Capturing love Immortal Gu was preparation Ancestor Giant Sun made in the past, we, his descendants, shall complete this perfectly."

"Black Extremity, prepare to move!"

South Desolation Immortal sent his command to Longevity Heaven through information path methods.

In Longevity Heaven, the Eight Extremities were still controlling Calamity Luck Altar and besieging Five Elements Grandmaster.

As they heard the command, two rank seven Gu Immortals immediately separated from the formation, Black Extremity and Flood Extremity.

"We shall go now." Black Extremity said to the others.

"Come back quickly." Heaven Extremity did not dare to split too much of his attention, without two rank seven Gu Immortals, they were even more helpless against Five Elements Grandmaster, and could only maintain the current situation while they waited for Black Extremity and Flood Extremity to return.

Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace.

"Everything is going according to plan, if this continues, love Immortal Gu and Ma Hong Yun will return to Longevity Heaven. Central Continent Gu Immortals, if you still don't make a move, it will be too late." South Desolation Immortal thought to himself.

Rumble!

A loud sound was heard.

The entirety of Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace shook violently and was actually forced to reveal itself.

"Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace! So all of it was your doing!!"

"Destroy this Heavenly Palace, take revenge for our companions!"

Two Immortal Gu Houses were floating in front of Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace.

One was giving off sounds of hundreds of canaries singing together, extremely agile, it was Canary Pavilion. The other was surrounded by strong winds and stood lofty and tall, it was Wind Sweeping Building!

The two Immortal Gu Houses had imposing air, but cracks could be seen on both of them, clearly, Central Continent's Gu Immortals had to pay a huge price to get out from the spaceless tunnel.

"Hmph, all of you finally appeared?!" South Desolation Immortal gave a cold snort as he quickly controlled Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace to defend themselves.

The two Immortal Gu Houses from Central Continent pincer attacked Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace from in front and behind.

Although there was Giant Sun immortal zombie inside Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace, he showed no intention of making a move. He had been sitting here for countless years, only retaining enough strength to make one attack, it was to repay a debt to someone.

Right now, even though Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace was being attacked, he was still sitting cross-legged at the center of the palace, aloof and indifferent.

Soon, sweat started forming on South Desolation Immortal's forehead.

Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace was strong, but it had one big weakness, it had to stay at this place and could not be moved. The moment it moved, even if it was just a hairsbreadth of distance, it would destroy its three hundred thousand years of effort.

Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace had spent three hundred thousand years before it was able to influence black heaven and white heaven above Northern Plains. The moment it moved, this effort will be wasted and it would no longer be able to influence black and white heaven.

Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace was like a huge defensive umbrella that firmly protected Northern Plains. This was the arrangement Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had left behind for his descendants.

How could South Desolation Immortal destroy Ancestor Giant Sun's motives just because he was being attacked? He could only choose to face the attacks head-on.

Central Continent's side had come prepared as they erupted in explosive offenses, actually gaining the upper hand against Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace.

"Yao Huang, come help me in controlling this Immortal Gu House and fight off the enemies!" South Desolation Immortal spoke.

Yao Huang quickly agreed and moved to help.

With a second rank eight Gu Immortal controlling the Immortal Gu House, there was an immediate effect.

The battle situation stabilized.

South Desolation Immortal's expression was filled with doubts: "Strange, why did these Central Continent Gu Immortals' attacks suddenly fall off? Also, they seem to have met with an accident in the spaceless tunnel. I remember there were clearly three Immortal Gu Houses, where is that strongest one, Edge Link Camp? Was it destroyed in the spaceless tunnel?"

But at the next moment, South Desolation Immortal's eyes opened wide as he received the latest information.

"Edge Link Camp has appeared above Snowy Mountain blessed land!"

Longevity Heaven had already infiltrated Snowy Mountain blessed land, thus South Desolation Immortal was extremely clear of the situation in Snowy Mountain blessed land.

Boom!

A huge explosion resounded, and a continuous and intense tremor spread.

The twelve snowy peaks of Snowy Mountain blessed land were all shaking violently.

Immortal Gu House Edge Link Camp's power was extremely high, after all, this Immortal Gu House had two rank eight Gu Immortals.

One was Wei Ling Yang, the other was Bi Chen Tian.

Myriad Tidal Dragon was controlling Wind Sweeping Building while also using Canary Pavilion, restricting Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace.

Edge Link Camp had great might, even if it was in Snowy Mountain blessed land, it was contending with the power of the fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation, firmly floating in the air like a nail.

"We are saved!"

"Reinforcements have come!!"

"Why is there only Edge Link Camp, what about the other two?"

The five Central Continent Gu Immortals who were at different snowy peaks, simultaneously raised their heads and looked at Edge Link Camp, their spirits greatly lifted.

Edge Link Camp also discovered these five Gu Immortals, especially Zhao Lian Yun who had love Immortal Gu.

Wei Ling Yang and Bi Chen Tian naturally wanted to save them, however, the fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation was not for show, Edge Link Camp tried to charge down but was met with a very strong formless force.

"The super Gu formation here is not simple, it actually uses Reverse Flow River!"

"Reverse Flow River is actually in Old Ancestor Xue Hu's hands? But this Gu formation relies on Snowy Mountain blessed land, it is rooted to the blessed land. We cannot deal with the Gu formation, but we can destroy Snowy Mountain blessed land, thus destroying its roots. This Gu formation would then collapse by itself."

Wei Ling Yang and Bi Chen Tian discussed for a moment before deciding on the plan.

Boom boom boom...

Edge Link Camp let out fierce offense, giant horn shadows continuously bombarded at various areas of Snowy Mountain blessed land, causing extremely huge quakes.

Snowy Mountain blessed land turned into an apocalyptic scene.

Avalanches took place at all the snowy peaks, huge rifts opened on the ground, and countless birds and animals fled in panic.

"Husband." Lady Wan Shou had stopped Gu refinement for the moment. She was standing beside Old Ancestor Xue Hu with a worried expression.

"Dear, if we let this Immortal Gu House continue to attack, Snowy Mountain blessed land will be destroyed sooner or later. At that time, this refinement path Gu formation will also be destroyed. But you can relax, what can a mere Immortal Gu House do to me? Let me teach these meddlesome Central Continent Gu Immortals and make them have no way back!" Old Ancestor Xue Hu laughed loudly, as he boldly charged towards Edge Link Camp.

Both sides fought an intense battle in the air.

Edge Link Camp, which was being controlled by two Central Continent's rank eights, was actually suppressed, unable to obtain an advantage.

Chapter 1268: Shadows in Snowy Mountain

Old Ancestor Xue Hu displayed the power that belonged to the strongest of Northern Plains!

In possession of such vast might that shook heaven and earth. His great power would drive off deities and scare off ghosts!

"Old Ancestor Xue Hu is indeed worthy of being called the strongest of Northern Plains!" Bi Chen Tian was not arrogant.

These experts were beyond ordinary. With just a few exchanges of moves, Bi Chen Tian knew he was not Xue Hu's match!

Edge Link Camp was shaking continuously and even looked like it could not bear Old Ancestor Xue Hu's tyrannical offense.

"Unfortunately, Old Ancestor Xue Hu, you are only one person, while we have two rank eight Gu Immortals." Wei Ling Yang sneered, and said to Bi Chen Tian, "I will leave the Immortal Gu House to you."

Bi Chen Tian transmitted his voice in reply: "You can rest assured, I can hold on! If something is wrong, I will call you back."

Wei Ling Yang used his methods to quietly fly out of Edge Link Camp.

He naturally could not resist the strength of the fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation by himself, but right now, most of the formation's power was being used to protect Snowy Mountain blessed land, so the pressure on Wei Ling Yang had decreased, and he was confident he could use his methods to go to each snowy peak.

Because he was a rule path Gu Immortal.

Rule path possessed a huge advantage in this aspect.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu was stronger than Wei Ling Yang, but he could not compare in this aspect.

However, Wei Ling Yang had only sneaked half the distance, when he was discovered by Old Ancestor Xue Hu's powerful investigative killer move.

"Where are you going?" Old Ancestor Xue Hu furiously shouted, as he waved his hand.

Immediately, a boundless blizzard rose up from thin air, heaven and earth changed colors, all living beings went silent, Wei Ling Yang was immediately overwhelmed.

Wei Ling Yang was not discouraged by being obstructed, he constantly changed his directions to break through Old Ancestor Xue Hu's obstruction, and with Bi Chen Tian's cooperation, it was a very good tactic of distraction!

Lady Wan Shou was breaking out in cold sweat, she did not have any mood to refine currently and was concentrating on this crucial battle.

If Old Ancestor Xue Hu won, everything would be safe, any danger would also take a turn for the better.

If Old Ancestor Xue Hu lost, then everything was lost, all their efforts would burst like a bubble.

Although Old Ancestor Xue Hu had high battle strength, the other side had two rank eight Gu Immortals and an Immortal Gu House, Edge Link Camp. On the contrary, the fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation was of limited help to a rank eight Gu Immortal like Old Ancestor Xue Hu.

Wei Ling Yang wanted to pincer attack, which no doubt attracted a lot of Old Ancestor Xue Hu's attention, causing the latter to find it hard to use his full strength.

"If one of the rank eight Gu Immortals attacks the snowy peaks, the consequences will be unimaginable!" Lady Wan Shou was filled with worries.

Right now, Snowy Mountain blessed land was already in danger that threatened its very existence!

"Lady Wan Shou, I have an idea which can let you resolve this danger." Right at this time, a message arrived in Lady Wan Shou's immortal aperture.

"This is?!" Lady Wan Shou was greatly shocked.

Because the Gu worm that had transmitted the message was one which Lady Wan Shou had all along kept in her immortal aperture and never used.

Many years ago, not long after Lady Wan Shou had underwent immortal ascension.

Inside a cave.

"Senior, so you were already here, this junior will leave, I don't dare disturb senior from taking this true inheritance." Lady Wan Shou's heart palpitated at the surging aura released by this mysterious Gu Immortal.

But who knew this mysterious Gu Immortal would suddenly say: "Little girl, you could become a Gu Immortal at such a young age, and also know your own limits, knowing when to retreat or advance, quite good. I don't have the qualifications to take this true inheritance. I am willing to give this true inheritance to you, but, after you inherit it, you need to tell its contents to me. You will also owe me a favor, if there is a situation in the future, you must help the person who uses this information path Gu worm."

Lady Wan Shou considered for just a moment before agreeing.

She actually had no other choice.

Because if she did not agree, she probably could not leave this place alive with her cultivation level.

If so, it was better to take a bet on this!

"Good. Come, we shall set the agreement." The mysterious Gu Immortal smiled brightly while stroking his beard.

...

This scene of the past quickly flashed in Lady Wan Shou's mind.

She immediately replied: "May I ask if you also have interest in fortune rivalling heaven Gu?"

That Gu worm quickly transmitted the reply: "Haha, Lady Wan Shou, it seems you have genuine feelings towards Old Ancestor Xue Hu. Rest assured, we don't have any ill intention towards you, we only need you to refine a Gu material. If you can do this, we will help you and your husband to force back these Central Continent experts."

"Then I shall welcome you, honored guests." Lady Wan Shou nodded after a bit of pondering.

After a while, a group of four Gu Immortals appeared before Lady Wan Shou.

They were Ying Wu Xie and the others!

"Hei Lou Lan, Tai Bai Yun Sheng!" Lady Wan Shou immediately recognized two of them.

The destruction of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had caused the culprits to be hunted everywhere, Hei Lou Lan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng had become 'famous' together with Fang Yuan.

Right now, Lady Wan Shou was very surprised to see these two great culprits.

After all, previously, such a huge super force like Hei tribe had taken the blame for Hei Lou Lan, and was besieged by various Huang Jin tribes, before being annexed by Bai Zu tribe in the end.

As for Bai Ning Bing and Ying Wu Xie, Lady Wan Shou naturally did not recognize them.

However, what made her even more surprised was that the leader of these four Gu Immortals was the weakest strength path immortal zombie, Ying Wu Xie.

"Distinguished guests, I wonder how you can help us repel the enemies?" Lady Wan Shou asked.

Ying Wu Xie smiled brightly, and spoke with assurance: "Lady Wan Shou, I know Old Ancestor Xue Hu had invited people to remove the alliance agreement on you from back then. But we indeed came with no ill intent, we both have mutual enemies, these Gu Immortals of Central Continent. We are the best allies you can have."

"At this moment, you let us in, it meant that you still acknowledge the favor from back then and that you realize the dangerous situation you are in. But as long as you help us refine an immortal material first, everything can be solved easily."

"What immortal material, take it out." Lady Wan Shou extended her hands.

However, Ying Wu Xie shook his head, giving a bitter smile: "This immortal material is inside your immortal aperture, Lady Wan Shou."

"Oh?"

"It is that purple gold rock which Old Ancestor Xue Hu took from Northern Plains Zombie Alliance's graveyard in the past." Ying Wu Xie replied.

Lady Wan Shou's pupils shrunk slightly, letting out wisps of sharp light as she took out an immortal material: "This?"

The four immortals looked at it, this rock was only the size of a palm and was shining in purple-gold light.

Ying Wu Xie heaved a sigh: "Yes, it is this rock."

"So you are members of Shadow Sect." Lady Wan Shou exposed the identity of Ying Wu Xie and the group.

Ying Wu Xie was not surprised, admitting frankly: "Fairy, you have great knowledge, I will trouble you."

Lady Wan Shou nodded.

As such, Central Continent's Gu Immortals were indeed enemies of her and these Shadow Sect Gu Immortals.

As the common saying went, the enemy of an enemy is a friend.

Also!

Lady Wan Shou glanced at the battle in the air, before turning her gaze to this purple gold rock: "What kind of immortal material is this? I was not able to identify it and even others did not know. I won't hide it from you, I have already tried to refine this purple gold rock, but I had no results."

Ying Wu Xie smiled brightly, his tone carrying some pride: "That is because this is a special method of my Shadow Sect, Lady Wan Shou, you don't know the correct procedures and methods, I will teach you, you just need to follow them and you will succeed."

....

An ancient sword dragon was flying above the clouds as it finally arrived at Snowy Mountain blessed land.

From the outside world, the scenes inside Snowy Mountain blessed land could not be seen.

Life and death battles were going on in the blessed land, storms and lightning razed the battlefield, but in the outside world, it was sunny and peaceful.

"They entered Snowy Mountain blessed land? Strange!"

Fang Yuan could not help but have some doubts.

He knew Old Ancestor Xue Hu had turned Snowy Mountain blessed land into a danger zone, to refine fortune rivalling heaven Gu.

Ying Wu Xie and the others actually entered it?

Was this true or an illusion?

Would it be like that time in Eastern Sea when Ying Wu Xie and the others made arrangements in the Gu formation, creating a facade and deceiving Fang Yuan's qi luck sensation?

But if it was true...

It signified too many things!

Fang Yuan hesitated.

He had the upper extreme heavenly eagle, but it was not wise to rashly charge in.

He decided to not to charge in for the moment, and simply wait and see.

Chapter 1269: Rank Eight Miniman

"Xue Hu, take this!" Wei Ling Yang softly pointed his right hand towards Old Ancestor Xue Hu, immediately, a grand beam of light shot towards Old Ancestor Xue Hu.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu gave a light snort as he waved his hand, a large wall of ice appeared and blocked the beam of light easily.

Next, Old Ancestor Xue Hu breathed out cold air which flew towards Wei Ling Yang, resembling spiralling hatchets.

Wei Ling Yang's expression immediately changed.

These spiralling ice hatchets were extremely difficult to deal with, he had already suffered from them, the main thing was, he did not have restrictive methods against them.

Helplessly, Wei Ling Yang could only fly back into Edge Link Camp, and use the powerful defensive ability of Edge Link Camp to protect himself.

Boom boom boom.

A series of soft sounds echoed as the ice hatchets followed Wei Ling Yang, and smashed into Edge Link Camp.

Edge Link Camp shook intensely, large amounts of cold air spread over it, instantly freezing many of its mortal Gu to death.

"Quick, repair the Immortal Gu House!"

"Someone is injured, heal them quickly."

"Activate the Immortal Gu House, use offense as defense!!"

The Gu Immortals inside the Immortal Gu House were agitated.

Wei Ling Yang was breathing roughly, his right hand had frozen completely, who knew when it happened.

"When was I hit?" Even Wei Ling Yang himself was surprised at the condition of his right hand.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu's methods were endless, even when they were not very powerful, they were sinister and insidious, making people unable to defend effectively.

Wei Ling Yang had been struck by Old Ancestor Xue Hu's move unknowingly, and was injured.

He tried several methods, but the condition of his right hand showed no signs of improving.

"This injury is so troublesome..." Bi Chen Tian breathed sharply.

"It is not a big problem, I only need to seal my right hand for the moment. I am now worried about Myriad Tidal Dragon's end. He is controlling two Immortal Gu Houses and also has the help of most of the Gu Immortals that came in this expedition, but what he is facing is Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace as well as Longevity Heaven! We must rescue Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun quickly, and join up with Myriad Tidal Dragon, then retreat to Central Continent!"

Wei Ling Yang's gaze flickered continuously.

Central Continent's Gu Immortals naturally had come prepared, although they met with an accident in the spaceless tunnel, Central Continent's accumulation was more than enough, when these Gu Immortals reacted, they quickly and smoothly escaped the danger.

But the current situation was extremely unfavorable to them!

It was already difficult to deal with Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace. Now that they had split their forces, the decision maker, Wei Ling Yang, was facing great mental pressure.

Rumble!

Thunderous explosions occurred endlessly, Edge Link Camp was shaking continuously and was losing ground.

Central Continent's two rank eight Gu Immortals were elites among rank eights and were qualified to be members of Heavenly Court, they were naturally very powerful.

However, Northern Plains excelled in battle strength among the five regions, and Old Ancestor Xue Hu was the strongest expert among the rank eights of the current Northern Plains.

Right now, he displayed such astonishing offense that Central Continent's side was not able to gain the upper hand since the moment they had started fighting him!

"This won't do! Treat your injuries and control the Immortal Gu House. I will go distract Old Ancestor Xue Hu!" Bi Chen Tian said through clenched teeth.

"You must be careful." Wei Ling Yang said to Bi Chen Tian with concern in his voice, as he knew his injuries had yet to recover.

Bi Chen Tian flew out of Edge Link Camp and quickly used his immortal killer move, turning into a green ray of light, and flying down towards the snowy peaks.

Bi Chen Tian intended to destroy the fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation.

With its destruction, Edge Link Camp would not be obstructed and could dive down without resistance, directly saving Zhao Lian Yun and perhaps Ma Hong Yun as well.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu might be powerful, but he would not be able to block Edge Link Camp's charge.

"Stop daydreaming." Old Ancestor Xue Hu had already seen through Central Continent's tactics, he activated his immortal killer move, immediately, endless hailstones fell down from the sky.

Each of these hailstones was enormous, the size of a mound. They crashed down with loud sounds, and started turning into snow monsters.

These snow monsters were of at least desolate beast level and among them were ancient desolate beast snow monsters as well.

They stood on the snowy peaks and roared towards the sky.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu suddenly took in a deep breath, two lumps of cold air, so deeply blue that they were to the point of being black, were forming in his breath.

The cold air was emitted, giving rise to a powerful blizzard. The snow monsters were like fish in water in the blizzard, they were even able to soar with the help of the blizzard. Bi Chen Tian, however, was greatly restricted.

"So powerful!"

"Old Ancestor Xue Hu knows he cannot use battlefield killer moves inside the Gu formation, so he actually disassembled his signature battlefield killer move. His ice and snow path attainment is probably already at great grandmaster level!"

Whether it be Bi Chen Tian or Wei Ling Yang, they were both shocked at this scene.

At great grandmaster level, every killer move could be casually disassembled and interchanged at will, their understanding towards the path was already close to the Dao.

"But, what if you add me?" Wei Ling Yang sneered, the next moment, he also charged out of Edge Link Camp, towards the Gu formation.

The injury on his right had already healed completely.

He clearly had very high attainment in the healing aspect.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu's expression slightly changed.

Facing two rank eight Gu Immortals at once, along with an Immortal Gu House, he clearly appeared to be stretched thin and had slightly lost his control over the battle situation.

After all, he was unable to destroy the Immortal Gu House for the moment, and the two rank eight Gu Immortals were also experts, most importantly, Old Ancestor Xue Hu had to protect the fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation.

Rank six and rank seven Gu Immortals could not break this formation, but rank eight Gu Immortals were different.

Bi Chen Tian and Wei Ling Yang were attacking the enemy's weak points, gradually turning around their situation and gaining slight initiative. Immortal Gu House Edge Link Camp was controlled by a group of rank seven Gu Immortals and was like a turtle shell in defense, not seeking glory on the battlefield but content with not showing flaws, not allowing Old Ancestor Xue Hu to make a fatal move for some time.

Boom boom boom.

Every now and then, the fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation shook and emitted buzzing sounds.

This was the result of a small portion of attacks from Bi Chen Tian or Wei Ling Yang that had escaped Old Ancestor Xue Hu's obstruction, striking Snowy Mountain blessed land.

"Amazing!"

"Hang in there, lords and our comrades of Central Continent!"

Zhao Lian Yun and the group no longer needed to take a risk, they were standing at the top of their respective snowy peaks, and gazing at the battle above.

Similarly, the surviving snowy peak lords were also gazing at the sky.

Their faces were filled with worry.

"The is the power of rank eight Gu Immortals... It is truly astonishing and terrifying!"

"Because of this formation, the aftereffects of the battle have not spread, otherwise we would have died miserably."

"Lord Xue Hu is strong, but the Central Continent invaders are extremely crafty. If this goes on, the formation will be destroyed sooner or later..."

And, on the first snowy peak of Snowy Mountain, the refinement of the purple gold rock immortal material had reached its final stage.

"I didn't expect that I had to use enshrouding fragrance to dissolve the purple gold rock." Lady Wan Shou's horizons had broadened at this moment.

Enshrouding fragrance was also an immortal material.

Using immortal material to refine immortal material, this method was rarely seen, and Lady Wan Shou also found that the essence of this method was food path!

Food path was rare, no wonder Lady Wan Shou had no ideas on how to deal with this purple gold rock.

The last layer of the rock surface was dissolved, and a dazzling purple light soared to the skies, forcing everyone to look away.

Lady Wan Shou narrowed her eyes to a slit, and was barely able to see a figure in the purple light.

This figure was very small, only about the size of an adult's thumb, and it had two thin purple wings on its back.

"Miniman?" Lady Wan Shou was slightly stunned as she recognized this figure's race.

Bathed in the purple light, the miniman slowly opened his eyes. His eyes were a bright and deep purple color.

As he opened his eyes, a powerful aura leaked out of him.

Rank eight Gu Immortal!

In an instant, this aura caused the fierce battle in the air to slow down.

"Why is there another rank eight Gu Immortal? And it... is the aura of Northern Plains!" Bi Chen Tian and Wei Ling Yang looked at each other, both feeling the situation going awry.

"We pay respects to Lord Purple!" Ying Wu Xie had already brought the Gu Immortals with him, to bow towards this rank eight miniman.

Only Bai Ning Bing was still standing upright.

"I have woken up again. Hmm..." The miniman Gu Immortal blinked his eyes, the expression of confusion quickly disappeared from his face, replaced by a cold and indifferent expression.

Chapter 1270: Sub and Main Fate Reversing Sacrificial Refinement Formation

The miniman Gu Immortal thought briefly before using an immortal killer move, calling out: "Big, big, big."

Thus, his body rapidly expanded like a balloon, soon, he reached a normal human size.

Furthermore, the wings on his back vanished as well, on the outside, he looked just like a normal human.

Right now, the Gu Immortals present could finally see the appearance of this mysterious rank eight Gu Immortal.

He was an unimpressive old man, even looking a little dishevelled. His only special feature was his purple hair, so messy that he resembled a beggar.

Plop.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had tears flowing down his face, he knelt down as he shook in excitement, shouting: "Master!"

"Oh? It is you, I remember I gave you a time path true inheritance." The rank eight Gu Immortal smiled, exposing his uneven yellow teeth.

"Even though our sect's plan succeeded, many unexpected mishaps occurred. This was what happened..." Fighting against time, Ying Wu Xie went forward and transmitted many wills and thoughts to the purple haired old man.

In a moment, the purple haired old man understood everything.

"It was a pity, heaven's will won by a margin."

"But all hope is not lost."

"Ying Wu Xie, you did well, it has been hard on you."

"And Tai Bai Yun Sheng, stand up."

"Now, while I am still conscious, we will join with Xue Hu and take down these Central Continent Gu Immortals!"

The situation was dire, the purple haired old man noticed that the rank eight Gu Immortals were the key to this battle.

He did not hesitate, his body turned into a purple light as he flew into the sky, in a moment, he stood beside Old Ancestor Xue Hu.

"Friend, your name is?" Old Ancestor Xue Hu was not surprised, Lady Wan Shou had already used a Gu worm to inform him about everything that happened regarding the group from Shadow Sect.

With the help of the mysterious expert, Old Ancestor Xue Hu felt very excited.

"I have many names, but..." The purple haired old man said this and showed a smile with deep meaning: "Xue Hu, you may call me Purple Mountain True Monarch."

At this point, Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Purple Mountain True Monarch collaborated, dealing with the two rank eights from Central Continent, as well as Edge Link Camp.

Purple Mountain True Monarch had incredible strength, even though he only attacked sparsely, each of his attacks were extremely effective in turning the situation around.

Any ordinary rank eight could already help Old Ancestor Xue Hu turn this around. Not to mention the mysterious and unfathomable Purple Mountain True Monarch!

Wei Ling Yang and Bi Chen Tian fought desperately, they exerted all their efforts, but they could not stop the situation from tilting towards Northern Plains' favor.

After more than ten rounds of fighting, they were forced to return to Edge Link Camp, they could not defend against Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Purple Mountain True Monarch personally.

The peak lords saw this and cheered loudly.

Without Central Continent's Gu Immortals attacking the fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation, the result of this battle was obvious.

Zhao Lian Yun and the other four Gu Immortals who were trapped in Snowy Mountain blessed land had pale expressions. The battle had turned for the worse, their hopes of survival were dwindling.

What should they do?

Outside Snowy Mountain blessed land, an ancient sword dragon was hiding among the clouds.

"Shadow Sect actually has connections with Snowy Mountain..."

"Then why did Qin Bai Sheng not request for Snowy Mountain's help when he was fighting against Feng Jiu Ge in Luo Po Valley?"

"Or perhaps their relationship is not as deep as I think."

Qi luck sensation was telling Fang Yuan that Ying Wu Xie and the rest were inside Snowy Mountain blessed land, they did not leave.

Fang Yuan's pursuit was obstructed, he was unwilling to give up, he was waiting outside, to see if there was a chance.

And at a certain place a thousand li away, two Gu Immortals descended from the sky.

They were none other than Longevity Heaven's Black Extremity and Flood Extremity.

"This is the place." Black Extremity said as he used his Gu worms, causing a huge commotion.

The small slope that was in front of them started to shine in rainbow light.

Flood Extremity realized at once: "So you have set up a Gu formation at this place, you need me to control the Gu formation now?"

Black Extremity shook his head: "Wait until we get inside."

He took a large step ahead, entering the Gu formation, as Flood Extremity followed behind.

Once they were inside the Gu formation, Flood Extremity's expression changed, he said in shock: "This Gu formation has a grand aura, as expected of your personal arrangement, Black Extremity, I can tell that once activated, it will have incredible strength. But..."

Towards the end, Flood Extremity had a hesitant tone.

"But what?" Black Extremity looked at him with much interest.

Flood Extremity said in a profound tone: "But I feel that this formation is not complete, it is missing something. It is like a lake, there should be something connecting it to the sea."

Black Extremity heard this and his eyebrows rose, he praised and clapped: "As expected of a quasi-great grandmaster of water path, you are already proficient in comprehending other paths through your main path. That's right! This Gu formation is just a sub formation, there is a corresponding main formation."

"Then where is the main formation?" Flood Extremity frowned.

Before Black Extremity answered, he had an inspiration as he said in realization: "I understand! The main formation is the fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation in Snowy Mountain blessed land!"

"Indeed." Black Extremity laughed: "I was tasked earlier to act as Sun Ming Lu and get near Lady Wan Shou. Eventually, I created the fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation which used Reverse Flow River. Even though Old Ancestor Xue Hu is currently the strongest person in Northern Plains, he is not proficient in formation path, he could not tell that I had a backdoor."

"Right now, as long as I activate this sub formation, I can make the main formation in Snowy Mountain blessed land break apart, and draw the Reverse Flow River here."

"Once the Gu formation collapses, everyone and everything in the surrounding ten thousand li of Snowy Mountain blessed land would all be swept here."

Black Extremity said with an excited gaze.

Flood Extremity was shocked: "In this case, wouldn't those four rank eight great experts be sent here too?"

Black Extremity shook his head: "Reverse Flow River is a secluded domain of heaven and earth, it is not ordinary, it has an incredibly large number of dao marks. As long as one falls into Reverse Flow River, even rank eight great experts cannot use any Gu worms. In \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, when Ren Zu traveled up the Reverse Flow River, he did not use any Gu worms within the river."

"Then wouldn't they be meat on the chopping block for us?" Flood Extremity was excited.

But Black Extremity shook his head: "We are outside Reverse Flow River, if we make any attacks, it will be reversed and reflect back at us. This is Reverse Flow River, the word reverse naturally has deep meaning."

Flood Extremity was confused: "In this case, how can we save Ma Hong Yun and capture Zhao Lian Yun?"

"Hahaha." Black Extremity laughed: "Did you forget that Reverse Flow River is still subjected to the influence of both my sub and main fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation."

"When the main formation collapses, Reverse Flow River would flow towards us. By then, the order of everyone in Snowy Mountain blessed land would be arranged by me, Zhao Lian Yun and Ma Hong Yun would be at the front of Reverse Flow River."

"Lady Wan Shou and the rest would be behind, while Central Continent's Gu Immortals would be even further back, those rank eight Gu Immortals would be at the end."

"Incredible!" Flood Extremity said with shining eyes, he clapped: "This way, in order to escape from Lady Wan Shou and the rest, Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun would desperately struggle and move forward, to pull ahead of the rest behind. But as long as they are ahead, we will be able to interact with them here and capture them alive."

"However..." Flood Extremity frowned: "If Zhao Lian Yun and Ma Hong Yun are unable to persevere, would they be like Ren Zu and be washed away by the river? If that happens, they would fall behind the other Gu Immortals, wouldn't it foil our plans?"

Black Extremity smiled bitterly: "This is the biggest flaw in the plan. But traveling in Reverse Flow River has nothing to do with cultivation level or strength, Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun are not at a disadvantage."

"But this is not an assured result." Flood Extremity was not satisfied with this.

Black Extremity shrugged: "Then what do you want from a rank seven Gu Immortal like me? This is the best way already, after all, we are not plotting against two rank seven Gu Immortals, but the entirety of Snowy Mountain blessed land and Central Continent's Gu Immortal experts, involving multiple rank eight great experts, a total of four at that!"

Flood Extremity was speechless, he nodded helplessly, this was their limit indeed.

In fact, it was already very impressive that Black Extremity could achieve this much.

"Don't worry, we are just part of the arrangements, Lord South Desolation has woken up, he definitely has other plans. We just need to do our part, that will suffice." Black Extremity patted Flood Extremity's shoulder in consolation.

Chapter 1271: Implicating Fang Yuan

Boom boom boom!

The silhouette of the giant horn shot around in the sky, sending out a barrage of attacks.

Around Old Ancestor Xue Hu, frost energy was oozing, turning into blue icy cold frost that swept at Edge Link Camp in layers.

The two Central Continent rank eights in Edge Link Camp were desperately gritting their teeth, the Gu Immortals behind them were trying to repair the Immortal Gu Houses, they were covered in sweat and had panicked expressions.

Meanwhile, beside Old Ancestor Xue Hu, Purple Mountain True Monarch was covered in dazzling purple light, radiating in the entire Snowy Mountain blessed land.

Central Continent's group was attacking Snowy Mountain, Purple Mountain True Monarch was tasked to defend it. This blessed land was the foundation of the fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation, as long as they defended it, Central Continent would lose.

"What should we do?" Bi Chen Tian had a frantic expression: "If this continues, not only will we fail to save Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun, we will also lose this Immortal Gu House and our own lives!"

Wei Ling Yang was the leader of this expedition, he had a grim expression.

The situation was very disadvantageous for the Central Continent Gu Immortals.

It could even be said they were hopeless.

According to the plans of Central Continent's Gu Immortals, they were split into two, one group would restrain Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace, while the other would save Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun, before they joined up and left Northern Plains together.

But now, the group that went to Snowy Mountain blessed land was already close to defeat, and the other group was also waiting for their rescue.

This was Northern Plains, not Central Continent.

Three rank eights and three Immortal Gu Houses, along with a band of Gu Immortals, were still a relatively small number of people.

Of course, this was also because the Northern Plains Gu Immortals were prepared. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's plan was not known to Central Continent.

Central Continent struck with a powerful attack, according to the planning of this assault, there was a huge chance of success.

But as the situation progressed, the targets of their sneak attack became strong foes, and with Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's arrangements, Central Continent's Gu Immortals fell into this dangerous situation.

Wei Ling Yang's thoughts were churning rapidly.

A moment later, he gritted his teeth and gave his orders, seemingly exerting his last bit of strength: "We will retreat!"

Forget about Zhao Lian Yun and Ma Hong Yun.

After Purple Mountain True Monarch appeared, the situation went beyond Wei Ling Yang's control.

If this dragged on, Central Continent would suffer even greater losses!

Wei Ling Yang decided to retreat back to black heaven, and join up with the other two Immortal Gu Houses and escape to Central Continent.

Edge Link Camp was directed to leave, Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Purple Mountain True Monarch could not stop it together. After all, they had no Immortal Gu Houses, they could not stop it from charging away.

However!

Just when Edge Link Camp was about to charge out of the Gu formation, a change occurred.

The entirety of Snowy Mountain blessed land was rumbling intensely.

A great earthquake!

"What is going on?"

"The blessed land is collapsing!"

Zhao Lian Yun and the others, as well as the remaining peak lords, were extremely shocked.

Rumble!

With a loud sound, the snowy peaks started to break apart.

"What is going on?!" Old Ancestor Xue Hu showed shock on his face.

"The entire formation is breaking apart." Purple Mountain True Monarch's eyes shined brightly, before he corrected himself: "No! This formation..."

Before he finished his words, the Gu Immortals present heard the sound of waves.

At the next moment, giant rushing waves appeared out of nowhere, sweeping the battlefield!

It was the secluded domain of heaven and earth — Reverse Flow River!!

"Oh no, my wife!" Everything happened too quickly, Old Ancestor Xue Hu wanted to charge back to the first peak, but he was engulfed by the river along the way.

Within Reverse Flow River, no Gu worms could be activated.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu could not defend himself, he was washed away by the rushing tides.

He had the highest battle strength in this place, if this happened to him, there was no need to mention the rest.

Immortal Gu House Edge Link Camp broke apart in the river, the Central Continent Gu Immortals were washed along the river like falling dumplings.

Zhao Lian Yun and the rest, the peak lords of Snowy Mountain blessed land, Lady Wan Shou, Ying Wu Xie's group, and Ma Hong Yun, were all inside Reverse Flow River.

Snowy Mountain blessed land completely collapsed, only a framework was left as the winds of assimilation started to blow.

"They're coming!" Far away, Black Extremity's head was bulging with veins, he manipulated the sub formation with all his strength.

He was the culprit behind Snowy Mountain's destruction.

And beside him, Flood Extremity was defending him vigilantly, at the final moment, Flood Extremity had to use his water path methods to direct Reverse Flow River.

"What?!" Fang Yuan felt his vision turning bright as a huge torrent engulfed him in an instant.

Once the fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation broke, everyone and everything within the surrounding ten thousand li of Snowy Mountain blessed land was engulfed by Reverse Flow River.

Fang Yuan was within this range, he was not spared.

From the raging river water, Fang Yuan's head emerged on the surface.

"This is — Reverse Flow River?!" He had a wide range of knowledge, after his shock, he realized the origin of the river that he was in.

"Snowy Mountain blessed land contains Reverse Flow River?"

"No wonder my ancient sword dragon transformation was removed for no apparent reason."

This was natural.

Inside Reverse Flow River, Gu worms could not be used. Fang Yuan's ancient sword dragon transformation was an immortal killer move, it needed Immortal Gu and mortal Gu to activate.

Thus, the moment Fang Yuan was swept in, all of his Gu worms stopped working, he returned to his original form.

"Thankfully, I can swim." Fang Yuan moved his limbs, swimming skillfully.

He looked ahead, on the surface of the raging river, there were many things floating or swimming. Large numbers of wild beasts, trees and grass, and even rocks.

Reverse Flow River's waves were extremely rough, gushes of currents caused rocks or trees to move around randomly, creating chaos in the river.

Fang Yuan's heart sank, in this situation, he could not use Gu worms, his battle strength was at rock bottom, he could only rely on his own body's defense.

At this time, Fang Yuan heard something that did not sound right near him.

He quickly turned around, he saw that a giant metal tree was flowing along the river, the trunk was as thick as an elephant, it rushed towards him.

"Danger!" Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk, he wanted to dodge.

But in the torrential Reverse Flow River, he could not move easily, his speed was very slow, the metal tree crashed into his waist.

Fang Yuan was quickly knocked into the depths of the river.

Next, he rapidly moved his four limbs, before resurfacing above the river.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh!

He breathed raggedly, taking in fresh air as he inspected his body, checking his injuries.

He was shocked when he checked it.

Because he had no injuries.

He only had a bruise on his waist.

But soon, his bruise vanished.

Fang Yuan's eyes shined, he realized: "Oh right! My body is not normal, I have the sovereign immortal body!"

Inside Reverse Flow River, Fang Yuan could not use any Gu worms, he could only rely on his own body.

However!

His sovereign immortal body was not normal at all.

Chapter 1272: What is that?

After the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain ended, Fang Yuan had tested this body's limits.

He did not use any Gu worms, but he was fast like a charging horse.

By just leaping gently, he could jump ten meters of distance.

Jumping down from a hundred and eighty meters while pointing his head downwards, he felt a little dizzy but it only lasted for three breaths of time, and was gone before he knew it.

He had great strength and endurance as well, he ran for minutes without feeling any fatigue at all.

His five senses and visual acuity were beyond amazing! His vision was outstanding, looking ten thousand steps ahead, everything was clear to him.

His heartbeat returned to normal after exercising intensely, every time it beat, it was very strong and lively.

His thinking speed was extremely fast as well. Even if it was under the light of wisdom, he could maintain it for a long time. Even Gu Immortals could rarely reach this extent with only their bodies.

Not just a metal tree, even if a metal hill crashed at him, Fang Yuan would be intact.

This was the sovereign immortal body's own physique, it had nothing to do with Gu worms, it had to do with his dao marks.

"Inside Reverse Flow River, I cannot use Gu worms, but the same goes for others!"

"Meanwhile, my sovereign immortal body is sufficiently strong, my dao marks are also high in quantity."

Fang Yuan thought about it, his mood turned into excitement.

"Ying Wu Xie!"

He flung his limbs as he swam forward like a swordfish.

The whole Reverse Flow River was running quickly, but the overall flow was affected by the formation, it flowed towards Black Extremity and Flood Extremity.

Roar!

A striped tiger was climbing onto a plank with its limbs.

Fang Yuan swam to the tiger but it was unmoved. Meanwhile, Fang Yuan panted as he took a little rest on the plank.

But this plank could not endure the weight of both the human and tiger, it started sinking.

The tiger was anxious, it bore its fangs at Fang Yuan and wanted to bite him, but Fang Yuan snorted and stretched out his arm, crushing the tiger's head as he raised his fist and punched this tiger to death.

"Thankfully, this is not a desolate beast but an ordinary beast instead."

Against a desolate beast, the sovereign immortal body was not enough.

Snowy Mountain blessed land did not lack desolate beasts. But to refine fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu, in activating the formation and defending against enemies, Snowy Mountain blessed land had already been modified. Gu Immortals with desolate beasts had kept them in their immortal apertures, they would not allow enemies to kill the desolate beasts, that would just be stupid.

Fang Yuan swam in Reverse Flow River, he wanted to find Ying Wu Xie.

Snowy Mountain blessed land collapsed, Reverse Flow River was pouring out, Fang Yuan did not know that Purple Mountain True Monarch had awakened.

He was still thinking of Old Ancestor Xue Hu as the main enemy. He estimated that Ying Wu Xie had some relationship with Snowy Mountain, but it was not close. Otherwise, why would Old Ancestor Xue Hu not help during the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain?

Fang Yuan's analysis was not wrong.

But his information path methods were too lacking, he did not have enough intel.

"Right now, even if I meet Old Ancestor Xue Hu, I can survive. Because in Reverse Flow River, Gu worms cannot be used, it is a special environment!"

"Since Ying Wu Xie has some connection with Old Ancestor Xue Hu, if I miss this chance, they will definitely grow rapidly under his protection."

"If I miss this chance, I might not have another opportunity to eliminate them again!"

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan moved ahead after resting shortly.

But he met Bi Chen Tian.

A Central Continent rank eight Gu Immortal!

Fang Yuan was shocked.

"What is going on?"

"A rank eight Gu Immortal who isn't Old Ancestor Xue Hu, and is from Central Continent?!"

Bi Chen Tian was in a terrible state, he was covered in injuries as he rested on a huge turtle's back.

These injuries were not from Reverse Flow River's journey, but were sustained in the battle earlier. He was a rank eight Gu Immortal, his dao marks conflicted and it was harder to heal from injuries once he sustained them.

But in that battle, he was in a weaker position, how could he have time to heal himself?

Thus, after the main formation collapsed, he was swept by Reverse Flow River and could not use his Gu worms to heal himself, all the way until now.

But fortunately, while being washed away in the river, he met a floating turtle and managed to get a chance to rest on it.

Fang Yuan discovered Bi Chen Tian, Bi Chen Tian also saw Fang Yuan.

But Bi Chen Tian did not recognize Fang Yuan.

Because Fang Yuan was in his sovereign immortal body's appearance! His original appearance was exposed by Heavenly Court and was spread over all five regions.

Even though Bi Chen Tian did not know Fang Yuan, he frowned and became alert.

Because Fang Yuan's aura showed that he was a Northern Plains Gu Immortal.

This was also because of the sovereign immortal body.

After passing the regional wall, Fang Yuan could change his aura into that of the region he was in, he was a Gu Immortal of the region and could perfectly fuse into it.

"Who is this? He is not one of the peak lords of Snowy Mountain blessed land, however, he could have been recruited by Old Ancestor Xue Hu secretly."

Bi Chen Tian stood up on the turtle's shell, looking at Fang Yuan's every movement.

Inside Reverse Flow River, even though Bi Chen Tian had rank eight cultivation level, his Gu worms could not be used, he had limited battle strength.

Fang Yuan also looked at him alertly, he did not get close.

Even though Fang Yuan had the sovereign immortal body, he would be stupid if he thought he was the strongest person in Reverse Flow River!

Reverse Flow River did not allow Gu worms to be used, but his body was intact, his dao marks were effective.

Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal body was very powerful, because of the dao marks on the immortal body.

Similarly, if a Gu Master used black boar Gu to gain the strength of a boar, he would have the strength path dao marks carved into his body. If this Gu Master falls into Reverse Flow River, and is unable to use Gu worms, he would still be able to use his body and attack with the strength of a boar.

As for other Gu Immortals, over the long course of their cultivation journey, how could they not use any Gu worms like black boar Gu to increase the number of dao marks in their bodies?

This was natural!

Anyone who was not a fool would know the advantages of such dao marks.

Fang Yuan's body had its advantages, so did other Gu Immortals, the extent simply varied from one person to another.

For rank eight Gu Immortals, they had deep foundations, Fang Yuan did not want to fight against Bi Chen Tian at the moment.

"You are a Central Continent Gu Immortal?"

"I am a Northern Plains Gu Immortal, but I have a grudge with Old Ancestor Xue Hu."

"I saw him trying to refine the rank eight Immortal Gu, I did not want him to succeed, so I went to the outside of the blessed land and tried to find a way to break in."

"Are you a helper for him to refine the Gu?"

Fang Yuan probed.

Bi Chen Tian's frown eased a little, he answered: "Old Ancestor Xue Hu is also my enemy."

"Not long ago, I was fighting against him in Snowy Mountain blessed land, but this unexpected surprise happened."

"My injuries are all caused by Old Ancestor Xue Hu."

The two talked and exchanged information.

Fang Yuan realized now that so many things had happened in Snowy Mountain blessed land!

But Bi Chen Tian was very vague about many things, Fang Yuan could not get much intel.

They did not trust each other after all.

This was natural.

They only had interacted a little, it was hard to tell what the other person's intentions were.

And in this situation where Gu worms could not be used, both sides were at their highest alertness.

Fang Yuan knew he could not get more information from Bi Chen Tian and decided to leave.

He left that huge wild turtle.

Even during the conversation, he did not get closer, while Bi Chen Tian did not invite Fang Yuan to rest on the turtle's back.

Bi Chen Tian saw that Fang Yuan was leaving and his expression relaxed a little.

But at this moment, an unexpected surprise occurred.

Ping.

A soft sound echoed.

A fist-sized thing was washed down by the river, landing on Fang Yuan's face.

This thing was soft and tiny, like a jellyfish, it stuck to Fang Yuan's forehead.

"What is this?" Fang Yuan was stunned, he wanted to pull it away.

But at this time, he heard Bi Chen Tian call out: "Be gentle, don't crush it!"

"Oh?" Fang Yuan was surprised, what was it that made a rank eight Gu Immortal nervous?

Chapter 1273: Affection Immortal Gu

Fang Yuan held this jellyfish-like Gu in his hand, looking at it.

At the next moment, his eyes shined.

This was an Immortal Gu.

But he did not know its rank.

Because in Reverse Flow River, no Gu worm could be used. These Gu worms that fell into Reverse Flow River were like fossils, they were sealed and their auras could not be felt.

This made Fang Yuan unaware of the nature of this jellyfish Immortal Gu earlier, when it was on his face.

Only when Bi Chen Tian reminded him did Fang Yuan realize.

If this were in the outside world, without Reverse Flow River, Immortal Gu aura would leak, Fang Yuan would detect it from far away, and determine what its rank was.

As for what Immortal Gu it was, that would depend on the Gu Immortal's own knowledge.

"This Immortal Gu seems to be... affection Gu?" Fang Yuan's knowledge was wide, after looking at it, he could guess this what this Gu was.

Wisdom path had three elements, thoughts, wills, and emotions.

Since there was love Immortal Gu, there was also affection Immortal Gu, of course[1].

Fang Yuan's guess was right.

Bi Chen Tian could not help but feel anxious. Affection Gu was very important to Central Continent's Gu Immortals.

Why?

Because this Immortal Gu was temporarily used in Edge Link Camp, there were many mortal Gu along with it.

This affection Immortal Gu, along with many mortal Gu, could create a new effect in Edge Link Camp, that was to track the location of love Gu. Even if love Gu was in an immortal aperture, it would not be affected.

That was how Edge Link Camp managed to find Snowy Mountain blessed land.

Otherwise, inside the spaceless tunnel, when love Gu sent Zhao Lian Yun, Yu Yi Ye Zi, Shi Zheng Yi, Bu Zhen Zi, and Mu Ling Lan away, who would know where they went?

After adding affection Immortal Gu and other Gu worms, Edge Link Camp could detect love Immortal Gu and traced it to Snowy Mountain blessed land.

But afterwards, because they fought with Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Purple Mountain True Monarch, Edge Link Camp sustained great pressure, and took much damage. Before this, due to the long journey and the collapse of the spaceless tunnel, Edge Link Camp was not complete to begin with.

And now, after Flood Extremity and Black Extremity activated the Gu formation, destroying the main formation, Reverse Flow River flowed out and struck the heavily damaged Edge Link Camp.

This way, the Immortal Gu House broke apart and the Immortal Gu and mortal Gu inside were all swept away by the water.

If this were the outside world, these Immortal Gu and mortal Gu would fly towards the Gu Immortals who had their wills contained.

But inside Reverse Flow River, these Gu worms were restricted by the special environment, they were forcefully sealed, hibernating like they were no longer alive.

Affection Gu was one of the countless Gu worms that made up the Immortal Gu House.

Or rather, it was a very lucky one.

Because most of the Gu worms had flowed along the river and were destroyed by the waves, or crashed into rocks or trees.

Gu worms were very fragile.

Reverse Flow River became their grave.

Of course, there were different types of Gu worm body types.

Most were broken with one squeeze, but some were like jade or rocks, as tough as jade. Affection Gu was different, it had a soft body, it could survive even if there was an impact.

Evidently, this was how it survived in Reverse Flow River.

But after ending up in Fang Yuan's hands, it was not in good shape.

The jellyfish body was very tattered, there was a huge injury that was about a quarter of its size, it was terrifying.

Bi Chen Tian's eyes were very sharp, seeing that Fang Yuan was about to pull away this affection Gu, he called out in worry.

But after reminding him, he felt great regret.

If he did not say it, Fang Yuan might have thrown it away without care or concern.

But now, Fang Yuan's eyes were shining, he realized the truth.

Bi Chen Tian withheld the unease in his heart as he cupped his fists at Fang Yuan: "Friend, this Gu belongs to Central Continent. Why don't you give this Immortal Gu to me, you will gain the friendship of Central Continent. Is that alright?"

Fang Yuan squinted: "I can consider that, but what Gu is this? You need to tell me."

Bi Chen Tian answered: "This is affection Gu, a wisdom path Gu worm."

Wisdom path Gu Immortals were rare, Bi Chen Tian emphasized that this was affection Immortal Gu because he thought that Fang Yuan was not a wisdom path Gu Immortal. Affection Gu was not useful to most Gu Immortals after all.

It was a waste to give it away, but it was a burden in one's hands.

Why?

Gu Immortals needed wills as their assistants. Be it in sect meetings or in treasure yellow heaven, any will Gu could be used widely.

But mortal level will Gu could achieve this.

There was no need to waste one's effort in raising an affection Immortal Gu.

After all, if one was not a wisdom path Gu Immortal, with their conflicting dao marks, using the Immortal Gu of other paths would have lower effects. At the same time, just affection Immortal Gu could not form any immortal killer moves.

Unless it was an immortal killer move of other paths that needed affection Immortal Gu, or any special methods that needed it, then the Gu Immortal would desire it.

Not all Immortal Gu were popular with people.

Gu Immortals had different paths, so did Immortal Gu. Gu Immortals were of rank six, seven, and eight, so were Immortal Gu.

For Gu Immortals, only suitable Immortal Gu had value to them.

In the five hundred years of Fang Yuan's previous life, during the five regions chaotic war, Gu Immortals often held trading sessions to exchange their Immortal Gu.

But Bi Chen Tian would not think that Fang Yuan was the most special Gu Immortal of all.

Firstly, he had grandmaster wisdom path attainment level, such a person had to be considered a wisdom path Gu Immortal.

Secondly, Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal body did not have conflicting dao marks, he could cultivate any path!

Lastly, Fang Yuan had been fretting over this matter, even though he had wisdom path attainment level and methods, he did not have relevant wisdom path Immortal Gu.

Thus, this affection Immortal Gu was very important to Fang Yuan.

Thus, he placed affection Immortal Gu into the pocket of his shirt.

Inside Reverse Flow River, the immortal aperture's entrance could not be opened, he had to carry it with him.

Bi Chen Tian saw this and his heart sank, his tone was even more anxious: "Friend! Take out that Immortal Gu, we are not enemies, we can go through a transaction according to what we need."

Fang Yuan looked at Bi Chen Tian: "We can have a transaction, but not here."

[1] Love Gu is read as 'love emotion' Gu in Chinese characters while affection is 'love will'. Back

Chapter 1274: Fighting Rank Eight in the River

If possible, Fang Yuan wanted to use affection Immortal Gu to trade for Immortal Gu that suited him more.

But in Reverse Flow River, transactions were impossible.

Because no Gu worms could be used, information path methods that allowed two parties to engage in transactions were unusable.

Fang Yuan wanted to exchange for Immortal Gu, but Bi Chen Tian could not take out any Immortal Gu, because Gu worms hibernated while inside Reverse Flow River, let alone those in an immortal aperture, they would not respond to any of a Gu Immortal's summons even if they were inside their bodies.

Thus, Bi Chen Tian did not have any chips to use for trade.

Bi Chen Tian knew Fang Yuan's concern, but should he give up this chance and wait for the future?

Who knew what would happen in the future?

After Black Extremity's action, Snowy Mountain blessed land was gone, Central Continent's Edge Link Camp was destroyed as well, if Central Continent's group fought again, they would fall into an even deeper disadvantage.

Central Continent's Gu Immortals were barely able to defend themselves, once they escaped Reverse Flow River, wouldn't they flee immediately?

Thus, there was no chance to undergo trade with Fang Yuan.

If they did not do the transaction now, what about in the future?

Fang Yuan was a Northern Plains Gu Immortal, while Bi Chen Tian was a Central Continent Gu Immortal, both were in different regions, even in treasure yellow heaven, Central Continent could not dictate Fang Yuan to do a transaction with them later.

What if he made a deal with someone else? What if he raised prices to an absurd level without fear?

There were worse situations possible.

Bi Chen Tian was someone with the foresight to consider bad outcomes in advance, seeing that he could not coax Fang Yuan to give the Immortal Gu, his killing intent rose!

"I am a rank eight Gu Immortal, even if I cannot use Immortal Gu here, with my dao mark foundation, how can I lose to a rank seven Gu Immortal?"

Thinking like this, Bi Chen Tian jumped into the river water and swam towards Fang Yuan.

At this moment, his hostility was obvious.

Fang Yuan sneered internally, as he charged towards Bi Chen Tian as well.

Bi Chen Tian saw this and became joyful, thinking: "This Northern Plains Gu Immortal looks like a battle maniac. He's simply brainless!"

The river water moved rapidly, but both parties had extraordinary bodies, they quickly met in the middle.

Boom boom boom.

Fang Yuan raised his fist and punched at Bi Chen Tian thrice.

Bi Chen Tian was a wood path Gu Immortal, he had great stamina and eyesight, he blocked all three attacks.

He was shocked: "This person looks so young, how can he have such strength? Does he cultivate strength path?"

He felt that his arm was numb from blocking.

But while he was shocked, Bi Chen Tian still retaliated with his other hand.

Both sides exchanged fists, they quickly got into a scuffle.

Fang Yuan's entire body was a weapon, his head, knee, elbow, and all sorts of jabs were used.

Bi Chen Tian was on the back foot, but soon, he held up evenly against Fang Yuan's attacks. Because he had incredible foundation, and his close combat skills were very deep. Even though he had rarely used these techniques after becoming a Gu Immortal, currently in actual battle, he was recovering his combat skills.

As for Fang Yuan, he had become a Gu Immortal more recently, many years ago, he was a mortal Gu Master roaming Northern Plains and Southern Border, he was familiar with close combat.

The two fought in the water, at times, they lifted their heads above the water and breathed roughly, temporarily resting.

Reverse Flow River moved rapidly, most of their energy was spent in swimming, they did not actually fight too much.

When they fought, the environment was very complex.

Because at times, logs or wild beasts would float down the river and force the two to evade them.

As a result, after tens of rounds of battle, both sides were breathing roughly, but they could do nothing to the other party.

"This rank eight Gu Immortal is truly deep in foundation. I wanted to kill a rank eight in Reverse Flow River, but now it seems to be wishful thinking."

Bi Chen Tian, however, was filled with shock.

"How can this be? This person is on par with me?!"

"I have used grass python Immortal Gu previously to gain a huge amount of strength."

"I have also used immortal killer move wood armor to carve dao marks in my body, my body has naturally strong defenses."

"I even turned my heart into a wood heart and turned my blood into green blood, giving me super healing abilities."

"These immortal killer moves and Immortal Gu, along with my dao marks as a rank eight Gu Immortal who has so many calamities and tribulations, I definitely outclass this rank seven."

"But why am I simply evenly matched with him?"

Bi Chen Tian stared at Fang Yuan, as if he was looking at a monster.

Speaking of which, Fang Yuan did not have as many dao marks as the rank eight Bi Chen Tian, but in fact, his dao mark accumulation surpassed most rank seven Gu Immortals. Even though he only became a rank seven Gu Immortal recently.

What resisted Bi Chen Tian was the sovereign immortal body.

The sovereign immortal body was not a normal human body, it was refined from a Gu worm. Be it Wei Ling Yang or Bi Chen Tian, they were humans. But Fang Yuan's body was made from a Gu worm.

It could therefore be said that Fang Yuan being a complete otherworldly demon was one of the reasons.

The sovereign immortal body made up for the difference in dao marks between him and Bi Chen Tian, allowing them to fight evenly.

Fang Yuan decided to retreat.

Even though he did not lose, his intention was to kill the huge threat Ying Wu Xie.

Earlier, when fighting with Bi Chen Tian, he wanted to test his strength, to see if he could kill a rank eight Gu Immortal.

But in fact, Fang Yuan was overly optimistic.

He could do nothing to Bi Chen Tian, Fang Yuan had to give up. He did not want to stall it out with Bi Chen Tian, his objective had not been met yet.

Fang Yuan wanted to leave, but Bi Chen Tian did not allow him to.

Even though Bi Chen Tian could not do anything to Fang Yuan, affection Immortal Gu was still with Fang Yuan.

"Even if I cannot win, I need to keep him here. If my companions come later, we can encircle him together. I cannot let him escape!"

"Damn it, this guy." Fang Yuan quickly frowned.

He wanted to retreat, but Bi Chen Tian's speed and strength were not inferior to his, even though Fang Yuan wanted to leave, Bi Chen Tian was preventing him from doing so.

This gravely affected Fang Yuan's plan.

"In that case, don't blame me for being ruthless!" Fang Yuan's eyes flashed with cold light.

Obstructed by the wild beast corpse ahead, Fang Yuan's speed fell and Bi Chen Tian reached him again.

Fang Yuan turned around to fight him.

Both were fighting with their fists and legs in Reverse Flow River, it was a draw, at the crucial moment, Fang Yuan stretched out his arm and placed affection Immortal Gu in front of himself.

Bi Chen Tian wanted to punch at Fang Yuan's torso.

If he hit, Fang Yuan would lose his oxygen supply and would need to go to the surface and breathe in fresh air.

This was one of the key points of fighting underwater.

But Fang Yuan suddenly took out affection Immortal Gu, and put it in front of Bi Chen Tian's fist.

Bi Chen Tian turned pale from shock, he quickly pulled back his fist and revealed a flaw.

Fang Yuan laughed coldly on the inside, he used this flaw and charged, Bi Chen Tian had made a mistake and could only block and defend himself, preparing to counterattack.

But Fang Yuan suddenly raised affection Immortal Gu in front of himself, causing Bi Chen Tian to be unable to attack and exposing a flaw.

With two flaws exposed, Fang Yuan made use of his advantage and kicked at Bi Chen Tian's stomach.

Bi Chen Tian was hit and immediately opened his mouth as air bubbles floated up.

He did not have enough oxygen now, he changed his tactics and wanted to escape to the surface.

But Fang Yuan did not allow this, he stretched out his arms and gripped with them like pincers, pulling Bi Chen Tian and preventing him from reaching the surface.

Bi Chen Tian suddenly twisted his waist and escaped with a difficult maneuver. He moved like a fish, bursting out with strength, Fang Yuan's left arm could not catch him.

Fang Yuan praised on the inside towards this response.

Bi Chen Tian was a Central Continent Gu Immortal, but his rank eight foundation really held no weaknesses. In terms of fighting underwater, he even slightly surpassed Fang Yuan.

There was a need to mention, Fang Yuan had lived in Eastern Sea for a long time during the five hundred years of his previous life.

This way, Bi Chen Tian instantly swam until he was on top of Fang Yuan.

Chapter 1275: Kicking a Rank Eight Great Expert

Fang Yuan's grasp earlier had failed, he raised his arms and grabbed upwards.

His left arm missed but his right arm grabbed onto Bi Chen Tian's leg.

Bi Chen Tian was obstructed, his other leg kicked towards Fang Yuan's head like a fierce dragon.

This blow was heavy, if it landed, Fang Yuan would become dizzy and Bi Chen Tian would easily escape.

But Fang Yuan took out affection Immortal Gu and raised it up.

Bi Chen Tian wanted to curse, his leg stopped.

Fang Yuan managed to obtain some time to react, he moved his head backwards as his entire body went upside down in the water.

Originally, he was like Bi Chen Tian, they were floating upright.

But now that he grabbed Bi Chen Tian's leg, he became upside down.

Bi Chen Tian saw this and his heart sank, he gasped in his mind.

This was because Fang Yuan was grabbing onto his leg with one hand, while the other was holding affection Immortal Gu, he could not attack with strength.

But at this moment, in this scene, Fang Yuan had two legs to use.

Meanwhile, Bi Chen Tian's leg was held by Fang Yuan, he could only attack with one other leg.

Bi Chen Tian was shocked, the leg that was free moved around like a butterfly, it was extremely nimble, after kicking for several times, Fang Yuan could only see many shadows of his moving leg.

But Fang Yuan had no fear, he kicked with both legs, as he unleashed a flurry of kicks moving like shadows as well.

Both parties were fighting in the water, causing huge spirals to form around the river water, each time their legs collided, a loud sound was emitted in the river water.

Bi Chen Tian could only use one leg, how could he compete with both of Fang Yuan's legs?

During the process of fighting, he was often hit by Fang Yuan's legs.

Bi Chen Tian mainly defended himself, as he felt downcast: "I am a great rank eight Gu Immortal, to think that this would happen. Scoundrel! As long as I get to the surface and recover my breath, I will deal with you!"

His arms flailed furiously, dragging Fang Yuan towards the surface as well.

But at the next moment, Fang Yuan's eyes shined with brilliance, as he blocked Bi Chen Tian's kick with one leg, while his other leg kicked at a crucial location.

"Ah!"

Bi Chen Tian was kicked by Fang Yuan, it landed on his crotch.

In an instant, his entire face stiffened, he stared with wide opened eyes, he was about to gasp out his last bit of oxygen left.

Bi Chen Tian was a rank eight great expert after all, he had superhuman endurance, he forcefully endured it and moved his arms, wanting to swim up to the surface.

Boom!

Fang Yuan kicked again.

Bi Chen Tian's body shook, this time, he could not help but breathe out a chain of bubbles.

Boom boom boom.

Sensing his huge weakness, Fang Yuan continued to kick.

Bi Chen Tian's face was flushed red, his eyes were bloodshot, he no longer thought of getting to\ the surface, he wanted to kill Fang Yuan!

"Who would fight you to the death?" Fang Yuan let go, kicking Bi Chen Tian away with another blow.

At the same time, he was pushed away by the force, pulling some distance from Bi Chen Tian.

After getting free, Bi Chen Tian was dazed for a while before giving up on Fang Yuan, he went to the surface to recover his breath.

Fang Yuan turned around and escaped successfully from Bi Chen Tian.

Bi Chen Tian's head came up to the surface as he breathed in deeply continuously.

His crotch was hurting, waves of pain was assaulting his nerves, he felt himself getting dizzy.

"This accursed fellow! If I have a chance, I will tear out your tendons and burn you to ashes!" Bi Chen Tian watched at the river surface as Fang Yuan swam away rapidly, their distance was enlarging, he could not catch up.

Fang Yuan successfully escaped from Bi Chen Tian, he slowed down to recover his stamina.

His legs were numb.

Bi Chen Tian's crotch was not easy to kick. Fang Yuan had immense strength, but his legs still felt numb from kicking it.

Evidently, Bi Chen Tian had thought of defending his crotch, there were many wood path dao marks there.

At the final crucial moment, Fang Yuan did not fight with Bi Chen Tian.

He knew that with Bi Chen Tian's methods, even if he killed him, he would have to face a terrifying retaliation and would likely get heavily injured or end up dead.

Fang Yuan did not want this outcome.

He did not need to fight to the death with a rank eight Gu Immortal.

He had the sovereign immortal body, his future was bright. And his goal to begin with was Ying Wu Xie.

If he died with Bi Chen Tian, wouldn't Ying Wu Xie be laughing his head off? Even if only Bi Chen Tian died, Fang Yuan would still be heavily injured, he would lose the ability to kill Ying Wu Xie.

Of course, there was something crucial.

Even if he killed Bi Chen Tian, Fang Yuan could gain nothing!

Immortal apertures could not be opened here, Bi Chen Tian's corpse would be a burden. Fang Yuan could not carry this corpse around with him, even if he could, what if he met Ying Wu Xie? Even if he did not meet Ying Wu Xie, what would he do if he met Central Continent's Gu Immortals?

Rank seven Gu Immortal killing rank eight, this would be a grand feat that would grant him unparalleled honor and glory.

But this honor was worthless to Fang Yuan!

He continued to swim ahead, trying to find Ying Wu Xie.

"Fang Yuan, is that you?"

Ying Wu Xie heard this and turned around, expressing joy on his face.

"Come closer, I will pull you up." He quickly said.

After a moment, Ying Wu Xie dragged Tai Bai Yun Sheng onto a huge lotus leaf.

"This is the leaf of the king lotus, it can float on the surface of the water, to think that you are so lucky." Tai Bai Yun Sheng sighed deeply.

Ying Wu Xie laughed, thinking: "I am luck connected to Fang Yuan, how can my luck be bad?"

But soon, his smile faded as worry appeared on his face again.

He looked at the flowing river: "Reverse Flow River's state is really strange now, we cannot escape. We have to meet up with Purple Mountain True Monarch now, we might be able to take back Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun, and even kill that ancient sword dragon that was chasing us!"

At the mention of Purple Mountain True Monarch, Tai Bai Yun Sheng showed admiration on his face: "Yes, we should meet up with master."

"Achoo!"

Purple Mountain True Monarch sneezed loudly.

He had a bitter expression, sighing: "Oh, to think that I would end up like this so soon after waking up. Sigh, I am old, my body is weak now, I seem to be getting a cold just because of some water."

He was sitting on Old Ancestor Xue Hu's shoulder.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu was swimming, he looked around, trying to find something in Reverse Flow River.

Hearing Purple Mountain True Monarch's words, he snorted: "You are doing nothing but you are still complaining? Don't you have wings? Why don't you fly out of Reverse Flow River?"

Purple Mountain True Monarch was in his original form now.

Like how Fang Yuan turned back to a human from ancient sword dragon form, Purple Mountain True Monarch was a rank eight miniman Gu Immortal, he had turned large earlier using an immortal method. Now that he was in Reverse Flow River, he became a miniman again.

Precisely because of this, he could sit on Old Ancestor Xue Hu's shoulder.

"You think I don't want to? But this Reverse Flow River is affected by some power, it is very chaotic, I cannot leave the river. Hehe, who created this Gu formation for you?" Purple Mountain True Monarch asked.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu had a grim expression: "Sun Ming Lu."

Purple Mountain True Monarch responded with an 'oh'.

"It should be him. This was out of my expectations." Old Ancestor Xue Hu said: "He is a member of Longevity Heaven!"

Old Ancestor Xue Hu was astute, at this moment, it was not hard to guess where Sun Ming Lu came from.

Because Central Continent's Gu Immortals were already in danger, in the entirety of Northern Plains, who could have the ability and guts to deal with Old Ancestor Xue Hu?

Other than Longevity Heaven, there was no one else.

Purple Mountain True Monarch said: "Longevity Heaven is definitely after Ma Hong Yun, as well as Zhao Lian Yun. They must be in front."

"I need to find my wife!" Old Ancestor Xue Hu said.

Purple Mountain True Monarch patted his shoulder: "Then we need to go ahead, Lady Wan Shou was right beside Ma Hong Yun at the time, she was swept away by the river along with them, she should be near them."

The fate reversing refinement sub formation was shining with a brilliant white-golden light.

The light burst into the sky, like a huge unconcealable pillar.

At this moment, Black Extremity was at the center of the Gu formation, manipulating it and directing the flow of Reverse Flow River. Flood Extremity was outside the Gu formation, preventing any intruders from approaching the pillar of light.

Chapter 1276: Perseverance of the Miniman

"So impressive, this Gu formation can actually control Reverse Flow River." Flood Extremity looked at the pillar of light and praised sincerely.

But Black Extremity shook his head: "This is not control, I merely created the fate reversing sacrificial refinement formation, it is like digging a river channel and letting Reverse Flow River move in it. We dug the river channel, thus, we can influence the direction that Reverse Flow River goes."

"When we retrieve Reverse Flow River, Longevity Heaven will gain another secluded domain of heaven and earth." Flood Extremity anticipated.

Black Extremity instructed again: "When we collect Reverse Flow River, the sub formation will be destroyed. You have to take note of the time and direction, opening your immortal aperture and letting the river flow in. You are a water path Gu Immortal, you have a big advantage in doing this."

Flood Extremity was troubled: "What if Reverse Flow River changes direction? Are there really no Gu worms in this world that can control Reverse Flow River?"

Black Extremity frowned slightly: "Well no, there isn't, but maybe not necessarily... there might be another possibility."

"What do you mean?"

"You know the contents of \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>. It stated that: Ren Zu sighed, as long as he had that Immortal Gu, he would conquer Reverse Flow River."

"You mean Immortal Gu — Perseverance? No way, perseverance Immortal Gu has never appeared before. In my opinion, that story is only telling us to persevere in cultivating and to never give up easily."

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, chapter four, section twenty-six —

Ren Zu's daughter, Boundless Forest Samsara, was trapped inside Ordinary Abyss.

She made friends with a miniman, the miniman brought Boundless Forest Samsara to see his home — City Well.

After Boundless Forest Samsara saw City Well, she raised her head at the sky.

"I understand now." Boundless Forest Samsara looked above her.

She was trapped inside Ordinary Abyss, she was just like the minimen who were trapped under the well. The minimen raised their heads and saw the sky within the well, it was like the sky that Boundless Forest Samsara saw when she looked up at Ordinary Abyss.

"I have decided, I will work hard and get out of this abyss to meet with father again!" Boundless Forest Samsara raised her fists, making up her mind.

The miniman was overjoyed: "Sure. I want to leave Ordinary Abyss and see the world outside as well. I see that there are many trees here in Ordinary Abyss, we can chop them down and make a ladder to climb up."

Boundless Forest Samsara gasped, looking at the miniman: "Oh miniman, don't you have wings? Why can't you fly out?"

The miniman smiled bitterly: "Oh human, I might have a pair of wings, but they are flimsy and weak. They can only carry me for a short distance. When I left City Well, I also used a ladder."

"So that's it." Boundless Forest Samsara realized.

In the following days, she stayed with the miniman, chopping trees and creating a ladder.

Trees were chopped down one by one, wisdom Gu flew out from them.

Boundless Forest Samsara was shocked: "Wisdom Gu, why are you here?"

"Wisdom is hidden in the ordinary, of course I can be here." Wisdom Gu answered.

Next, wisdom Gu said: "You are all very smart, you know how to use the achievements of predecessors to escape from being ordinary. But if you two want to leave Ordinary Abyss, you need to build your own ladders and complete them alone. Otherwise, you cannot leave."

Boundless Forest Samsara quickly nodded: "Oh wisdom Gu, thanks for reminding us, we will take note."

She and the miniman made their own ladders.

The ladders became taller and taller, soon, Boundless Forest Samsara's ladder surpassed the miniman.

The miniman's ladder was short and small, the distance between each step was also small.

In comparison, Boundless Forest Samsara's ladder was long and tall.

Boundless Forest Samsara teased the miniman: "Miniman, oh miniman, the ladder I make in half a day is as tall as the one you make in half a month. At this rate, when can you make a proper ladder to step on and escape from Ordinary Abyss?"

The miniman was helpless: "I can't help it, I am already doing my best, but this is all the wood I can carry after spending half a day, while you only need one hand to carry this over. I need to use a long time to chop down a small tree, but you only take three swings. I am already doing my best to reach this extent."

Boundless Forest Samsara nodded: "It is a pity we can only make our own ladders."

The miniman replied: "That's right, to leave Ordinary Abyss, we can use our predecessors' achievements, but we truly need to rely on ourselves. Let's continue working hard."

Boundless Forest Samsara and the miniman continued to chop down trees to make their ladders.

Trees fell one by one, from within, strength Gu flew out.

Boundless Forest Samsara was shocked: "Oh strength Gu, why are you here?"

"Strength is hidden in the ordinary, of course I can be here." Strength Gu answered.

Boundless Forest Samsara thought about it and asked: "Oh strength Gu, can you give us any advice? Like wisdom Gu."

Strength Gu said: "I have no advice to give you, but I can grant you great strength, as long as you give me your youth."

Boundless Forest Samsara fell into hesitation.

Strength Gu said: "According to your current strength, when will you be able to build a ladder tall enough to escape Ordinary Abyss?"

Boundless Forest Samsara thought: "Very long, I will need twenty to thirty years."

Strength Gu said: "Yes, by then, you will no longer be young, you will lose your youth and became middle aged, rather than that, you might as well give me your youth, even though you will become middle aged, you only need a few years to build the ladder."

Boundless Forest Samsara thought about it and nodded: "You are absolutely right, strength Gu, I will rely on you."

Thus, Boundless Forest Samsara obtained strength Gu, her speed in building the ladder became very fast, she could chop more trees at once. A year later, her ladder was extremely tall.

She stood at the top of the ladder and looked down.

She saw that the trees were very small, the grass was a field of green, she was very happy: "So when I stand at a high point, things that are big usually will become small. It is just like City Well."

She looked down at the miniman's ladder, it was very short, less than one percent of hers. She pouted.

Boundless Forest Samsara walked down and said to the miniman: "Why are you still so slow, my ladder is already so tall!"

The miniman looked at her ladder in admiration, saying helplessly: "I really admire you, your strength surpassed me to begin with, but now you also have strength Gu, it is too bad that I have no help, I can only rely on myself. I have already tried my best, everyday, other than eating and resting, I spend all my time building this ladder, but it cannot match yours."

Boundless Forest Samsara nodded: "That is natural."

Another year passed.

Boundless Forest Samsara continued to build the ladder even taller.

She stood at the peak and looked down.

The trees were like grass, while everything smaller than trees could not be seen clearly.

She looked at the miniman's ladder, even though it was taller than most trees, it was less than one-thousandth of hers.

Boundless Forest Samsara walked down the ladder, laughing at the miniman: "Miniman oh miniman, stop wasting your efforts. Your strength is too low, you will not be able to build that ladder even if you spend an entire lifetime. You might as well use this time to enjoy your life."

"Actually, you are already very amazing, compared to those minimen, you actually walked out of City Well, you should just enjoy your life now."

The miniman thought about it and shook his head: "I am not satisfied with being ordinary. When I am not happy with being ordinary, being ordinary would be like an abyss to me, I want to go out. Even if I cannot succeed, I want to try, if I do not try hard enough, I will not be happy."

Thus, the miniman continued building his ladder.

The third year passed.

Boundless Forest Samsara's ladder was extremely tall.

She stood at the peak and looked down.

Only to see that clouds were blocking her vision.

She wanted to look at the miniman's ladder, but she could barely see it, it was less than one ten-thousandth of her ladder.

Boundless Forest Samsara sighed, she felt lonely.

When the wind blew, she shuddered, feeling cold.

"So when I stand at this tall point, not only will I feel lonely, I will also feel cold." Boundless Forest Samsara walked down the ladder and told the miniman about this.

The miniman shook his head: "My ladder is not tall enough, I don't know how you feel."

Boundless Forest Samsara felt bored.

She continued to build the ladder, but the time she spent on it was decreasing.

Strength Gu asked her: "Oh human, why are you not building your ladder?"

Boundless Forest Samsara answered: "The ladder is too tall and cold, I need to rest and regain warmth.

Another year passed.

Boundless Forest Samsara felt extremely bored.

She was still building her ladder, but she was spending less and less time on it.

Strength Gu asked her: "Oh human, why are you not building your ladder?"

Boundless Forest Samsara answered: "The ladder is too tall, when I look down, I get afraid. I need to rest and let my heart calm down."

Another year passed.

Boundless Forest Samsara became even more lazy.

Strength Gu asked her: "Look at the miniman, he has never stopped building his ladder, he is giving it his all. If you continue being lazy, he will surpass you one day."

Boundless Forest Samsara laughed: "How can that be possible? One day of work for me is a month of his. How can he ever surpass me?"

Like this, years passed without stopping.

Finally, one day, the miniman found Boundless Forest Samsara who was resting under a tree, saying to her: "Oh friend, my ladder is at the edge of Ordinary Abyss, tomorrow, I will step out and leave Ordinary Abyss."

Boundless Forest Samsara laughed: "Oh miniman, don't lie to me, this is too funny."

The miniman shook his head, saying seriously: "Grandness and being laughable is merely an inch apart. But I am not laughable anymore, I am grand and can finally leave this Ordinary Abyss. If you do not believe me, watch as I leave."

Thus, the miniman started to climb his ladder.

Boundless Forest Samsara was shocked at this, the miniman was really at the edge of the abyss,he could leave if he continued like this.

Boundless Forest Samsara shouted: "Oh miniman, do you not feel cold?"

The miniman said: "Of course, but I want to build my ladder and climb out of here."

Boundless Forest Samsara shouted again: "Oh miniman, do you not feel lonely?"

The miniman said: "Of course, but I want to build my ladder and climb out of here."

Boundless Forest Samsara shouted again: "Oh miniman, do you not feel afraid?"

The miniman said: "Of course, but I want to build my ladder and climb out of here."

After saying those three lines, a bright light flashed on his body, rapidly forming into a Gu worm.

"My name is Perseverance, oh miniman, thank you for giving me life." Perseverance Gu thanked the miniman.

The miniman laughed: "Great, even though I do not have strength, I have perseverance."

The miniman said as he climbed out of Ordinary Abyss, stepping into the outside world.

He first saw someone.

It was Ren Zu.

The rate of time inside Ordinary Abyss was different from the outside world.

Ren Zu sighed as he saw the miniman: "This is perseverance Gu? What a pity, if I had it, I would have been able to conquer Reverse Flow River."

Chapter 1277: Meeting of Ma and Zhao

Flood Extremity believed that perseverance Gu was only a Gu worm found in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

But Black Extremity shook his head, saying: "Perseverance Immortal Gu is not a fictitious Gu worm. In fact, it has existed before."

Flood Extremity was shocked: "How did I not know that?"

"This was something I had learned while traveling Northern Plains. The person who refined perseverance Immortal Gu was the famous Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable. He was the one who entered the door of life and death and brought Reverse Flow River out into the world. He was the first owner of Reverse Flow River."

"Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable! Is that so? Then why is Reverse Flow River in the hands of Old Ancestor Xue Hu?" Flood Extremity asked.

Black Extremity shook his head: "I am unsure about the details regarding this... what is going on?!"

At this moment, there was a loud sound.

Inside the fate reversing refinement sub formation, some mortal Gu had exploded.

The pillar of light that the sub formation emitted also shrunk by ten percent.

This sudden change disrupted their conversation, Flood Extremity became nervous: "A portion of the Gu formation was destroyed, aren't you repairing it?"

Black Extremity shook his head: "This situation is within my expectations, even the fate reversing refinement sub formation cannot endure the might of Reverse Flow River, it will be destroyed. And this formation has a weakness, once it activates, it cannot be repaired, unless the entire formation stops functioning."

Flood Extremity frowned deeply: "Reverse Flow River has not reached here yet, what do we do now?"

Black Extremity smiled: "Don't worry, I created this formation, how could I not see this coming? In fact, there are benefits in destroying the Gu formation."

Flood Extremity was confused: "The Gu formation being destroyed has benefits?"

"Every ten percent of destruction would reduce our influence on Reverse Flow River by ten percent. The back part of Reverse Flow River will return to normal and stop being drawn to us. That way, it will display its original might and wash out everyone and everything behind." Black Extremity explained.

"Incredible!" Flood Extremity clapped and praised, his eyes were shining: "Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun are all at the front, that means, they will be the last to be washed away."

Black Extremity nodded: "Precisely."

Inside Reverse Flow River.

"Lord Bi Chen Tian!" Three Central Continent Gu Immortals greeted Bi Chen Tian.

Bi Chen Tian nodded, at this moment, there were five people gathered around him, with the addition of these three and himself, there were nine people.

"Did you see Ma Hong Yun or Zhao Lian Yun?" The Gu Immortals shook their heads.

"Then did you see this person?" Bi Chen Tian described Fang Yuan's appearance and clothing to them.

The Central Continent Gu Immortals looked at each other, one of them said: "I think I saw him, but I did not stop him. I was hiding behind a floating plank, he swam ahead without noticing me."

Bi Chen Tian nodded.

"Lord, this person is not in our information, is he an ally or foe?" Someone asked.

The Central Continent Gu Immortals were very perplexed, because Bi Chen Tian was a grand rank eight Gu Immortal, he would not ask for information about a rank seven Gu Immortal for no reason.

Speaking of which, Fang Yuan's cultivation level was not outstanding. Most of the Central Continent Gu Immortals were rank seven.

But Bi Chen Tian's following words made all of their hearts shake!

"He is a strong foe. If you meet him, be very careful, I am merely on par with him in terms of physical brawling."

The Central Continent Gu Immortals nodded solemnly.

"What do we do now?" Someone asked.

"We have many people with us, we will swim up and get rid of our enemies along Reverse Flow River, that would be the best outcome!" Bi Chen Tian said this as killing intent surged in him.

This was a good tactic indeed.

The Central Continent Gu Immortals were not the match of Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Purple Mountain True Monarch if they fought normally. Right now, they had lost Edge Link Camp, they were completely outclassed.

The sudden change with Reverse Flow River gave them a good chance.

Bi Chen Tian felt that: As long as they could make use of this opportunity, they might be able to get rid of their enemies in Reverse Flow River and obtain victory.

"Hmm? What is going on?" At this moment, a certain water path Gu Immortal among the Central Continent Gu Immortals felt a change in the river water.

Next, these Central Continent Gu Immortals saw that the water of Reverse Flow River around them started to calm down rapidly from a turbulent state.

Finally, the river flow slowed gradually, before starting to have small ripples.

Large amounts of rocks and wild beast corpses, which were flowing along the river currents, were washed away rapidly.

It was five times faster than the speed of flow earlier!

"How can this be?" Some Central Continent Gu Immortals were caught off-guard and were washed away by the river, in the blink of an eye, they were three hundred steps of distance away from Bi Chen Tian.

Bi Chen Tian was the first to react.

"Quick, swim, do not stop for even a moment, Reverse Flow River has returned to its usual state, if we stop for a moment, we will be washed away by the currents." He called out.

Getting Bi Chen Tian's reminder, the remaining Central Continent Gu Immortals reacted and tried to swim earnestly.

"It is so difficult!"

"The water is flowing slowly and smoothly, but it is actually many times harder than the raging tides earlier!"

"These floating logs and corpses are annoying, they are blocking our paths."

The Central Continent Gu Immortals quickly found that it was far more difficult to swim in this river that had returned to normal.

"What is this? The higher we swim up Reverse Flow River, the harder every step is! We need to persevere, we do not need to reach the upper part of the river, as long as we meet enemies, we can kill them. If we kill one rank eight Gu Immortal, we will be able to obtain victory later!" Bi Chen Tian raised the morale.

The Central Continent Gu Immortals cheered in response.

"This way, Reverse Flow River is our opportunity!"

"Lord Bi Chen Tian, look ahead, to the front, the river is extremely turbulent!"

Bi Chen Tian heard this and found something weird.

He frowned.

This was a nightmare.

Swimming in this calm part of Reverse Flow River was much harder than swimming in the strong currents. At this rate, as time passes, when the Central Continent Gu Immortals met the enemies that were washed down by Reverse Flow River, they would already be exhausted and out of stamina!

"Quick, we need to get in front and swim in the turbulent water!" Bi Chen Tian had a grave expression, he gave the most accurate instructions.

The Central Continent Gu Immortals increased their speed in response.

Fang Yuan swam in the river, he continued to pursue Ying Wu Xie, but he could not find any trace.

The river water was turbulent, huge waves were created from time to time. From within these waves, wild beast corpses and countless rocks would flow along them.

The situation in the river was very complex. And most importantly, the river was very wide.

Fang Yuan could not get on high ground for observation, even though he had good eyesight, he could not see much.

However, he had found many Gu Immortals, among which, there were Central Continent Gu Immortals and also Snowy Mountain blessed land's peak lords.

Fang Yuan avoided them all, he did not deal with them.

Fighting these people would waste his time and would not reap any benefits.

"This river is too wide, I might have passed Ying Wu Xie earlier while I was diving, I might be in front of him. This is totally possible!"

But Fang Yuan did not give up.

Because Ying Wu Xie had a higher chance of being in front.

He swam with all his strength, moving agilely in the complex water like a fish. The sovereign immortal body gave him incredible eyesight, stamina, and his recovery speed was on par with rank eight Gu Immortals, and most importantly, he had practiced his own incredible swimming ability.

All these caused him to surpass many Gu Immortals.

In contrast, Bi Chen Tian had to keep searching in the river for the other Central Continent Gu Immortals, he was at the very back.

A leopard fox was swimming in the water, charging at Zhao Lian Yun.

The leopard fox was smaller than regular leopards, but it could swim, thus, even inside Reverse Flow River, it survived.

"Go away!" Mu Ling Lan slapped as he killed the leopard fox which came.

His other arm was grabbing onto Zhao Lian Yun.

Zhao Lian Yun was a false immortal created with a phantom aperture, she had low foundation and barely any dao marks. Without Gu worms, she was as weak as a mortal.

Thankfully, while she was inside Reverse Flow River, the rank seven water path Gu Immortal Mu Ling Lan was around her.

With Mu Ling Lan defending her, Zhao Lian Yun managed to survive until now.

Mu Ling Lan was covered in water path dao marks, he could actually breathe freely in water, he could also swim well, along the way, he protected Zhao Lian Yun and resolved crises, while swimming ahead and bringing her along.

"Quickly look, there is a mound in front." Mu Ling Lan killed the leopard fox and suddenly said this with shining eyes, there was a mound floating ahead in the river.

"This mound is made of float soil, no wonder it can float on water and not sink! We will go rest there!" Mu Ling Lan dragged Zhao Lian Yun along and climbed onto the floating mound with much difficulty.

Zhao Lian Yun was extremely tired, she was barely alive.

Once she got on shore, she laid down on the mound and stopped moving entirely as she rested.

Mu Ling Lan was extremely tired, he was breathing roughly.

"Wait, there's someone on the mound!" Mu Ling Lan suddenly stood up with a ruthless expression.

"Calm down, calm down!" A figure had to walk out of the forest on the mound.

Mu Ling Lan saw this person and became stunned.

Zhao Lian Yun was frozen like a statue.

Because the one who appeared in front of them was Ma Hong Yun!

All of the immortals were in terrible conditions, but Ma Hong Yun was wearing clean clothes as he chewed on a half eaten fruit.

"You are Ma Hong Yun!" Mu Ling Lan shouted in surprise.

Ma Hong Yun took a step back: "Are you also here to capture me?"

Zhao Lian Yun tried her best to get up, as she stood shakily.

She looked at Ma Hong Yun, her throat was moving but no voice came out. As the price for using love Gu earlier, she had been using Gu worms to speak, but inside Reverse Flow River, no Gu worms could be used.

At this moment, Zhao Lian Yun finally saw the lover that she had been thinking of for so long.

She was extremely agitated, she took a step forward.

But at the next moment, she hesitated.

How did she look like now? She was clear in her heart.

She was no longer young, she was an elderly woman. Her hair was white, her face had deep wrinkles, and she was dry like a twig.

In this appearance, could Ma Hong Yun recognize her?

Could she meet her lover in this appearance, could she bear to let him see her like this?

Zhao Lian Yun lost all of her courage.

She lowered her head, she did not dare to look at Ma Hong Yun's eyes.

Zhao Lian Yun was hesitant, but she suddenly heard Ma Hong Yun call out: "You, you are Lady Xiao Yun?"

Zhao Lian Yun's body shook.

She raised her head, only to see that Ma Hong Yun had thrown away the fruit as he ran towards her.

"Lady Xiao Yun, Lady Xiao Yun! I miss you so much!" Ma Hong Yun shouted loudly.

Mu Ling Lan saw this and felt a lot of emotions, he explained: "Fairy Lian Yun became like this because she rushed here from Central Continent to save you."

"Lady Xiao Yun!" Ma Hong Yun grabbed Zhao Lian Yun's hands as he stood before her.

He was also unable to speak, his words were choked in his throat.

At this moment, Zhao Lian Yun felt: This was truly immense bliss. All of her sacrifices were worth it!